<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="zh-HK-WanLungNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />當下祭畢，讓他母子到寺中擺茶飯，勸他吃了些。王六兒見天色將晚，催促他起身，他只顧不思動身。一面跪著春梅、葛翠屏哭說：「奴情願不歸父母，同姐姐守孝寡居。明日死，傍他魂靈，也是奴和他恩情一場，說是他妻小。」說著那淚如泉涌。翠屏只顧不言語。春梅便說：「我的姐姐，只怕年小青春，守不住，卻不誤了你好時光。」愛姐便道：「奶奶說那裡話？奴既為他，雖刳目斷鼻也當守節，誓不再配他人。」囑付他父母：「你老公婆回去罷，我跟奶奶和姐姐府中去也。」那王六兒眼中垂淚，哭道：「我承望你養活俺兩口兒到老，才從虎穴龍潭中奪得你來。今日倒閃賺了我。」那愛姐口裡只說：「我不去了。你就留下我，到家也尋了無常。」那韓道國因見女兒堅意不去，和王六兒大哭一場，灑淚而別，回上臨清店中去了。這韓愛姐同春梅、翠屏，坐轎子往府里來。那王六兒一路上悲悲切切，只是舍不的他女兒，哭了一場又一場。那韓道國又怕天色晚了，雇上兩匹頭口，望前趕路。正是：<break time="100ms" />　　馬遲心急路途窮，身似浮萍類轉蓬。只有都門樓上月，照人離恨各西東。<break time="100ms" />　 ↑返回頂部<break time="100ms" />About this digital edition<break time="100ms" />This e-book comes from the online library Wikisource[1]. This multilingual digital library, built by volunteers, is committed to developing a free accessible collection of publications of every kind: novels, poems, magazines, letters...<break time="100ms" />We distribute our books for free, starting from works not copyrighted or published under a free license. You are free to use our e-books for any purpose (including commercial exploitation), under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 Unported[2] license or, at your choice, those of the GNU FDL[3].<break time="100ms" />Wikisource is constantly looking for new members. During the realization of this book, it's possible that we made some errors. You can report them at this page[4].<break time="100ms" />The following users contributed to this book:<break time="100ms" />Liouxiao<break time="100ms" />鸟甲<break time="100ms" />Chen Changhong<break time="100ms" />2A02:810D:9C80:170:7049:FCEF:B5D1:1A7E<break time="100ms" />* * *<break time="100ms" />↑ https://wikisource.org<break time="100ms" />↑ https://www.creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0<break time="100ms" />↑ https://www.gnu.org/copyleft/fdl.html<break time="100ms" />↑ https://wikisource.org/wiki/Wikisource:Scriptorium<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
