<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Mother Brown had in the mean time agreed the terms with this liquorish old goat, which I afterwards understood were to be fifty guineas peremptory for the liberty of attempting me, and a hundred more at the compleat gratification of his desires, in the triumph over my virginity: and as for me, I was to be left entirely at the discretion of his liking and generosity. This unrighteous contract being thus settled, he was so eager to be put in possession, that he insisted on being introduc'd to drink tea with me that afternoon, when we were to be left alone; nor would he hearken to the procuress's remonstrances, that I was not sufficiently prepared, and ripened for such an attack; that I was too green and untam'd, having been scarce twenty-four hours in the house: it is the character of lust to be impatient, and his vanity arming him against any supposition of other than the common resistance of a maid on those occasions, made him reject all proposals of a delay, and my dreadful trial was thus fix'd, unknown to me that very evening.<break time="100ms" />At dinner, Mrs. Brown and Phœbe did nothing but run riot in praises of this wonderful cousin, and how happy that woman would be that he would favour with his addresses: in short my two gossips exhausted all their rhetoric to persuade me to accept them, "that the gentleman was violently smitten with me at first sight —— that he would make my fortune if I would be a good girl, and not stand in my own light —— that I should trust his honour —— that I should be made for ever, and have a chariot to go abroad in," —— with all such stuff as was fit to turn the head of such a silly ignorant girl as I then was: but luckily here my aversion had taken already such deep root in me, my heart was so strongly defended from him by my senses, that, wanting the art to mask my sentiments, I gave them no hopes of their employer's succeeding, at least very easily, with me. The glass too march'd pretty quick, with a view, I suppose, to make a friend of the warmth of my constitution, in the minutes of the imminent attack.<break time="100ms" />Thus they kept me pretty long at table, and about six in the evening, after I was retired to my own apartment, and the tea-board was set, enters my venerable mistress, follow'd close by that satyr, who came in grinning in a way peculiar to him, and by his odious presence confirm'd me in all the sentiments of detestation which his first appearance had given birth to.<break time="100ms" />He sat down fronting me, and all tea-time kept ogling me in a manner that gave me the utmost pain and confusion, all the marks of which he still explained to be my bashfulness, and not being used to see company.<break time="100ms" />Tea over, the commode old lady pleaded urgent business, (which indeed was true) to go out, and earnestly desir'd me to entertain her cousin kindly till she came back, both for my own sake and her's; and then, with a "pray, sir, be very good, be very tender of the sweet child," she went out of the room, leaving me staring, with my mouth open, and unprepared, by the suddenness of her departure, to oppose it.<break time="100ms" />We were now alone; and on that idea a sudden fit of trembling seized me;—— I was so afraid, without a precise notion of why, and what I had to fear, that I sat on the settee, by the fire-side, motionless, and petrified, without life or spirit, not knowing how to look, or how to stir.<break time="100ms" />But long I was not suffered to remain in this state of stupefaction: the monster squatted down by me on the settee, and without farther ceremony, or preamble, flings his arms about my neck, and drawing me pretty forcibly towards him, oblig'd me to receive, in spite of my struggles to disengage from him, his pestilential kisses, which quite overcame me: finding me then next to senseless and unresisting, he tears off my neck handkerchief, and laid all open there to his eyes, and hands; still I endur'd all without flinching, till embolden'd by my sufferance, and silence, (for I had not the power to speak, or cry out) he attempted to lay me down on the settee, and I felt his hand on the lower part of my naked thighs, which were cross'd, and which he endeavour'd to unlock. Oh then! I was rouzed out of my passive endurance, and springing from him with an activity he was not prepar'd for, threw myself at his feet, and begg'd him, in the most moving tone, not to be rude, and that he would not hurt me:——"Hurt you, my dear!" says the brute, "I intend you no harm —— has not the old lady told you that I love you? —— that I shall do handsomely by you?" —— she has indeed, sir, said I; but I cannot love you, indeed I can not! —— pray let me alone ———— yes! I will love you dearly if you will let me alone, and go away ———— but I was talking to the wind; for whether my tears, my attitude, or the disorder of my dress prov'd fresh incentives, or whether he was now under the dominion of desires he could not bridle, but snorting and foaming with lust and rage, he renews his attack, seizes me, and again attempts to extend and fix me on the settee; in which he succeeded so far as to lay me along; and even to toss my petticoats over my head, and lay my thighs bare, which I obstinately kept close, nor could he, though he attempted with his knee to force them open, effect it so as to stand fair for being master of the main avenue: he was unbuttoned, both waistcoat and breeches, yet I only felt the weight of his body upon me, whilst I lay struggling with indignation, and dying with terrors; but he stopt all of a sudden, and got off, panting, blowing, cursing, and rehearsing upon me old and ugly! for so I had very naturally called him, in the heat of my defence.<break time="100ms" />The brute had, it seems, as I afterwards understood, brought on, by his eagerness, and struggle, the ultimate period of his hot fit of lust, which his power was too short liv'd to carry him through the full execution of; of which my thighs and linnen received the effusion.<break time="100ms" />When it was over, he bid me, with a tone of displeasure, get up, —— "that he would not do me the honour to think of me any more, —— that the old b—h might look out for another cully, —— that he would not be fool'd so by e'er a country mock-modesty in England —— that he supposed I had left my maidenhead with some hobnail in the country, and was come to dispose of my skim-milk in town," with a volley of the like abuse; which I listened to with more pleasure than ever fond woman did to protestations of love, from her darling minion: for, incapable as I was of receiving any addition to my perfect hatred and aversion to him, I look'd on this railing as my security against his renewing his most odious caresses.<break time="100ms" />Yet, plain as Mrs. Brown's views were now come out, I had not the heart or spirit to open my eyes to them: still I could not part with my dependence on that beldam; so much did I think myself her's, soul and body: or rather, I sought to deceive myself with the continuation of my good opinion of her, and chose to wait the worst at her hands, sooner than being turn'd out to starve in the streets, without a penny of money, or a friend to apply to: these fears were my folly.
    </voice>
</speak>
