<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Whilst this confusion of ideas was passing in my head, and I sat pensive by the fire, with my eyes brimming with tears, my neck still bare, and my cap fall'n off in the struggle, so that my hair was in the disorder you may guess, the villain's lust began, I suppose, to be again in flow, at the sight of all that bloom of youth which presented itself to his view, a bloom yet unenjoy'd, and of course not yet indifferent to him.<break time="100ms" />After some pause, he ask'd me, with a tone of voice mightily soften'd, whether I would make it up with him before the old lady returned, and all should be well; he would restore me his affections: at the same time offering to kiss me, and feel my breasts. But now my extreme aversion, my fears, my indignation, all acting upon me, gave me a spirit not natural to me, so that breaking loose from him, I ran to the bell, and rang it, before he was aware, with such violence and effect, as brought up the maid to know what was the matter, or whether the gentleman wanted any thing? and, before he could proceed to greater extremities, she bounc'd into the room, and seeing me stretch'd on the floor, my hair all dishevell'd, my nose guishing out blood, (which did not a little tragedize the scene) and my odious persecutor still intent of pushing his brutal point, unmov'd by all my cries and distress, she was herself confounded, and did not know what to do.<break time="100ms" />As much, however, as Martha might be prepared, and hardened to transactions of this sort, all womanhood must have been out of her heart, could she have seen this unmov'd. Besides that, on the face of things, she imagined that matters had gone greater lengths than they really had, and that the courtesy of the house had been actually consummated on me, and flung me into the condition I was in: in this notion she instantly took my part, and advis'd the gentleman to go down, and leave me to recover myself, and that all would be soon over with me. ——— That when Mrs. Brown and Phœbe, who were gone out, were return'd, they would take order for every thing to his satisfaction, ———— that nothing would be lost by a little patience with the poor tender thing, ———— that for her part, she was frighten'd, ———— she could not tell what to say to such doings, —— but that she would stay by me till my mistress came home. As the wench said all this in a resolute tone, and the monster himself began to perceive that things would not mend by his staying, he took his hat and went out of the room murmuring, and pleating his brows like an old ape, so that I was delivered from the horrors of his detestable presence.<break time="100ms" />As soon as he was gone, Martha very tenderly offered me her assistance in any thing, and would have got me some hartshorn drops, and put me to bed; which last I, at first, positively refused, in the fear that the monster might return, and take me at that advantage: however, with much persuasion, and assurances that I should not be molested that night, she prevailed on me to lie down; and indeed I was so weakened by my struggles, so dejected by my fearful apprehensions, so terrour-struck, that I had no power to sit up, or hardly to give answers to the questions with which the curious Martha ply'd and perplex'd me.<break time="100ms" />Such too, and so cruel was my fate, that I dreaded the sight of Mrs. Brown, as if I had been the criminal, and she the person injur'd: a mistake which you will not think so strange, on distinguishing that neither virtue, nor principles, had the least share in the defence I had made; but only the particular aversion I had conceiv'd against this first brutal and frightful invader of my tender innocence.<break time="100ms" />I pass'd then the time till Mrs. Brown's return home, under all the agitations of fear and despair that may easily be guessed.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
