<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Phœbe herself, the hackney'd, thorough-bred Phœbe, to whom all modes and devices of pleasure were known and familiar, found, it seems, in this exercise of her art to break young girls, the gratification of one of those arbitrary tastes, for which there is no accounting: not that she hated men, or did not even prefer them to her own sex; but when she met with such occasions as this was, a satiety of enjoyments in the common road, perhaps too, a secret byass, inclined her to make the most of pleasure, wherever she could find it, without distinction of sexes. In this view, now well assured that she had, by her touches, sufficiently inflamed me for her purpose, she roll'd down the bed-cloaths gently, and I saw myself stretched nak'd, my shift being turned up to my neck, whilst I had no power or sense to oppose it; even my glowing blushes expressed more desire than modesty, whilst the candle left, to be sure not undesignedly, burning, threw a full light on my whole body.<break time="100ms" />"No! (says Phœbe) you must not, my sweet girl, think to hide all these treasures from me, my sight must be feasted as well as my touch —— I must devour with my eyes this springing bosom, —— suffer me to kiss it —— I have not seen it enough —— let me kiss it once more —— what firm, smooth, white flesh is here —— how delicately shaped! ———— then this delicious down! Oh! let me view the small, dear, tender cleft! —— this is too much, I cannot bear it, I must, I must ———" Here she took my hand, and, in a transport, carried it where you will easily guess; but what a difference in the state of the same thing! —— a spreading thicket of bushy curls mark'd the full-grown complete woman. Then the cavity to which she guided my hand, easily received it, and as soon as she felt it within her, she moved herself to and fro, with so rapid a friction that I presently withdrew it, wet and clammy, when instantly Phœbe grew more composed, after two or three sighs, and heart-fetch'd Oh's! and giving me a kiss, that seemed to exhale her soul through her lips, she replaced the bed-cloaths over us.<break time="100ms" />What pleasure she had found I will not say; but this I know, that the first sparks of kindling nature, the first ideas of pollution, were caught by me that night, and that the acquaintance and communication with the bad of our own sex, is often as fatal to innocence as all the seductions of the other: But to go on. ——— when Phœbe was restor'd to that calm, which I was far from the enjoyment of myself, she artfully sounded me on all the points necessary to govern the designs of my virtuous mistress on me, and by my answers, drawn from pure undissembled nature, she had no reason but to promise herself all imaginable success, so far as it depended on my ignorance, easiness, and warmth of constitution.<break time="100ms" />After a sufficient length of dialogue, my bed-fellow left me to my rest, and I fell asleep, through pure weariness, from the violent emotions I had been led into, when nature (which had been too warmly stir'd and fermented to subside without allaying by some means or other) relieved me by one of those luscious dreams, the transports of which are scarce inferior to those of waking, real action.<break time="100ms" />In the morning I awoke, about ten, perfectly gay and refreshed; Phœbe was up before me, and asked me in the kindest manner how I did, how I had rested, and if I was ready for breakfast? carefully at the same time avoiding to encrease the confusion she saw I was in, at looking her in the face, by any hint of the night's bed-scene. —— I told her, if she pleased, I would get up, and begin any work she would be pleased to set me about. She smil'd; presently the maid brought in the tea-equipage, and I had just huddled my cloaths on, when in waddled my mistress. I expected no less than to be told of, if not chid for, my late rising, when I was agreeably disappointed by her compliments on my pure and fresh looks: "I was a bud of beauty; (this was her stile) and how vastly all the fine men would admire me!" to all which my answer did not, I can assure you, wrong my breeding: they were as simple, and silly as they could wish, and, no doubt, flattered them infinitely more than had they proved me enlightened by education and knowledge of the world.<break time="100ms" />We breakfasted; and the tea-things were scarce removed, when in were brought two bundles of linnen and wearing apparel; in short, all the necessaries for rigging me out, as they termed it, compleatly.<break time="100ms" />Imagine to yourself, madam, how my little coquette-heart flutter'd with joy at the sight of a white lute-string, flower'd with silver, scoured indeed, but passed on me for spick-and-span new, a Brussel-lace cap, braided shoes, and the rest in proportion, all second-hand finery, and procured instantly for the occasion, by the diligence and industry of the good Mrs. Brown, who had already a chapman for me in the house, before whom my charms were to pass in review; for he had not only in course insisted on a previous sight of the premisses, but also on immediate surrender to him, in case of his agreeing for me; concluding very wisely that such a place as I was in, was of the hottest, to trust the keeping of such a perishable commodity in, as a maidenhead.<break time="100ms" />The care of dressing, and tricking me out for the market, was then left to Phœbe, who acquitted herself, if not well, at least perfectly to the satisfaction of every thing but my impatience of seeing myself dress'd. When it was over, and I view'd myself in the glass, I was, no doubt, too natural, too artless, to hide my childish joy at the change; a change in the real truth, for much the worse, since I must have much better become the neat easy simplicity of my rustic dress, than the awkward, untoward, taudry finery, that I could not conceal my strangeness to. Phœbe's compliments, however, in which her own share in dressing me was not forgot, did not a little confirm me in now the first notions I had ever entertained concerning my person, which, be it said without vanity, was then tolerable enough to justify a taste for me, and of which it may not be out of place here to sketch you an unflatter'd picture.
    </voice>
</speak>
