<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />In the midst of these false explanations of the nature of my future service, we were rung for down again, and I was reintroduced into the same parlour, where there was a table laid with three covers; and my mistress had now got with her one of her favourite girls, a notable manager of her house, and whose business it was to prepare and break such young Fillies as I was to the mounting-block: and she was accordingly, in that view, allotted me for a bed-fellow; and, to give her the more authority, she had the title of cousin confer'd on her by the venerable president of this college.<break time="100ms" />Here I underwent a second survey, which ended in the full approbation of Mrs. Phœbe Ayres, the name of my tutoress elect, to whose care and instructions I was affectionately recommended.<break time="100ms" />Dinner was now set on table, and in pursuance of treating me as a companion, Mrs. Brown, with a tone to cut off all dispute, soon over-rul'd my most humble and most confused protestations against sitting down with her Ladyship, which my very short breeding just suggested to me could not be right, or in the order of things.<break time="100ms" />At table, the conversation was chiefly kept up by the two madams, and carried on in double-meaning expressions, interrupted every now and then by kind assurance to me, all tending to confirm and fix my satisfaction with my present condition: augment it they could not, so very a novice was I then.<break time="100ms" />It was here agreed, that I should keep myself up and out of sight for a few days, till such cloaths could be procured for me as were fit for the character I was to appear in, of my mistress's companion, observing withal, that on the first impressions of my figure, much might depend; and, as they well judged, the prospect of exchanging my country-cloaths for London finery, made the clause of confinement digest perfectly well with me. But the truth was, Mrs. Brown did not care that I should be seen or talked to by any, either of her customers, or her Does (as they call'd the girls provided for them), till she had secured a good market for my maidenhead, which I had at least all the appearances of having brought into her ladyship's service.<break time="100ms" />To slip over minuties of no importance to the main of my story, I pass the interval to bed-time, in which I was more and more pleas'd with the views that open'd to me of an easy service under these good people: and after supper, being shew'd up to bed, Miss Phœbe, who observed a kind of reluctance in me to strip, and go to bed in my shift before her, now the maid was withdrawn, came up to me, and beginning with unpinning my handkerchief, and gown, soon encouraged me to go on with undressing myself, and, still blushing at now seeing myself naked to my shift, I hurried to get under the bedcloaths, out of sight. Phœbe laugh'd, and was not long before she placed herself by my side. She was about five and twenty, by her most suspicious account, in which, according to all appearances, she must have sunk at least ten good years, allowance too being made for the havoc which a long course of hackney-ship and hot waters, must have made of her constitution, and which had already brought on, upon the spur, that stale stage, in which those of her profession are reduced to think of showing company, instead of seeing it.<break time="100ms" />No sooner then was this precious substitute of my mystress's laid down, but she, who was never out of her way when any occasion of lewdness presented itself, turned to me, embraced, and kiss'd me with great eagerness. This was new, this was odd; but imputing it to nothing but pure kindness, which, for ought I knew, it might be the London way to express in that manner, I was determin'd not to be behind-hand with her, and returned her the kiss and embrace, with all the fervour that perfect innocence knew.<break time="100ms" />Encouraged by this, her hands became extremely free, and wander'd over my whole body, with touches, squeezes, pressures, that rather warm'd and surpriz'd me with their novelty, than they either shock'd or alarm'd me.<break time="100ms" />The flattering praises she intermingled with these invasions, contributed also not a little to bribe my passiveness, and, knowing no ill, I fear'd none; especially from one who had prevented all doubt of her womanhood, by conducting my hands to a pair of breasts that hung loosely down, in a size and volume that full sufficiently distinguished her sex, to me at least, who had never made any other comparison.<break time="100ms" />I lay then all tame and passive as she could wish, whilst her freedom raised no other emotions but those of a strange, and till then unfelt pleasure: every part of me was open, and exposed to the licentious courses of her hands, which like a lambent fire ran over my whole body, and thaw'd all coldness as they went.<break time="100ms" />My breasts, if it is not too bold a figure to call so, two hard, firm, rising hillocks, that just began to shew themselves, or signify any thing to the touch, employ'd and amus'd her hands a while, till slipping down lower, over a smooth track, she could just feel the soft silky down that had but a few months before put forth, and garnish'd the mount-pleasant of those parts, and promised to spread a grateful shelter over the seat of the most exquisite sensation, and which had been, till that instant, the seat of the most insensible innocence. Her fingers play'd, and strove to twine in the young tendrils of that moss which nature has contrived at once for use and ornament.<break time="100ms" />But not contented with these outer-posts, she now attempts the main-spot, and began to twitch, to insinuate, and at length to force an introduction of a finger into the quick itself, in such a manner, that had she not proceeded by insensible gradations, that inflamed me beyond the power of modesty to oppose its resistance to their progress, I should have jump'd out of bed, and cried for help against such strange assaults.<break time="100ms" />Instead of which, her lascivious touches had lighted up a new fire that wanton'd through all my veins, but fix'd with violence in that center appointed them by nature, where the first strange hands were now busied in feeling, squeezing, compressing the lips, then opening them again, with a finger between, till an Oh! express'd her hurting me, where the narrowness of the unbroken passage refused it entrance to any depth.<break time="100ms" />In the mean time, the extension of my limbs, languid stretchings, sighs, short heavings, all conspired to assure that experienced wanton that I was more pleased than offended at her proceedings, which she seasoned with repeated kisses and exclamations, such as "Oh! what a charming creature thou art! —— what a happy man will he be that first makes a woman of you! ———— Oh! that I were a man for your sake————!" with the like broken expressions, interrupted by kisses as fierce and falacious as ever I received from the other sex.<break time="100ms" />For my part, I was transported, confused, and out of myself: feelings so new were too much for me; my heated and alarm'd senses were in a tumult that robbed me of all liberty of thought; tears of pleasure gush'd from my eyes, and somewhat assuaged the fire that rag'd all over me.
    </voice>
</speak>
