<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Letter the First
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />About eleven at night my two ladies came home, and having receiv'd rather a favourable account from Martha, who had run down to let them in: (for Mr. Crofts, that was the name of my brute, was gone out of the house, after waiting till he had tired his patience for Mrs. Brown's return) they came thundering up stairs, and seeing me pale, my face bloody, and all the marks of the most thorough dejection, they employed themselves more to comfort and re-inspirit me, than in making me the reproaches I was weak enough to fear: I who had so many juster and stronger to retort upon them.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Brown withdrawn, Phœbe came presently to bed to me, and what with the answers she drew from me, what with her own method of palpably satisfying herself, she soon discovered that I had been more frighted than hurt; upon which, I suppose being herself seiz'd with sleep, and reserving her lectures and instructions till the next morning, she left me, properly speaking, to my unrest: for after tossing, and turning, the greatest part of the night, and tormenting myself with the falsest notions and apprehensions of things, I fell, through meer fatigue, into a kind of delirious doze, out of which I wak'd late in the morning, in a violent fever; a circumstance which was extremely critical to reprive me, at least for a time, from the attacks of a wretch infinitely more terrible to me than death itself.<break time="100ms" />The interested care that was taken of me during my illness, in order to restore me to a condition of making good the bawd's engagements, or of enduring further trials, had however such an effect on my grateful disposition, that I even thought myself oblig'd to my undoers for their attentions to promote my recovery, and, above all, for the keeping out of my sight of that brutal ravisher, the author of my disorder, on their finding I was too strongly mov'd at the bare mention of his name.<break time="100ms" />Youth is soon raised; and a few days were sufficient to conquer the fury of my fever: but what contributed most to my perfect recovery, and to my reconciliation with life, was the timely news, that Mr. Crofts, who was a merchant of considerable dealings, was arrested at the king's suit, for nearly forty thousand pounds, on account of his driving a certain contraband trade, and that his affairs were so desperate, that even were it in his inclination, it would not be in his power to renew his designs upon me: for he was instantly thrown into a prison, which it was not likely he would get out of in haste.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Brown, who had touch'd his fifty guineas, advanc'd to so little purpose, and lost all hopes of the remaining hundred, began to look upon my treatment of him with a more favourable eye; and as they had observ'd my temper to be perfectly tractable, and conformable to their views, all the girls that compos'd her flock, were suffer'd to visit me, and had their cue to dispose me, by their conversation, to a perfect resignation of myself to Mrs. Brown's direction.<break time="100ms" />Accordingly they were let in upon me, and all that frolic and thoughtless gaiety in which those giddy creatures consume their leisure, made me envy a condition of which I only saw the fair side: insomuch, that the being one of them became even my ambition: a disposition which they all carefully cultivated; and I wanted now nothing but to restore my health, that I might be able to undergo the ceremony of the initiation.<break time="100ms" />Conversation, example, all, in short, contributed, in that house, to corrupt my native purity, which had taken no root in education, whilst now the inflammable principle of pleasure, so easily fired at my age, made strange work within me, and all the modesty I was brought up in the habit, (not the instruction) of, began to melt away, like dew before the sun's heat; not to mention that I made a vice of necessity, from the constant fears I had of being turn'd out to starve.<break time="100ms" />I was soon pretty well recover'd, and at certain hours allow'd to range all over the house, but cautiously kept from seeing any company, till the arrival of Lord B——— from Bath, to whom Mrs. Brown, in respect to his experienced generosity on such occasions, proposed to offer the perusal of that trinket of mine, which bears so great an imaginary value; and his lordship being expected in town in less than a fortnight, Mrs. Brown judged I would be entirely renewed in beauty, and freshness, by that time, and afford her the chance of a better bargain than she had driven with Mr. Crofts.<break time="100ms" />In the mean time, I was so thoroughly, as they call it, brought over, so tame to their whistle, that, had my cage-door been set open, I had no idea that I ought to fly anywhere, sooner than stay where I was; nor had I the least sense of regretting my condition, but waited very quietly for whatever Mrs. Brown should order concerning me, who on her side, by herself, and her agents, took more than the necessary precautions to lull and lay asleep all just reflexions on my destination.<break time="100ms" />Preachments of morality over the left shoulder, a life of joy painted in the gayest colours, caresses, promises, indulgent treatment, nothing in short was wanting to domesticate me entirely, and to prevent my going out any where to get better advice; alas! I dream'd of no such thing.<break time="100ms" />Hitherto I had been indebted only to the girls of the house for the corruption of my innocence: their luscious talk, in which modesty was far from respected, their description of their engagements with men, had given me a tolerable insight into the nature and mysteries of their profession, at the same time that they highly provok'd an itch of florid warm-spirited blood through every vein; but above all, my bed-fellow Phœbe, whose pupil I more immediately was, exerted her talents in giving me the first tinctures of pleasure: whilst nature, now warm'd, and wantoned with discoveries so interesting, piqu'd a curiosity which Phœbe artfully whetted, and leading me from question to question of her own suggestion, explain'd to me all the mysteries of Venus; but I could not long remain in such an house as that, without being an eye-witness of more than I could conceive from her descriptions.<break time="100ms" />One day about twelve at noon, being thoroughly recover'd of my fever, I happen'd to be in Mrs. Brown's dark closet, where I had not been half an hour, resting upon the maids settle-bed, before I heard a rustling in the bed-chamber, separated from the closet only by two sash-doors, before the glasses of which were drawn two yellow-damask curtains, but not so close as to exclude the full view of the room from any person in the closet.<break time="100ms" />I instantly crept softly, and posted myself so, that seeing every thing minutely, I could not myself be seen; and who should come in but the venerable mother Abbess herself! handed in by a tall, brawny young horse-grenadier, moulded in the Hercules-stile; in fine, the choice of the most experienced dame, in those Affairs, in all London.<break time="100ms" />Oh! how still and hush did I keep at my stand, lest any noise should baulk my curiosity, or bring Madam into the closet!
    </voice>
</speak>
