<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />As soon as I heard them go down stairs, I stole up softly to my own room, out of which I had been luckily not mist. There I began to breathe a little freer, and to give a loose to those warm emotions which the sight of such an encounter had rais'd in me. I laid me down on the bed stretch'd myself out, joining, and ardently wishing, and requiring any means to divert or allay the rekindl'd rage and tumult of my desires, which all pointed strongly to their pole, man. I felt about the bed, as if I sought for something that I grasp'd in my waking dream, and not finding it, could have cried for vexation, every part of me glowing with stimulating fires. At length, I resorted to the only present remedy, that of vain attempts at digitation, where the smallness of the theater did not yet afford room enough for action, and where the pain my fingers gave me, in striving for admission, though they procur'd me a slight satisfaction for the present, started an apprehension, which I could not be easy till I had communicated to Phœbe, and received her explanations upon it.<break time="100ms" />The opportunity however did not offer till next morning, for Phœbe did not come to bed till long after I was gone to sleep: as soon then, as we were both awake, it was but in course to bring our ly-a-bed chat to land on the subject of my uneasiness: to which a recital of the love scene, I had thus, by a chance been spectatress of, served for a preface.<break time="100ms" />Phœbe could not hear it to the end without more than one interruption by peals of laughter, and my ingenuous way of relating matters did not a little heighten the joke to her.<break time="100ms" />But on her sounding me how the sight had affected me: without mincing or hiding the pleasurable emotions it had inspir'd me with, I told her at the same time that one remark had perplex'd me, and that very considerably: "Aye!" say she, what was that?" Why, replied I, having very curiously and attentively compared the size of that enormous machine, which did not appear, at least to my fearful imagination, less than my wrist, and at least three of my handfuls long, to that of the tender, small part of me which was framed to receive it, I can not conceive its being possible to afford it entrance there, without dying, perhaps in the greatest pain, since she well knew that even a finger thrust in there, hurt me beyond bearing————as to my mistress's and yours,————I can very plainly distinguish the different dimensions of them from mine, palpable to the touch, and visible to the eye, so that in short, great as the promised pleasure may be, I am afraid of the pain of the experiment.<break time="100ms" />Phœbe at this redoubl'd her laugh, and, whilst I expected a very serious solution of my doubts and apprehensions in this matter, only told me that she never heard of a mortal wound being given in those parts, by that terrible weapon, and that some she knew younger, and as delicately made as myself, had outlived the operation, that she believed, at the worst, I should take a great deal of killing:————that true it was, there was a great diversity of sizes in those parts, owing to nature child-bearing, frequent over-stretching with unmerciful machines; but that at a certain age, and habit of body, even the most experienc'd in those affairs could not well distinguish between the maid, and the woman, supposing too an absence of all artifice, and things in their natural situation: but that since chance had thrown in my way one sight of that sort, she would procure me another, that should feast my eyes more delicately, and go a great way in the cure of my fears from that imaginary disproportion.<break time="100ms" />On this she asked me if I knew Polly Philips. Undoubtedly, says I, the fair girl which was so tender of me when I was sick, and has been, as you told me, but two months in the house? the same, says Phœbe. You must know then, she is kept by a young Genoese merchant, whom his uncle, who is immensely rich, and whose darling he is, sent over here with an English merchant his friend, on a pretext of settling some accounts, but in reality to humour his inclinations for travelling, and seeing the world. He met casually with this Polly once in company, and taking a liking to her, makes it worth her while to keep entirely to him: he comes to her here twice or thrice a week, and she receives him in the light closet up one pair of stairs, where he enjoys her in a taste I suppose peculiar to the heat, or perhaps the caprices of his own country. I say no more; but tomorrow being his day, you shall see what passes between them, from a place only known to your mistress, and myself.<break time="100ms" />You may be sure, in the ply I was now taking, I had no objection to the proposal, and was rather a tip-toe for its accomplishment.<break time="100ms" />At five in the evening then, next day, Phœbe, punctual to her promise, came to me as I sat alone in my own room, and beckon'd me to follow her.<break time="100ms" />We went down the back-stairs very softly, and opening the door of a dark closet, where there was some old furniture kept, and some cases of liquor, she drew me in after her, and fastening the door upon us, we had no light but what came through a long crevice in the partition between ours and the light closet, where the scene of action lay: so that sitting on those low cases, we could, with the greatest ease, as well as clearness, see all objects, (ourselves unseen) only by applying our eyes close to the crevice, where the moulding of a pannel had warp'd, or started a little on the other side.<break time="100ms" />The young gentleman was the first person I saw, with his back directly towards me, looking at a print. Polly was not yet come, In less than a minute tho', the door opened, and she came in, and at the noise the door made, he turned about, and came to meet her, with an air of the greatest tenderness and satisfaction.<break time="100ms" />After saluting her, he led her to a couch that fronted us, where they both sat down, and the young Genoese help'd her to a glass of wine, with some Naples bisket on a salver.<break time="100ms" />Presently, when they had exchanged a few kisses, and questions in broken English on one side, he began to unbutton, and, in fine, stript to his shirt.<break time="100ms" />As if this had been the signal agreed on for pulling off all their cloaths, a scheme which the heat of the season perfectly favoured, Polly began to draw her pins, and as she had no stays to unlace, she was in a trice, with her gallant's officious assistance, undress'd to all but her shift.<break time="100ms" />When he saw this, his breeches were immediately loosen'd, waist, and knee-bands, and slipt over his ancles, clean off: his shirt collar was unbuttoned too: then, first giving Polly an encouraging kiss, he stole as it were the shift off the girl, who being I suppose broke and familiariz'd to this humour, blush'd indeed, but less than I did, at the apparition of her now standing stark-naked, just as she came out of the hands of pure nature, with her black hair loose, and a-float down her dazzling white neck and shoulders, whilst the deepen'd carnation of her cheeks went off gradually into the hue of glaz'd snow; for such were the blended tints, and polish of her skin.
    </voice>
</speak>
