<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I got to the street-door, the key whereof was always laid on the chair by our bed-side, in trust with Phœbe, who having not the least suspicion of my entertaining any design to go from them, (nor indeed had I but the day before) made no reserve, or concealment of it from me. I open'd the door then with great ease; love that embolden'd, protected me too: and now, got safe into the street, I saw my new guardian-angel waiting at a coach-door ready open. How I got to him I know not: I suppose I flew; but I was in the coach in a trice, and he by the side of me, with his arms clasp'd round me, and giving me the kiss of welcome.——The coachman had his orders, and drove to them.<break time="100ms" />My eyes were instantly fill'd with tears, but tears of the most delicious delight. To find myself in the arms of that beauteous youth, was a rapture that my little heart swam in. Past or future were equally out of the question with me. The present was as much as all my powers of life were sufficient to bear the transport of without fainting. Nor were the most tender embraces, the most soothing expressions wanting on his side, to assure me of his love, and of never giving me cause to repent the bold step I had taken, in throwing myself thus entirely upon his honour and generosity: but, alas! this was no merit in me, for I was drove to it by a passion too impetuous for me to resist, and I did what I did, because I could not help it.<break time="100ms" />In an instant, for time was now annihilated with me, we landed at a public house in Chelsea, hospitably commodious for the reception of duet-parties of pleasure, where a breakfast of chocolate was prepared for us.<break time="100ms" />An old jolly stager, who kept it, and understood life perfectly well, breakfasted with us, and leering archly at me, gave us both joy, and said, we were well paired, e'faith! that a great many gentlemen and ladies used his house, but he had never seen a handsomer couple;———He was sure I was a fresh piece———I look'd so country, so innocent! well my spouse was a lucky man!———all which common landlord's cant, not only pleas'd and sooth'd me, but help'd to divert my confusion at being with my new sovereign, whom, now the minute approach'd, I began to fear to be alone with, a timidity which true love had a greater share in, than even maiden bashfulness.<break time="100ms" />I wish'd, I doated, I could have died for him, and yet I know not how, or why, I dreaded the point which had been the object of my fiercest wishes; my pulses beat fears, amidst a flush of the warmest desires: this struggle of the passions, however, this conflict betwixt modesty and love-sick longings, made me burst again into tears, which he took as he had done before, only for the remains of concern and emotion at the suddenness of my change of condition, in committing myself to his care, and in consequence of that idea, did, and said, all that he thought would most comfort and re inspirit me.<break time="100ms" />After breakfast, Charles, the dear familiar name I must take the liberty henceforward to distinguish my Adonis by, with a smile full of meaning, took me gently by the hand, and said, "Come, my dear, I will show you a room that commands a fine prospect over some gardens:" and without waiting for an answer, in which he relieved me extremely, he led me up into a chamber, airy and lightsome, where all seeing of prospects was out of the question, except that of a bed, which had all the air of having recommended the room to him.<break time="100ms" />Charles had just slipp'd the bolt of the door, and running, caught me in his arms, and lifting me from the ground, with his lips glew'd to mine, bore me trembling, panting, dying, with soft fears, and tender wishes, to the bed; where his impatience would not suffer him to undress me more than just unpinning my handkerchief, and gown, and unlacing my stays.<break time="100ms" />My bosom was now bare, and rising in the warmest throbs, presented to his sight and feeling the firm hard-swell of a pair of young breasts, such as may be imagin'd of a girl not sixteen, fresh out of the country, and never before handled; but even their pride, whiteness, fashion, pleasing resistance to the touch, could not bribe his restless hands from roving, but giving them the loose, my petty-coats and shift were soon taken up, and their stronger center of attraction laid open to their tender invasion: my fears however made me mechanically close my thighs; but the very touch of his hand insinuated between them, disclosed them, and open'd a way for the main attack.<break time="100ms" />In the mean time I lay fairly exposed to the examination of his eyes, and hands, quiet and unresisting, which confirm'd him in the opinion he proceeded so cavalierly upon, that I was no novice in these matters, since he had taken me out of a common bawdy-house: nor had I said one thing to prepossess him of my virginity; and if I had, he would sooner have believ'd that I took him for a cully that would swallow such an improbability, than that I was still mistress of that darling treasure, that hidden mine, so eagerly sought after by the men, and which they never dig for but they destroy.<break time="100ms" />Being now too high wound up to bear a delay, he unbutton'd, and drawing out the engine of love-assaults, drove it currently, as at a ready-made breach: then! then! for the first time did I feel that stiff horn-hard gristle, battering against the tender part; but imagine to yourself his surprize, when he found, after several vigorous pushes, which hurt me extremely, that he made not the least impression.<break time="100ms" />I complain'd, but tenderly complain'd; "I could not bear it———" Indeed! he hurt me——still he thought no more than that being so young, the largeness of his machine (for few men could dispute size with him) made all the dificulty, and that possible I had not been enjoy'd by any so advantageously made in that part as himself; for still, that my virgin-flower was yet uncrop'd never once enter'd into his head, and he would have thought it idling with time and words to have question'd me upon it.<break time="100ms" />He tries again; still no admittance; still no penetration; but he had hurt me yet more, whilst my extreme love made me bear extreme pain almost without a groan: at length, after repeated fruitless trials, he lay down panting by me, kiss'd my falling tears, and ask'd me tenderly, what was the meaning of so much complaining, and if I had not born it better from others than I did from him? I answer'd, with a simplicity fram'd to perswade, that he was the first man that ever serv'd me so: truth is powerful, and it is not always that we do not believe what we eagerly wish.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
