<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The young foreigner was sitting down, fronting us, on the couch; with Polly upon one knee, who had her arms round his neck, whilst the extreme whiteness of her skin was not undelightfully contrasted by the smooth glossy brown of her lover's.<break time="100ms" />But who could count the fierce, unnumber's kisses given and taken? in which I could often discover their exchanging the velvet thrust, when both their mouths were double-tongued, and seem'd to favour the mutual insertion with the greatest gust and delight.<break time="100ms" />In the mean time, his red-headed champion that has so lately fled the pit, quell'd, and abash'd, was now recover'd to the top of its condition, perk'd and crested up between Polly's thighs, who was not wanting on her part to coax and deep it in good humour, stroking it with her head down, and receiv'd even its velvet tip between the lips of not its proper mouth, whether she did this out of any particular pleasure, or whether it was to render it more glib, and easy of entrance, I could not tell; but it had such an effect, that the young gentleman seem'd by his eyes, that sparkled with more excited lustre, and his inflamed countenance, to receive encrease of pleasure. He got up, and taking Polly in his arms embraced her, and said something too softly for me to hear, leading her withal to the foot of the couch, and taking delight to slap her thighs, and posteriours with that stiff sinew of his, which hit them, with a spring, that he gave it with his hand, and made them resound again, but hurt her about as much as he meant to hurt her, for she seem'd to have as frolick a taste as himself.<break time="100ms" />But, guess my surprise, when I saw the lazy young rogue lie down on his back, and gently pull down Polly upon him, who giving way to his humour, straddled, and with her hands conducted her blind favourite to the right place, and following her impulse, ran directly upon the flaming point of this weapon of pleasure, which she stak'd herself upon, up-pierc'd, and infix'd to the extremest hair-breadth of it: thus she sat on him, a few instants, enjoying, and relishing her situation, whilst he toyed with her provoking breasts.——Sometimes she would stoop to meet his kiss: but presently the sting of pleasure spurr'd them up to fiercer action: then began the storm of heaves, which, from the undermost combatant, were thrusts at the same time: he crossing his hands over her, and drawing her home to him with a sweet violence: the inverted strokes of anvil over hammer soon brought on the critical period, in which all the signs of a close conspiring extasy, informed us of the point they were at.<break time="100ms" />For me, I could bear to see no more: I was so overcome, so inflamed at this second part of the same play, that, mad to an intolerable desire, I hugg'd, I clasp'd Phœbe, as if she had wherewithal to relieve me: pleased however with, and pitying the taking she could feel me in, she drew me towards the door and opening it as softly as she could, we both got off undiscover'd, and she reconducted me to my own room, where unable to keep my legs, in the agitation, I was in, I instantly threw myself down on the bed, where I lay transported, tho' asham'd at what I felt.<break time="100ms" />Phœbe lay down by me, and ask'd me archly, if now that I had seen the enemy, and fully considered him, I was still afraid of him? or did I think I could venture to come to a close engagement with him? to all which not a word on my side: I sigh'd, and could scarce breathe: She takes hold of my hand, and having roll'd up her own petticoats, forced it half-strivingly towards those parts, where now grown more knowing, I mist the main object of my wishes; and finding not even the shadow of what I wanted, where every thing was so flat! or so hollow! In the vexation I was in at it, I should have withdrawn my hand, but for fear of disobliging her. Abandoning it then entirely to her management, she made use of it as she thought proper, to procure herself rather the shadow than the substance of any pleasure. For my part, I now pin'd for more solid food, and promis'd tacitly to myself that I would not be put off much longer with this foolery from woman to woman, if Mrs. Brown did not soon provide me with the essential specific: in short I had all the air of not being able to wait the arrival of my lord B———, tho' he was now expected in a very few days: nor did I wait for him, for love itself took charge of the disposal of me, in spite of interest, or gross lust.<break time="100ms" />It was now two days after the closet-scene, that I got up about six in the morning, and leaving my bed-fellow fast a-sleep, stole down, with no other thought than of taking a little fresh air in a small garden, which our back-parlour open'd into, and from which my confinement debarr'd me at the times company came to the house; but now sleep and silence reign'd all over it.<break time="100ms" />I open'd the parlour-door, and well surpriz'd was I, at seeing, by the side of a fire half out, a young gentleman in the old lady's elbow chair, with his legs laid upon another, fast a-sleep, and left there, by his thoughtless companions, who had drank him down, and then went off with every one his mistress, whilst he stay'd behind by the curtesy of the old matron, who would not disturb, or turn him out in that condition at one in the morning, and beds, it is more than probable, there were none to spare: On the table still remain'd the punch-bowl and glasses, strow's about in their usual disorder after a drunken revel.<break time="100ms" />But when I drew nearer to view the sleeping estray: Heavens! what a sight! no! no term of years, no turn of fortune could ever eraze the lightening-like impression his form made on me. . . . . . Yes! dearest object of my earliest passion, I command for ever the remembrance of thy first appearance to my ravish'd eyes,——it calls thee up, present; and I see thee now!<break time="100ms" />Figure to yourself, Madam, a fair stripling, between eighteen and nineteen, with his head reclin'd on one of the sides of the chair, his hair in disorder'd curls, irregularly shading a face, on which all the roseate bloom of youth, and all the manly graces conspired to fix my eyes and heart. Even the languor, and paleness of his face, in which the momentary triumph of the lily over the rose, was owing to the excesses of the night, gave an inexpressible sweetness to the finest features imaginable: his eyes closed in sleep, displayed the meeting edges of their lids beautifully bordered with long eye-lashes; over which no pencil could have describ'd two more regular arches than those that grac'd his fore-head, which was high, perfectly white and smooth; then a pair of vermillion lips, pouting, and swelling to the touch, as if a bee had freshly stung them, seem'd to challenge me to get the gloves off this lovely sleeper, had not the modesty, and respect, which in both sexes are inseparable from a true passion, check'd my impulses.
    </voice>
</speak>
