<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />There are not, on earth at least, eternal griefs; mine were, if not at an end, at least suspended: my heart, which had been so long overloaded with anguish and vexation, began to dilate and open to the least gleam of diversion, or amusement. I wept a little, and my tears reliev'd me: I sigh'd, and my sighs seem'd to lighten me of a load that opprest me: my countenance grew, if not chearful, at least more compos'd, and free.<break time="100ms" />Mr. H——— who had watched, perhaps brought on this change, knew too well not to seize it: He thrust the table imperceptibly from between us, and bringing his chair to face me, he soon began, after preparing me by all the endearments of assurances, and protestations, to lay hold of my hands, to kiss me, and once more to make free with my bosom, which being at full liberty from the disorder of my loose dishabil, now panted and throb'd less with indignation than with fear and bashfulness, at being used so familiarly by still a stranger: but he soon gave me greater occasion to exclaim, by stooping down and slipping his hand above my garters; thence he strove to regain the pass which he had before found so open, and unguarded: but now he could not unlock the twist of my thighs: I gently complain'd, and begg'd him to let me alone; told him I was not well: however, as he saw there was more form and ceremony in my resistance, than good earnest, he made his conditions for desisting from pursuing his point that I should be put instantly to bed, whilst he gave certain orders to the landlady, and that he would return in an hour, when he hop'd to find me more reconcil'd to his passion for me, than I seem'd at present. I neither assented nor deny'd, but my air and manner of receiving this proposal, gave him to see that I did not think myself enough my own mistress to refuse it.<break time="100ms" />Accordingly he went out and left me, when a minute or two after, before I could recover myself into any composure for thinking, the maid came in with her mistress's service, and a small silver porrenger of what she call'd a bridal posset, and desir'd me to eat it as I went to bed, which consequently I did, and felt immediately a heat, a fire run like a hue-and-cry through ev'ry part of my body; I burnt, I glow'd, and wanted even little of wishing for any man.<break time="100ms" />The maid, as soon as I was lain down, took the candle away, and wishing me a good night, went out of the room, and shut the door after her.<break time="100ms" />She had hardly time to get down stairs before Mr. H——— open'd my room door softly, and came in, now undrest, in his night-gown and cap, with two lighted wax-candles, and bolting the door, gave me, though I expected him, some sort of alarm. He came a tip-toe to the bed-side, and said with a gentle whisper, "pray my dear do not be startl'd, —— I will be very tender and kind to you." He then hurry'd off his cloaths, and leap'd into bed, having given me openings enough, whilst he was stripping, to observe his brawny structure, strong made limbs, and rough shaggy breast.<break time="100ms" />The bed shook again when it receiv'd this new load: He lay on the outside, where he kept the candles burning, no doubt for the satisfaction of ev'ry sense; for as soon as he had kiss'd me, he roll'd down the bed-cloaths, and seem'd transported with the view of all my person at full length, which he cover'd with a profusion of kisses, sparing no part of me. Then, being on his knees between my thighs, he drew up his shirt, and bared all his hairy thighs, and stiff staring truncheon, red-topt, and rooted into a thicket of curls, which cover'd his belly to the navel, and gave it the air of a flesh-brush: and soon I felt it joining close to mine, when he had drove the nail up to the head, and left no partition but the intermediate hair on both sides.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
