<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />As to money, though he brought me constantly all he receiv'd, it was with difficulty he even got me to give it room in my bureau, and what cloaths I had, he could prevail on me to accept on, on no other foot, than that of pleasing him by the greater neatness in my dress, beyond which I had no ambition; I could have made a pleasure of the greatest toil, and work'd my fingers to the bone, with joy, to have supported him: guess, then, if I could harbour any idea of being burdensome to him: and this disinterested turn in me was so unaffected, so much the dictate of my heart, that Charles could not but feel it, and if he did not love me as I did him (which was the constant and only matter of sweet contention between us) he manag'd so at least as to give me the satisfaction of believing it impossible for man to be more tender, more true, more faithful than he was.<break time="100ms" />Our landlady, Mrs. Jones, came frequently up to my apartment from whence I never stirr'd on any pretext without Charles: nor was it long before she worm'd out, without much art, the secret of our having cheated the church of a ceremony; and in course of the terms we liv'd together upon: a circumstance which far from displeas'd her, considering the designs she had upon me, and which, alas! she will have too soon room to carry into execution. But in the mean time her own experience of life, let her see that any attempt however indirect, or disguis'd, to divert or break, at least presently, so strong a cement of hearts as ours was, could only end in losing two lodgers, of whom she made very competent advantages, if either of us came to smoak her commission, for a commission she had from one of her customers, either to debauch or get me away from my keeper at any rate.<break time="100ms" />But the barbarity of my fate soon sav'd her the task of disuniting us. I had now been eleven months with this life of my life, which had passed in one continu'd rapid stream of delight: but nothing so violent was ever made to last. I was about three months gone with child by him, a circumstance which would have added to his tenderness, had he ever left me room to believe it could receive an addition, when the mortal, the unexpected blow of separation fell upon us. I shall gallop post over the particulars, which I shudder yet to think of, and cannot to this instant reconcile myself how, or by what means I could outlive it.<break time="100ms" />Two live-long days had I linger'd through, without hearing from him, I who breath'd, who existed but in him, and had never yet seen twenty-four hours pass without seeing or hearing from him. The third day my impatience was so strong, my alarms had been so severe, that I perfectly sicken'd with them, and being unable to support the shock longer, I sunk upon the bed, and ringing for Mrs. Jones, who had far from comforted me under my anxieties, she came up and I had scarce breath and spirit enough to find words to beg of her if she would save my life, to fall upon some means of finding out instantly what was become of its only prop, and comfort: She pity'd me in a way that rather sharpen'd my affliction than suspended it, and went out upon this commission.<break time="100ms" />For she had not to go to Charles's house, who liv'd but at an easy distance, in one of the streets that run into Covent-Garden. There she went into a public-house, and from thence sent for a maid servant, whose name I had given her, as the properest to inform her.<break time="100ms" />The maid readily came, and as readily, when Mrs. Jones enquir'd of her what was become of Mr. Charles, or whether he was gone out of town, acquainted her with the disposal of her master's son, which the very day after was no secret to the servants; such sure measures had he taken for the most cruel punishment of his child, for having more interest with his grand-mother than he had, though he made use of a pretence, plausible enough to get rid of him in this secret and abrupt manner, for fear her fondness should have interpos'd a bar to his leaving England, and proceeding on a voyage he had concerted for him, which pretext was, that it was indispensably necessary to secure a considerable inheritance, that devolv'd to him by the death of a rich merchant (his own brother) at one of the factories in the South-Seas, of which he had lately receiv'd advice, together with a copy of the Will.<break time="100ms" />In consequence of which resolution to send away his son, he had, unknown to him, made the necessary preparations for fitting him out, struck a bargain with the captain of a ship, whose punctual execution of his orders he had secured by his interest with his principal owner and patron, and in short concerted his measures so secretly and effectually, that whilst his son thought he was going down the river that would take him a few hours, he was stopt on board of a ship, debar'd from writing, and more strictly watch'd than a state-criminal.<break time="100ms" />Thus was the idol of my soul torn from me, and forc'd on a long voyage without taking leave of one friend, or receiving one line of comfort, except a dry explanation and instructions from his father how to proceed, when he should arrive at his destin'd port, enclosing withal some letters of recommendation to a factor there: all these particulars I did not learn minutely till some time after.<break time="100ms" />The maid at the same time added, that she was sure this usage of her sweet young master would be the death of his grand-mama, as indeed it prov'd true, for the old lady on hearing it, did not survive the news a whole month, and as her fortune consisted in an annuity, out of which she had laid up no reserves, she left nothing worth mentioning to her so fatally envied darling, but absolutely refus'd to see his father before she died.<break time="100ms" />When Mrs. Jones return'd, and I observ'd her looks, they seem'd so unconcern'd and even nearest to pleas'd, that I half flatter'd myself, she was going to set my tortur'd heart at ease, by bringing me good news; but this indeed was a cruel delusion of hope: the barbarian, with all the coolness imaginable, stabs me to the heart, in telling me succinctly that he was sent away at least on a four years voyage, (here she stretch'd maliciously) and that I could not expect in reason ever to see him again: and all this with such pregnant circumstances, that I could not escape giving them credit, as in general they were indeed too true!<break time="100ms" />She had hardly finish'd her report, before I fainted away, and after several successive fits, all the while wild and senseless, I miscarried of the dear pledge of my Charles's love: but the wretched never die when it is fittest they should die, and women are hard-liv'd to a proverb.<break time="100ms" />The cruel and interested care taken to recover me, sav'd an odious life: which instead of the happiness and joys it had overflow'd in, all of a sudden presented no view before me of any thing but the depth of misery, horror, and the sharpest affliction.<break time="100ms" />Thus I lay six weeks, in the struggles of youth and constitution against the friendly efforts of death, which I constantly invok'd to my relief and deliverance, but which proving too weak for my wish, I recover'd at length, but into a state of stupefaction and despair that threaten'd me with a loss of my senses, and a mad-house.
    </voice>
</speak>
