<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />As for the wench, she was now spoil'd at least for my servant; and scarce eight and forty hours were gone round, before her insolence, on what had pass'd between Mr. H——— and her, gave me so fair an occasion to turn her away at a minute's warning, that not to have done it would have been the wonder; so that he could neither disapprove it, nor find in it the least reason to suspect my original motive. What became of her afterwards I know not; but generous as Mr. H——— was, he undoubtedly made her amends: tho' I dare answer, that he kept up no farther commerce with her of that sort; as his stooping to such a coarse morsel, was only a sudden sally of lust, on seeing a wholesome-looking, buxom country-wench, and no more strange than hunger, or even a whimsical appetite's making a fling meal of neck-beef, for change of diet.<break time="100ms" />Had I consider'd this escapade of Mr. H——— in no more than that light, and contented myself with turning away the wench, I had thought and acted right; but, flush'd as I was with imaginary wrongs, I should have held Mr. H——— to have been cheaply off, if I had not push'd my revenge farther, and repaid him, as exactly as I could for the soul of me, in the same coin.<break time="100ms" />Nor was this worthy act of justice long delaid: I had it too much at heart, Mr. H——— had, about a fortnight before, taken into his service a tenant's son, just come out of the country, a very handsome young lad scarce turn'd of nineteen, fresh as a rose, well shap'd and clever-limb'd: in short, a very good excuse for any woman's liking, even tho' revenge had been out of the question; any woman, I say, who was disprejudic'd, and had wit and spirit enough to prefer a point of pleasure to a point of pride.<break time="100ms" />Mr. H——— had clap'd a livery upon him; and his chief employ was, after being shewn my lodgings, to bring and carry letters or messages between his master and me; and as the situation of all kept-ladies is not the fittest to inspire respect even to the meanest of mankind, and perhaps less of it from the most ignorant, I could not help observing, that this lad, who was, I suppose, acquainted with my relation to his master by his fellow servants, used to eye me, in that bashful confus'd way, more expressive, more moving, and readier catch'd at by our sex, than any other declarations whatever: my figure had, it seems, struck him, and modest and innocent as he was, he did not himself know that the pleasure he took in looking at me was love, or desire; but his eyes, naturally wanton, and now enflam'd with passion, spoke a great deal more than he durst have imagin'd they did. Hitherto indeed I had only taken notice of the comeliness of the youth, but without the least design: My pride alone would have guarded me from a thought that way, had not Mr. H———'s condescension with my maid, where there was not half the temptation in point of person, set me a dangerous example; but now I began to look on this stripling as every way a delicious instrument of my design'd retaliation upon Mr. H———, of an obligation for which I should have made a conscience to die in his debt.<break time="100ms" />In order then to pave the way for the accomplishment of my scheme, for two or three times that the young fellow came to me with messages, I manag'd so, as without affectation to have him admitted to my bed-side, or brought to me at my toilet, where I was dressing; and by carelessly shewing, or letting him see, as if without meaning or design, sometimes my bosom rather more bare than it should be; sometimes my hair, of which I had a very fine head, in the natural flow of it while combing; sometimes a neat leg, that had unfortunately slipt its garter, which I made no scruple of tying before him; easily gave him the impressions favourable to my purpose, which I could perceive to sparkle in his eyes, and glow in his cheeks: Then certain slight squeezes by the hand, as I took letters from him, did his business compleatly.<break time="100ms" />When I saw him thus mov'd, and fir'd for my purpose, I inflam'd him yet more, by asking him several leading questions; such as, "had he a mistress?——— was she prettier than me?——— could he love such a one as I was?——— and the like;" to all which the blushing simpleton answer'd to my wish, in a strain of perfect nature, perfect undebauch'd innocence, but with all the aukwardness and simplicity of country-breeding.<break time="100ms" />When I thought I had sufficiently ripen'd him for the laudable point I had in view; one day that I expected him at a particular hour, I took care to have the coast clear for the reception I design'd him: and, as I had laid it, he came to the dining-room door, tapped at it, and on my bidding him come in, he did so, and shut the door after him: I desir'd him then to bolt it on the inside, pretending it would not otherwise keep shut.<break time="100ms" />I was then lying at length upon that very couch, the scene of Mr. H———'s polite joys, in an undress, which was with all the art of negligence flowing loose, and in a most tempting disorder, no stay, no hoop——no incumbrance whatever: on the other hand, he stood at a little distance, that gave me a full view of a fine featur'd, shapely, healthy, country lad, breathing the sweets of fresh blooming youth: his hair, which was of a perfect shining black, play'd to his face in natural side-curls, and was set out with a smart tuck-up behind: new buck-skin breeches, that clipping close, shew'd the shape of a plump well made thigh, white stockings, garter-laced livery, shoulder-knot, altogether compos'd a figure in which the beauties of pure flesh and blood, appear'd under no disgrace from the lowness of a dress, to which a certain spruce neatness seems peculiarly fitted.<break time="100ms" />I bid him come towards me, and give me his letter, at the same time throwing down carelessly, a book I had in my hands. He colour'd, and came within reach of delivering me the letter, which he held out aukwardly enough for me to take, with his eyes riveted on my bosom, which was, through the design'd disorder of my handkerchief, sufficiently bare, and rather shaded than hid.<break time="100ms" />I, smiling in his face, took the letter, and immediately catching gently hold of his shirt sleeve, drew him towards me, blushing, and almost trembling: for surely his extreme bashfulness, and utter inexperience, call'd for at least all the advances to encourage him: his body was now conveniently inclin'd towards me, and just softly chucking his smooth beardless chin, I ask'd him, If he was afraid of a lady?——— and with that took and carrying his hand to my breasts, I prest it tenderly to them; they were now finely furnish'd, and rais'd in flesh, so that panting with desire, they rose, and fell, in quick heaves, under his touch: at this the boy's eyes began to lighten with all the fires of inflam'd nature, and his cheeks flush'd with a deep scarlet: tongue-tied with joy, rapture, and bashfulness, he could not speak, but then his looks, his emotion, sufficiently satisfy'd me that my train had taken, and that I had no disappointment to fear.
    </voice>
</speak>
