<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I was now so bruised, so batter'd, so spent with this over-match, that I could hardly stir, or raise myself, but lay palpitating, till the ferment of my sense subsiding by degrees, and the hour striking at which I was oblig'd to dispatch my young man, I tenderly advis'd him of the necessity there was for parting; which I felt as much displeasure at as he could do, who seem'd eagerly dispos'd to keep the field, and to enter on a fresh action: but the danger was too great: and after some hearty kisses of leave, and recommendations of secrecy, and discretion, I forc'd myself to force him away, not without assurances of seeing him again, to the same purpose, as soon as possible, and thrust a guinea into his hands: not more; lest being too flush of money, a suspicion or discovery, might arise from thence, having every thing to fear from the dangerous indiscretion of that age in which young fellows would be too irresistable, too charming, if we had not that terrible fault to guard against.<break time="100ms" />Giddy and intoxicated as I was with such satiating draughts of pleasure, I still lay on the couch, supinely stretch'd out, in a delicious languor diffus'd over all my limbs, hugging myself for being thus reveng'd to my heart's content, and that in a manner so precisely alike, and on the identical spot, in which I had receiv'd the suppos'd injury: no reflections on the consequences ever once perplex'd me, nor did I make myself one single reproach for having, by this step, completely enter'd myself of a profession more decry'd than disus'd. I should have held it ingratitude to the pleasure I had receiv'd, to have repented of it; and since I was now over the bar, I thought by plunging over head and ears into the stream I was hurried away by, to drown all sense of shame or reflection.<break time="100ms" />Whilst I was thus making these laudable dispositions, and whispering to myself a kind of tacit vow of incontinency, enters Mr. H——— The consciousness of what I had been doing, deepen'd yet the glowing of my cheeks, flushed with the warmth of the late action, which, join'd to the piquant air of my dishabil, drew from Mr. H——— a compliment on my looks, which he was proceeding to back the sincerity of with proofs, and that with so brisk an action, as made me tremble for fear of a discovery from the condition those parts were left in from their late severe handling: the orifice dilated and inflam'd, the lips swoln with their uncommon distension, the ringlets press'd down, crush'd and uncurl'd with the overflowing moisture that had wet every thing round it; the different feel and state of things, in short, would hardly have pass'd, upon one of Mr. H———'s nicety and experience, unaccounted for but by the real cause; but here the woman sav'd me: I pretended a violent disorder of my head, and a feverish heat, that indispos'd me too much to receive his embraces. He gave in to this, and good-naturedly desisted. Soon after, an old lady coming in made a third, very a propos for the confusion I was in, and Mr. H———, after bidding me take care of myself, and recommending me to my repose, left me much at ease, and reliev'd by his absence.<break time="100ms" />In the close of the evening, I took care to have prepar'd for me a warm bath of aromatick and sweet herbs; in which, having fully lav'd, and solaced myself, I came out voluptuously refresh'd in body and spirit.<break time="100ms" />The next morning, waking pretty early after a night's perfect rest and composure, it was not without some dread and uneasiness, that I thought of what innovation that tender soft system of mine might have sustain'd from the shock of a machine so siz'd for its destruction.<break time="100ms" />Struck with this apprehension, I scarce dar'd to carry my hand thither, to inform myself of the state and posture of things.<break time="100ms" />But I was soon agreeably cur'd of my fears.<break time="100ms" />The silky hair that cover'd round the borders, now smooth'd and reprun'd, had resum'd its wonted curl and trimness; the fleshy pouting lips, that had stood the brunt of the engagement, were no longer swoln or moisture-drench'd: and neither they, nor the passage into which they open'd, that had suffer'd so great a dilatation, betray'd any the least alteration, outward or inwardly, to the most curious research, notwithstanding also the laxity that naturally follows the warm bath.<break time="100ms" />This continuation of that grateful stricture which is in us, to the men, the very jet of their pleasure, I ow'd, it seems, to a happy habit of body, juicy, plump and furnish'd towards the texture of those parts, with a fullness of soft springy flesh, that yeilding sufficiently as it does, to almost any distension, soon recovers itself so as to retighten that strict compression of its mantlings and folds which form the sides of the passage, wherewith it so tenderly embraces, and closely clips any foreign body introduc'd into it, such as my exploring finger then was.<break time="100ms" />Finding then every thing in due tone and order, I remember'd my fears, only to make a jest of them to myself. And now, palpably mistress of any size of man, and triumphing in my double achievement of pleasure and revenge, I abandon'd myself entirely to the ideas of all the delight I had swam in. I lay stretching out, glowingly alive all over, and tossing with burning impatience for the renewal of joys that had sinn'd but in a sweet excess: now did I lose my longing, for about ten in the morning, according to expectation, Will, my new humble sweet-heart, came with a message from his master, Mr. H———, to know how I did. I had taken care to send my maid on an errand into the city, that I was sure would take up time enough; and from the people of the house I had nothing to fear, as they were plain good sort of folks, and wise enough to mind no more other people's business than they could well help.<break time="100ms" />All dispositions then made, not forgetting that of lying in bed to receive him; when he was enter'd the door of my bed-chamber, a latch that I govern'd by a wire, descended, and secur'd it.<break time="100ms" />I could not but observe that my young minion was as much spruc'd out as could be expected from one in his condition; a desire of pleasing that could not be indifferent to me, since it prov'd that I pleased him, which I assure you was now a point I was not above having in view.<break time="100ms" />His hair trimly dress'd, clean linnen and above all, a hale, ruddy, wholesome country look, made him out as pretty a piece of woman's meat as you could see, and I should have thought any one much out of taste, that could not have made a hearty meal of such a morsel as nature seemed to have design'd for the highest diet of pleasure.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
