<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />As to Mr. H———, he was so much my superior in every sense, that I felt it too much to the disadvantage of the gratitude I ow'd him, thus he gain'd my esteem though he could not raise my taste; I was qualify'd for no sort of conversation with him, except one sort, and that is a satisfaction which leaves tiresome intervals, if not fill'd up by love, or other amusements.<break time="100ms" />Mr. H———, so experienc'd, so learned in the ways of women, numbers of whom had past through his hands, doubtless soon perceiv'd this uneasiness, and without approving or liking me the better for it, had the complaisance to indulge me.<break time="100ms" />He made suppers at my lodgings, where he brought several companions of his pleasures, with their mistresses, and by this means I got into a circle of acquaintance that soon strip'd me of all the remains of bashfulness and modesty which might be yet left of my country education, and were, to a just taste, perhaps, the greatest of my Charms.<break time="100ms" />We visited one another in form, and mimick'd, as near as we could, all the miseries, the follies, and impertinences of the women of quality, in the round of which they trifle away their time, without its ever entering into their little heads, that on earth there cannot subsist any thing more silly, more flat, more insipid and worthless, than, generally considered, their system of life is: they ought to treat the men as their tyrants indeed! were they to condemn them to it.<break time="100ms" />But tho', amongst the kept mistresses (and I was now acquainted with a good many, besides some useful matrons, who live by their connexions with them) I hardly knew one that did not perfectly detest her keepers, and of course, made little or no scruple of any infidelity they could safely accomplish, I had still no notion of wronging mine: for besides that no mark of jealousy on his side started me the hint, or gave me the provocation to play him a trick of that sort, and that his constant generosity, politeness, and tender attentions to please me, forc'd a regard to him, that, without affecting my heart, insur'd him my fidelity, no object had yet presented, that could overcome the habitual liking I had contracted for him: and I was on the eve of obtaining from the movements of his own voluntary generosity, a modest provision for life, when an accident happen'd which broke all the measures he had resolv'd upon in my favour,<break time="100ms" />I had now liv'd near seven months with Mr. H———, when one day returning to my lodgings, from a visit in the neighbourhood, where I us'd to stay longer, I found the street-door open, and the maid of the house standing at it talking with some of her acquaintance, so that I came in without knocking; and as I passed by, she told me Mr. H——— was above. I stept up stairs into my own bed-chamber, with no other thought than of pulling off my hat, andc. and then to wait upon him in the dining-room, into which my bed-chamber had a door, as is common enough. Whilst I was untying my hat-strings, I fancy'd I heard my maid Hannah's voice and a sort of tussle, which raising my curiosity, I stole softly to the door, where a knot in the wood had been slipt out, and afforded a very commanding peep-hole to the scene then in agitation, the actors of which had been too earnestly employ'd, to hear my opening my own door, from the landing place of the stairs, into my bed-chamber.<break time="100ms" />The first sight that struck me was Mr. H——— pulling and hauling this coarse country-strammel towards a couch that stood in a corner of the dining-room; to which the girl made only a sort of aukward hoidening resistance, crying out so loud! that I who listened at the door could scarce hear her, "Pray sir, don't —— let me alone —— I am not for your turn. —— You cannot, sure, demean yourself with such a poor body as I —— Lord! Sir, my mistress may come home —— I must not indeed —— I will cry out ——" All of which did not hinder her from insensibly suffering herself to be brought to the foot of the couch; upon which a push of no mighty violence serv'd to give her a very easy fall, and my gentleman having got up his hands to the strong-hold of her vartue, she no doubt thought it was time to give up the argument, and that all further defence would be in vain: and he throwing her petticoats over her face, which was now as red as scarlet, discover'd a pair of stout, plump, substantial thighs, and tolerably white; he mounted them round his hips, and coming out with his drawn weapon, stuck it in the cloven spot, where he seem'd to find a less difficult entrance than perhaps he had flatter'd himself with (for by the way this Blouze had left her place in the country for a bastard) and indeed all his motions shew'd he was lodg'd pretty much at large. After he had done, his dearee gets up, drops her petticoats down, and smooths her apron and handkerchief. Mr. H——— look'd a little silly, and taking out some money, gave it her, with an air indifferent enough, bidding her be a good girl, and say nothing.<break time="100ms" />Had I lov'd this man, it was not in nature for me to have had patience to see the whole scene through: I should have broke in and play'd the jealous princess with a vengeance; but that was not the case, my pride alone was hurt, my heart not, and I could easier win upon myself to see how far he would go, till I had no uncertainty upon my conscience.<break time="100ms" />The least delicate of all affairs of this sort being now over, I retir'd softly into my closet, where I began to consider what I should do: my first scheme naturally was to rush in and upbraid them: this, indeed, flatter'd my present emotions and vexations, as it would have given immediate vent to them; but, on second thoughts, not being so clear as to the consequences to be apprehended from such a step, I began to doubt whether it was not better to dissemble my discovery, till a safer season, when Mr. H——— should have perfected the settlement he had made overtures to me of, and which I was not to think such a violent explanation, as I was indeed not equal to the management of, could possibly forward, and might destroy. On the other hand, the provocation seem'd too gross, too flagrant, not to give me some thoughts of revenge; the very start of which idea restor'd me to perfect composure; and delighted as I was with the confus'd plan of it in my head, I was easily mistress enough of myself to support the part of ignorance I had prescrib'd to myself; and as all this circle of reflections was instantly over, I stole a tip-toe to the passage door, and opening it with a noise, past for having that moment come home; and after a short pause, as if to pull off my things, I open'd the door into the dining room, where I found the dowdy blowing the fire, and my faithful shepherd walking about the room, and whistling, as cool and unconcern'd, as if nothing had happen'd: I think, however, he had not much to brag of having out-dissembled me; for I kept up, nobly, the character of our sex for art, and went up to him with the same air of frankness, as I had ever receiv'd him. He staid but a little while, made some excuse for not being able to stay the evening with me, and went out.
    </voice>
</speak>
