<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Letter the First
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />I had it now, I felt it now: and beginning to drive, he soon gave nature such a powerful summons down to her favourite quarters, that she could no longer refuse repairing thither: all my animal spirits then rush'd mechanically to that center of attraction, and presently, inly warm'd, and stirr'd as I was beyond bearing, I lost all restraint, and yielding to the force of the emotion, gave down, as mere woman, those effusions of pleasure, which in the strictness of still faithful love, I could have wish'd to have held up.<break time="100ms" />Yet oh! what an immense difference did I feel between this impression of a pleasure merely animal, and struck out of the collision of the sexes, by a passive bodily effect, from that sweet fury, that rage of active delight which crowns the enjoyments of a mutual love-passion, where two hearts tenderly and truly united, club to exalt the joy, and give it a spirit and soul that bids defiance to that end, which mere momentary desires generally terminate in, when they die of a surfeit of satisfaction.<break time="100ms" />Mr. H——— whom no distinctions of that sort seem'd to distract, scarce gave himself or me breathing time from the last encounter, but as if he had task'd himself to prove that the appearances of his vigour, were not signs hung out in vain, in a few minutes he was in a condition for renewing the onset, to which preluding with a storm of kisses, he drove the same course as before with unabated fervour, and thus in repeated engagements, kept me constantly in exercise till dawn of morning, in all which time, he made me full sensible of the virtues of his firm texture of limbs, his square shoulders, broad chest, compact hard muscles, in short a system of manliness, that might pass for no bad image of our antient sturdy barons, when they weilded the battle-ax, whose race is now so thoroughly refin'd and fritter'd away into the more delicate and modern-built frame of our pap-nerv'd softlings, who are as pale, as pretty, and almost as masculine as their sisters.<break time="100ms" />Mr. H———, content however with having the day break upon his triumphs, resign'd me up to the refreshment of a rest we both wanted, and we soon dropt into a profound sleep.<break time="100ms" />Tho' he was some time awake before me, yet did he not offer to disturb a repose he had given me so much occasion for; but on my first stirring, which was not till past ten o'clock, I was oblig'd to endure one more trial of his manhood.<break time="100ms" />About eleven, in came Mrs. Jones, with two basins of the richest soupe, which her experience in these matters had mov'd her to prepare. I pass over the fulsome compliments, the cant of this decent procuress, with which she saluted us both, but tho' my blood rose at the sight of her, I supprest my emotions, and gave all my concern to reflections on what would be the consequence of this new engagement.<break time="100ms" />But Mr. H———, who penetrated my uneasiness, did not long suffer me to languish under it, and acquainted me, that having taken a solid sincere affection to me, he would begin by giving me one leading mark of it, in removing me out of a house which must for many reasons be irksome and disagreeable to me, into convenient lodgings, where he would take all imaginable care of me; and desiring me not to have any explanations with my landlady, or be impatient till he returned, he dress'd and went out, having left me a purse with two and twenty guineas in it, being all he had about him, as he exprest it, to keep my pocket till farther supplies.<break time="100ms" />As soon as he was gone, I felt the usual consequence of the first launch into vice; (for my love attachment to Charles never appear'd to me in that light). I was instantly born away down the stream, without the power of making back to the shore. My dreadful necessities, my gratitude, and above all, to say the plain truth, the dissipation, and diversion I began to find in this new acquaintance, from the black corroding thoughts my heart had been a prey to, ever since the absence of my dear Charles, concurr'd to stun all contrary reflections. If I now thought of my first, my only charmer, it was still with the tenderness and regret of the fondest love, embitter'd with the consciousness that I was no longer worthy of him. I could have beg'd my bread with him all over the world, but wretch that I was! I had neither the virtue nor courage requisite not to outlive my separation from him.<break time="100ms" />Yet! had not my heart been thus pre-ingag'd, Mr. H——— might probably have been the sole master of it, but the place was full, and the force of conjunctures alone had made him the possessor of my person; the charms of which had, by the bye been his sole object, and passion, and were of course, no foundation for a love either very delicate, or very durable.<break time="100ms" />He did not return till six in the evening, to take me away to my new lodgings, and my moveables being soon pack'd, and convey'd into a hackney-coach, it cost me but little regret to take my leave of a landlady whom I thought I had so much reason not to be overpleas'd with, and as for her part, she made no other difference to my staying, or going, but what that of the profit created.<break time="100ms" />We soon got to the house appointed for me, which was that of a plain tradesman, who, on the score of interest, was entirely at Mr. H———'s devotion, and who let him the first floor very genteelly furnish'd, for two guineas a week, of which I was instated mistress, with a maid to attend me.<break time="100ms" />He staid with me that evening, and we had a supper from a neighbouring tavern, after which, and a gay glass or two, the maid put me to bed, Mr. H——— soon follow'd, and notwithstanding the fatigues of the preceding night, I found no quarter nor remission from him: He piqu'd himself, as he told me, on doing the honours of my new apartment.<break time="100ms" />The morning being pretty well advanc'd, we got to breakfast: and the ice now broke, my heart, no longer engross'd by love, began to take ease, and to please itself with such trifles as Mr. H———'s liberal liking led him to make his court to the usual vanity of our sex. Silks, laces, ear-rings, pearl-necklace, gold watch, in short all the trinkets and articles of dress were lavishly heap'd upon me, the sense of which, if it did not create returns of love, forc'd a kind of grateful fondness something like love, a distinction it would be spoiling the pleasure of nine tenths of the keepers in the town to make, and is I suppose the very good reason why so few of them ever do make it.<break time="100ms" />I was now establish'd the kept mistress, in form, well lodg'd, with a very sufficient allowance, and lighted up with all the lustre of dress.<break time="100ms" />Mr. H——— continu'd kind and tender to me, yet, with all this I was far from happy; for, besides my regrets for my dear youth, which though often suspended, or diverted, still return'd upon me in certain melancholic moments with redoubl'd violence, I wanted more society, more dissipation.
    </voice>
</speak>
