<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Slipping then a pillow under me, that I might give him the fairest play, I guided officiously with my hand, this furious battering-ram, whose ruby head presenting nearest the resemblance of a heart, I applied to its proper mark, which lay as finely elevated as we could wish; my hips being born up, and my thighs at their utmost extension, the gleamy warmth that shot from it, made him feel that he was at the mouth of the indraught, and driving foreright, the powerfully divided lips of that pleasure-thirsty channel receiv'd him. He hesitated a little; then, settled well in the passage, he makes his way up the streights of it, with a difficulty nothing more than pleasing, widening as he went, so as to distend and smooth each soft furrow: our pleasure increasing deliciously, in proportion as our points of mutual touch increas'd, in that so vital part of me, in which I had now taken him, all indriven, and compleatly sheath'd, and which cram'd as it was, stretch'd, spliting ripe, gave it so gratefully strait an accommodation! so strict a fold! a suction so fierce, that gave and took unutterable delight! We had now reach'd the closest point of union; but when he backen'd to come on the fiercer, as if I had been actuated by a fear of losing him, in the height of my fury, I twist my legs round his naked loins, the flesh of which, so firm, so springy to the touch, quiver'd again under the pressure; and now I had him every way encircled and begirt; and having drawn him home to me, I kept him fast there, as if I had sought to unite bodies with him at that point. This bred a pause of action, a pleasure stop; whilst that delicate glutton, my neithermouth, as full as it could hold, kept palating, with exquisite relish, the morsel that so deliciously ingorg'd it. But nature could not long endure a pleasure that so highly provok'd without satisfying it; pursuing then its darling end, the battery recommenc'd with redoubled exertion; nor lay I inactive on my side, but encountring him with all the impetuosity of motion but encountering him with all the impetuosity of motion I was mistress of, the downy cloathing of our meeting mounts, was now of real use to break the violence of the tilt; and soon, too soon indeed! the high-wrought agitation, the sweet urgency of this to-and-fro friction, rais'd the titilation on me to it's height, so that finding myself on the point of going, and loath to leave the tender partner of my joys behind me, I employ'd all the forwarding motions and arts my experience suggested to me, to promote his keeping me company to our journey's end. I not only then tightened the pleasure-girth round my restless inmate by a secret spring of suction and compression, that obeys the will in those parts, but stole my hand softly to that store-bag of nature's prime sweets, which is so pleasingly attach'd to its conduit-pipe, from which we receive them; there feeling, and most gently indeed squeezing those tender globular reservoirs, the magic touch took instant effect, quicken'd, and brought on upon the spur, the symptoms of that sweet agony, the melting moment of dissolution, when pleasure dies by pleasure, and the mysterious engine of it overcomes the titillation it has rais'd in those parts, by plying them with the stream of a warm liquid, that is itself the highest of all titillations, and which they thirstily express, and draw in like the hot-natured leach, who, to cool itself, tenaciously attracts all the moisture within its sphere of exsuction: chiming then to me, with exquisite consent, as I melted away, his oily balsamic injection mixing deliciously with the sluices in flow from me, sheath'd and blunted all the stings of pleasure, whilst it flung us into an extacy, that extended us fainting, breathless, entranced. Thus we lay, whilst a voluptuous languor possest, and still maintain'd us motionless, and fast lock'd in one another's arms. Alas! that these delights should be no longer-liv'd! for now the point of pleasure, unedg'd by enjoyment, and all the brisk sensations flatten'd upon us, resign'd us up to the cool cares of insipid life. Disingaging myself then from his embrace, I made him sensible of the reasons there were for his present leaving me; on which, tho' reluctantly, he put on his cloaths with as little expedition, however, as he could help, wantonly interrupting himself between whiles, with kisses, touches and embraces, I could not refuse myself too; yet he happily return'd to his master before he was miss'd; but at taking leave, I forc'd him (for he had sentiments enough to refuse it) to receive money enough to buy a silver watch, that great article of subaltern finery, which he at length accepted of as a remembrance he was carefully to preserve of my affections.<break time="100ms" />And here, Madam, I ought perhaps to make you an apology for this minute detail of things, that dwelt so strongly upon my memory after so deep an impression. But besides that this intrigue bred one great revolution in my life, which historical truth requires I should not sink upon you; may I not presume that so exalted a pleasure ought not to be ungratefully forgotten, or suppress'd by me, because I found it in a character in low life, where, by the bye, it is oftner met with, purer, and more unsophisticate, than amongst the false ridiculous refinements with which the great suffer themselves to be so grosly cheated by their pride: the great! than whom, there exist few amongst those they call the vulgar, who are more ignorant of, or who cultivate less, the art of living than they do: they, I say, who for ever mistake things the most foreign to the nature of pleasure itself, whose capital favourite object is enjoyment of beauty, wherever that rare invaluable gift is found, without distinction of birth or station.<break time="100ms" />As love never had, so now revenge had no longer any share in my commerce with this handsome youth. The sole pleasures of enjoyment were now the link I held to him by: for though nature had done such great matters for him in his outward form, and especially in that superb piece of furniture she had so liberally enrich'd him with; though he was thus qualify'd to give the senses their richest feast, still there was something more wanting to create in me, and constitute the passion of love. Yet Will had very good qualities too, gentle, tractable, and, above all grateful: silentious, even to a fault; he spoke at any time very little, but made it up emphatically with action; and to do him justice, he never gave me the least reason to complain either of any tendency to encroach upon me for the liberties I allow'd him, or of his indiscretion in blabing them. There is then a fatality in love, or have loved him I must; for he was really a treasure, a bit for the bonne bouche of a duchess: and, to say the truth, my liking for him was so extreme, that it was distinguishing very nicely to deny that I lov'd him.
    </voice>
</speak>
