<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />My happiness, however, with him did not last long, but found an end from my own imprudent neglect. After having taken even superfluous precautions against a discovery, our success in repeated meetings embolden'd me to omit the barely necessary ones.——About a month after our first intercourse, one fatal morning (the season Mr. H.——— rarely, or never visited me in) I was in my closet, where my toilette stood, in nothing but my shift, a bed-gown and under-petty-coat. Will was with me, and both ever too well dispos'd to baulk an opportunity: for my part, a warm whim, a wanton toy had just taken me, and I had challeng'd my man to execute it on the spot, who hesitated not to comply with my humour; I was sat in the arm-chair, my shift and petty-coat up, my thighs wide spread, and mounted over the arms of the chair, presenting the fairest mark to Will's drawn weapon, which he stood in act to plunge into me, when, having neglected to secure the chamber door, and that of the closet standing a-jar, Mr. H——— stole in upon us, before either of us was aware, and saw us precisely in these convicting attitudes.<break time="100ms" />I gave a great scream, and drop'd my petty-coat: the thunderstruck lad stood trembling and pale, waiting his sentence of death. Mr. H——— look'd sometimes at one, sometimes at the other, with a mixture of indignation and scorn, and, without saying a word, spun upon his heel, and went out.<break time="100ms" />As confus'd as I was, I heard him very distinctly turn the key, and lock the chamber-door upon us, so that there was no escape but through the dining-room, where he himself was walking about with distemper'd strides, stamping in a great chafe, and doubtless debating what he should do with us.<break time="100ms" />In the mean time poor William was frighten'd out of his senses, and as much need as I had of spirits to support myself, I was oblig'd to employ them all to keep his a little up: The misfortune I had now brought upon him, endear'd him the more to me, and I could have joyfully suffer'd any punishment he had not shar'd in. I water'd plentifully with my tears the face of the frighten'd youth, who sat, not having strength to stand, as cold and as lifeless as a statue.<break time="100ms" />Presently Mr. H——— comes in to us again, and made us go before him into the dining-room, trembling and dreading the issue: Mr. H——— sat down on a chair, whilst we stood like criminals under examination; and, beginning with me, ask'd me with an even firm tone of voice, neither soft nor severe, but cruelly indifferent, what I could say for myself for having abus'd him in so unworthy a manner, with his own servant too, and how he had deserv'd this of me?<break time="100ms" />Without adding to the guilt of my infidelity that of an audacious defence of it, in the old style of a common kept Miss, my answer was modest, and often interrupted by my tears, in substance as follows: "That I never had a single thought of wronging him (which was true) till I had seen him taking the last liberties with my servant-wench (here he colour'd prodigiously) and that my resentment at that which I was over-aw'd from giving vent to by complaints, or explanations with him, had driven me to a course that I did not pretend to justify; but that as to the young man, he was entirely faultless, for that in the view of making him the instrument of my revenge, I had down-right seduced him to what he had done, and therefore hop'd, whatever he determin'd about me, he would distinguish between the guilty and the innocent; and that, for the rest, I was entirely at his mercy."<break time="100ms" />Mr. H———, on hearing what I said, hung his head a little; but instantly recovering himself, he said to me, as near as I can retain, to the following purpose:<break time="100ms" />"Madam, I owe shame to myself, and confess you have fairly turn'd the tables upon me.————It is not with one of your cast of breeding and sentiments that I should enter into a discussion of the very great difference of the provocations: be it sufficient that I allow you so much reason on your side, as to have changed my resolutions, in consideration of what you reproach me with: and I own too, that your clearing that rascal there is fair and honest in you: renew with you I cannot; the affront is too gross: I give you a week's warning, to go out of these lodgings: whatever I have given you, remains to you; and as I never intend to see you more, the landlord will pay you fifty pieces on my account, with which, and every debt paid, I hope you will own I do not leave you in a worse condition than what I took you up in, or than you deserve of me.——Blame yourself only that it is no better."<break time="100ms" />Then, without giving me time to reply, he addrest himself to the young fellow.<break time="100ms" />"For you, spark, I shall for your father's sake take care of you: the town is no place for such an easy fool as thou art; and to-morrow you shall set out under the charge of one of my men, well recommended, in my name, to your father, not to let you return and be spoilt here."<break time="100ms" />At these words he went out, after my vainly attempting to stop him, by throwing myself at his feet: he took me off, though he seem'd greatly mov'd too, and took Will away with him, who, I dare swear, thought himself very cheaply off.<break time="100ms" />I was now once more a-drift, and left upon my own hands, by a gentleman whom I certainly did not deserve. And all the letters, arts, friends entreaties that I employ'd within the week of grace in my lodging, could never win on him so much as to see me again. He had irrevocably pronounc'd my doom, and submission to it was my only part. Soon after he married a lady of birth and fortune, to whom I have heard he prov'd an irreproachable husband.<break time="100ms" />As for poor Will, he was immediately sent down to the country, to his father, who was an easy farmer, where he was not four months before an inn-keeper's buxom young widow, with a very good stock both in money and trade, fancy'd, and perhaps pre-acquainted with his secret excellencies, marry'd him; and I am sure there was at least one good foundation for their living happily together.<break time="100ms" />Though I should have been charm'd to see him before he went, such measures were taken, by Mr. H———'s orders, that it was impossible; otherwise I should certainly have endeavour'd to detain him in town, and would have spar'd neither offers nor expence to have procur'd myself the satisfaction of keeping him with me, he had such powerful holds upon my inclinations as were not easily to be shaken off or replac'd; as to my heart, it was quite out of the question: glad however I was from my soul that nothing worse, and, as things turn'd out, probably nothing better could have happen'd to him.<break time="100ms" />As to Mr. H———, though views of conveniency made me at first exert myself to regain his affection, I was giddy and thoughtless enough to be much easier reconcil'd to my failure than I ought to have been; but as I never had lov'd him, and his leaving me gave me a sort of liberty that I had often long'd for, I was soon comforted; and flattering myself that the stock of youth and beauty I was going into trade with could hardly fail of procuring me a maintenance, I saw myself under a necessity of trying my fortune with them, rather with pleasure and gayety, than with the least idea of despondence.
    </voice>
</speak>
