<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />In the mean time, several of my acquaintance among the sister hood, who had soon got wind of my misfortune, flock'd to insult me with their malicious consolations: most of them had long envied me the affluence and splendour I had been maintain'd in; and though there was scarce one of them that did not at least deserve to be in my case, and would probably sooner or later come to it, it was equally easy to remark, even in their affected pity, their secret pleasure at seeing me thus disgrac'd and discarded, and their secret grief that it was still no worse with me. Unaccountable malice of the human heart! and which is not confin'd to the class of life they were of.<break time="100ms" />But as the time approach'd for me to come to some resolution how to dispose of myself, and I was considering round where to shift my quarters to, Mrs. Cole, a middle-aged discret sort of woman, who had been brought into my acquaintance by one of the misses that visited me, upon learning my situation, came to offer her cordial advice and service to me; and as I had always taken to her more than to any of my female acquaintance, I listen'd the easier to her proposals; and as it happen'd, I could not have put myself into worse, or into better hands in all London; into worse, because keeping a house of conveniency, there were no lengths in lewdness she would not advise me to go in compliance with her customers, no schemes of pleasure, or even unbounded debauchery, she did not take even a delight in promoting: into better, because no body having had more experience of the wicked part of the town than she had, was fitter to advise and guard one against the worst dangers of our profession; and what was rare to be met with in those of her's, she contented herself with a moderate living profit upon her industry and good offices, and had nothing of their greedy rapacious turn. She was really too a gentlewoman born and bred, but through a train of accidents reduc'd to this course, which she pursued: partly through mecessity, partly through choice, as never woman delighted more in encouraging a brisk circulation of trade, for the sake of the trade itself, or better understood all the mysteries and refinements of it, than she did; so that she was consummately at the top of her profession, and dealt only with customers of distinction: to answer the demands of whom she kept a competent number of her daughters in constant recruit: so she call'd those whom their youth and personal charms recommended to her adoption and management: several of whom, by her means, and through her tuition and instructions, succeeded very well in the world.<break time="100ms" />This useful gentlewoman, upon whose protection I now threw myself, having her reasons of state, respecting Mr. H———, for not appearing too much in the thing herself, sent a friend of her's, on the day appointed for my removal, to conduct me to my new lodgings, at a brush-maker's in R——— street, Covent-Garden, the very next door to her own house, where she had no conveniences to lodge me herself; lodgings, that by having been for several successions tenanted by ladies of pleasure, the landlord of them was familiariz'd to their ways; and provided, the rent was duly paid, every thing else was as easy and commodious as one could desire.<break time="100ms" />The fifty guineas promis'd me by Mr. H———, at his parting with me, having been duly paid me, all my cloaths and moveables chested up, which were at least of two hundred pounds value, I had them convey'd into a coach, where I soon follow'd them, after taking a civil leave of the landlord and his family, with whom I had never liv'd in a degree of familiarity enough to regret the removal but still, the very circumstance of its being a removal drew tears from me. I left too a letter of thanks for Mr. H———, from whom I concluded myself, as I really was, irretrievably separated.<break time="100ms" />My maid I had discharged the day before, not only because I had her of Mr. H———, but that I suspected her of having some how or other been the occasion of his discovering me, in revenge perhaps for my not having trusted her in it.<break time="100ms" />We soon got to my lodgings, which, though not so handsomely furnish'd, nor so showy as those I left, were to the full as convenient, and at half price, though on the first floor. My trunks were safely landed, and stow'd in my apartments, where my neighbour, and now governante, Mrs. Cole, was ready with my landlord to receive me, to whom she took care to set me out in the most favourable light, that of one from whom there was the clearest reason to expect the regular payment of his rent: all the cardinal virtues attributed to me would not have had half the weight of that recommendation alone.<break time="100ms" />I was now settled in lodgings of my own, abandon'd to my own conduct, and turn'd loose upon the town, to sink or swim, as I could manage with the current of it: and what were the consequences, together with the number of adventures which befell me in the exercise of my new profession, will compose the matter of another letter; for, surely, it is high time to put a period to this.<break time="100ms" />⁠I am,<break time="100ms" />⁠MADAM,<break time="100ms" />⁠Yours, andc. andc. andc.<break time="100ms" />⁠. . . . . . .<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
