<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Letter the First
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />And why should I here suppress the delight I receiv'd from this amiable creature, in remarking each artless look, each motion of pure undissembled nature, betray'd by his wanton eyes, or shewing transparently the glow and suffusion of blood through his fresh, clear skin, whilst even his sturdy, rustic pressures, wanted not their peculiar charm? Oh! but say you, this was a young fellow in too low a rank of life to deserve so great a display. May be so! but was my condition, strictly consider'd, one jot more exalted? or had I really been much above him, did not his capacity of giving such exquisite pleasure sufficiently raise and enoble him, to me at least? Let who would, for me, cherish, respect, and reward the painter's, the statuary's, the musician's arts, in proportion to the delight taken in them; but at my age, and with my taste for pleasure, a taste strongly constitutional to me; the talent of pleasing, with which nature has endow'd a handsome person, form'd to me the greatest of all merits; compared to which the vulgar prejudices in favour of titles, dignities, honours, and the like, held a very low rank indeed! nor perhaps would the beauties of the body be so much affected to be held cheap, were they in their nature to be bought and deliver'd;. but for me, whose natural philosophy all resided in the favourite center of sense, and who was rul'd by its powerful instinct, in taking pleasure by its right handle, I could scarce have made a choice more to my purpose.<break time="100ms" />Mr. H———'s loftier qualifications of birth, fortune, and sense, laid me under a sort of subjection and constraint, that were far from making harmony in the concert of love; nor had he perhaps thought me worth softening that superiority to; but with this lad I was more on that level which love delights in.<break time="100ms" />We may say what we please, but those we can be the easiest and freest with, are ever those we like, not to say love the best.<break time="100ms" />With this strippling, all whose art of love was the action of it, I could without check of awe or restraint, give a loose to joy, and execute every scheme of dalliance my fond fancy might put me on, in which he was, in every sense, a most exquisite companion. And now my great pleasure lay in humouring all the petulances, all the wanton frolic of a raw novice just flesh'd, and keen on the burning scent of his game, but unbroken to the sport: and, to carry on the figure, who could better thread the wood than he, or stand fairer for the heart of the hunt?<break time="100ms" />He advanc'd then to my bedside, and whilst he faulter'd out his message, I could observe his colour rise, and his eyes lighten with joy, in seeing me in a situation as favourable to his loosest wishes, as if he had bespoke the play.<break time="100ms" />I, smil'd, and put out my hand towards him, which he kneel'd down to, (a politeness taught him by love alone, that great master of it) and greedily kiss'd. After exchanging a few confus'd questions and answers, I ask'd him if he would come to bed to me for the little time I could venture to detain him. This was just asking a person dying with hunger, to feast upon the dish on earth the most to his palate. Accordingly, without further reflection, his cloaths were off in an instant; when blushing still more at his new liberty, he got under the bed-cloaths I held up to receive him, and was now in bed with a woman for the first time in his life.<break time="100ms" />Here began the usual tender preliminaries, as delicious perhaps as the crowning act of enjoyment itself; which they often beget an impatience of, that makes pleasure destructive of itself, by hurrying on the final period, and closing that scene of bliss, in which the actors are generally too well pleas'd with their parts, not to wish them an eternity of duration.<break time="100ms" />When we had sufficiently graduated our advances towards the main point, by toying, kissing, clipping, feeling my breasts, now round and plump, feeling that part of me I might call a furnace-mouth, from the prodigious intense heat his fiery touches had rekindled there; my young sportsman, embolden'd by every freedom he could wish, wantonly takes my hand, and carries it to that enormous machine of his, that stood with a stiffness! a hardness! an upward bent of erection! and which, together with its bottom dependence, the inestimable bulse of lady's jewels, form'd a grand show out of goods indeed! Then its dimensions, mocking either grasp or span, almost renew'd my terrors. I could not conceive how, or by what means, I could take, or put such a bulk out of sight. I stroak'd it gently, on which the mutinous rogue seemed to swell, and gather a new degree of fierceness and insolence; so that finding it grew not to be trifl'd with any longer, I prepar'd for rubbers in good earnest.
    </voice>
</speak>
