<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />By this time I was so affected by this inward revolution of sentiments, so soften'd by this sight, that now, betray'd into a sudden transition from extreme fears to extreme desires, I found these last so strong upon me, the heat of the weather too perhaps conspiring to exalt their rage, that nature almost fainted under them: not that I so much as knew precisely what was wanting to me; my only thought was, that so sweet a creature as this youth seem'd to me, could only make me happy; but then the little likelihood there was of compassing an acquaintance with him, or perhaps of ever seeing him again, dash'd my desires, and turn'd them into torments. I was still gazing with all the powers of my sight on this bewitching object, when, in an instant, down he went. I had heard of such things as a cramp seizing on even the best swimmers, and occasioning their being drown'd; and imagining this so sudden eclipse to be owing to it: the inconceivable fondness this unknown had given birth to, distracted me with the most killing terrors, insomuch, that my concern giving me wings, I flew to the door, open'd it, ran down to the banks of the canal, guided thither by the madness of my fears for him, and the intense desire of being an instrument to save him, though I was ignorant how, or by what means to effect it; but was it for fears, and a passion so sudden as mine to reason? All this took up scarce the space of a few moments. I had then just life enough to reach the green borders of the water-piece, where wildly looking round for the young man, and missing him still, my fright and concern sunk me down in a deep swoon, which must have lasted me some time; for I did not come to myself, till I was rouz'd out of it by a sense of pain that pierced me to the vitals, and awak'd me to the most surpising circumstance of finding myself not only in the arms of this very same young gentleman I had been so solicitous to save; but taken at such an advantage in my unresisting condition, that he had actually completed his entrance into my body so far, that weakened as I was by all the preceding conflicts of mind I had suffer'd, and struck dumb by the violence of my surprize, I had neither the power to cry out, nor the strength to disengage myself from his strenuous embraces, before, urging his point, he had forced his way into me, and completely triumph'd over my virginity, as he might now as well see by the streams of blood that follow'd his drawing out, as he had felt by the difficulties he had met with in consummating his penetration. But the sight of the blood, and the sense of my condition, had (as he told me afterwards) since the ungovernable rage of his passion was somewhat appeas'd, now wrought so far on him, that at all risques, even of the worst consequences, he could not find in his heart to leave me, and make off, which he might easily have done. I still lay all discompos'd in bleeding ruin, palpitating, speechless, unable to get off, and frighten'd, and fluttering like a poor wounded partrige, and ready to faint away again at the sense of what had befallen me. The young gentleman was by me, kneeling, kissing my hand, and with tears in his eyes, beseeching me to forgive him, and offering all the reparation in his power———It is certain, that could I, at the instant of regaining my senses, have call'd out, or taken the bloodiest revenge, I would not have stuck at it: the violation was attended too with such aggravating circumstances! though he was ignorant of them, since it was to my concern for the preservation of his life, that I owed my ruin.
    </voice>
</speak>
