<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />As soon as she was gone, I told the maid I would go up and lie down on our lodger's bed, mine not being made, with a charge to her at the same time not to disturb me, as it was only rest I wanted. This injunction probably proved of eminent service to me. As soon as I was got into the bed-chamber, I unlaced my stays, and threw myself on the out-side of the bed cloaths in all the loosest undress. Here I gave myself up to the old insipid privy shifts of self-viewing, self-touching, self-enjoying, in fine to all the means of self-knowledge I could devise, in search of the pleasure that fled before me, and tantalized me with that unknown something that was out of my reach; thus all only served to enflame myself, and to provoke violently my desires, whilst the one thing needful to their satisfaction was not at hand, and I could have bit my fingers for representing it so ill. After then wearying and fatiguing myself with grasping of shadows, whilst that more sensible part of me disdain'd to content itself with less than realities, the strong yearnings, the urgent struggles of nature towards the melting relief, and the extreme self-agitations I had us'd to come at it, had wearied and thrown me into a kind of unquiet sleep, for if I toss'd and threw about my limbs in proportion to the distraction of my dreams, as I had reason to believe I did, a by-stander could not have help'd seeing all for love: and one there was, it seems; for waking out of my very short slumber, I found my hand lock'd in that of a young man, who was kneeling at my bed-side, and begging my pardon for his boldness, but that being son to the lady to whom this bed-chamber, he knew, belong'd, he had slipp'd by the servant of the shop, as he suppos'd, unperceiv'd; when finding me a sleep, his first ideas were to withdraw; but that he had been fix'd and detain'd there by a power he could better account for, than resist. What shall I say? my emotions, of fear and surprize were instantly subdu'd by those of the pleasure I bespoke in great presence of mind from the turn this adventure might take: he seem'd to me no other than a pitying angel, dropt out of the clouds; for he was young and perfectly handsome, which was more than even I had ask'd for; Man, in general, being all that my utmost desires had pointed at. I thought then I could not put too much encouragement into my eyes and voice; I regretted no leading advances: no matter for his after-opinion of my forwardness, so it might bring him to the point of answering my pressing demands of present ease; it was not now with his thoughts, but his actions, that my business immediately lay. I rais'd then my head, and told him in a soft tone that tended to prescribe the same key to him, that his mama was gone out, and would not return till late at night: which I thought no bad hint; but, as it prov'd, I had nothing of a novice to deal with: the impressions I had made on him, from the discoveries I had betray'd of my person in the disorder'd motions of it, during his view of me asleep, had, as he afterwards told me, so fix'd, and charmingly prepar'd him, that, had I known his dispositions, I had more to hope for from his violence, than to fear from his respect; and even less than the extreme tenderness which I threw into my voice, and eyes, would have serv'd to encourage him to make the most of the opportunity. Finding then that his kisses imprinted on my hand were taken as tamely as he could wish, he rose to my lips, and glewing his to them, made me so faint with overcoming joy, and pleasure, that I fell back, and he with me, in course, on the bed, upon which I had, by insensibly shifting from the side to near the middle, invitingly made room for him: He is now lain down by me, and the minutes being too precious to consume in untimely ceremony, or dalliance, my youth proceeds immediately to those extremities, which all my looks, flushings, and palpitations had assur'd him he might attempt without the fear of repulse: those rogues, the men, read us admirably on these occasions! I lay then at length panting for the imminent attack, with wishes far beyond my fears, and for which it was scarce possible for a girl barely thirteen, but tall and well grown, to have better dispositions. He threw up my petty coat and shift, whilst my thighs were by an instinct of nature unfolded to their best; and my desires had so thoroughly destroy'd all modesty in me, that even their being now naked, and all laid open to him, was part of the prelude that pleasure deepen'd my blushes at, more than shame; but when his hand, and touches, naturally attracted to their center, made me feel all their wantonness, and warmth in, and round it, oh! how immensely different a sense of things did I perceive there, than when under my own insipid handling and now his waistcoat was unbutton'd, and the confinement of the breeches burst through, when out starting to view the amazing, pleasing object of all my wishes, all my dreams, all my love, the king-member indeed I gaz'd at, I devour'd it, length and breadth with my eyes intently directed to it, till his getting upon me, and placing it between my thighs, took from me the enjoyment of its sight, to give me a far more grateful one, in its touch, in that part, where its touch is so exquisitely affecting: applying it then to the minute opening, for such at that age it certainly was, I met with too much good will, I felt with too great a rapture of pleasure the first insertion of it, to heed much the pain that follow'd: I thought nothing too dear to pay for this the richest treat of the senses; so that, split up, torn, bleeding, mangled, I was still superiourly pleas'd, and hugg'd the author of all this delicious ruin: but when soon after he made his second attack, sore, and red-raw as everything was, the smart was soon put away by the sovereign cordial; all my soft complainings were silenc'd, and the pain melting fast away into pleasure, I abandon'd myself over to all its transports, and gave it the full possession of my whole body and soul; for now all thought was at an end with me; I liv'd but in what I felt only: and who could describe those feelings, those agitations, yet exalted by the charm of their novelty, and surprize? when that part of me which had so long hunger'd and thirsted for the dear morsel that now so delightfully cramm'd it, forc'd all my vital sensations to fix their home there, during the stay of my new and belov'd guest; who too soon paid me for his hearty welcome, in a dissolvent, richer far than that I have heard of some queen treating her paramour with, in liquefy'd pearl, and ravishingly pour'd into me, where now myself too much melted to give it a dry reception, I hail'd it with the warmest confluence of sweets on my side, amidst all those extatic raptures, not unfamiliar I presume to this good company. Thus however, I arriv'd at the very top of all my wishes, by an accident unexpected indeed, but not so wonderful: for this young gentleman was just arriv'd in town from college, and came familiarly to his mother at her apartment, where he had once before been, though, by mere chance, I had not seen him: so that we knew one another by hear-say only, and finding me stretch'd on his mother's bed, he readily concluded, from her description, who it was———, the rest you know. This affair had however no ruinous consequences; the young gentleman escaping then, and many more times, undiscover'd; but the warmth of my constitution that made the pleasures of love a kind of necessary of life to me, having betray'd me into indiscretions fatal to my private fortune, I fell at length to the publick, which it is probable I might have met with the worst of ruin, if my better fate had not thrown me into this safe and agreeable refuge.
    </voice>
</speak>
