<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Letter the Second
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />Memoirs<break time="100ms" />of a<break time="100ms" />Woman of Pleasure.<break time="100ms" />⁠Madam,<break time="100ms" />f I have delay'd the sequel of my history, it has been purely to afford myself a little breathing time, not without some hopes that, instead of pressing me to a continuation, you would have acquitted me of the task of pursuing a confession, in the course of which, my self-esteem has so many wounds to sustain.<break time="100ms" />I imagined indeed, that you would have been cloy'd and tired with the uniformity of adventures and expressions, inseparable from a subject of this sort, whose bottom or ground-work being, in the nature of things, eternally one and the same, whatever variety of forms and modes, the situations are susceptible of, there is no escaping a repetition of near the same images, the same figures, the same expressions, with this further inconvenience added to the disgust it creates, that the words joys, ardours, transports, extasies, and the rest of those pathetic terms so congenial to, so received in the practise of pleasure, flatten, and lose much of their due spirit and energy, by the frequency they indispensibly recur with, in a narrative of which that practise professedly composes the whole basis: I must therefore trust to the candour of your judgment for your allowing for the disadvantage I am necessarily under, in that respect, and to your imagination and sensibility the pleasing task of repairing it, by their supplements, where my descriptions flag or fail: the one will readily place the pictures I present before your eyes, the other give life to the colours where they are dull, or worn with too frequent handling.<break time="100ms" />What you say besides, by way of encouragement concerning the extreme difficulty of continuing so long in one strain, in a mean temper'd with taste, between the revoltingness of gross, rank, and vulgar expressions, and the ridicule of mincing metaphors and affected circumlocutions, is so sensible, as well as good-natur'd, that you greatly justify me to myself for my compliance with a curiosity that is to be satisfied so extremely at my expence.<break time="100ms" />Resuming now where I broke off in my last; I am, in my way, to remark to you, that it was late in the evening before I arriv'd at my new lodgings, and Mrs. Cole, after helping me to range, and secure my things, spent the whole evening with me in my apartment, where we supped together, in giving me the best advice and instruction with regard to this new stage of my profession I was now to enter upon, and passing thus from a private devotee to pleasure, into a public one, to become a more general good, with all the advantages requisite to put my person out to use, either for interest, or pleasure, or both. But then she observ'd, as I was a kind of new face upon the town, that it was an establish'd rule, and mystery of trade, for me to pass for a maid, and dispose of myself as such on the first good occasion, without prejudice however, to such diversions as I might have a mind to in the interim, for that nobody could be a greater enemy than she was to the losing of time. That she would, in the mean time, do her best to find out a proper person, and would undertake to manage this nice point for me, if I would accept of her aid and advice to such good purpose, that in the loss of a fictitious maiden-head, I should reap all the advantages of a native one.<break time="100ms" />As a great delicacy of sentiments did not extremely belong to my character at that time, I confess, against myself, that I perhaps too readily closed with a proposal which my candor and ingenuity gave me some repugnance to; but not enough to contradict the intention of one to whom I had now throughly abandon'd the direction of all my steps. For Mrs. Cole had, I do not know how, unless by one of those unaccountable invincible simpathies, that nevertheless form the strongest links, especially of female friendship, won and got intire possession of me. On her side, she pretended that a strict resemblance, she fancied she saw in me to an only daughter, whom she had lost at my age, was the first motive of her taking to me so affectionately as she did: it might be so: there exist as slender motives of attachments, that gathering force from habit, and liking, have proved often more solid, and durable, than those founded on much stronger reasons: but this I know, that tho' I had had no other acquaintance with her, than seeing her at my lodgings, when I liv'd with Mr. H———, where she had made errands to sell me some millinary ware, she had by degrees insinuated herself so far into my confidence, that I threw my self blindly into her hands, and came at length to regard, love, and obey her implicitly: and to do her justice, I never experienc'd at her hands other than a sincerity of tenderness, and care for my interest, hardly heard of in those of her profession. We parted that night, after having settled a perfect unreserv'd agreement; and the next morning Mrs. Cole came, and took me with her to her house, for the first time.<break time="100ms" />Here, at the first sight of things, I found everything breath an air of decency, modesty, and order.<break time="100ms" />In the outer-parlour, or rather shop, sat three young women, very demurely employ'd on millinary work, which was the cover of a traffic in more precious commodities: but three beautifuller creatures could hardly be seen: two of them were extremely fair, the eldest not above nineteen, and the third, much about that age, was a piquant brunette, whose black sparkling eyes, and perfect harmony of features, and shapes, left her nothing to envy in her fairer companions: Their dress too, had the more design in it, the less it appeared to have, being in a taste of uniform correct neatness, and elegant simplicity. These were the girls that composed the small, and domestic flock, which my governess train'd up with surprising order and management, considering the giddy, wildness of young girls once got upon the loose. But then she never continued any in her house, whom after a due noviciate, she found untractable, or unwilling to comply with the rules of it. Thus had she insensibly formed a little family of love, in which the members found so sensibly their account in a rare alliance of pleasure with interest, and of a necessary outward decency, with unbounded secret liberty, that Mrs. Cole, who had pick'd them as much for their temper as their beauty, govern'd them with ease to herself, and them too.<break time="100ms" />To these pupils then of hers, whom she had prepar'd, she presented me as a new boarder, and one that was to be immediately admitted to all the intimacies of the house; upon which these charming girls gave me all the marks of a welcome reception, and indeed of being perfectly pleas'd with my figure, that I could possibly expect from any of my own sex; but they had been effectually brought to sacrifice all jealousy, or competition of charms, to a common interest; and consider'd me as a partner, that was bringing no despicable stock of goods into the trade of the house: they gather'd round me, view'd me on all sides; and, as my admission into this joyous troop made a little holiday, the shew of work was laid aside, and Mrs. Cole giving me up, with special recommendation, to their caresses and entertainment, went about her ordinary business of the house.
    </voice>
</speak>
