<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />According to my practical maxims of life, I ought to boast of my birth, since I owe it to pure love, without marriage; but this I know, it was scarce possible to inherit a stronger propensity to that cause of my being, than I did: I was the rare production of the first essay of a journeyman cabinet-maker, on his master's maid; the consequence of which was a big-belly, and the loss of her place. He was not in circumstances to do much for her; and yet, after all this blemish, she found means, after she had dropt her burthen, and disposed of me at a poor relation's in the country, to repair it by marrying a pastry cook here in London, in thriving business; on whom she soon, under favour of the compleat ascendant he had given her over him, passed me for a child she had by her first husband. I had, on that footing been taken home, and was not six years old when this father-in-law died, and left my mother in tolerable circumstances, and without any children by him. As to my natural father, he had betaken himself to the sea; where, when the truth of things came out, I was told that he died, not immensely rich you may think, since he was no more than a common sailor. As I grew up, under the eye of my mother, who kept on the business, I could not but see in her severe watchfulness, the marks of a slip, which she did not care should be hereditary; but we no more choose our passions than our features or complexion, and the bent of mine was so strong to the forbidden pleasure, that it got the better, at length, of all her care and precaution. I was scarce twelve years old, before that part of me which she wanted so much to keep out of harms way, made me feel its impatience to be taken notice of, and come into play: already had it put forth the signs of forwardness in the sprout of a soft down over it, which had often flatter'd, and I might also say, grown under my constant touch, and visitation: so pleas'd was I with what I took to be a kind of title to womanhood, that state I pined to be entered off, for the pleasures I conceiv'd where annex'd to it: and now the growing importance of that part to me, and the new sensations in it, demolish'd at once all my girlish play-things and amusements: nature now pointed me strongly<break time="100ms" />to more solid diversions, while all the stings of desire settled so fiercely in that little centre of them, that I could not mistake the spot I wanted a play-fellow in. I now shun'd all company in which there was no hopes of coming at the object of my longings, and used to shut my self up, to indulge in solitude some tender meditation on the pleasures, I strongly perceiv'd the overture of, in feeling and examining what nature assur'd me must be the chosen avenue, the gates for the unknown bliss to enter at, that I panted after.<break time="100ms" />But these meditations only encreased my disorder, and blew the fire that consum'd me. It was yet worse when yeilding at length to the insupportable irritations of the little fairy charm that tormented me; I searched it with my fingers, teazing it to no end. Sometimes, in the furious excitations of desire, I threw my self on my bed, spread my thighs abroad, and lay as it were expecting the long'd for relief, till finding my illusion, I shut and squeez'd them together again, burning and fretting. In short, this dev'lish thing, with its impetuous girds and itching fires, led me such a life, that I could neither, night or day, be at peace with it or my self. In time, however, I thought I had gained a prodigious prize, when figuring to myself, that my fingers were something of the shape of what I pined for, I worked my way in for one of them with great agitation and delight; yet not without pain too did I deflour myself as far as it could reach; proceeding with such a fury of passion, in this solitary and last shift of pleasure, as extended me at length breathless on the bed, in an amorous melting trance.<break time="100ms" />But frequency of use dulling the sensation, I soon began to perceive that this finger-work was but a paultry shallow expedient, that went but a little way to relieve me, and rather rais'd more flame than its dry insignificant titilation could rightly appease.<break time="100ms" />Man alone, I almost instinctively knew, as well as by what I had industiously picked up at weddings and christenings, was possess'd of the only very remedy that could reduce this rebellious disorder; but watch'd, and overlook'd as I was, how to come at it, was the point, and that to all appearance, an invincible one: not that I did not rack my brains and invention how at once to elude my mother's vigilance, and procure myself the satisfaction of my impetuous curiosity, and longings for this mighty and untasted pleasure. At length, however, a singular chance did at once the work of a long course of alertness. One day that we had dined at an acquaintance's over the way, together with a gentlewoman lodger that occupied the first floor of our house, there started an indispensible necessity for my mother's going down to Greenwich to accompany her: the party was settled, when I do not know what genius wispered me to plead a head-ach that I certainly had not, against my being included in a jaunt that I had not the least relish for: the pretext however passed, and my mother, with much reluctance, prevailed with herself to go without me; but took particular care to see me safe home, where she consign'd me into the hands of an old trusty maid-servant who served in the shop, for we had not a male creature in the house.
    </voice>
</speak>
