<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Neither my extraction, nor the most critical adventure of my life, are sublime enough to impeach me of any vanity in the advancement of the proposal you have approved of. My father and mother were, and for ought I know, are still, farmers in the country, not above forty miles from town. Their barbarity to me, in favour of a son, on whom only they vouchsafed to bestow their tenderness, had a thousand times determined me to fly their house, and throw myself on the wide world; but at length an accident forced me on this desperate step, at the age of fifteen. I had broken a China-bowl, the pride and idol of both their hearts, and as an unmerciful beating was the least I had to depend on at their hands, in the silliness and timidity of those tender years, I left the house, and at all adventures took the road to London. How my loss was resented I do not know, for till this instant I have not heard a syllable about them. My whole stock was two broad pieces of my god-mother's, a few shillings, silver shoe-buckles, and thimble. Thus equipp'd, with no more cloaths than the ordinary ones I had on my back, and frighten'd at every foot, or noise I heard behind me, I hurried on: and I dare swear, walked a dozen miles before I stopp'd thro' mere weariness and fatigue. I sat down on a stile, where I wept bitterly, and yet was still rather under encreased impressions of fear on the account of my escape; which made me dread worse than death, the going back to face my unnatural parents. Refresh'd by this little repose, and relieved by my tears, I was proceeding onward, when I was overtaken by a sturdy country lad, who was going to London, to see what he could do for himself there, and, like me, had given his friends the slip. He could not be above seventeen, was ruddy, well featur'd enough, with uncomb'd flaxen hair, a little flapp'd hat, a kersey-frock, yarn stockings; in short, a perfect plough-boy. I saw him come whistling behind me, with a bundle tied to the end of a stick: his travelling equipage. We walk'd by one another for some time without speaking, at length we join'd company, and agreed to keep together till we got to our journey's end. What his designs or ideas were I know not: the innocence of mine I can solemnly protest. As night drew on, it became us to look out for some inn, or shelter; to which perplexity another was added, and that was, what we should say for ourselves, if we were question'd: after some puzzle, the young fellow started a proposal, which I thought the finest that could be; and what was that? why that we should pass for husband and wife: I never once dream'd of consequences. We came presently, after having agreed on this notable expedient, to one of those hedge-accommodations for foot-passengers, at the door of which stood an old crazy beldam, who, seeing us trudge by, invited us to lodge there. Glad of any cover, we went in, and my fellow traveller taking all upon him, call'd for what the house afforded, and we supp'd together as man and wife, which considering our figures, and ages, could not have past on any one, but such as any thing could pass on. But when bed-time came on, we had neither of us the courage to contradict our first account of our selves; and what was extremely pleasant, the young lad seem'd as perplex'd as I was, how to evade the lying together, which was so natural for the state we had pretended to: whilst we were in this quandary, the landlady takes the candle, and lights us to our apartment, through a long yard, at the end of which it stood, separate from the body of the house. Thus we suffer'd ourselves to be conducted, without saying a word in opposition to it, and there, in a wretched room, with a bed answerable, we were left to pass the night together, as a thing quite in course. For my part, I was so incredibly innocent, as not even then to think much more harm of going into bed with the young man, than with one of our dairy wenches: nor had he perhaps any other notions than those of innocence, till such a fair occasion put them into his head. Before either of us undressed, however, he put out the candle; and the bitterness of the weather made it a kind of necessity for me to get into bed: slipping then my cloaths off, I crept under the bed-cloaths, where I found the young stripling already nestled, and the touch of his warm flesh rather pleased than alarmed me. I was indeed too much disturb'd with the novelty of my condition, to be able to sleep; but then I had not the least thought of harm: but oh! how powerful are the instincts of nature, and how little is there wanting to set them in action? The young man sliding his arm under my body, drew me gently towards him, as if to keep himself and me warmer; and the heat I felt from joining our breasts, kindled another that I had hitherto never felt, and was even then a stranger to the nature off. Embolden'd, I suppose, by my easiness, he ventur'd to kiss me, and I insensibly return'd it, without knowing the consequence of returning it: for on this encouragement, he slipp'd his hand all down from my breast, to that part of me, where the sense of feeling is so exquisitely critical, as I then experienc'd by its instant taking fire upon the touch, and glowing with a strange tickling heat: there he pleas'd himself and me, by feeling till growing a little too bold, he hurt me, and made me complain: then he took my hand, which he guided, not unwillingly on my side, between the twist of his closed thighs, which were extremely warm; there he lodg'd and press'd it, till raising it by degrees, he made me feel the proud distinction of his sex from mine. I was frighten'd at the novelty, and drew back my hand; yet, press'd and spurr'd on by sensations of a strange pleasure, I could not help asking him, what that was for? He told me, he would show me, if I would let him; and without waiting for my answer, which he prevented by stopping my mouth with kisses I was far from disrelishing, he got a-top of me, and inserting one of his thighs between mine, open'd them so as to make way for himself, and fix'd me to his purpose; whilst I was so much out of my usual sense, so subdu'd by the present power of a new one, that, between fear and desire, I lay utterly passive, till the piercing pain rouz'd, and made me cry out: but it was too late; he was too firm fix'd in the saddle for me to compass flinging him, with all the struggles I could use, some of which only serv'd to further his point, and at length an omnipotent thrust murther'd at once my maidenhead, and almost me: I now lay a bleeding witness of the necessity impos'd on our sex, to gather the first honey off the thorns.<break time="100ms" />But the pleasure rising, as the pain subsided, I was soon reconcil'd to fresh trials, and before morning, nothing on earth could be dearer to me than this rifler of my virgin-sweets. He was every thing to me now. How we agreed to join fortunes, how we came up to town together, where we lived some time, till necessity parted us, and drove me into this course of life, in which I had been long ago batter'd and torn to pieces before I came to this age, as much through my easiness, as through my inclination, had it not been for my finding refuge in this house; these are all circumstances which pass the mark I proposed, so that here my narrative ends.
    </voice>
</speak>
