<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />In the order of our fitting, it was Harriet's turn to go on. Amongst all the beauties of our sex that I had before or have since seen, few indeed were the forms that could dispute excellence with her's; it was not delicate, but delicacy itself incarnate. Such was the simmetry of her small, but exactly fashion'd limbs. Her complexion, fair as it was, appear'd yet more fair, from the effect of two black eyes, the brilliancy of which gave her face more vivacity than belong'd to the colour of it, which was only defended from paleness, by a sweetly pleasing blush in her cheeks, that grew fainter and fainter, till at length it died away insensibly into the overbearing white. Then her mignature features join'd to finish the extreme sweetness of it, which was not belied by that of a temper turn'd to indolence, languor, and the pleasures of love. Press'd to subscribe her contingent, she smil'd, blush'd a little, and thus complied with our desires.<break time="100ms" />My father was neither better nor worse than a miller, near the city of York; but both he and my mother dying whilst I was an infant, I fell under the care of a widow, and childless aunt, house-keeper to my lord N———, at his seat in the county of ———, where she brought me up with all imaginable tenderness. I was not seventeen, as I am not now eighteen, before I had, on the account of my person purely, (for fortune I had notoriously none) several advantageous proposals: but whether nature was slow in making me sensible of her favourite passion, or that I had not seen any of the other sex who had stirr'd up the least emotion or curiosity to be better acquainted with it, I had till that age preserv'd a perfect innocence even of thought: whilst my fears of I did not well know what, made me no more desirous of marrying than of dying. My aunt, good woman, favour'd my timorousness, which she look'd on as a childish affection, that her own experience might probably assure her would wear off in time, and gave my suiters proper answers for me.<break time="100ms" />The family had not been down at this seat for years, so that it was neglected, and committed entirely to my aunt, and two more old domestics, to take care of it.<break time="100ms" />Thus I had the full range of a spacious lonely house, and gardens, situate at above half a mile distance from any other habitation, except perhaps a straggling cottage, or so.<break time="100ms" />Here, in tranquility, and innocence, I grew up, without any memorable accident, till one fatal day I had, as I had often done before, left my aunt fast asleep, and secure for some hours, after dinner: and resorting to a kind of antient summer-house, at some distance from the house, I carry'd my work with me, and sat over a rivulet, which its door and window fac'd upon. Here I fell into a gentle-breathing slumber, which stole up on my senses, as they fainted under the excessive heat of the season, at that hour: a cane-couch, with my work basket for a pillow, were all the conveniences of my short repose; for I was soon awak'd and alarm'd by a flounce, and noise of splashing in the water, I got up to see what was the matter; and what indeed should it be but the son of a neighbouring gentleman, as I afterwards found, (for I had never seen him, before,) who had stray'd that way with his gun, and heated by his sport, and the sultriness of the day, had been tempted by the freshness of the clear stream; so that presently stripping, he jump'd into it on the other side which border'd on a wood, some trees whereof, inclin'd down to the water, form'd a pleasing, shady recess, commodious to undress, and leave his cloaths under.<break time="100ms" />My first emotions, at the sight of this youth naked in the water, were, with all imaginable respect to truth, those of surprize and fear; and in course I should immediately have run out, had not my modesty, fatally for itself, interposed the objection of the door and window being so situated, that it was scarce possible to get out, and make my way along the bank to the house, without his seeing me: which I could not bear the thought of, so much asham'd and confounded was I at having seen him. Condemn'd then to stay till his departure should release me, I was greatly embarrass'd how to dispose of myself: I kept sometime, betwixt terror and modesty, even from looking through the window, which being an old fashion'd casement, without any light behind me, could hardly betray any one's being there to him from within: then the door was so secure, that without violence, or my own consent, there was no opening it, from without.<break time="100ms" />But now, by my own experience, I found it too true, that objects which afright us, when we cannot get from them, draw our eyes as forcibly as those that please us. I could not long withstand that nameless impulse, which, without any desire of this novel sight, compell'd me towards it: embolden'd too by my certainty of being at once unseen and safe, I ventur'd by degrees to cast my eyes on an object so terrible and alarming to my virgin modesty as a naked man: But as I snatch'd a look, the first gleam that struck me, was in general, the dewy lustre of the whitest skin imaginable, which the sun playing upon, made the reflection of it perfectly beamy. His face, in the confusion I was in, I could not well distinguish the lineaments of, any farther than that there was a great deal of youth and freshness in it. The frolic, and various play of all his fine polish'd limbs, as they appear'd above the surface, in the course of his swimming, or wantoning with the water, amus'd and insensibly delighted me: sometimes he lay motionless on his back, water born, and dragging after him a fine head of hair, that floating swept the stream in a bush of black curls. Then the overflowing water would make a separation between his breast and glossy white belly; at the bottom of which, I could not escape observing so remarkable a distinction, as a black mossy tuft; out of which appear'd to emerge a round, softish, limber, white, something, that play'd every way, with every the least motion or whirling eddy. I cannot say but that part chiefly, by a kind of natural instinct, attracted, detain'd, captivated my attention: it was out of the power of all my modesty to command my eye away from it, and seeing nothing so very dreadful in its appearance, I sensibly look'd away all my fears: but as fast as they gave way, new desires and strange wishes took place, and I melted as I gazed. The fire of nature, that had so long lain dormant, or conceal'd, began to break out, and make me feel my sex for the first time. He had now chang'd his posture, and swam prone on his belly, striking out with his legs and arms, finer modell'd than which could not have been cast, whilst his floating locks play'd o'er a neck and shoulders, whose whiteness they delightfully set off. Then the luxuriant swell of flesh that rose from the small of his back, and terminates its double cope at where the thighs are sent off, perfectly dazzl'd one with its watery glistening gloss.
    </voice>
</speak>
