<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The sameness of our sex, age, profession, and views, soon created as unreserv'd a freedom and intimacy as if we had been for years acquainted. They took and shew'd me the house, their respective apartments, which were furnish'd with every article of conveniency and luxury, and above all, a spacious drawing-room, where a select revelling band usually met, in general parties of pleasure; the girls supping with their sparks, and acting their wanton pranks with unbounded licentiousness, whilst a defiance of awe, modesty, or jealousy, were their standing rules, by which, according to the principles of their society, whatever pleasure was lost on the side of sentiment, was abundantly made up to the senses, in the poignancy of variety, and the charms of ease and luxury. The authors and supporters of this secret institution, would, in the height of their humour, style themselves the restorers of the liberty of the golden age, and its simplicity of pleasures, before their innocence became so unjustly branded with the names of guilt, and shame.<break time="100ms" />As soon then as the evening began, and the shew of a shop was shut, the academy open'd, the mask of mock-modesty was compleatly taken off, and all the girls deliver'd over to their respective calls of pleasure, or interest, with their men: and none of that sex were promiscuously admitted, but only such as Mrs. Cole was previously satisfied of their character and discretion. In short, this was the safest, politest, and at the same time the most thorough house of accommodation in town, every thing being conducted so, that decency made no intrenchment up on the most libertine pleasures, in the practice of which too, the choice familiars of the house had found the secret so rare and difficult, of reconciling even all the refinements of taste and delicacy, with the most gross and determinate gratifications of sensuality.<break time="100ms" />After having consum'd the morning in the indearments and instructions of my new acquaintance, we went to dinner, when Mrs. Cole, presiding at the head of her cluck, gave me the first idea of her management and address, in inspiring these lively amiable girls with so sensible a love, and respect for her. There was no stiffness, no reserve, no airs of pique, or little jealousies, but all was unaffectedly gay, chearful, and easy.<break time="100ms" />After dinner, Mrs. Cole, seconded by the young ladies, acquainted me, that there was a chapter to be held that night in form, for the ceremony of my reception into the sisterhood, and in which, with all due reserve to my maiden-head, that was to be occasionally cooked up for the first proper chapman, I was to undergo a ceremonial of initiation, they were sure I should not be displeased with.<break time="100ms" />Embark'd as I was, and moreover captivated with the charms of my new companions, I was too much prejudiced in favour of any proposal they could make, to so much as hesitate an assent, which therefore readily giving, in the style of a charte blanche, I receiv'd fresh kisses of compliment from them all, in approval of my docility and good-nature, "now I was a sweet girl,———" "I came into things with a good grace,———" "I was not affectedly coy———" "I should be the pride of the house———" and the like.<break time="100ms" />This point thus adjusted, the young women left Mrs. Cole to talk and concert matters with me, when she explain'd to me, that I should be introduc'd that very evening to four of her best friends, one of whom she had, according to the custom of the house, favour'd with the preference of engaging me in the first party of pleasure, assuring me at the same time, that they were all young gentlemen agreeable in their persons, and unexceptionable in every respect; that united and holding together by the band of common pleasures, they composed the chief support of her house, and made very liberal presents to the girls that pleased and humour'd them, so that they were properly speaking the founders, and patrons of this little Seraglio. Not but that she had, at proper seasons, other customers to deal with, whom she stood less upon punctilio with, than with these: for instance, it was not on one of them she could attempt to pass me for a maid; they were not only too knowing, too much town-bred, to bite at such a bait, but they were such generous benefactors to her, that it would be unpardonable to think of it.<break time="100ms" />Amidst all the flutter and emotion which this promise of pleasure, for such I conceived it, stir'd up in me, I preserv'd so much of the woman as to feign just reluctance enough, to make some merit of sacrificing it to the influence of my patroness, whom I likewise, still in character, reminded of its perhaps being right for me to go home and dress in favour of my first impressions.<break time="100ms" />But Mrs. Cole, in opposition to this, assured me that the gentlemen I should be presented to, were, by their rank and taste of things, infinitely superior to the being touch'd with any glare of dress, or ornaments, such as silly women rather con found, and overlay, than set off their beauty with; that these veteran voluptuaries knew better than not to hold them in the highest contempt, they with whom the pure native charms alone could pass current, and who would at any time leave a sallow, washy, painted dutchess on her own hands, for a ruddy, healthy, firm-flesh'd country-maid: and as for my part, that nature had done enough for me, to set me above owing the least favour to art; concluding withall, that for the instant occasion, there was no dress like an undress.<break time="100ms" />I thought my governess too good a judge of these matters, not to be easily over-rul'd by her: after which she went on preaching very pathetically the doctrine of passive obedience, and nonresistance to all those arbitrary tastes of pleasure, which are by some stil'd the refinements, and by others, the depravations of it; between whom it was not the business of a simple girl, who was to profit by pleasing, to decide, but to conform.<break time="100ms" />Whilst I was edifying by these whole some lessons, tea was brought in, and the young ladies, returning, join'd company with us.<break time="100ms" />After a great deal of mix'd chat, frolick, and humour, one of them, observing that there would be a good deal of time on hand before the assembly-hour, proposed, that each girl should entertain the company with that critical period of her personal history, in which she first exchanged the maiden state for womanhood. The proposal was approv'd, with one only restriction of Mrs. Cole, that she, on the account of her age, and I on the account of my titular maidenhood, should be excused, at least till I had undergone the forms of the house. This obtained me a dispensation, and the promotress of this amusement was desired to begin.<break time="100ms" />Her name was Emily ———, a girl fair to excess, and whose limbs were if possible too well-made, since their plump fulness was rather to the prejudice of that delicate slimness of shape required by the nicer judges of beauty: her eyes were blue, and stream'd inexpressible sweetness, and nothing could be prettier than her mouth, and lips, which closed over a range of the evenest, whitest teeth. ——— Thus she began.
    </voice>
</speak>
