<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The first that stood up, to open the ball, were a cornet of horse and that sweetest of olive-beauties, the soft and amorous Louisa. He led her to the couch, "nothing loth," on which he gave her the fall; and extended her at her length with an air of roughness and vigour, relishing high of amourous eagerness and impatience. The girl spreading herself to the best advantage, with her head upon the pillow, was so concenter'd in what she was about, that our presence seem'd the least of her care or concern. Her petticoats thrown up with her shift, discover'd to the company the finest turn'd legs and thighs that could be imagin'd, and in a broad display, that gave us a full view of that delicious cleft of flesh, into which the pleasingly hair-grown mount over it parted, and presented a most inviting entrance, between two close ledges, delicately soft and pouting. Her gallant was now ready, having disincumbered himself from his cloaths overloaded with lace, and presently his shirt remov'd, shew'd us his forces in high plight, bandied, and ready for action: but giving us no time to consider dimensions, and proving the stiffness of his weapon, by his impatience of delay, he threw himself instantly over his charming antagonist, who receiv'd him as he push'd at once dead at mark, like a heroine without flinching, for surely never was girl constitutionally truer to the taste of joy, or sincerer in the expressions of its sensations than she was: we could observe the pleasure lighten in her eyes as he introduc'd its plenipotentiary instrument into her, till at length, having indulg'd her its utmost reach, its irritations grew so violent, and gave her the spurs so furiously, that collected within herself, and lost to every thing but the enjoyment of her favourite feelings, she retorted his thrusts with a just concert of springy heaves, keeping time so exactly with the most pathetic sighs, that one might have number'd the strokes in agitation by their distinct murmurs, whilst her active limbs kept wreathing and intertwisting with his in convulsive folds: Then the turtle-billing kisses, and the poignant painless love bites, which they both exchang'd in a rage of delight, all conspiring towards the melting period; it soon came on, when Louisa, in the ravings of her pleasure-frensy, impotent of all restraint, cry'd out: "Oh Sir!——Good Sir——pray do not spare me! ah! ah!——I can no more." And all her accents now faultering into heart-fetch'd sighs, she clos'd her eyes in the sweet death, in the instant of which she was deliciously embalm'd by an injection, of which we could easily see the signs, in the quiet, dying, languid posture of her late so furious driver, who was stopp'd of a sudden, breathing short, panting; and for that time, giving up the spirit of pleasure,<break time="100ms" />As soon as he was dismounted, Louisa sprung up, shook her petticoats, and running up to me, gave me a kiss, and drew me to the side-board, to which she was herself handed by her gallant, where they made me pledge them in a glass of wine, and toast a droll health of Louisa's proposal in high frolic, that of "the miraculous thing which wets were it tickles, and tickles where it wets".<break time="100ms" />By this time the second couple was ready to enter the lifts, which were a young baronet, and that delicatest of charmers, the winning tender Harriet. My gentle esquire came to acquaint me with it, and brought me back to the scene of action.<break time="100ms" />And surely, never did one of her profession accompany her dispositions for the bare-fac'd part she was engag'd to play, with such a peculiar grace of sweetness, modesty, and yeilding coyness as she did. All her air and motions breath'd only unreserv'd, unlimited complaisance, without the least mixture of impudence, or prostitution. But what was yet more surprising, her spark-elect, in the midst of the dissolution of a publick open enjoyment, doated on her to distraction, and had, by dint of love and sentiments, touched her heart, though for a while the restraint of their engagement to the house, laid him under a kind of necessity of complying with an institution which himself had had the greatest share in establishing.<break time="100ms" />Harriet then was led to the vacant couch by her gallant, blushing as she look'd at me, and with eyes made to justify any thing, tenderly bespeaking of me the most favourable construction of the step she was thus irresistibly drawn into.<break time="100ms" />Her lover, for such he was, sat her down at the foot of the couch, and passing his arms round her neck, preluded with a kiss fervently applied to her lips, that visibly gave her life and spirit to go through with the scene; and as he kiss'd, he gently inclin'd his head, till it fell back on a pillow dispos'd to receive it, and leaning himself down all the way with her, at once countenanc'd and endear'd her fall to her: there as if he had guess'd our wishes, or meant to gratify at once his pleasure and his pride, in being the master, by title of present possession of beauties delicate beyond imagination, he discover'd her breasts, to his own touch, and our common view; but oh! what delicious manuals of love-devotion! how inimitably fine-moulded! small, round, firm, and excellently white: then the grain of their skin so soothing, so flattering to the touch! and their nipples, that crown'd them the sweetest buds of beauty! when he had feasted his eyes with the touch and perusal, feasted his lips with kisses of the highest relish imprinted in those all-delicious twin orbs, he proceeded downwards.<break time="100ms" />Her legs still kept the ground; and now with the tenderest attention not to shock, or alarm her too suddenly, he, by degrees, rather stole than roll'd up her petticoats, at which, as if a signal had been given, Louisa and Emily took hold of her legs, in pure wantonness, and yet in ease too, to her, kept them stretch'd wide abroad. Then lay expos'd, or to speak more properly, display'd the greatest parade in nature of female charms. The whole company, who, except myself, had often seen them, seem'd as much dazzled, surpris'd, and delighted, as any one could be who had now beheld them for the first time. Beauties so excessive could not but enjoy the priviledges of eternal novelty. Her thighs were so exquisitely fashion'd, that either more in, or more out of flesh than they were, they would have declin'd from that point of perfection they presented. But what infinitely enrich'd and adorn'd them, was the sweet intersection, form'd where they met, at the bottom of the smoothest, roundest, whitest belly, by that central furrow which nature had sunk there, between the soft relievo of two pouting ridges, and which in this girl was in perfect simmetry of delicacy and mignature with the rest of her frame: no! nothing in nature could be of a beautifuller cut: then the dark umbrage of the downy sprig-moss that over-arch'd it, bestow'd on the luxury of the landscape, a touching warmth, a tender finishing, beyond the expression of words, or even the paint of thought.
    </voice>
</speak>
