<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Here I staid, in constant amusement, with one or other of these charming girls, till about five in the evening: when seiz'd with a sudden drowsy fit, I was prevailed on to go up and doze it off on Harriet's bed, who left me on it to my repose. There then I lay down in my cloaths, and fell fast asleep, and had now enjoy'd by guess, about an hour's rest; when I was pleasingly disturb'd by my new and favourite gallant, who enquiring for me, was readily directed where to find me. Coming then into my chamber, and seeing me lie alone, with my face turn'd from the light towards the inside of the bed, he, without more ado, just slipp'd off his breeches, for the greater ease and enjoyment of the naked touch; and softly turning up my petticoat and shift behind, open'd himself the prospect of the back avenue to the genial seat of pleasure; where, as I lay at my side length, inclining rather face downward, I appear'd full fair, and liable to be entered: laying himself then gently down by me, he invested me behind, and giving me to feel the warmth of his body, as he applied his thighs and belly close to me, and the endeavours of that machine, whose touch has something so exquisitely singular in it, to make its way good into me, I wak'd, pretty much startled at first; but seeing who it was, dispos'd myself to turn to him, when he gave me a kiss; and desiring me to keep my posture, just lifted up my upper thigh, and ascertaining the right opening, soon drove it up to the farthest; satisfied with which, and solacing himself with lying so close in full touch of flesh in those parts, he suspended all motion, and thus steep'd in pleasure, kept me lying on my side, in to him, spoon-fashion, as he term'd it, from the snug indent of the back-part of my thighs, and all upwards, into the space of the bending between his thighs and belly; till after some time, that restless, and turbulent inmate, impatient by nature of longer quiet, urg'd him to action, which now prosecuting, with all the usual train of toying, kissing, and the like, ended at length in the liquid proof on both sides, that we had not been exhausted, or at least were quickly recruited of last night's draughts of pleasure on us.<break time="100ms" />With this noble and agreable youth, liv'd I in perfect joy and constancy: he was full bent on keeping me to himself, for the honey-month at least: but his stay in London was not even so long, his father who had a great post in Ireland, taking him abruptly with him, on his repairing thither. Yet even then I was near keeping hold of his affection, and person, for he had propos'd, and I had consented to follow his order to go to Ireland after him, as soon as he should be settled there; but meeting with an agreeable and advantageous match in that kingdom, he chose the wiser part, and forbore sending for me, but at the same time took care that I should receive a magnificent present, which did not however compensate for all my deep regret on my loss of him.<break time="100ms" />This event also created a chasm in our little society, which Mrs. Cole, on the foot of her usual caution, was in no haste to fill up: but then it redoubl'd her attention to procure me in the advantages of the traffick for a counterfeit maidenhead, some consolation for the sort of widowhood I had been left in, and this was a scheme she had never lost prospect of, and only waited for a proper person to bring it to bear with.<break time="100ms" />But I was, it seems, fated to be my own caterer in this, as I had been in my first trial of the market.<break time="100ms" />I had now pass'd near a month in the enjoyment of all the pleasures of familiarity and society with my companions, whose particular favourites, (the Baronet excepted, who soon after took Harriet home) had all, on the terms of community establish'd in the house, sollicited the gratification of their taste for variety in my embraces; but I had with the utmost art and address, on various pretexts, eluded their persuit, without giving them cause to complain: and this reserve I used neither out of dislike to them, or disgust of the thing, but my true reason was my attachment to my own, and my tenderness of invading the choice of my companions, who outwardly exempt, as they seem'd, from jealousy, could not but in secret like me the better for the regard I had for, without making a merit of it to, them. Thus easy, and belov'd by the whole family did I go on, when one day, that, about five in the afternoon, I stepp'd over to a fruiterer's shop, in Covent-Garden, to pick some table-fruit for myself and the young women, I met with the following adventure.<break time="100ms" />Whilst I was chaffering for the fruit I wanted, I observ'd myself follow'd by a young gentleman, whose rich dress first attracted my notice; for the rest, he had nothing remarkable in his person, except that he was pale, thin-made, and ventur'd himself upon legs rather of the slenderest. Easy was it to perceive, without seeming to perceive it, that it was me he wanted to be at, by his making a full set at, and keeping his eyes fix'd on, me, till he came to the same basket that I stood at, and cheapening, or rather giving the first price ask'd for the firuit, began his approaches. Now most certainly I was not at all out of figure to pass for a modest girl. I had neither the feathers, nor fumet of a tawdry town-miss; a straw hat, a white gown, clean linnen, and above all, a certain natural and easy air of modesty (which the appearances of never forsook me, even on those occasions that I most broke in upon it, in practice) where all signs that gave him no opening to conjecture my condition. He spoke to me, and this address from a stranger throwing a blush into my cheeks, that still set him wider off the truth, I answer'd him, with an awkwardness and confusion the more apt to impose, as there was really, a mixture of the genuine in them. But when proceeding on the foot of having broke the ice, to join discourse, he went into other leading questions, I put so much innocence, simplicity, and even childishness, into my answers, that on no better foundation, liking my person as he did, I will answer for it, that he would have been sworn for my modesty. There is, in short, in the men, when once they are caught, by the eye especially, a fund of cullibility, that their lordly wisdom little dreams of, and in virtue of which the most sagacious of them are seen so often our dupes. Amongst other queries he put to me one was, whether I was married, or no? I replied, that I was too young, to think of that this many a year. To that of my age, I answer'd, and sunk a year upon him, passing myself for not seventeen. As to my way of life, I told him I had serv'd an apprenticeship to a millener in Preston, and was come to town after a relation that I found on my arrival was dead, and I now liv'd journey-woman to a millener in town. That last article indeed was not much on the side of what I pretended to pass for; but it did pass, under favour of the growing passion I had inspir'd him with. After he had next got out of me, very dextrously as he thought, what I had no sort of design to make a reserve of, my own, my mistress's name, and place of abode, he loaded me with fruit, all the rarest and dearest he could pick out, and sent me home pondering on what might be the consequence of this adventure.
    </voice>
</speak>
