<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Now, whether my partner had exhausted all the modes of regaling the touch, or sight, or whether he was now ungovernably wound up to strike, I know not; but briskly throwing off his cloaths the prodigious heat bred by a close room, a great fire, numerous candles, and even the inflammatory warmth of these scenes, induc'd him to lay aside his shirt too, when his breeches, before loosen'd, now gave up their contents to view, and shewed in front, the enemy I had to engage with, stifly bearing up the port of its head unhooded, and glowing red: then I plainly saw what I had to trust to: it was one of those just true-siz'd instruments of which the masters have a better command, than the more unweildy, inordinate siz'd ones are generally under. Straining me then close to his bosom, as he stood up fore-right against me, and applying to the obvious nich its peculiar idol, he aim'd at inserting it, which, as I forwardly favour'd, he effected at once by canting up my thighs over his naked hips, and made me receive every inch, and close home; so that stuck upon the pleasure-pivot, and clinging round his neck, in which and his hair, I hid my face burningly flushing with my present feelings as much as with shame, my bosom glew'd to his, he carried me once round the couch, on which he then, without quitting the middle-fastness, or dischannelling, laid me down, and began the pleasure grist, but so provokingly predispos'd and prim'd as we were, by all the moving sights of the night, our imagination was too much heated, not to melt us of the soonest, and accordingly I no sooner felt the warm spray darted up my inwards from him; but I was punctually on flow to share the momentary extasy; but I had yet greater reason to boast of our harmony; for finding that all the flames of desire were not yet quench'd within me: but that rather, like wetted coals, I glow'd the fiercer for this sprinkling: my hot-mettled spark sympathysing with me, and loaded for a double-fire, recontinu'd the sweet battery with undying vigour: greatly pleas'd at which, I gratefully endeavour'd to accommodate all my motions to his best advantage and delight; kisses, squeezes, tender murmurs, all came into play, till our joys growing more turbulent and riotous, threw us into a fond disorder, and as they raged to a point, bore us far from ourselves into an ocean of boundless pleasures, into which we both plung'd together in a transport of taste: now all the impressions of burning desire, from the lively scenes I had been spectatress of, ripen'd by the heat of this exercise, and collecting to a head, throb'd and agitated me with insupportable irritations: I perfectly fever'd and madden'd with their excess: I did not now enjoy a calm of reason enough to perceive, but I, extatically indeed! felt the policy and power of such rare and exquisite provocatives as the examples of the night had proved towards thus exalting our pleasures: which, with great joy, I sensibly found my gallant shar'd in, by his nervous and home expressions of it: his eyes flashing eloquent flames, his action infuriated with the stings of it, all conspiring to raise my delight by assuring me of his; lifted then to the utmost pitch of joy that human life can bear undestroy'd by excess, I touched that sweetly critical point, when scarce prevented by the spermatic injection from my partner spurting liquid fire up to my vitals, I dissolv'd, and breaking out in to a deep drawn sigh, sent my whole sensitive soul down to that passage where escape was denied it, by its being so deliciously plugged and choak'd up. Thus we lay a few blissful instants, overpower'd, still, and languid; till, as the sense of pleasure stagnated, we recover'd from our trance, and he slipt out of me, not, however, before he had protested his extreme satisfaction, by the tenderest kiss and embrace, as well as by the most cordial expressions.<break time="100ms" />The company who had stood round us in a profound silence, when all was over, help'd me to hurry on my cloaths in an instant, and complimented me on the sincere homage they could not escape observing had been done (as they term'd it) to the sovereignty of my charms, in my receiving a double payment of tribute at one juncture: but my partner, now dress'd again, signaliz'd, above all, a fondness unbated by the circumstance of recent enjoyment: the girls too kiss'd and embrac'd me, assuring me, that for that time, or indeed any other, unless I pleas'd, I was to go through no farther publick trials, and that I was now consummately initiated, and one of them.<break time="100ms" />As it was an inviolable law for every gallant to keep to his partner, for the night especially, and even till he relinquish'd possession over to the community, in order to preserve a pleasing property, and to avoid the disgusts and indelicacy of another arrangement, the company, after a short refection of biskets and wine, tea and chocolate, served in at, now, about one in the morning, broke up, and went off in pairsr Mrs. Cole had prepar'd my spark and me an occasional field-bed, to which we retired, and there ended the night in one continued strain of pleasure, sprightly and uncloy'd enough for us not to have form'd one wish for its ever knowing an end. In the morning, after a restorative breakfast in bed, he got up, and with very tender assurances of a particular regard for me, left me to the composure and refreshment of a sweet slumber; waking out of which, and getting up to dress before Mrs. Cole should come in, I found in one of my pockets a purse of guineas, which he had slipt there; and just as I was musing on a liberality I had certainly not expected, Mrs. Cole come in, to whom I immediately communicated the present, and naturally offer'd her whatever share she pleas'd; but assuring me that the gentleman had very nobly rewarded her, she would on no terms, no entreaties, no shape I could put it in, receive any part of it. Her denial, she observ'd, was not affectation or grimace, and proceeded to read me such admirable lessons on the œconomy of my person and my purse, as I became amply paid for my general attention and conformity to, in the course of my acquaintance with the town. After which, changing the discourse, she fell on the pleasures of the preceding night, where I learn'd, without much surprise, as I began to enter her character, that she had seen every thing that had passed, from a convenient place, manag'd solely for that purpose, and of which she readily made me the confidante.<break time="100ms" />She had scarce finish'd with this, when the little troop of love, the girls my Companions, broke in, and renew'd their compliments and caresses; I observ'd with pleasure, that the fatigues and exercises of the night, had not usurp'd in the least on the life of the complexion, or the freshness of their bloom; this I found by their confession, was owing to the management and advice of our rare directress. They went down then to figure it, as usual, in the shop; whilst I repair'd to my lodgings; where I employ'd myself till I return'd to dinner, at Mrs. Cole's.
    </voice>
</speak>
