<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Letter the Second
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />Mrs. Cole on this, taking me by the hand, with a smile of encouragement, led me up stairs, preceded by Louisa, who was come to hasten us, and lighted us with two candles, one in each hand.<break time="100ms" />On the landing place of the first pair of stairs, we were met by a young gentleman, extremely well dress'd, and a very pretty figure, to whom I was to be indebted for the first essay of the pleasures of the house. He saluted me with great gallantry, and handed me into the drawing room, the floor of which was overspread with a Turky-carpet, and all its furniture voluptuously adapted to every demand of the most study'd luxury; now too it was by means of a profuse illumination, enliven'd by a light scarce inferior to, and perhaps more favourable to joy, more tenderly pleasing, than that of broad sun-shine.<break time="100ms" />On my entrance into the room, I had the satisfaction to hear a buz of approbation run through the whole company, which now consisted of four gentlemen, including my particular, (this was the cant-term of the house for one's gallant for the time) the three young women, in a neat flowing dishabil, the mistress of the academy, and myself. I was welcom'd and saluted by a kiss all round, in which however it was easy to discover, in the superior warmth of that of the men, the distinction of the sexes.<break time="100ms" />Aw'd, and confounded as I was, at seeing myself surrounded, caress'd, and made court to by so many strangers, I could not immediately familiarize myself to all that air of gaiety, and joy, which dictated their compliments, and animated their caresses. They assur'd me that I was so perfectly their taste, as to have but one fault against me, which I might easily be cur'd of: and that was my modesty: this, they observ'd, might pass for a beauty the more with those who wanted it for a heightener; but their maxim was, that it was an impertinent mixture, and dash'd the cup so as to spoil the sincere draught of pleasure: they consider'd it accordingly as their mortal enemy, and gave it no quarter wherever they met with it: this was a prologue not unworthy of the revels that ensu'd.<break time="100ms" />In the midst of all the frolic and wantonnesses, which this joyous band had presently and all naturally run into, an elegant supper was serv'd in, and we sat down to it, my spark elect placing himself next to me, and the other couples without order, or ceremony. The delicate cheer, and good wine, soon banish'd all reserve; the conversation grew as lively as could be wish'd, without taking too loose a turn: these professors of pleasure knew too well, to stale the impressions of it, or evaporate the imagination in words, before the time of action. Kisses however were snatch'd at times, or where a handkerchief round the neck interpos'd its feeble barrier, it was not extremely respected: the hands of the men went to work with their usual petulance, till the provocations on both sides rose to such a pitch, that my particular's proposal for beginning the country-dances was receiv'd with instant assent: for, as he laughingly added, he fancied the instruments were in tune. This was a signal for preparation, that the complaisant Mrs. Cole, who understood life, took for her cue of disappearing; no longer so fit for personal service herself, and content with having settled the order of battle, she left us the field to fight it out at discretion.<break time="100ms" />As soon as she was gone, the table was remov'd from the middle, and became a side-board; a couch was brought into its place, of which when I whisperringly enquired the reason of my particular, he told me, that as it was chiefly on my account that this convention was met, the parties intended at once to humour their taste of variety in pleasures, and by an open publick enjoyment, to see me broke of any taint of reserve or modesty, which they look'd on as the poison of joy: that though they occasionally preached pleasure, and lived up to the text, they did not enthusiastically set up for its missionaries, and only indulg'd themselves in the delights of a practical instruction of all the pretty women they lik'd well enough to bestow it upon, and fell properly in the way of it, but that as such a proposal might be too violent, too shocking for a young beginner; the older standers were to set an example, which he hop'd I would not be averse to follow, since it was to him I was devolv'd in favour of the first experiment; but that still I was perfectly at my liberty to refuse the party, which being in its nature one of pleasure, suppos'd an exclusion of all force, or constraint.<break time="100ms" />My countenance expressed, no doubt, my surprise, as my silence did my acquiescence. I was now embark'd, and thoroughly determined on any voyage the company would take me on.
    </voice>
</speak>
