<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I was then in this vacancy from any regular employ of my person, in my way of business, when one day Mrs. Cole, in the course of the constant confidence we liv'd in, acquainted me that there was one Mr. Barvile, a gentleman who us'd her house, just come to town, whom she was not a little perplex'd about providing a suitable companion for; which was indeed a point of difficulty, as he was under the tyranny of a cruel taste; that of an ardent desire, not only of being unmercifully whipp'd himself, but of whipping others, in such sort, that tho' he paid extravagantly those who had the courage and complaisance to submit to his humour; there were few, delicate as he was in the choice of his subjects, who would exchange turns with him so terribly at the expence of their skin: but what yet increas'd the oddity of this strange fancy, was the gentleman's being young; whereas it generally attacks, it seems, such as are, through age, oblig'd to have recourse to this experiment, for quickening the circulation of their sluggish juices, and determining a conflux of the spirits of pleasure towards those flagging, shrivelly parts, that rise to life only by virtue of those titillating ardours created by the discipline of their opposites, with which they have so surprising a consent.<break time="100ms" />This Mrs. Cole could not well acquaint me with, in any expectation of my offering my service: for, sufficiently easy as I was in my circumstances, it must have been the temptation of an immense interest indeed, that could have induced me to embrace such a job; neither had I ever express'd, or indeed felt, the least impulse or curiosity to know more of a taste, that promis'd so much more pain than pleasure, to those that stood in no need of such violent goads: what then should move me to subscribe myself voluntarily to a party of pain, foreknowing it such? Why, to tell the plain truth; it was a sudden caprice, a gust of fancy for trying a new experiment, mix'd with the vanity of proving my personal courage to Mrs. Cole, that determin'd me, at all risques, to propose myself to her, and relieve her from any farther look-out; accordingly, I at once pleas'd and surpris'd her, with a frank and unreserv'd tender of my person to her, and her friend's absolute disposal on this occasion.<break time="100ms" />My good temporal mother, was however so kind as to use all the arguments she could imagine to dissuade me: but as I found they only turn'd on a motive of tenderness to me, I persisted in my resolution, and thereby acquitted my offer of any suspicion of its not having been sincerely made, or out of compliment only: acquiescing then thankfully in it, Mrs. Cole assur'd me, that bating the pain I should be put to, she had no scruple to engage me to this party, which she assur'd me I should be liberally paid for, and which the secrecy of the transaction, preserv'd safe from the ridicule that otherwise vulgarly attended it: that for her part, she consider'd pleasure of one sort or other, as the universal port of destination, and every wind that blew thither a good one, provided it blew nobody any harm: that she rather compassionated, than blam'd those unhappy persons, who are under a subjection they cannot shake off, to those arbitrary tastes that rule their appetites of pleasure with an unaccountable controul: tastes too, as infinitely diversify'd, as superior to, and independent of all reasoning, as the different relishes or palates of mankind in their viands; some delicate stomachs nauseating plain meats, and finding no savour but in high-season'd, luxurious dishes; whilst others again pique themselves upon detesting them.<break time="100ms" />I stood now in no need of this preamble of encouragement, or justification: my word was given, and I was determin'd to fulfil my engagements; accordingly the night was set, and I had all the necessary previous instructions how to act and conduct myself. The dining-room was duly prepar'd and lighted up, and the young gentleman posted there in waiting for my introduction to him.<break time="100ms" />I was then, by Mrs. Cole, handed in, and presented to him in a loose dishabil, fitted, by her direction, to the exercise I was to go through, all in the finest linnen, and a thorough white-uniform: gown, petticoat, stockings, and sattin slippers, like a victim led to the sacrifice; whilst my dark auburn hair, falling in drop-curls over my neck, created a pleasing distinction of colour from the rest of my dress.<break time="100ms" />As soon as Mr. Barvile saw me, he got up with a visible air of pleasure and surprise, and after saluting me, ask'd Mrs. Cole if it was possible that so fine, and delicate a creature would voluntarily submit to such sufferings and rigours as were the subject of his assignation. She answer'd him properly, and now, reading in his eyes that she could not too soon leave us together, she went out, after recommending to him to use moderation with so tender a novice.<break time="100ms" />But whilst she was employing his attention, mine had been taken up with examining the figure and person of this unhappy young gentleman, who was thus unaccountably condemn'd to have his pleasure lashed into him, as boys have their learning.<break time="100ms" />He was exceedingly fair, and smooth complexion'd, and appeared to me no more than twenty at most, tho' he was three years older than what my conjectures gave him; but then he ow'd this favourable mistake to a habit of fatness, which spread through a short, squab stature, and a round, plump, fresh-coloured face gave him greatly the look of a Bacchus, had not an air of austerity, not to say sternness, very even to his shape of face, dash'd that character of joy, necessary to complete the resemblance. His light-brown hair was pretty thick, uncurl'd, and look'd as if it had been trimm'd with a bowl-dish, as we are told the Roundheads were in Oliver's times. His dress was extremely neat, but plain, and far inferior to the ample fortune, he was in full possession of: this too was a taste in him, and not avarice.<break time="100ms" />As soon as Mrs. Cole was gone, he seated me near him, when now his face changed upon me into an expression of the most pleasing sweetness and good humour, the more remarkable for its sudden shift from the other extreme, which I found afterwards, when I knew more of his character, was owing to a habitual state of conflict with, and dislike of himself, for being enslav'd to so peculiar a gust, by the fatality of a constitutional ascendant, that render'd him incapable of receiving any pleasure, till he submitted to these extraordinary means of procuring it at the hands of pain, whilst the constancy of this repining consciousness, stamp'd at length that cast of sourness and severity on his features which was in fact, very foreign to the natural sweetness of his temper.<break time="100ms" />After a competent preparation by apologies, and encouragement to go through my part with spirit and constancy, he stood up near the fire, whilst I went to fetch the instruments of discipline, out of a closet hard by: these were several rods, made each of two or three strong twigs of birch tied together, which he took, handled, and view'd with as much pleasure as I did with a kind of shuddering presage.
    </voice>
</speak>
