<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />As soon as he was in bed, he threw off the bed-cloaths, which I suffer'd him to force from my hold, and I now lay as expos'd as he could wish, not only to his attacks, but his visitation of the sheets, where, in the various agitations of my body, through my endeavours to defend myself, he could easily assure himself there was no preparation, or stain of blood, though to do him justice, he seem'd less strict an examinant than I had apprehended from so experienc'd a practitioner. My shift then he fairly tore open, finding I made too much use of it to barricade my breasts, as well as the more important avenue: yet in every thing else he proceeded with all the marks of tenderness and regard to me, whilst the art of my play was, to shew none for him: I acted then all the niceties, apprehensions, and terrors, supposable for a girl perfectly innocent, to feel, at so great a novelty as a naked man in bed with her for the first time. He scarce even obtain'd a kiss but what he ravish'd: I put his hand away twenty times from my breasts, where he had satisfy'd himself of their hardness and consistence with passing for hitherto unhandled goods: but when grown impatient for the main point, he now threw himself upon me, and first trying to examine me with his finger, sought to make himself further way, I complain'd of his usage bitterly, "I thought he would not have serv'd a body so. I was ruin'd.———I did not know what I had done.———I would get up, so I would."———And at the same time kept my thighs so fast lock'd, that it was not for a strength like his to force them open, or do any good. Finding thus my advantages, and that I had both my own and his motions at command, the deceiving him became so easy, that it was perfect playing upon velvet: in the mean time, his machine, which was one of those sizes that slip in and out without being minded, kept pretty stifly bearing against that part, which the shutting my thighs barr'd access to; but finding, at length, he could do no good by mere dint of bodily strength, he resorted to intreaties and arguments; to which I only answer'd, with a tone of shame and timidity, "that I was afraid it would kill me——Lard!——I would not be serv'd so.——I was never so us'd in all my born days.——I wonder'd he was not asham'd of himself, so I did.——" With such silly infantine moods of repulse and complaint as I judg'd best adapted to express the characters of innocence, and afright, Pretending however to yield at length to the vehemence of his insistence, in action and words; I sparingly disclos'd my thighs so, that he could just touch the cloven inlet with the tip of his instrument, but as he fatigu'd and toil'd to get it in, a twist of of my body, so as to receive it obliquely, not only thwarted his admission, but giving a skream, as if he had pierced me to the heart, I shook him off me, with such violence that he could not with all his might to it, keep the saddle: vex'd indeed at this he seem'd, but not in the style of any displeasure with me for my skittishness; on the contrary, I dare swear, he held me the dearer, and hugg'd himself for the difficulties that even hurt his instant pleasure: fired, however, now, beyond all bearance of delay, he remounts, and begg'd of me to have patience, stroaking and soothing me to it by all the tenderest endearments and protestations of what he would moreover do for me, at which feigning to be something soften'd, and abating of the anger that I had shewn at his hurting me so prodigiously, I suffer'd him to lay my thighs aside, and make way for a new trial; but I watch'd the directions and management of his point so well, that no sooner was the orifice in the least open to to it; but I gave such a timely jerk, as seem'd to proceed, not from the evasion of his entry, but from the pain his efforts at it put me to: a circumstance too that I did not fail to accompany with proper gestures, sighs, and cries of complaint, of which, "that he had hurt me——he kill'd me——I should die——" were the most frequent interjections. But now, after repeated attempts, in which he had not made the least impression, towards gaining his point, at least for that time, the pleasure rose so fast upon him that he could not check or delay it, and in the vigour and fury, which the approaches of the heigh of it inspir'd him, he made one fierce thrust that had almost put me by my guard, and lodg'd it so far that I could feel the warm inspersion just within the exterior orifice, which I had the cruelty not to let him finish there, but threw him out again, not without a most piercing loud exclamation, as if the pain had put me beyond all regard of being over-heard. It was easy then to observe that he was more satisfy'd, more highly pleas'd with the suppos'd motives of his baulk of consummation, than he would have been at the full attainment of it. It was on this foot that I salv'd to myself all the falsity I employ'd to procure him that blissful pleasure in it, which most certainly he would not have tasted in the truth of things. Eas'd however, and reliev'd by one discharge, he now apply'd himself to sooth, encourage, and put me into humour, and patience to bear his next attempt, which he began to prepare and gather force for, from all the incentives of the touch and sight, which he could think of, by examining every individual part off my whole body, which he declar'd his satisfaction with, in raptures of applause, kisses universally imprinted, and sparing no part of me, in all the eagerest wantonnesses of feeling, seeing and toying: his vigour however did not return so soon, and I felt him more than once pushing at the door, but so little in a condition to break in, that I question whether he had the power to enter, had I held it ever so open; but this he then thought me too little acquainted with the nature of things to have any regret or confusion about, and he kept fatiguing himself and me for a long time before he was in any state of stiffness to resume his attempts with any prospect of success! and then I breath'd him so warmly, and kept him so at bay, that before he had made any sensible progress in point of penetration, he was deliciously sweated, and weary'd out indeed! so that it was deep in the morning before he had atchiev'd his second let-go, about half way of entrance, I all the time crying and complaining of his prodigious vigour, and the immensity of what I appear'd to suffer splitting up with. Tir'd however at length, with such athletic drudgery, my champion began now to give out, and to gladly embrace the refreshment of some rest; kissing me then with much affection, and recommending me to my repose, be presently fell fast asleep: which as soon as I had well satisfied myself of, I, with much composure of body, so as not to wake him by any motion, with much ease and safety too, play'd off Mrs. Cole's device for perfecting the signs of my virginity.
    </voice>
</speak>
