<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Leaving me then to my much wanted rest, he got up, and Mrs. Cole, after settling with him all points relating to me, got him undiscover'd out of the house. Aftar which, and I was awake, she came in, and gave me due praises on my success; behaving too with her usual moderation, aod disinterestness, she refus'd any share of the sum I had thus earn'd, and put me into such a secure and easy way of disposing of my affairs, which now amounted to a kind of little fortune, that a child of ten years old might have kept the account, and property of them safe in its hands.<break time="100ms" />I was now restor'd again to my former state of a kept mistress, and us'd punctually to wait on Mr. Norbert at his chambers, whenever he sent a messenger for me, which I constantly took care to be in the way of, and manag'd with so much caution that he never once penetrated the nature of my connexions with Mrs. Cole, but indolently given up to ease, and the town-dissipations, the perpetual hurry to them hinder'd him from looking into his own affairs, much less into mine.<break time="100ms" />In the mean time, if I may judge from my own experience, none are better paid, or better treated, during their reign, than the mistresses of those who, enervate by nature, debaucheries, or age, have the least employment for the sex: sensible that a woman must be satisfy'd some way, they ply her with a thousand little tender attentions, presents, caresses, confidences, and exhaust their invention in means and devices to make up for the capital deficiency; and even towards lessening that, what arts, what modes, what refinements of pleasure have they not recourse to, to raise their languid powers, and press nature into the service of their sensuality? But here is their misfortune, that when by a course of teazing, worrying, handling, wanton postures, lacivious motions, they have at length accomplish'd a flashy enervate enjoyment, they have at the same time lighted up a flame in the object of their passion, that not having the means themselves to quench, drives her for relief, into the next person's arms, who can finish their work: and thus they become bawds to some secret favourite, tried, and approv'd of for a more vigorous, and satisfactory execution; for with women, of our turn especially, however well our hearts may be dispos'd, there is a controuling part, or queen-seat in us, that governs itself by its own maxims of state, amongst which not one is stronger in practise with it, than, in matter of its dues, never to accept the will for the deed.<break time="100ms" />Mr. Norbert, who was much in this ungracious case, though he profess'd and shew'd to like me extremely, could but seldom consummate the main-joy itself with me, without such a length and variety of preparations as were at once wearisome and inflammatory.<break time="100ms" />Sometimes he would strip me stark naked on a carpet, by a good fire; when he would contemplate me almost by the hour, disposing me in all the figures and attitudes of body, that it was susceptible of being view'd in: kissing me in every part, the most secret and critical one so far from excepted, that it receiv'd most of that branch of homage, then his touches were so exquisitely wanton, and luxuriously diffus'd, and penetrative at times, that he made me perfectly rage with titillating fires, when, after all, and when with much ado, he had gain'd a short-liv'd erection, he would perhaps melt it away in a washy sweat, or a premature abortive effusion, that provokingly mock'd my eager desires; or, if carried home, how faulter'd and unnervous the execution! how insufficient the sprinkle of a few heat-drops to extinguish all the flames he had kindled.<break time="100ms" />One evening I cannot help remembring, that returning home from him with a spirit he had rais'd in a circle his wand had prov'd too weak to lay, as I turn'd the corner of a street, I was overtaken by a young sailor. I was then in that spruce, neat, and plain dress, which I ever affected, and perhaps might have in my trip a certain air of restlessness unknown to the composure of cooler thoughts. However he seiz'd me as prize, and, without ceremony, threw his hands round my neck, and kiss'd me boisterously, and sweetly. I look'd at him with a beginning of anger and indignation at his rudeness, that soften'd away into other sentiments as fast I view'd him: for he was tall, manly-carriag'd, handsome of body and face, so that I ended my stare, with asking him in a tone turn'd to tenderness, what he meant: at which, with the same frankness, and vivacity as he had begun with me, he propos'd treating me with a glass of wine: now, certain it is, that had I been in a calmer state of blood than I was; had I been less under the dominion of unappeas'd irritations and desires, I should have refus'd him without hesitation: but I do not know how it was, my pressing calls, his figure, the occasion, and if you will, the powerful combination of all these with a start of curiosity, to see the end of an adventure so novel to me as being thus treated like a common street-plyer, made me give a silent consent: in short, it was not my head that I now obey'd. I suffer'd myself then to be tow'd along as it were by this man-of-war, who took me under his arm as familiarly as if he had known me all his life-time, and led me into the next convenient tavern, where we were shown in to a little room on one side of the passage. Here, scarce allowing himself patience till the drawer brought in the wine call'd for, he fell directly on board me: when untucking my handkerchief, and giving me a smacking buss, he laid my breasts bare at once, which he handled with that keenness of gust that abridges a ceremonial ever more tiresome than pleasing on such pressing occasions; and now hurrying towards the main-point, we found no conveniency for our purpose; two or three disabled chairs, and a ricketty table composing the whole furniture of the room).
    </voice>
</speak>
