<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />In each of the head bed-posts, just above where the bed-steads are inserted into them, there was a small drawer so artfully adapted to the mouldings of the timber-work, that it might have escap'd even the most curious search, which drawers were easily open'd or shut, by the touch of a spring, and were fitted each with a shallow glass tumbler, full of a prepar'd fluid blood; in which lay soak'd, for ready use, a spunge; that requir'd no more than gently reaching the hand to it, taking it out, and properly squeezing between the thighs, when it yielded a great deal more of the red liquid than would save a girl's honour: after which, replacing it, and touching the spring, all possibility of discovery, or even of suspicion, was taken away; and all this was not the work of the fourth part of a minute, and of which ever side one lay, the thing was equally easy and practicable, by the double care taken to have each bed-post provided a like. True it is, that had he wak'd, and caught me in the fact, it would at least have cover'd me with shame and confusion; but then, that he did not, was, with the precautions I took, a risque of a thousand to one in my favour.<break time="100ms" />At ease now, and out of all fear of any doubt or suspicion, on his side, I address'd myself in good earnest to my repose; but could obtain none, and in about half an hour's time, my gentleman wak'd again, and turning towards me, I feign'd a sound sleep, which he did not long respect; but girding himself again to renew the onset, he began to kiss and caress me, when now making as if I just wak'd, I complain'd of the disturbance, and of the cruel pain that this little rest had stolen my senses from. Eager, however, for the pleasure, as well as honour of consummating an entire triumph over my virginity; he said, and did every thing that could overcome my resistance, and bribe my patience to the end, which now I was ready to listen to, from being secure of the bloody proofs I had prepar'd of his victorious violence, though I still thought it good policy not to let him in yet awhile. I answer'd then only to his importunities, in sighs and moans, "that I was so hurt, I could not bear it.——I was sure he had done me a mischief; that he had,——he was such a sad man!" Turning at this, down the cloaths, and viewing the field of battle by the glimmer of a dying taper, he saw plainly my thighs, shift, and sheets, all yet wet, and stain'd with what he readily took for virgin gore, proceeding from his last half-penetration: convinc'd, and transported at which, nothing could equal his joy and exultation. The illusion was complete: no other conception enter'd his head but that of his having been at work upon an unopen'd mine: which idea, upon so strong an evidence, redoubled at once his tenderness for me, and his ardour for breaking it wholly up. Kissing me then with the utmost rapture, he comforted me, and begg'd my pardon for the pain he had put me to, observing withal, that it was only a thing in course; but the worst was certainly past, and that with a little courage and constancy I should get it once well over, and never after experience any thing but the greatest pleasure. By little and little I suffer'd myself to be prevail'd on, and giving, as it were, up the point to him, I made my thighs, insensibly spreading them, yield him liberty of access, which improving, he got a little within me, when, by a well-manag'd reception, I work'd the female screw so nicely, that I kept him from the easy mid channel direction, and by dexterous wreathings and contorsions creating an artificial difficulty of entrance, made him win it inch by inch, with the most laborious struggles, I all the time sorely complainig, till at length, with might and main, winding his way in, he got it completely home, and giving my virginity, as he thought, the coup de grace, furnish'd me the cue of setting up a terrible outcry, whilst he, triumphant, and like a cock, clapping his wings over his down-trod mistress, pursu'd his pleasure, which presently rose in virtue cf this idea of a complete victory, to a pitch that made me soon sensible of his melting period, whilst I now lay acting the deep wounded, breathless, frighten'd, undone, no longer, maid.<break time="100ms" />You will ask me perhaps, whether all this time I enjoy'd any perception of pleasure? I assure you, little or none; till just towards the latter end, a faintish sense of it came on mechanically, from so long a struggle, and frequent fret in that ever sensible part: but, in the first place, I had no taste for the person I was suffering the embraces of, on a purely mercenary account, and then I was not entirely delighted with myself for the jade's part I was playing, whatever excuses I might have to plead for being brought into it: but then this insensibility kept me so much the mistress of my mind and motions, that I could the better manage so close a counterfeit, through the whole scene of deception.<break time="100ms" />Recover'd at length to more shew of life, by his tender condoleances, kisses, and embraces, I upbraided him, and reproach'd him for my ruin, in such natural terms, as added to his satisfaction with himself, for having accomplish'd it; and guessing, by certain observations of mine, that it would be rather favourable to him, to spare him, when he sometime after, feebly enough, came on again to the assault, I resolutely withstood, any further endeavours, on a pretext that flatter'd his prowess, of my being so violently hurt and sore, that I could not possibly endure a fresh trial: he then graciously granted me a respite, and the morning soon after advancing, I got rid of farther importunity, till Mrs. Cole, being rang for by him, came in, and was made acquainted in terms of the utmost joy and rapture, with his triumphant certainty of my virtue, and the finishing stroke he had given it, in the course of the night; of which he added, she would see proof enough, in bloody characters, on the sheets.<break time="100ms" />You may guess how a woman of her turn of address and experience, humour'd the jest, and play'd him off with mix'd exclamations of shame, anger, compassion for me, and of her being pleas'd that all was so well over; in which last, I believe, she was perfectly sincere. And now, as the objection which she had represented as an invincible one, to my lying the first night at his lodgings (which were studiously calculated for a freedom of intrigues) on the account of my maiden fears and terrors, at the thoughts of going to a gentleman's chambers, and being alone with him in bed, was surmounted, she pretended to persuade me, in favour to him, that I should go there to him, whenever he pleas'd, and still keep up all the necessary appearances of working with her, that I might not lose, with my character, the prospect of getting a good husband, and at the same time her house would be kept the safer from scandal. All this seem'd so reasonable, so considerate to Mr. Norbert, that he never once perceiv'd, that she did not want him to resort to her house, left he might in time discover certain inconsistencies with the character she had set out with to him; besides that this plan greatly flatter'd his own ease, and views of liberty.
    </voice>
</speak>
