<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Without more ado, he plants me with my back standing against the wall, and my petticoats up; and coming out with a splitter indeed, made it shine, as he brandish'd it, in my eyes, and going to work with an impetuosity and eagerness, bred very likely by a long fast at sea, went to give me the taste of it: I straddled, I humour'd my posture, and did my best in short to buckle to it; I took part of it in too; but still things did not jee to his thorough liking: changing then in a trice his system of battery, he leads me to the table, and with a master-hand lays my head down on the edge of it, and with the other canting up my petticoat and shift, bares my naked posteriours to his blind, and furious guide: it forces his way between them, and I feeling pretty sensibly that it was going by the right door, and knocking desperately at the wrong one, I told him of it: "Pooh, says he my dear, any port in a storm." —— Altering, however directly, his course, and lowering his point, he fix'd it right, and driving it up with a delicious stiffness, made all foam again, and gave me the tout with such fire, and spirit, that in the fine disposition I was in, when I submitted to him, and stirr'd up so fiercely as I was, I got the start of him, and went away into the melting swoon, and squeezing him, whilst in the convulsive grasp of it, drew from him such a plenteous bedewal of balmy sweets, as join'd to my own effusion, perfectly floated those parts, and drown'd in a deluge all my raging conflagration of desire.<break time="100ms" />When this was over, how to make my retreat was my concern; for though I had been so extremely pleas'd with the difference between this warm broadside pour'd so briskly into me, and the tiresome pawing and toying, to which I had ow'd the unappeas'd flames that had driven me into this step; now I was grown cooler, I began to apprehend the danger of contracting an acquaintance with this, however agreeable, stranger; who, on his side, spoke of passing the evening with me, and continuing our intimacy, with an air of determination that made me afraid of its being not so easy to get away from him as I could wish: in the mean time I carefully conceal'd my uneasiness, and readily pretended to consent to stay with him, telling him, I should only step to my lodgings, to leave a necessary direction, and then instantly return. This he very glibly swallow'd, on the notion of my being one of those unhappy street-errants, who devote themselves to the pleasure of the first ruffian that will stoop to pick them up, and of course, that I would scarce bilk myself of my hire by my not returning, to make the most of the job. Thus he parted with me, not before, however, he had order'd, in my hearing, a supper, which I had the barbarity to disappoint him of my company to.<break time="100ms" />But when I got home, and told Mrs. Cole my adventure, she represented so strongly to me the nature and dangerous consequences of my folly, the risques to my health, in being so open-legg'd, and free of my flesh, that I not only took resolutions never to venture so rashly again, which I inviolably preserv'd; but pass'd a good many days in continual uneasiness lest I should have met with other reasons, besides the pleasure of that rencounter, to remember it: but these fears wrong'd my pretty sailor, for which I gladly make him this reparation.<break time="100ms" />I had now liv'd with Mr. Norbert near a quarter of a year, in which space I circulated my time very pleasantly, between my amusements at Mrs. Cole's, and a proper attendance on that gentleman, who paid me profusely for the unlimited complaisance with which I passively humour'd every caprice of pleasure, and which had won upon him so greatly, that finding, as he said, all that variety in me alone, which he had sought for in a number of women, I had made him lose his taste for inconstancy, and new faces. But what was yet at least as agreeable to me as his fondness and attachment, as well as much more flattering; the love I had inspir'd him with, bred a deference to me that was of great service to his health. For having by degrees, and with most pathetic representations, brought him to some husbandry of it, and to ensure the duration of his pleasures by moderating their use, and correcting those excesses in them he was so addicted to, and which had shatter'd his constitution, and destroy'd his powers of life, in the very point, for which he seem'd chiefly desirous to live; he was grown more delicate, more temperate, and all in course more healthy; his gratitude for which was taking a turn very favourable for my fortune, when once more the caprice of it, dash'd the cup from my lips.<break time="100ms" />His sister, lady L———, for whom he had a great affection, desiring him to accompany her down to Bath for her health, he could not refuse her such a favour, and accordingly, though he counted on staying away from me no more than a week at farthest, he took his leave of me, with an ominous heaviness of heart, and left with me a sum far above the state of his fortune, and very inconsistent with the intended shortness of his journey, but it ended in the longest that can be, and is never but once taken; for, arriv'd at Bath, he was not there two days before he fell into a debauch of drinking with some gentlemen, that threw him into a high fever, which carry'd him off in four days time, never once out of a delirium. Had he been in his senses to make a will, perhaps he might have made favourable mention of me in it. Thus, however, I lost him; and as no condition of life is more subject to revolutions than that of a woman of pleasure, I soon recover'd my chearfulness, and now beheld myself once more struck off the list of kept-mistresses, and return'd into the bosom of the community, from which I had been in some manner taken.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Cole still continuing her friendship, offer'd me her assistances and advice towards another choice; but I was now in a state of ease and affluence enough to look about me at leisure; and as to any constitutional calls of pleasure, their pressure or sensibility was greatly lessen'd by a consciousness of the ease with which they were to be satisfy'd at Mrs. Cole's house, where Louisa and Emily still continu'd in the old way; and my great favourite Harriet, us'd often to come and see me, and entertain me, with her head and heart full of the happiness she enjoy'd with her dear baronet, whom she lov'd with tenderness and constancy, even though he was her keeper; and what is yet more, had made her independent by a handsome provision for her, and hers.
    </voice>
</speak>
