<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The night then was fix'd, with all possible respect to the eagerness of his impatience, and in the mean time Mrs. Cole had omitted no instructions, nor even neglected any preparation that might enable me to come off with honour, in regard to the appearance of virginity, except that, favour'd as I was by nature, with all the narrowness of stricture in that part requisite to conduct my designs, I had no occasion to borrow those auxiliaries of art that create a momentary one, easily discover'd by the test of a warm bath: and as to the usual bloody symptoms of defloration, which, if not always, are generally attendants on it, Mrs. Cole had made me the mistress of an invention of her own, which could hardly miss its effect, and of which more in its place.<break time="100ms" />Every thing then being dispos'd and fix'd for Mr. Norbert's reception, he was at the hour of eleven at night, with all the mysteries of silence and secrecy, let in by Mrs. Cole herself, and introduc'd into her bed-chamber, where, in an old fashion'd bed of her's, I lay, fully undress'd, and panting, if not with the fears of a real maid, at least with those perhaps greater, of a dissembled one, which gave me an air of confusion and bashfulness that maiden modesty had all the honour of, and was indeed scarce distinguishable from it, even by less partial eyes than those of my lover, so let me call him, for I ever thought the term cully too cruel a reproach to the men, for their abus'd weakness for us.<break time="100ms" />As soon as Mrs. Cole, after the old gossipery, on those occasions, us'd to young women abandon'd for the first time to the will of man, had left us alone in her room, which, by-the-bye, was well lighted up, at his previous desire, that seem'd to bode a stricter examination than he afterwards made; Mr. Norbert, still dress'd, sprung towards the bed, where I had got my head under the cloaths, and defended them a good while before he could even get at my lips, to kiss them: so true it is, that a false virtue, on this occasion, ever makes a greater rout and resistance, than a true one! from thence he descended to my breasts, the feel of which I disputed tooth and nail with him, till tir'd with my resistance, and thinking probably to give a better account of me, when got into bed to me; he hurry'd his cloaths off in an instant, and came into bed.<break time="100ms" />Mean while, by the glimpse I stole of him, I could easily discover a person far from promising any such doughty performances as the storming of maidenheads generally requires, and whose flimzy consumptive texture, gave him more the air of an invalid that was press'd, than of a volunteer, on such hot service.<break time="100ms" />At scarce thirty, he had already reduc'd his strength of appetite down to a wretched dependance on forc'd provocatives, very little seconded by the natural powers of a body jaded, and wrack'd off to the lees by constant repeated overdraughts of pleasure, which had done the work of sixty winters on his springs of life; leaving him at the same time all the fire and heat of youth in his imagination, which serv'd at once to torment and to spur him down the precipice.
    </voice>
</speak>
