<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Louisa and she went one night to a ball; the first in the habit of a shepherdess; Emily in that of a shepherd: I saw them in their dresses before they went, and nothing in nature could represent a prettier boy than this last did; being so extremely fair and well limb'd. They had kept together for some time, when Louisa meeting with an old acquaintance of hers, very cordially gives her companion the drop, and leaves her under the protection of her boy's habit, which was not much, and of her discretion which was, it seems, yet less. Emily finding herself deserted, saunter'd thoughtlesly about a while, and as much for coolness and air, as any thing else, pull'd off her mask, at length, and went to the side-board, where, eyed and mark'd out by a gentleman in a very handsome domino, she was accosted by, and fell into chat with, him. The domino, after a little discourse, in which Emily doubtless distinguish'd her good nature and easiness more than her wit, began to make violent love to her, and drawing her insensibly to some benches at the lower end of the masquerade-room, got her to sit by him, where he squeez'd her hands, pinch'd her cheeks, prais'd and play'd with her fair hair, admir'd her complexion, and all in a style of courtship dash'd with a certain oddity, that not comprehending the mystery of, poor Emily attributed to his falling in with the humour of her disguise, and being naturally not the cruellest of her profession, began to incline to a parley on essentials: but here was the stress of the joke: He took her really for what she appear'd to be, a smock-fac'd boy, and she forgetting her dress, and of course ranging quite wide of his ideas, took all those addresses to be paid to herself as a woman, which she precisely ow'd to his not thinking her one: however this double error was push'd to such a height on both sides, that Emily who saw nothing in him but a gentle man of distinction by those points of dress, to which his disguise did not extend, warm'd too by the wine he had ply'd her with, and the caresses he had lavish'd upon her, suffer'd herself to be perswaded to go to a bagnio with him; and thus loosing sight of Mrs. Cole's cautions, with a blind confidence put herself into his hands to be carried wherever he pleas'd: or his part equally blinded by his wishes, whilst her egregious simplicity favour'd his deception more than the most exquisite art could have done, he suppos'd, no doubt, that he had lighted on some soft simpleton fit for his purpose, or some kept minion broke to his hand, who understood him perfectly well, and enter'd into his designs; but be that as it would, he led her to a coach, went into it with her, and brought her into a very handsome apartment, with a bed in it, but whether it were a bagnio or not, she could not tell, having spoke to nobody but himself. But when they were alone together, and her enamorato began to proceed to those extremities which instantly discover the sex, she remark'd that no description could paint up to the life, the mixture of pique, confusion, and disappointment, that appear'd in his countenance, which join'd to the mournful exclamation, "By heavens a woman!" This at once open'd her eyes which had hitherto been shut in downright stupidity. However, as if he had meant to retrieve that escape, he still continu'd to toy with and fondle her, but with so staring an alteration from extreme warmth into a chill and forc'd civility, that even Emily herself could not but take notice of it, and now began to wish she had paid more regard to Mrs. Cole's premonitions against ever engaging with a stranger: and now an excess of timidity succeeded to an excess of confidence, and she thought herself so much at his mercy and discretion, that she stood passive throughout the whole progress of his prelude: for now, whether the impressions of so great a beauty had even made him forgive her, her sex, or whether her appearance or figure in that dress still humour'd his first illusion, he recover'd by degrees a good part of his first warmth, and keeping Emily with her breeches still unbuttoned, stript them down to her knees, and gently impelling her to lean down, with her face against the bed-side, placed her so, that the double-way between the double rising behind, presented the choice fair to him, and he was so fiercely set on a mis-direction, as to give the girl no small alarms for fear of loosing a maiden-head she had not dreamt of; however her complaints, and a resistance gentle, but firm, check'd, and brought him to himself again; so that turning his steed's head, he drove him at length in the right road, in which his imagination having probably made the most of those resemblances that flatter'd his taste, he got with much ado whip and spur to his journey's end: after which he led her out himself, and walking with her two or three streets length, got her a chair, when making her a present not any thing inferior to what she could have expected, he left her, well recommended to the chairmen, who on her directions, brought her home.<break time="100ms" />This she related to Mrs. Cole and me, the same morning, not without the visible remains of the fear and confusion she had been in, still stamp'd on her countenance, Mrs. Cole's remark was, that her indiscretion proceeding from a constitutional facility, there were little hopes of any thing curing her of it, but repeated severe experience. Mine was that I could not conceive how it was possible for mankind to run into a taste, not only universally odious, but absurd, and impossible to gratify, since, according to the notions and experience I had of things, it was not in nature to force such immense disproportions: Mrs. Cole only smill'd at my ignorance, and said nothing towards my undeception, which was not effected but by occular demonstration, some months after, which a most singular accident furnish'd me, and I will here set down, that I may not return again to so disagreable a subject,<break time="100ms" />I had on a visit intended to Harriet, who had lodgings at Hampton-Court, hired a chariot to go out thither, Mrs. Cole having promis'd to accompany me: but some indispensible business intervening to detain her, I was obliged to set out alone; and scarce had I got a third of my way, before the axle-tree broke down, and I was well off, to get out safe and unhurt, into a publick-house of a tolerably handsome appearance, on the road. Here the people told me that the stage would come by in a couple of hours at farthest, upon which, determining to wait for it, sooner than loose the jaunt I had got so far forward on, I was carried into a very clean decent room up one pair of stairs, which I took possession of for the time I had to stay, in right of calling for sufficient to do the house justice.<break time="100ms" />Here, whilst I was amuſing myself with looking out of the window, a single horse-chaise stopt at the door, out of which lightly leap'd two young gentlemen, for so they seem'd, who came in as it were only to bait and refresh a little, for they gave their horse to be held in a readiness against they came out: and presently I heard the door of the next room to me open, where they were let in and call'd about them briskly, and as soon as they were serv'd, I could just hear that they shut and fasten'd the door on the inside.
    </voice>
</speak>
