<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />This had continu'd a good half hour, when bethinking me of some directions to be given to the coachman, I sent for him, and not caring that his shoes should soil the very clean parlour, in which the cloth was laid, I stept into the hall-kitchen, where he was, and where, whilst I was talking to him, I slantingly observ'd two horsemen driven in by the weather, and both wringing wet? one of whom was asking if they could be assisted with a change, till their cloaths could be dried: but heavens! who can express what I felt at the sound of a voice, ever present to my heart, and that it now rebounded at? or when pointing my eyes towards the person it came from, they confirm'd its information; in spite of so long an absence, and of a dress one would have imagin'd studied for disguise: a horseman's great coat with a stand-up cape, and his hat flapp'd; but what could escape the piercing alertness of a sense surely guided by love? a transport then, like mine, was above all consideration, or schemes of surprize, and I, that instant, with the rapidity of the emotions that I felt the spur of, shot into his arms, crying out as I threw mine round his Neck, "My life!— my soul! – my Charles!—and, without further power of speech swoon'd away, under the oppressing agitations of joy and surprise.<break time="100ms" />Recover'd out of my entrancement, I found myself in my charmer's arms, but in the parlour, surrounded by a croud which this event had gather'd round us, and which immediately, on a signal from the discreet landlady, who currently took him for my husband, clear'd the room, and desirably left us alone to the raptures of this re-union, my joy at which, had like to have prov'd, at the expence of of my life, its power superior to that of grief at our fatal separation.<break time="100ms" />The first object then, that my eyes open'd on, were their supreme idol, and my supreme wish, Charles, on one knee, holding me fast by the hand, and gazing at me in a transport of fondness. Observing my recovery, he attempted to speak, and give vent to his impatience of hearing my voice again, to satisfy him once more that it was me: but the mightiness, and suddenness of the surprize continuing to stun him, choak'd his utterance: he could only stammer out a few broken, half-form'd, faultering accents, which my ears greedily drinking in, spelt, and put together so as to make out their sense. "After so long!——so cruel!—an absence,—my dearest Fanny!— Can it? can it be you?"—stifling me at the same time with kisses, that stopping my mouth, at once prevented the answer that he panted for, and encreas'd the delicious disorder, in which all my senses were rapturously lost. Amidst, however, this croud of ideas, and all blissful ones, there obtruded only one cruel doubt, that poison'd nearly all this transcendent happiness: and what was it, but my dread of its being too excessive to be real? I trembled now with the fear of its being no more than a dream, and of my waking out of it into the horrors of finding it one: under this fond apprehension, imagining I could not make too much of the present prodigious joy, before it should vanish and leave me in the desart again, nor verify its reality too strongly, I clung to him, I clasp'd him, as if to hinder him from escaping me again. "Where have you been?—how could you, could you leave me?—Say you are still mine,–that you still love me,–and thus! thus! (kissing him as if I would consolidate lips with him) I forgive you—forgive my hard fortune in favour of this restoration."—All these interjections breaking from me, in that wildness of expression, that justly passes for eloquence in love, drew from him all the returns my fond heart could wish, or require. Our caresses, our questions, our answers, for some time, observ'd no order? all crossing, or interrupting one another in sweet confusion, whilst we exchang'd hearts at our eyes, and renew'd the ratifications of a love unabated by time or absence: not a breath, not a motion, not a gesture on either side, but what was strongly impressed with it. Our hands lock'd in each other, repeated the most passionate squeezes, so that their fiery thrill went to the heart again.<break time="100ms" />Thus absorpt, and concenter'd in this unutterable delight; I had not attended to the sweet author of it, being thoroughly wet, and in danger of catching cold? when, in good time, the landlady, whom the appearance of my equipage (which by the by Charles knew nothing of) had gain'd me an interest in, for me, and mine, interrupted us, by bringing in a decent shift of linnen, and cloaths, which now, somewhat recover'd into a calmer composure by the coming in of a third person, I prest him to take the benefit of, with a tender concern, and anxiety, that made me tremble for his health.<break time="100ms" />The landlady leaving us again, he proceeded to shift, in the act of which, tho' he proceeded with all that modesty, which became these first solemner instants of our re-meeting, after so long an absence, I could not contain certain snatches of my eyes, lur'd by the dazzling discoveries of his naked skin, that escap'd him as he chang'd his linnen, and which I could not observe the unfaded life, and complexion of, without emotions of tenderness and joy, that had himself too purely for their object, to partake of a loose, or mis-tim'd desire.<break time="100ms" />He was soon drest in these tempory cloaths, which neither fitted him, nor became the light my passion plac'd him in, to me at least: yet as they were on him, they look'd extremely well, in virtue of that magic charm which love put into every thing that he touch'd, or had relation to him; and where indeed was that dress that a figure like his would not give grace to? For now as I ey'd him more in detail, I could not but observe the even favourable alteration which the time of his absence had produc'd in his person.
    </voice>
</speak>
