<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-MiaNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />But as action was now a necessity to desires so much on edge as ours, Charles, after a very short prelusive dalliance, lifting up my linen and his own, laid the broad treasures of his manly chest close to my bosom, both beating with the tenderest alarms! when now, the sense of his glowing body in naked touch with mine, took all power over my thoughts out of my own disposal, and deliver'd up every faculty of my soul to the sensiblest of joys, that affecting me infinitely more with my distinction of the person, than of the sex, now brought my conscious heart deliciously into play; my heart, which, eternally constant to Charles, had never taken any part in my occasional sacrifices to the calls of constitution, complaisance, or interest. But, ah! what became of me, when, as the powers of solid pleasure thickened upon me, I could not help feeling the stiff stake that had been adorned with the trophies of my despoiled virginity, bearing hard and inflexible against one of my thighs, which I had not yet opened, from a true principle of modesty, revived by a passion too sincere to suffer any aiming at the false merit of difficulty, or my putting on an impertinent mock-coyness.<break time="100ms" />I have, I believe, somewhere before remark'd, that the feel of that favourite piece of manhood has, in the very nature of it, something inimitably pathetic. Nothing can be dearer to the touch, or can affect it with a more delicious sensation. Think then! as a lover think, what must be the consummate transport of that quickest of our senses, in their central seat too! when after so long a deprival, it felt itself re-inflamed under the pressure of that peculiar scepter-member, which commands us all: but especially my darling elect from the face of the whole earth. And now, at its mightiest point of stiffness, it felt to me something so subduing, so active, so solid, and agreeable that I know not what name to give its singular impression; but the sentiment of consciousness of its belonging to my supremely beloved youth, gave me so pleasing an agitation, and work'd so strongly on my soul, that it sent all its sensitive spirits to that organ of bliss in me, dedicated to its reception: there concentering to a point, like rays in a burning-glass, they glow'd, they burnt with the intensest heat: the springs of pleasure were, in short, wound up to such a pitch! I panted now with so exquisitely keen an appetite for the imminent enjoyment, that I was even sick with desire, and unequal to support the combination of two distinct ideas, that delightfully distracted me! for all the thought I was capable of, was that I was now in touch at once with the instrument of pleasure, and the great-seal of love; ideas that mingling streams, pour'd such an ocean of intoxicating bliss on a weak vessel, all too narrow to contain it, that I lay overwhelm'd, absorpt, lost in an abyss of joy, and dying of nothing but immoderate delight.<break time="100ms" />Charles then rouz'd me somewhat out of this extatic distraction, with a complaint softly murmur'd amidst a croud of kisses, at the position, not so favourable to his desires, in which I receiv'd his urgent insistance for admission, where that insistence was alone so engrossing a pleasure, that it made me inconsistently suffer a much dearer one to be kept out; but how sweet to correct such a mistake! my thighs now obedient to the intimations of love and nature, gladly disclose, and with a ready submission resign up the soft gateway to entrance at pleasure: I see! I feel! the delicious velvet tip!—he enters might and main with—oh!—my pen drops from me here in the extasy now present to my faithful memory! Description too deserts me, and delivers over a task, above its strength of Wing, to the imagination: but it must be an imagination exalted by such a flame as mine, that can do justice to that sweetest, noblest of all Sensations that hailed and accompany'd the stiff insinuation all the way up, till it was at the end of its penetration, sending up, through my eyes, the Sparks of the love-fire that ran all over me, and blaz'd in every vein, and every pore of me: a system incarnate of joy all over.<break time="100ms" />I had now totally taken in love's true arrow from the point up to the feather, in that part, where making no new wound, the lips of the original one of nature, which had owed its first breathing to this dear instrument, clung, as if sensible of gratitude, in eager suction round it, whilst all its inwards embrac'd it tenderly, with a warmth of gust, a compressive energy that gave it, in its way, the heartiest welcome in nature, every fibre there gathering tight round it, and straining ambitiously to come in for its share of the blissful touch.<break time="100ms" />As we were giving then a few moments of pause to the delectation of the senses, in dwelling with the highest relish on this intimatest point of re-union, and chewing the cud of enjoyment, the impatience natural to the pleasure soon drove us into action. Then began the driving tumult on his side, and the responsive heaves on mine, which kept me up to him: whilst as our joys grew too mighty for utterance, the organs of our voice, voluptuously intermixing, became organs of the touch: And, oh, that touch, how delicious! how poignantly luscious!—And now! now! I felt! to the heart of me, I felt the prodigious keen edge, with which love, presiding over this act, points the pleasure: Love! that may be stiled the attic salt of enjoyment: and indeed, without it, the joy, great as it is, is still a vulgar one, whether in a king or a beggar: for it is undoubtedly love alone, that refines, ennobles, and exalts it.<break time="100ms" />Thus happy then, by the heart, happy by the senses, it was beyond all power, even of thought, to form the conception of a greater delight, than what I was now consummating the fruition of.<break time="100ms" />Charles, whose whole frame all convulsed with the agitation of his rapture, whilst the tenderest fires trembled in his eyes, all assured me of a perfect concord of joy, penetrated me so profoundly, touch'd me so vitally, took me so much out of my own possession, whilst he seem'd himself so much in mine, that in a delicious enthusiasm I imagin'd such a tranfusion of heart and spirit, as that coaliting, and making one body and soul with him, I was him, and he, me.
    </voice>
</speak>
