<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Fanny could not stand this caressing. She let go of my prick and tried, clothed as she was, to impale herself on it. It slipped beneath her motte. She felt it do so. She pulled up her dress a little and, suddenly opening her thighs, she closed them, equally suddenly, on my prick, and I acted just as though it had been in her cunt! Gods! Gods! I think I should have burst, only nature came to my relief, and I poured forth a torrent of hot, burning spend! This recalled me to my senses.<break time="100ms" />Gently pushing Fanny away, I begged her to seat herself, whilst I went and changed into trousers. The intelligent and excited girl saw the necessity and reason, as she looked at me in the quite transparent pajamas flooded with spend, and extended in front by my enraged prick, of which the coloring and shape of the head was as clear as if seen in crystal water. But instead of sitting down she came and peeped at me from behind the purdah, as I took off my pajamas and fed her eyes on the galaxy I showed her, with pleasure indescribable. She saw the mighty prick, its ponderous, well shaped balls, and the forest out of which they grew, and knew that they were now all hers, as she gazed, she tried to quiet the throbbing of the hot little cunt by put ting her hand between her lovely thighs. But before I had finished putting these treasures away from sight, some stir made her drop the purdah and flee to a chair, and when I came out, in shirt, trousers, socks and shoes, she was seated in it. She looked for he! new possessions, and with burning eyes asked me where it had gone. For all answer I took her willing little hand and laid it on my prick which was buttoned back against my belly. Once more did the excited “My darling! my darling!” resound, but in whispered tones, and then feeling frightened lest our disordered minds might betray themselves to Mrs. Selwyn who was still talking to Lavie, who might at any moment come into our room, I got a book of views, and opened it so as to look as if Fanny and I had been examining it during their absence.<break time="100ms" />“You made the wet come in me, as well as yourself, my darling! my darling!” whispered Fanny.<break time="100ms" />“Did I?” Well! my sweetest, next time such wet comes it must not be outside of us, but inside you. Inside here! Do you understand?”<break time="100ms" />For all answer Fanny kissed me, whilst she pressed the hand I had slipped between those thighs, which, if. Ever opened for man, would first be opened to admit me!<break time="100ms" />Whilst thus engaged in deliciously feeling one another and talking the language, not the less eloquent because it was dumb, Mrs. Selwyn came almost staggering into the room. She was evidently overcome with emotion, and was far too excited herself to notice any appearance of heat in either Fanny or myself. She managed to reach the chair, to drop into it, but for a moment or two could not speak a word. Fanny and I, both in alarm, were at her side at once, and waited for Mrs. Selwyn to speak.<break time="100ms" />“Oh! Captain Devereaux!” she whispered, and then paused for breath for she was panting with agitation, “Go in! go in to that—that—mad man, and for goodness sake, for God's sake, I implore you, calm him, and tell him he must not persecute me in this manner. He talks of cut ting his throat if I do not give him Fanny!”<break time="100ms" />“I will settle him, Mrs. Selwyn,” said I, as quietly as I could, “I will go in now. Fanny, look after your mother, there's a good creature!” and so saying, I made her eyes speak volumes. They said to me, “Get rid of Lavie and then we will fuck, my Charlie!”<break time="100ms" />I went into the next room and there I found the miserable lover, who had, that very morning, been talking, whilst I had been acting! That very morning! Why, it was not yet five minutes since I had had my prick, not in Fanny's darling little cunt indeed, but between her thighs, and had spent a perfect flood, and had shown her my prick and balls naked, and had had her hand caressing it, and herself calling me “darling,” and telling me I had made her spend, as she had made me! I must say I felt a considerable amount of con tempt for Lavie, and wondered where all that good sense had gone to, for which I had once given him so much credit.<break time="100ms" />Poor devil! The fact was, he was quite out of his mind, and his lunacy had taken the form of a passion for Fanny Selwyn. But no one knew or suspected the facts for some days still. N a wonder it was no use my speaking to him or advising him to desist from following Fanny, for a time at least. He moaned and groaned, and weeped, and behaved in the most extraordinary manner. At last I persuaded him to go home, promising I would see him again the next day. But when he had gone, and when I had ascertained that Fanny and Mrs. 'Selwyn had gone too, I put on my helmet and went myself to Dr. Bridges, our P. M. 0., and put the whole case to him, and begged him to get Lavie removed to some other station. Bridges hemmed and hawed at first; but at last he said that he had noticed that Lavie was not doing his work as well as he used to, and he would see him and come to a conclusion in. a day or two. I had to be content with that, but it was something.<break time="100ms" />That afternoon I got a little note from Fanny saying that Mama had desired her to write and ask me to dine with them unless I had a prior engagement. That was the propriety part, but in the corner, written very small and hurriedly, was, “Do come, my darling!” I sent reply that I should have much pleasure in accepting the invitation and I went.<break time="100ms" />As I suspected it was for the sake of a council of war that I was wanted, and I told Colonel and Mrs. Selwyn what I had done, saw old Bridges, and both thought it was an excellent move. The poor Colonel was especially anxious to get rid of Lavie, for that fellow used to come in by the most convenient door of my bungalow which happened to suit him, at any time of the day he wanted to see me, and as he used to come some nine or ten times a day, the Colonel was twice nearly caught, in one of my spare rooms, fucking Mrs. Soubratie, and for a week or more he had been entirely without his accustomed greens, and as he never knew when Lavie might perhaps find him partaking of them between Mrs. Soubratie's brown thighs, the Colonel, also, naturally, wanted to put an end to the courtship, which was ridiculous and scandalous, so he determined to see Dr. Bridges himself, and insist on Lavie being sent away.<break time="100ms" />After dinner we all walked up and down the fine avenue, in the cool evening air, and with the sky lit up by a myriad of lovely stars.<break time="100ms" />We talked of nothing but Lavie, until Mrs. Selwyn, get ting tired, took the Colonel in, leaving Fanny, Amy, Mabel and me walking together. Amy got rid of Mabel and I would have been as glad as Fanny if we could have equally got rid of Amy too. Our conversation naturally fell on love and matrimony, and Amy said, “Well! I only hope nobody will ever ask me to marry them. I will surely say no!”<break time="100ms" />“Why?” said I, laughing.<break time="100ms" />“Oh! Fancy going to bed with a man! I should die of shame!”<break time="100ms" />“Your mother goes to bed every night with your father, Amy, and she does not die of shame.”<break time="100ms" />“Oh! that's different!”
    </voice>
</speak>
