<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />It was a tough job. Amy's maidenhead was thrice as strong as Fanny's, and much more unyielding than” the majority of those it has been my excellent good fortune” to take. And I did not feel tender minded toward her. I am afraid I was more rough than I should have been but oh! Had she not deceived me and robbed her sister? So without mercy I went on plunging and plunging, ruthlessly grinding and tearing my way up, until that really sweet little cunt was filled, and stretched, to the uttermost, and my balls rattled against her bottom, just at the exact spot where the Afghan's had first had that pre-eminent happiness.<break time="100ms" />But Amy, though she said I hurt her dreadfully forcing my prick in so roughly, was by nature voluptuous like Fanny. Her “Ah! Now that's nice. Ah! Do that again. Oh my! Oh! Captain Devereaux! How you tickle!” told me that fuck, and, my temper having been satisfied by my first burst of anger, I fucked her as sweetly as I could, and was rewarded by her spending copiously, and ravishingly, at the exact moment that I inundated her cunt with the first boiling torrent which had ever been poured by man into it.<break time="100ms" />Sugdaya stood by, holding the lamp, and watching, with keen and voluptuous interest, the real combat' between my prick and Amy's cunt, and when she perceived by the cessation of my movements, and the way in which Amy was holding her breath, that I was inundating the shrine, she gave vent to the prolonged “oh-h-h-h!” as though she envied the girl who was getting such delight.<break time="100ms" />“Now! Miss Amy Baba! Now! You have been well fucked!” cried she. “Yes. I suppose I have,” said Amy, in a kind of dreamy manner, usual with her when her thoughts were much occupied; then waking up as if from a trance, she clasped me tight, and gave me kiss after kiss.<break time="100ms" />“Ah! that is all very well, Amy,” I said, “but I have a bone to pick with Sugdaya and you. A very nice pair you are. Do you know what you have done?”<break time="100ms" />“Yes, dear,” said Amy, laughing, and closing her legs over me, for I had commenced to withdraw my prick from her strongly palpitating cunt, “I do. I laid a very neat trap and caught a very splendid bird, and I have him now in my cage.”<break time="100ms" />“It's all very well, Amy. You have won this round—but oh!” and I felt my voice quiver with the anguish I really felt, “you do not know what you have done! Here! Let me go!”<break time="100ms" />“No, indeed,” said Amy, folding me tighter and tighter, and forcing her cunt about my prick, which had been half pulled out of it. “No! I won't let you go. You are my property now, Captain Devereaux. I have fairly caught you—to think of letting you go yet! Oh dear no! You will have to fuck me now as often as you have fucked Fanny. And as she has had you ever since last March, you will have to pay me a good deal of attention, before I shall be even with Fanny.”<break time="100ms" />“Oh Amy!” I cried, bitterly, for I assure you, dear reader, much as I love fucking, and well worth fucking as Amy was, and still is, I felt that I had been betrayed, quite and perfectly innocent indeed, doing what I now had done, would come nigh to breaking Fanny's heart. Now I loved Fanny. I was passionately devoted to her, and not for all the cunts in the world did I feel inclined to outrage her by fucking her sister, before her own sweet cunt could be said to have ceased throbbing from the very recent fucking it had had from my prick. I did not desire Amy. The stand I had, when I got into bed with her, was not for her cunt, nice as it was, but for Fanny. But oh! Amy! I'll tell you what you have done! You have broken poor Fanny's heart!<break time="100ms" />“Pooh! ha! ha! ha!” laughed Amy. “What do I care? Broken her heart indeed. Oh ! Poor Fanny! Much I pity her! What more right has she to you, I should like to know, than I have, or Mabel? She is not your wife. But to hear her talk, and to hear you, too, Captain Devereaux, one would think there was no Lome in the world. I tell you I have every bit as much right to you as Fanny has, and mind, if you refuse to fuck me, you will never fuck her again. I can tell you!”<break time="100ms" />This thrust I felt was no empty one. Amy had once said she could not imagine herself going to bed with a man, and that for herself to be stark naked in the presence of a stark naked man would be something too horrible to contemplate! Here she was, however, stark naked in my stark naked arms, and the will to fuck was all on her side, not mine. It was plain all her former ideas had become completely changed; and her whole tone and manner was that of a strong-minded woman, who knew what she was about, and that she could compel, if she could not gain her ends by any more gentle way. Unfortunately it lay in her power to put an end to the delicious liaison between Fanny and me. I lay quietly in her arms, thinking how I should escape this terrible dilemma.<break time="100ms" />“How do you know that I fuck Fanny, Amy?”<break time="100ms" />“How do I know? Now, Captain Devereaux! Do you take me for a complete fool? Do you think that Fanny could leave this room, with me sleeping in it, night after night, without my knowing it sooner or later? Do you think I cannot put two and two together as well as yourself? Why! I have known it these five months at least. I taxed Fanny with it, and she could not deny it, and she told me herself, too, about how you fucked her twice, that evening of her birthday, when she and you left us playing cards. Well! I don't care! I thought her a fool for her pains, but by degrees I began to think it must be as nice as Sugdaya has always told me it was to be fucked, and the moment I heard that Fanny was to go to Rampur with Papa, I laid a plan with Sugdaya to catch you! Ah! now, my boy! You wanted me to go to Rampur, but here I am. You wanted Fanny's cunt, did you? Well! Now you are in mine, and I think mine must be every bit as nice as Fanny's. I have better and bigger breasts, too, and more hair than she has, and J don't think you have any :reason to complain of Fanny either.”<break time="100ms" />I saw it was no use trying to urge a higher tone with Amy. It was of no use talking to her of love. Fucking was all she could see in my intimacy with Fanny, nothing nobler.<break time="100ms" />“So you see, my dear Captain Devereaux, you will now have two wives in India, and one at home, perhaps three wives in India, because Mabel, I know, wants to be fucked too and you will have to do it.”<break time="100ms" />“I will not!” I cried passionately and angrily.<break time="100ms" />“Oh I dear, yes you will. The thing is in a. nutshell.<break time="100ms" />Do you really love Fanny? Are you really so fond of her as you say?”<break time="100ms" />“Oh, Amy! You don't know how fond.”<break time="100ms" />“Very well! Then I suppose you would be awfully sorry if anything happened to prevent you fucking her again.”<break time="100ms" />“Don't speak of it!”<break time="100ms" />“Oh! but I will. I have only some night to pretend to be ill, call Papa and let him see Fanny's bed empty, and Sugdaya not to be found in the house, and I think Fanny will never see your prick again, Captain Devereaux.”<break time="100ms" />I groaned.
    </voice>
</speak>
