<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />“Because I expect, when Fanny hears the news, she will go into one of her dreadful states of excitement and do or say something rash before your father; and, if he hears of what has happened he will certainly take steps to prevent any more of my fucking his daughters. He could, for instance, as easily get me sent to another station as I could get Lavie sent to Benares. Nobody need know why, but you and Fanny would have to find another beau, if fucking is all either of you wish for.”<break time="100ms" />This speech made Amy thoughtful. She had entirely lost sight of the possible effects a too brilliant triumph over Fanny might have.<break time="100ms" />“That is worth thinking about, Captain Devereaux.”<break time="100ms" />“It is, Amy, in all solemn earnest. Now will you do me a favor?”<break time="100ms" />“What is it?”<break time="100ms" />“Will you give this note to Fanny for me?”<break time="100ms" />“What have you said in it?”<break time="100ms" />“All I have said is to ask her not to come over to me to-night.”<break time="100ms" />“Have you told her what has happened?”<break time="100ms" />“No!”<break time="100ms" />Amy walked in silence, evidently thinking what she should do. I imagine she had intended to crow vigorously over Fanny, but my warning had made her begin to reconsider this. As we walked we approached the stable, and Amy, who had been twisting my note to Fanny between her fingers suddenly looked up.<break time="100ms" />“Oh! Here we are at the stable,” said she.<break time="100ms" />“Yes,” said I, reading her thoughts, “but, Amy, dear, I really could not do it now!”<break time="100ms" />“What nonsense!” she cried, reddening, “I never asked you either, but now, for saying that you shall.”<break time="100ms" />“I really can't, Amy.”<break time="100ms" />“Bosh! come, Captain Devereaux, I wish to be fucked now, this instant. It may be my last chance, if so much depends upon Fanny, as you seem to think. I will not throwaway a chance. Come into the stable at once and do what you are bid.”<break time="100ms" />“I will go into the stable, Amy, but you will see I speak nothing but the truth when I tell you that I am not able to fuck you now.”<break time="100ms" />I went in.<break time="100ms" />“Now,” said Amy, “explain yourself.”<break time="100ms" />“Here is the best explanation possible,” said I, undoing my braces and letting down my trousers, “look, and see if you can get that into your cunt, Amy.”<break time="100ms" />Amy raised my shirt and saw me in a state that she had never contemplated as possible. My prick hung dead and nerveless, my balls were loose in an elongated and relaxed bag, everything denoted the most marked fatigue.<break time="100ms" />“You are, foxing!” cried Amy angrily, stamping her foot. “Make it stiff at once! Do you hear me! Ah! Do! Captain Devereaux!” she continued in an imploring tone of voice. “Don't be so unkind to me.”<break time="100ms" />I heard her with a mixed sentiment of amusement and pain.<break time="100ms" />I was amused at her thinking I was my prick's master and able to make it stand or not, at my pleasure, and pained that I was really unable to comply with her wishes and fuck her, for I felt if I could gratify her now she would be in good humor, and more inclined to spare Fanny, and so soften down the announcement of her triumph.<break time="100ms" />“Amy dear! I would if I could. But the want or sleep and the painful anxiety about Fanny that I have been under all day, have killed me; but try if you can make it stiff yourself! I really am not foxing. I should very much like to fuck you, if I could. Here. Let us lie down in this grass, and while you try what you can do with your hands, I will feel your nice, soft cunt.” .<break time="100ms" />We lay down. Amy cuddled up to me, looking at times into my face with a keen glance as if to see whether I was deceiving her or not, whilst she handled my prick and my balls, in the most voluptuously exciting manner possible. It was of no use whatever I was in a state of mental and bodily prostration, and my prick remained as limp as ever, though my balls gradually grew up in a tighter bunch than they had been in before Amy's gentle fingers titillated them.<break time="100ms" />After about ten minutes of these mutual caresses I with drew my hand, wet with her frequent spendings, from between Amy's lovely thighs, and said:<break time="100ms" />“I am afraid we must give up the idea of it, Amy. My prick is too dead. Too tired.”<break time="100ms" />“Too obstinate and too abominably selfish, you mean,” said Amy in great anger, “take that for the sulky beast you are,” and with these words addressed to my prick, she suddenly gave it a stinging slap with her hand, not only hurting it considerably, but making my poor balls throb with pain.<break time="100ms" />“Oh, Amy! Oh, 'my! You have hurt me.”<break time="100ms" />Now if a woman has a tender place in her heart for any thing in this world, she has for a man's prick and balls. Let my readers think for a second, and I think nearly all must recollect instances where women of their acquaintances have heard with apparent indifference of men being mutilated in any particular, but have shown the very greatest sympathy and have shuddered when they have been told of the mutilation of prick or bans, or both. Amy was no exception.<break time="100ms" />“Oh! Captain Devereaux! I really did not mean to hurt it so much. Oh, poor thing, poor thing. She hung over me, as I had turned on to my face, for I had some extremely sharp pains in my groin, and a dull heavy pain at the lower part of my belly. I felt Amy's hand groping along my right groin, and at first I resisted a little, but a sharp bit of grass happening to run into my prick, I made a sudden movement, which enabled her to get at what she wished to caress and soothe, but to my astonishment, for I had no sensation to ten me the fact, she cried out:<break time="100ms" />“Oh, Captain Devereaux! It's stiff. It's stiff. It's standing beautifully.”<break time="100ms" />The pain I had endured had been sharp enough, but it passed like a sudden twinge of toothache. Amy's exclamation seemed to drive it away and I could now feel that I had indeed a glorious stand. I felt so grateful to Amy that I turned and caught her in my arms and kissed her before I pushed her on her back, and got between those beautiful rounded, snowy thighs, which she uncovered for me with immense haste and speed as though she feared the stiffness of my prick might go as suddenly as it had come.<break time="100ms" />It was a lovely fuck! A completely glorious luck! and at the end, whilst I was still lying with my motte hard pressed to her which leaped and jumped, and whilst I still enjoying the throbbing and squeezing, and cuking of her deliciously excited and melting little cunt, I could. not help saying:<break time="100ms" />“Oh, Amy, try and reconcile Fanny and we will have many another like this.
    </voice>
</speak>
