<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I remember that awakening very vividly. It was bright daylight. The window was open, as well as the door of the room, and the sweet cool air blew gently in upon me in the most refreshing manner, sometimes mingled with a loud laugh, came rolling up from the hillside from the busy bazaar. The twelve fine young whores had arrived, and I dare say I heard the happy laughter of some of the Tommies waiting anxiously for their turn for a jolly good fuck. I heard of this event from my young friend Crean, who told me later that Jumali was really an Al poke, and a splendid and very pretty woman. In fact, Jumali was the favorite of all those useful and graceful women. It was she who I afterwards heard at Peshawar had always commenced the night with the Colonel to be followed by three or four of the other fresh and plump ones. Ah! that “inspection” cost the Colonel dear, and might have cost him more than it did. Poor Amy! Poor Amy!<break time="100ms" />Well, then, I woke up, and at first wondered where I could be but my arm in a sling, and a feeling of painful stiff” ness all over me, quickly recalled my wandering memory. There was some one in my room. I could hear him or her gently stirring on the chair, but I could not see who it was. I called out in a weak voice, “Is anyone there?”<break time="100ms" />“Oh! Captain Devereaux! Are you all right then? Do you know me?” cried the sprightly Fanny, who came swiftly and smiling to my bedside, looking as fresh as a rose and as neat as usual, for Fanny was a very tidy girl at all times.<break time="100ms" />“Know you!” I cried in surprise, “of course I know you, Fanny dear!”<break time="100ms" />“Mama! Mama! Papa! Come! Captain Devereaux is not silly now! Come! Come!” she cried, running out of the bed room.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Selwyn soon came as fast as her weakness would permit her, for the deadly narcotic which had been administered to her had made her exceedingly ill, and this was the first day she had left her bed since the events which I have, I fear, so feebly described, took place. At first she could not speak from emotion. The tears rose to her eyes and sought along the lashes a place to roll forth, which at last they did. She took my unbound hand in both of hers and pressed it, and at length finding her voice, said, with much emotion and very slowly, “Oh! Captain Devereaux! Captain Devereaux! What do we not owe you ?”<break time="100ms" />“Nothing at all, dear Mrs. Selwyn.”<break time="100ms" />“Nothing! Oh no! We owe you everything, the lives and honor of our girls! We can never repay you!” and without another word she bent down and kissed me, letting her tears fall upon my cheeks.<break time="100ms" />I could not but feel moved. Fanny stood by looking on with a mixture of amusement and apprehension on her face, very comical. She was evidently amused at her mother kissing me, but why she should be apprehensive I could not tell. At all events she said nervously, “He does not call me Louie now, Mama!”<break time="100ms" />“Why! Did I call you that?” said I.<break time="100ms" />“Oh yes! You seemed to think I was your wife! You would insist that I should come to bed! You said you wanted me very badly, and I do not know what other rubbish.” Mrs. Selwyn looked at Fanny and then at me.<break time="100ms" />“Well! Fanny! That shows that Captain Devereaux loves his wife and that his only thoughts were on her when he was delirious!”<break time="100ms" />“Was I delirious?” I asked in amazement.<break time="100ms" />“I should think you were,” said Fanny, bursting into almost uncontrollable laughter. “The things you said to me! You would have it I was your wife!”<break time="100ms" />“Ah me!” said Mrs. Selwyn, “I never saw your wife Captain Devereaux, but I never in my life wished a man to be a married man as I wished you were not!”<break time="100ms" />“Because then he would marry me!” laughed Fanny.<break time="100ms" />There was a little awkward pause which I ended by saying, “And I should have got a good and very lovely wife in that case, Fanny!”<break time="100ms" />Fanny blushed and looked more than pleased. Her eyes assumed that look which at times gave them the appearance of speaking love and affection.<break time="100ms" />“Ah now!” said I, laughing, “if I were only a Mohammedan and you another, Fanny, I could marry you now I But you see we have the misfortune to be Christians.”<break time="100ms" />“Worse luck,” said Fanny with a sigh.<break time="100ms" />“Well!” said Mrs. Selwyn, “I can only say if it could be a pleasure to a mother to give her daughter to a man, it would have indeed been a pleasure to me to give Fanny to you, Captain Devereaux, for you have deserved her.”<break time="100ms" />“And who can tell,” said Fanny, innocently and quite unconscious of the sense of her words, “why he may not have me yet!”<break time="100ms" />I thought of that sweet, little cunt I had seen so much of and a feeble ripple stirred my prick. This latter sensation astonished me, for it suddenly flashed on me that I was desperately weak. Whenever the thought of fucking a girl had got into my mind before, it was always accompanied by a vigorous stand, but though Fanny's sweet naked charms floated before me, strengthened by her presence, clad though it was in the flesh, only a ripple passed. along that hitherto noble weapon. I had never known what it was before to doubt of my power, and the shock I sustained was far greater than I can hope to make my readers understand.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Selwyn noticed the change in me and said, “Come, Fanny! Get Captain Devereaux's beef tea, I can see he is tired. We have been talking too much to him and Dr. Lavie will be mad with us if he finds it out”<break time="100ms" />The Colonel here entered the room. He looked the picture of misery and woe. His conscience smote him. He knew that the young man lying prostrate and unable to move before him on his daughter's bed was in that condition owing to his “lust.” Poor man! He knew that a number of innocent persons had gone to their doom for the same cause, and that his wife and one daughter were still ill from effects springing from the same cause. I took his grieved appearance to be simply that of sympathy, but as he wrung my hand, he said quietly to me, “Devereaux, I owe all to you, and you owe all to me!”<break time="100ms" />“How, Colonel?”<break time="100ms" />“I owe you the honor and lives of my girls—and—I ought never to have gone to Peshawar!” and he drew his hand across his eyes and groaned heavily.<break time="100ms" />Presently he added, “Lavie tells me it will be some little time before you are strong enough to do duty, and that he would like to see you in your own quarters which are nearer to him, but he allows that you will be better in a house where you can be nursed and looked after, so you will remain here till you are quite well and strong again.”<break time="100ms" />“Thanks very much, Colonel. I hope however I shall soon be all right. How is Amy?” I added, “I have not seen her.”<break time="100ms" />“She is still in bed, poor girl!” said the Colonel. “The attack made on her had a very curious and I am sorry to say a serious effect. She had the recurrence of an ailment which attacked her as a baby.”
    </voice>
</speak>
