<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />But all of a sudden I felt something hard under my feet and, as if instantaneously, my leg tide round and round up to the knee, by a rope which tightened and tightened, until it caused me considerable pain. The thing was instantaneous.' I had no time for reflection, yet Providence made me halt as though shot, and prevented my raising my foot. Had I done so, Amy would never have been fucked by me, nor Fanny, nor would Mabel, Sugdaya, or Mrs. Paul—but halt! I must not tell all my secrets out at once. Well, I never would have fucked again in the world. For I had trodden, as good luck would have it, on the head of a very large cobra. I say by good luck, for had I trodden on it on any other part I should have been inevitably bitten, and in a couple of hours, or three at most, I should have been a dead man. With intense fright and that ungovernable rage which ensues, I ground that unlucky serpent's head until it was nothing but pulp, and then, and not till then, did I attempt to remove it from my leg, which, even in death, it grasped as though it were a vise. Covered with a cold perspiration and trembling with excitement due to shock, and not denying the fright I had received, I ran to my bungalow and right glad was I when I got well within its safe walls, and there I examined the reptile which had so miserably perished, because it had so foolishly crossed my path, but which might have put an end to me as easily as I had done to it but for the upholding hand of a merciful providence.<break time="100ms" />Sleep was out of the question for a long time, and it was broad daylight before its refreshing hand touched me. My thoughts ran on Fanny and the awful risks she had run twice almost every night, since she had been in the habit of coming over to my bungalow to be fucked by me. She must never do so again. How lucky it really was that Amy had entrapped me. There would be no reason why I should not go myself now every night to the Colonel's bungalow, Amy would not be in the way! I should fuck Fanny and her, turn and turn about, and there would be no danger to either of them from snakes. It is true I should have to make my peace with Fanny, but I had no doubt, at that moment, of being able to do so. Meanwhile I must warn Amy, who would run risks just as great, going to her father's bungalow from the Corbetts to be fucked.<break time="100ms" />It was late, about five o'clock in the afternoon, before I went over to the Corbetts to see Amy, and Mrs. Corbett after a cordial reception of me, told me in the presence of Amy that I must really scold that young lady, as she had been extraordinarily lazy, not having got out of bed until nearly four o'clock. Amy, who blushed a little, excused herself on the ground that she never could sleep for the first few nights in a strange bed, upon which, Mrs. Corbett, looking significantly at me, said that her husband would be delighted to find that this was the case, as men loved to talk a good deal to their wives in bed, especially when they were first married. We all laughed. Amy took the chaff very well and rather astonished Mrs. Corbett by her aplomb. After some more conversation, I proposed a stroll around the garden to see Mrs. Corbett's vines, and as that lady wished to continue a novel she was reading, she did not volunteer to go herself .<break time="100ms" />“Oh! Captain Devereaux!” said Amy when we were alone, “I can hardly walk. You stretched the joints of my thighs last night to such an extent and I feel so stiff and regularly ground about the lower part of my body.”<break time="100ms" />“Does your cunt feel sore today, dear?”<break time="100ms" />“No! not at all! Oh! how you did hurt me the first time!<break time="100ms" />And how delicious it was every time after that! I do so wish it was ten o'clock. Mind, don't keep me waiting. You won't do that, now, will you, Captain Devereaux”<break time="100ms" />I told Amy that I was not in the least attempting to evade my promise, but that I really thought that this walk in the night extremely dangerous on account of snakes. At first she indignantly refused to believe that I had trodden on one, saying it was very curious that Fanny should have never even seen or heard of one, and that she believed it was a trumped up story, and that the truth was I wanted to get out of fucking her.<break time="100ms" />“But if I have to come to you, I will, Captain Devereaux I<break time="100ms" />You don't know how angry I am with you for never having offered to fuck me, all these months. What do you see finer in Fanny than in me, I should like to know! I know I consider myself better than she is in every way. Now tell me, you have fucked me, am I not as nice as Fanny? Has she a sweeter or nicer cunt than I have? I have better bubbies I know.”<break time="100ms" />Ah! Amy dear, don't talk that way! If I could come and fuck you in Mrs. Corbett's house, I would. But I really am alarmed at your having to walk at night to your own house to meet me.”<break time="100ms" />“Then I'll come to yours if you prefer it.”<break time="100ms" />“That is just as dangerous—more so, in fact. My compound has a bad name for snakes, as you know.”<break time="100ms" />“A very proper place for you, Captain Devereaux! I call you nothing more or less than a deceitful serpent.”<break time="100ms" />No, she would risk everything. She did not believe in the cobra, and she was determined that I should fuck her every night. She threatened to send Mabel to me as soon as I got home, if I did not stop at once all reference to danger.<break time="100ms" />“Amy, do you think I have an objection to fucking you? Do you think I would rather not—or that I don't think you worth it?”<break time="100ms" />“Something like that idea comes into my head I must say!”<break time="100ms" />There was a stable in which was a lot of grass freshly cut for the Padre's horses. I took Amy in and looking around that there was no one watching us, laid' her on the grass. She laughed and clapped her hands and then, undoing my braces and trousers, I turned up her petticoats and had a truly delicious fuck. Amy went almost mad with pleasure, and when it was all over, she let me do the glove stretcher to her cunt, to let out the dangerous spend, and when I had wiped her between the thighs with my pocket handkerchief, she kissed me most sweetly, saying she saw now I had no personal objection to her and that I was really not a bad fellow.<break time="100ms" />“A personal objection, Amy,” said I, buttoning my prick and balls away out of sight, “why you know I think you a splendid girl, and well worth going thousands of miles for to get at, but you must remember that Fanny is almost' a wife to me, and I never had the slightest intention of being unfaithful to her.”<break time="100ms" />“Then the sooner you see things in the proper light the better for you, Captain Devereaux! Fanny is not your wife. You have no business to love her. For the matter of that you have no more business to fuck her than to fuck me, but as you have chosen to d9 that, and Fanny thinks it nice, I choose that you should fuck me also, for; to tell you the truth, I think it something more than nice. It's simply rapturous! Oh! don't be a stupid man! Now, are not two cunts better than one?”<break time="100ms" />I laughed. I could not help it.
    </voice>
</speak>
