<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I saw Fanny and her mother half way home, and the way Fanny pressed the moist palm of her hand in mine sent a thrill through both of us, and I could see that she had quite made up her mind to have me at the earliest opportunity. By God! How my balls and groins did ache all that day. Willingly would I tell my readers the ins and outs of the courtship, as performed by Lavie, which filled up the next fortnight, but I fear to be tedious. Never was there a more terrible lover than he. I did not act upon Mrs. Selwyn's request. I thought it best to let Lavie hang himself, and he did so most effectually. He had one or two interviews with Fanny, and stood like a dumb calf, open mouthed and gasping, but utterly unable to formulate a word. Both she and her mother were nearly driven distracted by the poor cunt struck fool, and the last scene, in which Lavie having been refused admittance by Fanny, had insisted on seeing Mrs. Selwyn, and in weeping and wailing before her, because she would not order Fanny to marry him, drove both ladies once more to my bungalow.<break time="100ms" />It was in the middle of March, the sun was simply blazing through the day, the crows, fowls, all birds in fact, went about in the shade with their beaks wide open, and wings lifted from their bodies, so much did they feel the blasting heat at this time. I was seated in my long arm chair, dressed only in the thinnest of jerseys, without sleeves, and the slightest of pajamas, in fact, as naked as I could well be, for the clothes I had on hid only the color of my skin, and even that very imperfectly. The Punkah slowly swinging from side to side, poured down a breeze of cooling air upon me, and wafted away the smoke of my cheroot. It was midday, frightfully hot, and I could hear the leaves of the trees crackling under the sun's rays, when to my in tense astonishment, Mrs. Selwyn and Fanny rushed rather than walked into my room.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Selwyn seemed half demented. Fanny looked as if she had been crying and fearfully annoyed. Both looked reproachfully at me. I jumped up, apologized for my state of dishabille, for I had not even slippers on, and was in my bare feet, and I got them chairs under the punkah. But before she attempted to sit down, Mrs. Selwyn cried, “Captain Devereaux, you must, you really must, insist on Dr. Lavie ceasing to annoy us any more! He is killing me! He is mad! I am certain he is not right in his mind! He is killing Fanny too! Oh!” and down she flopped into her chair.<break time="100ms" />I looked at Fanny but said nothing. Mrs. Selwyn then told me that Lavie had taken to going at all hours, even at night when everyone had gone to bed, and that he moaned and raved and wept. That Colonel Selwyn had spoken to him kindly, harshly, every way, had ordered him never to come again, and so forth, but it had no effect, and they were at their wits ends, because they feared if they took any other, that is, forcible means, and kept him out of the house, it would only create a scandal, and the people were dying with laughter over Lavie's miserable courtship.<break time="100ms" />Whilst she was telling me this, and I was wondering what I could do, in came Lavie, his eyes glaring, his face pale, his lips hard set. He went straight up to Mrs. Selwyn and asked her to go into another room which I had and which was empty.<break time="100ms" />I begged him to sit down where he was, but he smiled inanely at me, and said he would not keep Mrs. Selwyn two seconds, and she weakly rose and followed him. Fanny drew her chair near mine and begged me to do what I could.<break time="100ms" />“Oh! dear, dear, Captain Devereaux, do rid us of this monster!” was her cry. I took her hand and assured her that I would; that I had a plan, and that was to get him sent to some other station. I knew the P. M. O. very well indeed, and I would represent the case to him. Poor Fanny was delighted. She gave me one of those looks which meant “kiss me!” I hesitated a moment, but at last I could resist no longer. Jumping up I seized the willing girl round the waist, lifted her to her feet, and pressing her to me I kissed her red, red mouth, over and over again.<break time="100ms" />“Oh! my darling Fanny!” I exclaimed in a low tone, quivering with passion that communicated itself to her. “How I do blame myself for having countenanced that idiot's making love to you!”<break time="100ms" />“Oh! Charlie! Charlie!” she cried, pressing her swelling bosom to mine, and letting me pull her to me until our bodies seemed to form one, not denying me the thigh I took between mine, nor the motte, the sweet, delicious motte, against which I pressed my own thigh, “I know now that you love me as I love you! Oh I my darling! darling! so I forgive you! But oh! if it were not for that I would hate you!”<break time="100ms" />“And do you really and truly love me, Fanny? Oh! My sweetest, own girl, and you must be all mine! Every bit of you! heart, soul, body, all!”<break time="100ms" />“Oh! I do! I do!” cried the excited girl in an ecstasy of passion. “Oh! can you not feel that I do?”<break time="100ms" />“With your heart, my own love!” and I pressed a delicious and firm, round, hard, elastic bubby in my hand.<break time="100ms" />“Yes! Yes!”<break time="100ms" />“On your soul?” and I glided a hand swiftly between her thighs and pressed the equally elastic and soft motte, and delicious cunt with my fingers. For a moment Fanny drew . her hips back, but on my again pressing her matte and throbbing cunt with my hands, closing her thighs also on it, and giving me such a kiss as I had never yet had from her. That was, her answer. Gods! Gods! I took my hand away. I put my arms round her yielding waist. My prick furious, mad, raging to get at her, mane a perfect tent pole, and stood out my pajamas in front of it. But for the pajamas it would have risen at a bound to an angle much too acute with my body to have enabled me to do what I did, but the pajamas held it's head somewhat down, and I pressed the mighty weapon against Fanny's quivering matte with all my force, whilst I kissed her and felt her tumultuous bubbies, which she was pressing against my bosom as though she was trying to flatten them against it. For a moment we stood thus, only that I kept, as it were unconsciously, thrusting at her astonished matte. Then suddenly putting down her hand she said, “Oh!” what is that pressing against me?”<break time="100ms" />“It is me, my darling!” I whispered in a voice hardly audible or articulate from the excess of passionate emotions, “it is me!” There, take me in your dear. hand “and take possession of the treasure which is yours henceforth and yours only.”<break time="100ms" />(Poor Louie! Had she heard those words spoken in a moment of blinding passion!)<break time="100ms" />“Oh! my darling! My darling!” exclaimed Fanny absolutely beside herself with ecstasy. “My darling! my darling!” and her little hand nervously and excitedly kept clasping my burning prick, as if she hardly knew what to say or do, but in delight inexpressible.<break time="100ms" />“Yes! Yes! Darling Fanny! That is for you' For this! It must be admitted to this above! To the temple of love!” I again had my hand once more excitedly caressing her now maddened cunt, between thighs more than willingly opened to admit it!
    </voice>
</speak>
