<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />When on our downy bed we fondly lay,<break time="100ms" />Heating each other by our am'rous play;<break time="100ms" />Till Nature, yielding to the luscious game,<break time="100ms" />Would fierce desire and quenchless lust inflame!<break time="100ms" />Oh! then we join'd in love's most warm embrace,<break time="100ms" />And pressed soft kisses on our every grace!<break time="100ms" />Around my form his pliant limbs entwined,<break time="100ms" />Love's seat of bliss to him I then resigned!<break time="100ms" />We pant, we throb, we both convulsive start!<break time="100ms" />Heavens! then what passions thro' our fibres dart!<break time="100ms" />We heave, we wriggle, bite, laugh, tremble, sigh!<break time="100ms" />We taste Elysian bliss—we fondle—die.<break time="100ms" />An English and an American vessel of war being in port together, Captain Balls, of the former, invited the officers of the Yankee frigate to dine in board of his ship, but stipulated, in order to avoid any unpleasantness, that no offensive or personal toasts should be proposed, to which the Americans cheerfully assented. However, after dinner, during dessert, when the conversation happened to turn warmly upon the respective merits of the two nations, a Yankee officer suddenly stood up, and said he wished to propose a toast, which he should take as a personal offense if anyone refused to drink it.<break time="100ms" />Captain B. mildly expressed a hope that it was nothing offensive, but consented to drink to whatever it might be, with the proviso that, if he thought fit to do so, he should propose another afterwards.<break time="100ms" />Then shouted the American, exultingly: "Here's to the glorious American flag: Stars to enlighten all nations, and Stripes to flog them."<break time="100ms" />Captain B. drained a bumper to the American's toast; then turning to the old ship's steward, standing behind his chair, said quietly: "You can beat that, can't you, Jack?"<break time="100ms" />"Ay! Aye! Sir! If you fill me a stiff'un."<break time="100ms" />The Captain mixed him a good swig of hot and strong. Then handing the steward the glass, he thundered out: "Silence for Jack's toast, and any gentleman here present, refusing to drink to it, I shall not take it as a personal offense, but at once order the gunner's mate to give him three dozen. Now then, Jack."<break time="100ms" />Jack, with a grim smile, and bowing to the Yankee officer, said: "Then here's to the ramping, roaring British Lion, who pisses on the stars, and wipes his arse on the stripes."<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Bombay,<break time="100ms" />Who fashioned a cunt out of clay;<break time="100ms" />But the heat of his prick<break time="100ms" />Turned it into a brick,<break time="100ms" />And chafed all his foreskin away.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Peru,<break time="100ms" />Who had nothing whatever to do;<break time="100ms" />So he took out his carrot<break time="100ms" />And buggered his parrot,<break time="100ms" />And sent the result to the Zoo.<break time="100ms" />There was a young girl of Ostend,<break time="100ms" />Who her maidenhead tried to defend,<break time="100ms" />But a Chasseur d'Afrique<break time="100ms" />Inserted his prick,<break time="100ms" />And taught that ex-maid how to spend.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Calcutta,<break time="100ms" />Who tried to write "Cunt" on a shutter.<break time="100ms" />When he got to C-U,<break time="100ms" />A pious Hindoo<break time="100ms" />Knocked him arse over head in the gutter.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Ostend,<break time="100ms" />Whose wife caught him fucking her friend;<break time="100ms" />"It's no use, my duck,<break time="100ms" />Interrupting our fuck,<break time="100ms" />For I'm damned if I draw till I spend."<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Wood Green,<break time="100ms" />Who tried to fart "God Save the Queen."<break time="100ms" />When he reached the soprano,<break time="100ms" />He shot his guano,<break time="100ms" />And his breeches weren't fit to be seen.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Dundee,<break time="100ms" />Who one night went out on the spree;<break time="100ms" />He wound up his clock<break time="100ms" />With the tip of his cock,<break time="100ms" />And buggered himself with the key.<break time="100ms" />There was a young lady of Troy,<break time="100ms" />Who invented a new kind of joy:<break time="100ms" />She sugared her thing<break time="100ms" />Both outside and in,<break time="100ms" />And then had it sucked by a boy.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Santander,<break time="100ms" />Who tried hard to bugger a gander;<break time="100ms" />But the virtuous bird<break time="100ms" />Plugged his arse with a turd,<break time="100ms" />And refused to such low tastes to pander.<break time="100ms" />There was a young lady of Hitchin,<break time="100ms" />Who was skrotching her cunt in the kitchen;<break time="100ms" />Her father said "Rose,<break time="100ms" />It's the crabs, I suppose."<break time="100ms" />"You're right, pa, the buggers are itching."<break time="100ms" />There was an old person of Sark,<break time="100ms" />Who buggered a pig in the dark;<break time="100ms" />The swine, in surprise,<break time="100ms" />Murmured "God blast your eyes,<break time="100ms" />Do you take me for Boulton or Park?"<break time="100ms" />Oh! cunt is a kingdom, and prick is its lord;<break time="100ms" />A whore is a slave, and her mistress a bawd;<break time="100ms" />Her quim is her freehold, which brings in her rent;<break time="100ms" />Where you pay when you enter, and leave when you've spent.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
