<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The butler's excuses and pleading of fear, in case he was missed, andc., were all of no avail; she fairly drove him on, and he was soon as furiously excited as herself, and with a profusion of sighs, expressions of pleasure, endearment, andc., they soon died away again into a state of short voluptuous oblivion. However, Mr. William was too nervous and afraid to let her lay long; he withdrew his instrument from her foaming cunny, just as it was all slimy and glistening with the mingled juices of their love; but what a contrast to its former state, as Alice now beheld it much reduced in size, and already drooping its fiery head.<break time="100ms" />Lucy jumped up and let down her clothes, but kneeling on the floor before her lover, she took hold of his limp affair, and gave it a most luscious sucking, to the great delight of Mr. William, whose face flushed again with pleasure, and as soon as Lucy had done with her sucking kiss, Alice saw that his instrument was again stiff and ready for a renewal of their joys.<break time="100ms" />LUCY, laughing in a low tone.—"There, my boy, I'll leave you like that; think of me till to-morrow; I couldn't help giving the darling a good suck after the exquisite pleasure he had afforded me, it's like being in heaven for a little while."<break time="100ms" />With a last kiss on the lips as they parted, and Mr. William again locked his door, whilst Alice made good her retreat to prepare herself for breakfast.<break time="100ms" />It was a fine warm morning in May, and soon after breakfast Alice, with William for her guardian, set off for a ramble in the park, her blood was in a boil, and she longed to experience the joys she was sure Lucy had been surfeited with; they sauntered down to the lake, and she asked William to give her a row in the boat; he unlocked the boat-house, and handed her into a nice, broad, comfortable skiff, well furnished with soft seats and cushions.<break time="100ms" />"How nice to be here, in the shade," said Alice; "come into the boat, Willie, we will sit in it a little while, and you shall read to me before we have a row."<break time="100ms" />"Just as you please, Miss Alice," he replied, with unwonted deference, stepping into the boat, and sitting down in the stern sheets.<break time="100ms" />"Ah my head aches a little, let me recline it in your lap," said Alice, throwing off her hat, and stretching herself along on a cushion. "Why are you so precise this morning, Willie? You know I don't like to be called Miss, you can keep that for Lucy." Then noticing his confusion, "You may blush, sir, I could make you sink into your shoes if you only knew all I have seen between you and Miss Lucy."<break time="100ms" />Alice reclined her head in a languid manner on his lap, looking up and enjoying the confusion she had thrown him into; then designedly resting one hand on the lump which he seemed to have in his pocket, as if to support herself a little, she continued: "Do you think, Willie, I shall ever have as fine legs as Lucy? Don't you think I ought soon to have long dresses, sir! I'm getting quite bashful about showing my calves so much," The butler had hard work to recover his composure, the vivid recollection of the luscious episode with Lucy before breakfast was so fresh in his mind that Alice's allusions to her, and the soft girlish hand resting on his privates (even although he thought her as innocent as a lamb) raised an utter of desire in his feverish blood, which he tried to allay as much as possible, but little by little the unruly member began to swell, till he was sure she must feel it throb under her hand. With an effort he slightly shifted himself, so as to remove her hand lower down on to the thigh, as he answered as gravely as possible (feeling assured Alice could know nothing): "You're making game of me this morning. Don't you wish me to read, Alice?"<break time="100ms" />ALICE, excitedly, with an unusual flush on her face.—"You naughty man, you shall tell me what I want to know this time: How do babies come? What is the parsley bed, the nurses and doctors say they come out of? Is it not a curly lot of hair at the bottom of the woman's belly? I know that's what Lucy's got, and I've seen you kiss it, sir!"<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Spoke by Miss Bella de Lancy, on her retiring from the Stage to open a Fashionable Bawdy House.<break time="100ms" />(Written by S. Johnson, LL.D.)<break time="100ms" />When cunt first triumphed (as the learned suppose)<break time="100ms" />O'er failing pricks, Immortal Dildo rose,<break time="100ms" />From fucks unnumbered, still erect he drew,<break time="100ms" />Exhausted cunts, and then demanded new;<break time="100ms" />Dame Nature saw him spurn her bounded reign,<break time="100ms" />And panting pricks toiled after him in vain;<break time="100ms" />The laxest folds, the deepest depths he filled;<break time="100ms" />The juiciest drained; the toughest hymens drilled.<break time="100ms" />The fair lay gasping with distended limbs,<break time="100ms" />And unremitting cockstands stormed their quims.<break time="100ms" />Then Frigging came, instructed from the school,<break time="100ms" />And scorned the aid of India-rubber tool.<break time="100ms" />With restless finger, fired the dormant blood,<break time="100ms" />Till Clitoris rose, sly, peeping thro' her hood.<break time="100ms" />Gently was worked this titillating art,<break time="100ms" />It broke no hymen, and scarce stretched the part;<break time="100ms" />Yet lured its votaries to a sudden doom,<break time="100ms" />And stamped Consumption's flush on Beauty's bloom.<break time="100ms" />Sweet Gamahuche found softer ways to fame,<break time="100ms" />It asked not Dildo's art, nor Frigging's flame.<break time="100ms" />Tongue, not prick, now probes the central hole,<break time="100ms" />And mouth, not cunt, becomes prick's destined goal.<break time="100ms" />It always found a sympathetic friend;<break time="100ms" />And pleased limp pricks, and those who could not spend,<break time="100ms" />No tedious wait, for laboured stand, delays<break time="100ms" />The hot and pouting cunt, which tongue allays.<break time="100ms" />The taste was luscious, tho' the smell was strong;<break time="100ms" />The fuck was easy, and would last so long;<break time="100ms" />Til wearied tongues found gamahuching cloy,<break time="100ms" />And pricks, and cunts, grew callous to the joy.<break time="100ms" />Then dulled by frigging, by mock pricks enlarged,<break time="100ms" />Her noble duties Cunt but ill discharged.<break time="100ms" />Her nymphæ drooped, her devil's bite grew weak,<break time="100ms" />And twice two pricks might flounder in her creek;<break time="100ms" />Till all the edge was taken off the bliss,<break time="100ms" />And Cunt's sole occupation was to piss.<break time="100ms" />Forced from her former joys, with scoft and brunt,<break time="100ms" />She saw great Arsehole lay the ghost Cunt<break time="100ms" />Exulting buggers hailed the joyful day,<break time="100ms" />And piles and hœmerrids confirmed his sway.<break time="100ms" />But who lust's future fancies can explore,<break time="100ms" />And mark the whimsies that remain in store?<break time="100ms" />Perhaps it shall be deemed a lover's treat,<break time="100ms" />To suck the flowering quims of mares in heat;<break time="100ms" />Perhaps, where beauty held unequalled sway,
    </voice>
</speak>
