<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />George Stokes, the cheesemonger in Snowhill, had Dr. Cullen one night as a guest. Cullen did not fancy the cheese on the table, and said, "You do not know how to select cheese; let me go into the warehouse and pick one out." He did this, and the cheese he selected was delicious. Everyone declared it most excellent. "How did you pitch upon it, and in the dark, too?" said Stokes. "I'll tell you," said the Doctor. "I tried several, till I came to one which made my prick stand. This is it; a prime cheese smells exactly like a blooming, ripe, girl's cunt."<break time="100ms" />Nursery Rhymes.<break time="100ms" />There was a young lady of Gaza,<break time="100ms" />Who shaved her cunt clean with a razor;<break time="100ms" />The crabs in a lump<break time="100ms" />Made tracks to her rump,<break time="100ms" />Which proceeding did greatly amaze her<break time="100ms" />There was a young lass of Surat,<break time="100ms" />The cheeks of whose arse were so fat<break time="100ms" />That they had to be parted,<break time="100ms" />Whenever she farted,<break time="100ms" />And also whenever she shat.<break time="100ms" />There was an old priest of Siberia,<break time="100ms" />Who of fucking grew wearier and wearier;<break time="100ms" />So one night after prayers,<break time="100ms" />He bolted upstairs,<break time="100ms" />And buggered the Lady Superior.<break time="100ms" />There was an old man of Natal,<break time="100ms" />Who was lazily fucking a gal,<break time="100ms" />Says she, "You're a sluggard,"<break time="100ms" />Said he, "You be buggered,<break time="100ms" />I like to fuck slowly, and shall."<break time="100ms" />There was a young farmer of Nant;<break time="100ms" />Whose conduct was gay and gallant,<break time="100ms" />For he fucked all his dozens<break time="100ms" />Of nieces and cousins,<break time="100ms" />In addition, of course, to his aunt.<break time="100ms" />There was an old man of Tantivy,<break time="100ms" />Who followed his son to the privy,<break time="100ms" />He lifted the lid,<break time="100ms" />To see what he did,<break time="100ms" />And found that it smelt of Capivi.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of this Nation,<break time="100ms" />Who didn't much like fornication;<break time="100ms" />When asked, "Do you fuck?"<break time="100ms" />He said, "No, I suck<break time="100ms" />Women's quims, and I use Masturbation."<break time="100ms" />There was a young parson of Eltham,<break time="100ms" />Who seldom fucked whores, but oft felt 'em.<break time="100ms" />In the lanes he would linger,<break time="100ms" />And play at stick finger,<break time="100ms" />'Twas on the way home that he smelt 'em.<break time="100ms" />There was a young lady of Rheims,<break time="100ms" />Who was terribly plagued with wet dreams;<break time="100ms" />She saved up a dozen,<break time="100ms" />And sent to her cousin,<break time="100ms" />Who ate them and thought they were creams.<break time="100ms" />There was a gay parson of Tooting,<break time="100ms" />Whose roe he was frequently shooting;<break time="100ms" />Till he married a lass,<break time="100ms" />With a face like my arse,<break time="100ms" />And a cunt you could put a top-boot in.<break time="100ms" />A learned divine down at Buckingham,<break time="100ms" />Wrote a treatise on cunts and on fucking 'em;<break time="100ms" />A learned Parsee,<break time="100ms" />Taught him Gamahuchee,<break time="100ms" />So he added a chapter on sucking 'em.<break time="100ms" />Not the Thing.<break time="100ms" />Said Lady Macneill, to Sir John, eating ling,<break time="100ms" />I'm afraid. Sir, that fish a'nt exactly the thing<break time="100ms" />Why really, he answer'd, I do not dislike it,<break time="100ms" />It's not the thing, but it's mightily like it.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
