<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Frederick is in agony; his writhing and contortions seemed excruciating in the extreme, he fairly groaned out: "Oh! Oh! Alice, let me down. On my word, I will do anything you order. Oh! Oh! Ah! You make me do it," as he shuts his eyes, and we saw quite a jet of sperm shoot from his virile member.<break time="100ms" />Alice dropped her rod, and we let down the culprit who was terribly crestfallen.<break time="100ms" />"Now, sir," she said, "down on your knees, and kiss the rod."<break time="100ms" />Without a word, he dropped down, and kissed the worn-out stump, saying: "Oh! Alice; the last few moments have been so heavenly. It has blotted out all sense of pain. My dear sister, I thank you for punishing me, and will keep my promise to Beatrice."<break time="100ms" />I wiped the drops of blood from his slightly-bleeding rump, and then we gave him a couple of glasses of wine, and allowed him to sleep with Lucy, in her room, for the rest of the night, where they had a most luscious time of it, whilst Alice and myself indulged in our favourite touches.<break time="100ms" />You may be sure Frederick was not long before he renewed his pleasures with me, whilst his sister took pleasure in our happiness; but she seemed to have contracted a penchant for the use of the rod, and, once or twice a week, would have us all in her room, for a birch seance, as she called it, when Lucy or myself had to submit to be victims; but the heating of our bottoms only seemed to add to our enjoyment when we were afterwards allowed to soothe our raging passions in the arms of our mutual lover.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />A gentleman, who is blessed with a beautiful and lewdly disposed wife, has long been very unhappy and disappointed at the results of his endeavours to become a parent. But returning home from the City, very unexpectedly, the other morning, he caught the Vicar of the parish gamahuching his spouse. "Ho! Ho!" he exclaimed, in a fury. "So you're the bugger who swallows all my children."<break time="100ms" />Part of a Letter From Harriet Keene.<break time="100ms" />I'll tell you a funny dream I had the night before last. I thought I was sitting on a green bank, and a man was sitting by the side of me; he fell to kissing and talking, but did nothing else. Well, after a while, he got up and went away; then, at the side of me, as I sat there, lay the largest prick I ever saw. It was at least half a yard long, and as thick as the calf of my leg; it had four bollox, but it tapered towards the end. I thought I took it up and felt it. It was warm flesh and blood, and I said to myself, "Why the man has left his prick behind him; what a pity! and it is such a fine one tool what will he do without it?" So I thought to myself, "I wonder if it will spend if I suck it," so I kept sucking it, but it was so big and thick that it made my mouth ache, and I said to myself, "Never mind, it will do to frig myself with." So I got up, and put it under my cloak, and cuddled it so close to me that I felt as lewd as could be. As I was going along I met the man coming back, and when he came up to me, he said, "Have you seen my trumpet?"<break time="100ms" />"Your trumpet," said I, "why you mean your prick!"<break time="100ms" />Says he, "You nasty, lying woman, it's my best trumpet."<break time="100ms" />"Well," said I, "if this is a trumpet, why a trumpet's a prick, and a prick is a trumpet," and I held it up to look at. He snatched it out of my hand. "Now, then, I'll show you if it's a prick or a trumpet," and he began to blow away on it so loud that I awoke and lost my prick and trumpet too.<break time="100ms" />What woke me up was the sound of a trumpet in the street, so I suppose that was the cause of my funny dream.<break time="100ms" />The Wise Lover.<break time="100ms" />Woman and man whene'er inclined,<break time="100ms" />In mutual goodness pleasure find,<break time="100ms" />The lawful spouse 'tis sweet to embrace,<break time="100ms" />In hopes to see a lengthen'd race,<break time="100ms" />But let who will the truth contest,<break time="100ms" />Another's wife is still the best.<break time="100ms" />When I was young and slightly skill'd,<break time="100ms" />In blisses womankind can yield;<break time="100ms" />I lov'd the maid, I lov'd the piece;<break time="100ms" />But as my wit and years increase,<break time="100ms" />I own the sweetest sport in life,<break time="100ms" />Is to enjoy your neighbour's wife.<break time="100ms" />A virgin coy with sidelong eye,<break time="100ms" />Your mere approach, at once will fly,<break time="100ms" />Abhors your nasty hot desires,<break time="100ms" />Nought less than marriage she requires,<break time="100ms" />Such maidenheads the wise detest,<break time="100ms" />The adultery maidenhead's the best.<break time="100ms" />The vagrant nymph who sells her charms,<break time="100ms" />And fills in turn a thousand arms,<break time="100ms" />Besides the loss of gold and fame,<break time="100ms" />May set Priapus in a flame,<break time="100ms" />Such fire-tailed comets God confound.<break time="100ms" />A wife is always safe and sound.<break time="100ms" />The genial flame I've oft allayed,<break time="100ms" />With buxom Kate, my chambermaid,<break time="100ms" />And dozens such as her, but found<break time="100ms" />Such sport with ills beset around;<break time="100ms" />He who at liberty would feast,<break time="100ms" />Will find another's wife the best.<break time="100ms" />A mistress kept at first is sweet,<break time="100ms" />And joys to do the merry feat;<break time="100ms" />But bastards come, and hundreds gone,<break time="100ms" />You'll wish you'd left her charms alone;<break time="100ms" />Such breeding hussy's are a pest,<break time="100ms" />A neighbour's wife is far the best.<break time="100ms" />If you are rash, a wife at first<break time="100ms" />May into horrid fury burst,<break time="100ms" />"Sir, you shall rue throughout your life<break time="100ms" />The day you've kissed another's wife."<break time="100ms" />Reply, "My dear, this gives the zest,<break time="100ms" />I always like my neighbour's best."<break time="100ms" />Jove, I remember, when inclined<break time="100ms" />To feast himself on womankind,<break time="100ms" />Though maids enough to him were free,<break time="100ms" />Always preferr'd adultery;<break time="100ms" />He took the shape of bird and beast,<break time="100ms" />To prove Adultery the best.<break time="100ms" />But while this naughty sport we sing,<break time="100ms" />Who can forget our gracious King (Geo. IV);<break time="100ms" />Him many a lady pleasures gives,<break time="100ms" />For which her husband pay receives,<break time="100ms" />God bless King George! His Majesty<break time="100ms" />Is patron of Adultery.<break time="100ms" />I own the dangers of the suit,<break time="100ms" />The sweetest is forbidden fruit,<break time="100ms" />And laws as thick as hairs are set,<break time="100ms" />Around the center of delight;<break time="100ms" />This peril gives the highest zest,<break time="100ms" />And guarded hoard is sure the best.<break time="100ms" />The wandering nymph your purse desires,<break time="100ms" />The chambermaid to rank aspires;<break time="100ms" />Your wife content with marriage dues,<break time="100ms" />All further license will refuse;<break time="100ms" />He who has put them to the test,
    </voice>
</speak>
