<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Must own his neighbour's wife's the best.<break time="100ms" />Queen Bathsheba.<break time="100ms" />A Temperance Ballad. (Attributed to Sir Wilfrid Lawson.)<break time="100ms" />Grass widows and princes! a warning I sing,<break time="100ms" />Of the sad wicked doing of David, the King;<break time="100ms" />With Bathsheba, wife of poor Major Uriah,<break time="100ms" />Who was bathing one day, when the King chanc'd to spy her.<break time="100ms" />He was drinking up-stairs, and the weather was hot;<break time="100ms" />And her window was open (a thing she forgot);<break time="100ms" />And the stark-naked beauty had not an idea,<break time="100ms" />That while she was washing, a creature could see her!<break time="100ms" />She and her little sister were sporting together,<break time="100ms" />Enjoying the heat of the bright summer weather;<break time="100ms" />They bath'd in the fountain, and while they were washing,<break time="100ms" />Were romping all naked, and leaping and splashing.<break time="100ms" />What man could resist such an awful temptation?<break time="100ms" />He forgot he was King of the sanctified nation;<break time="100ms" />He was fill'd with delight, and lewd admiration,<break time="100ms" />And was mad for the raptures of fierce fornication.<break time="100ms" />Beware of the Devil, who seldom lies sleeping!<break time="100ms" />So while she was washing, and while he was peeping,<break time="100ms" />The King's living sceptre grew stiff as a rod,<break time="100ms" />"Nice mutton!" cried David, "I'll fuck her, by G—!"<break time="100ms" />So calling a page, he desir'd him to go,<break time="100ms" />And enquire all about her.—He answered, "I know<break time="100ms" />The lady your Majesty's pleas'd to admire,<break time="100ms" />Is the wife of the valorous Major Uriah."<break time="100ms" />His Majesty answer'd: "Go, fetch her! Be quick!<break time="100ms" />Much conscience, indeed, has a stiff-standing prick!"<break time="100ms" />The page ran to call her; she put on her smock,<break time="100ms" />And hurried to wait on his Majesty's cock.<break time="100ms" />One touch to her hand, and one word in her ear,<break time="100ms" />And she fell on her back, like a sweet willing dear;<break time="100ms" />He was frantic with lust, but she seiz'd his erection,<break time="100ms" />And put it at once in the proper direction.<break time="100ms" />She was girlish and lively, a heavenly figure,<break time="100ms" />With the cunt of an angel, and fucking with vigour;<break time="100ms" />He got her at once with child of a son,<break time="100ms" />And he said a long grace when the swiving was done.<break time="100ms" />So the lady went home, and she very soon found<break time="100ms" />Her belly was growing unluckily round.<break time="100ms" />"This an honour," said she, "I could hardly expect,<break time="100ms" />Your Majesty now must your handmaid protect."<break time="100ms" />"Never fear," cried the King, "I'll be your adviser,<break time="100ms" />I'll send for the Major, and no one's the wiser."<break time="100ms" />So he sent for Uriah, who speedily came.<break time="100ms" />But unluckily never laid hands on the dame.<break time="100ms" />King David was puzzled, he made the man tipsy,<break time="100ms" />But still he avoided the lewd little gipsy;<break time="100ms" />David laid a new plot, and his wish was fulfill'd,<break time="100ms" />In the front of the battle Uriah was kill'd.<break time="100ms" />The Horrible Fright.<break time="100ms" />Poor Sally! I hear from your loving Mamma,<break time="100ms" />That you're in a horrible fright of Papa;<break time="100ms" />Take courage, dear girl, for the sweetest delight,<break time="100ms" />Is closely akin to a horrible fright.<break time="100ms" />In your dreams, did you ne'er see a horrible man,<break time="100ms" />Who crushes and conquers you, do all you can?<break time="100ms" />He treats your poor innocent mouse like a rat<break time="100ms" />That's touzled and claw'd, and devour'd by a cat.<break time="100ms" />He produces a horrible fright of a thing,<break time="100ms" />That fits like a finger in conjugal ring;<break time="100ms" />He thrusts, and he pokes, and he enters your belly,<break time="100ms" />Till the horrible monster is melted to jelly.<break time="100ms" />When you draw a new glove on your finger so tight,<break time="100ms" />The glove is, you know, in a horrible fright;<break time="100ms" />But soon it is taught your dear finger to love,<break time="100ms" />The man and the woman are finger and glove.<break time="100ms" />Away with your horrible fright, and away<break time="100ms" />With the wretch of a father, who hinders the play;<break time="100ms" />If he dares interfere, when you kiss on the sly,<break time="100ms" />Just pull up your petticoat, piss in his eye.<break time="100ms" />Ah! Sally, my darling, I wish that this night,<break time="100ms" />I might put you, my love, in a horrible fright;<break time="100ms" />You might lie down a maiden, in five minutes more,<break time="100ms" />I would open a secret, ne'er open'd before.<break time="100ms" />You then would behold, long, ruddy, and thick,<break time="100ms" />That horrible monster, a stiff-standing prick;<break time="100ms" />You'd cry out, "Oh, softly! Oh, gently! Ah! Ah!<break time="100ms" />Oh lordy, oh lordy, oh harder, la! la!"<break time="100ms" />At last, dearest Sally, your horrible fright<break time="100ms" />Would end in a shudder of tipsy delight;<break time="100ms" />You'll open your buttocks, as wide as you can,<break time="100ms" />To admit every inch of the dear cruel man.<break time="100ms" />You'll devour every inch of his horrible yard,<break time="100ms" />Till the testicles hit on your bottom so hard;<break time="100ms" />Your terrible fright, my dear girl, will be over,<break time="100ms" />You'll breathe out your soul, on the lips of your lover.<break time="100ms" />There's an end of this horrible fright of a song,<break time="100ms" />Your mother shall read it, and say if it's wrong;<break time="100ms" />No, she will approve it—her greatest delight<break time="100ms" />Is the prick which you fancy such a horrible fright.<break time="100ms" />Payne's Hill (Mons Veneris).<break time="100ms" />In Middlesex a hill we meet,<break time="100ms" />For beauty known to fame;<break time="100ms" />Where wealthy Payne has built his seat,<break time="100ms" />Payne's Hill they call its name.<break time="100ms" />"Pray,Mr. Burke," said Lady Payne,<break time="100ms" />"What Latin word is this?<break time="100ms" />(I've searched the dictionary in vain),<break time="100ms" />Pray what's Mons Veneris?"<break time="100ms" />He look'd into her beauteous eyes,<break time="100ms" />So innocent of ill;<break time="100ms" />And gave the happiest of replies,<break time="100ms" />"It signifies Payne's Hill!"<break time="100ms" />Instance of Self-Denial.<break time="100ms" />Mohammed Sadig, a gentleman at Hyderabad, received a female slave, belonging to his brother at Kurnool, who was going to Bengal, and requested Sadig to keep his property for a year. Her beauty excited his passions greatly. He told the story to my friend, Captain Keighley, and ended thus: "To lie with her carnally would have been wrong, as my brother had not permitted it, so I governed my love by the holy rules of moderation and virtue, and contented myself with merely fucking her in the arse."
    </voice>
</speak>
