<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Ah, Charlie, my boy, you don't mind it, eh do you? it's nothing to bear.<break time="100ms" />Though a small boy may cry for a flogging, that's natural, but Charlie don't care.<break time="100ms" />That's right, Sir, don't spare him! that cut was a stinger, but Charlie don't mind;<break time="100ms" />All the rods in the kingdom would only be wasted on Charlie's behind,<break time="100ms" />At each cut, how the red flesh rises, the red weals tingle and swell!<break time="100ms" />How he blushes! I told you the Master would flog Charlie Collingwood well.<break time="100ms" />There are long red ridges and furrows, across his great, broad, nether cheeks,<break time="100ms" />And on both his plump, rosy, round buttocks, the blood stands in drops and in streaks.<break time="100ms" />Well hit, Sir! Well caught! how he drew in his bottom, and flinched from the cut!<break time="100ms" />At each touch of the birch on his bum, how the smart makes it open and shut!<break time="100ms" />Well struck, Sir, again, how it made the blood spin! there's a drop on the floor,<break time="100ms" />Each long, fleshy furrow grows ruddy, and Charlie can bear it no more.<break time="100ms" />Blood runs from each weal on his bottom, and all Charlie's bottom is wealed<break time="100ms" />'Twill be many a day ere the scars of this flogging are thoroughly healed.<break time="100ms" />Now just under the hollow of Charlie's bare back, where the flanks are aslope.<break time="100ms" />The rod catches and stings him, and now at the point where the downward ways ope;<break time="100ms" />Round his flanks, now like serpents, the birchen twigs twining bend round as they bite,<break time="100ms" />And you see on his naked, white belly, red ridges, where all was so white.<break time="100ms" />Where between his white thighs, something hairy, the body's division reveals.<break time="100ms" />Falls the next cut, and now Charlie Collingwood's bottom is all over weals.<break time="100ms" />Not a twig on the rod, but has raised a red ridge on his flesh, not a bud,<break time="100ms" />But has drawn from his naked and writhing posteriors, a fresh drop of blood.<break time="100ms" />And the Schoolmaster warms to his work now, as harder and harder he hits,<break time="100ms" />And picks out the most sensitive places, as though he'd cut Charlie to bits.<break time="100ms" />"So you'll fidget and whisper in school-time, and make a disturbance in Church?<break time="100ms" />"Can't sit still, Master Charlie, eh, can't you? Well, what do you think of the birch?<break time="100ms" />"Oh, it hurts you so, does it, my boy, to sit down, since I flogged you last night?<break time="100ms" />"It was that made you fidget all church time? Indeed, you can't help it, please God-<break time="100ms" />"By the help of the birch, Master Charlie, I'll teach you to help it, please God-<break time="100ms" />"If you don't mend your manners in future, it shan't be for want of a rod.<break time="100ms" />"You're a big boy, no doubt, to be flogged; the more shame for you, Sir, at your age-<break time="100ms" />"But as long as you're here, I shall flog you," he lays on the cuts in a rage.<break time="100ms" />"Aye, and if you were older and bigger, you'd come to the flogging block still—<break time="100ms" />"Boys are never too big to be beaten!" he lays on the birch with a will,<break time="100ms" />"if a boy's not too old to go wrong, Sir, he can't be too old to be whipped;<break time="100ms" />"So take that!" and he lays on the rod, till the twigs all with crimson are tipped.<break time="100ms" />There are drops of the boy's blood visible now, on each tender young bud-<break time="100ms" />Blood has dropped on his trousers, and Charlie's bare bottom is covered with blood.<break time="100ms" />But I'd rather be shut up for days, in a hole you would scarce put a dog in.<break time="100ms" />And brought out once a day to be birched, than have missed Charlie Collingwood's flogging.<break time="100ms" />How each cut brings the blood to his forehead, and makes him bite half through his lips!<break time="100ms" />How the birch cuts his bottom right over, and makes the blood spin from his hips!<break time="100ms" />How his brawny bare haunches, all bloody, and wealed, with red furrows like ruts,<break time="100ms" />Shrink quivering with pain at each stroke, that revives all the smart of past cuts!<break time="100ms" />How the Schoolmaster seems to hit harder, the birch to sting more at each blow!<break time="100ms" />Till at last Charlie Collingwood, writhing with agony, bellows out,"Oh!"<break time="100ms" />That was all; not a word of petition; a single short cry and no more;<break time="100ms" />And the younger boys laugh, that the birch should have made such a big fellow roar.<break time="100ms" />For a moment, the Master too pauses; but not for a truce or a parley:<break time="100ms" />Then the birch falls afresh, on the bloody wealed flesh, with "Take that, Master Charlie."<break time="100ms" />All the small boys are breathless and hushed; but they hear not a syllable come,<break time="100ms" />They hear only the swish of the birch, as it meets Charlie Collingwood's bum.<break time="100ms" />And the Master's face flushes with anger; he signs to Fred Fane with a nod;<break time="100ms" />And Freddy reluctantly hands him another stout, supple birch rod.<break time="100ms" />And again as he flogs Charlie Collingwood's bottom, his face seems aflame;<break time="100ms" />At each cut he reminds him of this thing or that, and rebukes him by name.<break time="100ms" />Each cut makes the boy's haunches quiver, and scores them all over afresh;<break time="100ms" />You can trace where each separate birch twig has marked Charlie Collingwood's flesh.<break time="100ms" />Till the Master, tired out with hard work, and quite satiate with flogging for once.<break time="100ms" />With one last cut, that stings to the quick, bids him rise for an Obstinate Dunce.<break time="100ms" />From the block Charlie Collingwood rises, red faced, and with tumbled red hair.<break time="100ms" />And with crimson hued bottom, and tearful blue eyes, and a look of "Don't Care."<break time="100ms" />Then he draws up his breeches, and walks out of school with a crowd of boys dogging<break time="100ms" />The heels of their hero, all proud to have seen Charlie Collingwood's flogging.<break time="100ms" />FINIS.<break time="100ms" />"Jack, my boy, what a devil of an appetite you have this morning," said one friend to another as they were breakfasting at their hotel. "And so would you," replied Jack, "if you had only had a whore's tongue and a toothbrush in your mouth since yesterday!"<break time="100ms" />Madame Rollin had three monkeys, of which one was a she; and the lady used to amuse herself with watching their tricks. "It is curious," said she, "to observe them, for while one of them is caressing the other, the third comforts himself!"<break time="100ms" />Her expression was "suffices for himself"!!<break time="100ms" />Meaning Masturbation of Course!!!<break time="100ms" />Lady Pokingham, or They All Do It.<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />Part II.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)
    </voice>
</speak>
