<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Sir Eyre.- "Why, Rosie, I thought you were stronger than that. Poor thing, your punishment was too much for you. I'll finish the culprit. If she won't confess, she must be executed, that's all," snatching up another whip, much heavier than the one I had used, and with three tips of cord on the end. "You won't confess, won't you, you obstinate wicked creature? My blood boils when I think how I punished the other two innocent girls," he exclaimed, cutting her fearfully on the calves of her legs, knocking the delicate silk of the stockings to pieces, and wealing and bruising her legs all over. The victim cannot plunge about, as her ankles are fastened, but she moans with agony, and shrieks and sobs hysterically in turns at this terrible attack. The General seems beside himself with rage, for he next turns to her beautiful white shoulders, and slashes them about, fearfully cutting through the skin and deluging poor Jemima with her own blood.<break time="100ms" />Sir Eyre.- "I shall murder her; I can't help it; she's made me quite mad." His cuts wind round her ribs, and even weal the beauties of her splendid bosom, and stains the snowy belly with their blood.<break time="100ms" />Jemima (in low broken sobs).- "Oh! Oh! Mercy! Let me die! Don't torture an innocent thing like me any longer." She seems going to faint, when Mrs. Mansell interposes, saying: "It is enough; more may do serious injury."<break time="100ms" />Sir Eyre (gasping for breath).- "Oh! Oh! I know you are right to take me away, or I shall really murder her."<break time="100ms" />The bleeding victim is a pitiable and terrible sight as we release her from the ladder; she is scarcely able to stand; her boots covered with blood, and little pools of the sanguineous fluid stand on the floor; and we had to administer a cordial before she was able to be supported to her room, where she was confined to her bed for several days.<break time="100ms" />I had now had all the revenge I was so anxious to inflict; but the great avenger of all, to my great grief, soon removed poor old grandfather from this world, and left me indeed an orphan. Being still very young, my guardians under Sir Eyre's will placed me at Miss Flaybum's Academy to finish my education, and the old home was broken up, and inmates scattered.<break time="100ms" />I shall send you some of my school experiences in my next, and remain,<break time="100ms" />Dear Nellie,<break time="100ms" />Yours affectionately. ROSA BELINDA COOTE.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />"Pray, mama," said Sally, "what's the meaning of Hush?"<break time="100ms" />"My dear," said mama, "what makes you ask such a question?"<break time="100ms" />"Because I asked Fanny what made her belly stick out so, and she answered, 'Hush.'<break time="100ms" />Charlie Collingwood's Flogging, by Etoniensis.<break time="100ms" />Seventeen years of age, with round limbs, and broad shoulders, tall, rosy and fair,<break time="100ms" />And all over his forehead and temples, a forest of curly red hair;<break time="100ms" />Good in the playing fields, good on the water, or in it, this lad:<break time="100ms" />But at sums, or at themes, or at verses, oh! ain't Charlie Collingwood bad?<break time="100ms" />Six days out of seven, or five at the least, he's sent up to be stripped;<break time="100ms" />But it's nuts for the lower boys always, to see Charlie Collingwood whipped;<break time="100ms" />For the marks of the birch on his bottom are more than the leaves on a tree,<break time="100ms" />And a bum that has worn so much birch out, as Charlie's, is jolly to see.<break time="100ms" />When his shirt is turned up, and his breeches, unbuttoned, hang down to his heels,<break time="100ms" />From the small of his back, to the thick of his thighs is one mass of red weals.<break time="100ms" />Ted Beauchamp last year began keeping a list of his floggings and he<break time="100ms" />Says, they come; in a year-and-a-half, to a hundred and sixty and three.<break time="100ms" />And you see how this morning, in front of the flogging block silent he stands,<break time="100ms" />And hitches his waistband up slightly, and feels his backside with his hands.<break time="100ms" />Then he lifts his blue eyes to the face of the Master, nor shrinks at his frown,<break time="100ms" />Nor at sight of the birch, nor at sound of the sentence of judgment, "Go down."<break time="100ms" />Not a word, Charlie Collingwood says, not a syllable, piteous or pert;<break time="100ms" />But goes down with his breeches unbuttoned, and Errington takes up his shirt.<break time="100ms" />And again we can see his great naked red bottom, round, fleshy, and plump.<break time="100ms" />And the bystanders look from the Master's red rod, to the schoolboy's red rump:<break time="100ms" />There are weals over weals, there are stripes upon stripes, there are cuts after cuts,<break time="100ms" />All across Charlie Collingwood's bottom, and isn't the sight of it nuts?<break time="100ms" />There, that cut on the fleshiest part of the buttocks, high up on the right,<break time="100ms" />He got that before supper last evening, oh! isn't his bottom a sight?<break time="100ms" />And that scar that's just healed, don't you see where the birch cut the flesh?<break time="100ms" />That's a token of Charlie's last flogging, the rod will soon stamp it afresh.<break time="100ms" />And this morning you saw he could hardly sit down, or be quiet in Church;<break time="100ms" />It's a pleasure to see Charlie's bottom, it looks just cut out for the birch.<break time="100ms" />Now, look out, Master Charlie, it's coming: you won't get off this time, by God!<break time="100ms" />For your Master's in, oh, such a wax! and he's picked you out, oh, such a rod!<break time="100ms" />Such a jolly good rod, with the buds on, so stout, and so supple and lithe,<break time="100ms" />You've been flogged till you're hardened to flogging, but won't the first cut make you writhe?<break time="100ms" />You've been birched till you say you don't care as you used for a birching! Indeed?<break time="100ms" />Wait a bit, Master Charlie, I'll bet the third cut or the fourth makes you bleed.<break time="100ms" />Though they say a boy's bottom grows harder with whipping, and times make it tough,<break time="100ms" />Yet the sturdiest boy's bottom will wince if the Schoolmaster whips it enough.<break time="100ms" />Aye, the stoutest posteriors will redden, and flinch from the cuts as they come,<break time="100ms" />If they're flogged half as hard as the Master will flog Charlie Collingwood's bum.<break time="100ms" />We shall see a real jolly good swishing, as good as a fellow could wish;<break time="100ms" />Here's a stunning good rod, and a jolly big bottom just under it - Swish!<break time="100ms" />Oh, by Jove, he's drawn blood at the very first cut! in two places by God!<break time="100ms" />Aye, and Charlie's red bottom grows redder all over with marks of the rod.<break time="100ms" />And the pain of the cut makes his burning posteriors quiver and heave,<break time="100ms" />And he's hiding his face-yes, by Jove, and he's wiping his eyes on his sleeve!<break time="100ms" />Now; give it him well, Sir, lay into him well, till the pain makes him roar!<break time="100ms" />Flog him, then, till he stops, and then flog him again, till he bellows once more!
    </voice>
</speak>
