<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />In the wars in India, in the year 1800, Major Torrens's party was pursuing some of the enemy. One day, while they were dining and very merry, a sergeant came and reported to the Major that two prisoners were brought in, one old and one young. The Sergeant requested orders regarding them. The Major merrily answered: "Oh, take them away and frig them." The Sergeant retired. In an hour he returned, and respectfully made this report: "Please your honour, we have frigged the young one. but we can't make the old man's cock stand."<break time="100ms" />This story was related to me, in 1818, by Torrens, who was then an old General at Madras.<break time="100ms" />Nursery Rhymes.<break time="100ms" />There was a young lady of Harrow.<break time="100ms" />Who complained that her Cunt was too narrow,<break time="100ms" />For times without number<break time="100ms" />She would use a cucumber,<break time="100ms" />But could not accomplish a marrow.<break time="100ms" />There was a young lady of Glasgow,<break time="100ms" />And fondly her lover did ask, "Oh,<break time="100ms" />Pray allow me a fuck,"<break time="100ms" />But she said, "No, my duck,<break time="100ms" />But you may, if you please, up my arse go."<break time="100ms" />There was a young man had the art<break time="100ms" />Of making a capital tart,<break time="100ms" />With a handful of shit,<break time="100ms" />Some snot and a spit,<break time="100ms" />And he'd flavor the whole with a fart.<break time="100ms" />There was an old man of Connaught.<break time="100ms" />Whose prick was remarkably short,<break time="100ms" />When he got into bed<break time="100ms" />The old woman said,<break time="100ms" />"This isn't a prick, it's a wart."<break time="100ms" />There was a gay Countess of Bray,<break time="100ms" />And you may think it odd when I say,<break time="100ms" />That in spite of high station,<break time="100ms" />Rank and education,<break time="100ms" />She always spelt Cunt with a K.<break time="100ms" />There was an old parson of Lundy,<break time="100ms" />Fell asleep in his vestry on Sunday;<break time="100ms" />He awoke with a scream,<break time="100ms" />"What, another wet dream,<break time="100ms" />This comes of not frigging since Monday."<break time="100ms" />There was a strong man of Drumrig,<break time="100ms" />Who one day did seven times frig;<break time="100ms" />He buggered three Sailors,<break time="100ms" />Four Jews and two Tailors,<break time="100ms" />And ended by fucking a pig.<break time="100ms" />There was an Old Man of the Mountain.<break time="100ms" />Who frigged himself into a fountain,<break time="100ms" />Fifteen times had he spent.<break time="100ms" />Still he wasn't content.<break time="100ms" />He simply got tired of the counting.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Nantucket.<break time="100ms" />Who went down a well in a bucket;<break time="100ms" />The last words he spoke.<break time="100ms" />Before the rope broke,<break time="100ms" />Were, "Arsehole, you bugger, and suck it."<break time="100ms" />A native of Havre de Grace<break time="100ms" />Once tired of Cunt, said "I'll try arse."<break time="100ms" />He unfolded his plan<break time="100ms" />To another young man,<break time="100ms" />Who said, "Most decidedly, my arse!"<break time="100ms" />At the Parish Church, South Hackney, by the Rev. C. A. White, John Henry Bottomfeldt, of Hamburgh, to Sarah Jane Greens, of South Hackney. (Vide "Daily Telegraph," January 3, 1875).<break time="100ms" />How lovely everything now seems<break time="100ms" />When joined in one by Hymen's belt,<break time="100ms" />For now John Henry has his Greens,<break time="100ms" />And Sarah Jane her Bottom-feldt.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
