<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The stout and strong Maria immediately appears and conducts me into a kind of small vestry sacred to the goddess of flagellation, if there is such a deity; there she strips off all my clothes, except chemise and drawers, and makes me put on a kind of penitential dress, consisting of a white mobcap and a long white garment, something like a nightdress; it fitted close up round the throat with a little plain frill round the neck and down the front, being fastened by a band round the waist.<break time="100ms" />Maria now ushers me again into the presence of Miss Flaybum, all blushing as I am at the degrading costume, and ridiculous figure I must look to my schoolfellows, who are all in a titter.<break time="100ms" />Maria lays a fine bunch of fresh birch twigs (especially tied up with ribbons) at my feet, I have to pick it up and kiss it in a most respectful manner, and ask my schoolmistress to chastise me properly with it. All this was frightfully humiliating, especially the first time, for however free we might have been with one another in our bedrooms there was such a sense of mortifying shame, sure to be felt all through the proceedings.<break time="100ms" />Miss Flaybum, rising with great dignity from her seat, motions with her hand, and Miss Herbert assisted by the German governess, Frau Bildaur, at once mounted me on Maria's broad back, and pinned up the dress above my waist, then the English governess with evident pleasure opened my drawers behind so as to expose my bare bottom, whilst the soft-hearted young German showed her sympathy by eyes brimming with tears.<break time="100ms" />Miss Flaybum. - "I shall administer a dozen sharp cuts, and then insist upon your begging Miss Herbert's pardon," commencing to count the strokes one by one. As she whisks steadily, but with great force, every blow falling with a loud "whack," and making my bottom smart and tingle with pain, and giving assurance of a plentiful crop of weals. My red blushing bottom must have been a most edifying sight to the pupils, and a regular caution to timid offenders, two or three more of whom might expect their turn in a day or two; although I screamed and cried out in apparent anguish it was nothing to what I had suffered at the hands of Sir Eyre or Mrs. Mansell; the worst part of the punishment was in the degrading ceremony and charity girl costume the victim had to assume.<break time="100ms" />The dozen duly inflicted, I had first to beg Miss Herbert's pardon, and then having again kissed the rod, and thanked Miss Flaybum for what she called her loving correction, I was allowed to retire and resume my own apparel. I could tell you about many punishment scenes, but in my next shall have the grand finale to my school life, and how we paid off Miss Flaybum and the English governess before leaving.<break time="100ms" />And remain, dear Nellie.<break time="100ms" />Your ever loving ROSA BELINDA COOTE.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />"Now, dear Nelly, as we are both snug in bed, give me the account you promised of all that passed at your uncle's during your visit."<break time="100ms" />Well, don't frig me so hard, or you'll cut short my story. My uncle, you know, is a widower. He has three children, Gussy, who is fourteen, Johnny eleven, and Janey nine years of age. I was only just fifteen. So we were all well suited together, and soon became great friends. The two boys had lately come home for their holidays, and were up to every kind of fun. Our favourite place for play was the hay loft; and our chief amusement rolling down the hay one after the other. On one occasion my frock flew up in the descent, so that when I reached the bottom, my legs were all uncovered, and the little slit between them (just newly fringed with hair) was fully exposed to view.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, look!" cried Johnny, pointing to it, and throwing himself upon me. "See what she has there."<break time="100ms" />"For shame," I said, struggling to get up.<break time="100ms" />"Hold her down," cried Gussy spreading my thighs, and opening my cunt with his fingers.<break time="100ms" />"What a funny little place, Nelly. Let us have a good look. Why need you mind? You may see mine if you like. Let's all look at one another, and see which has the nicest."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, do!" cried John and Janey, "it will be great fun."<break time="100ms" />So the two boys pulled out their little pricks, and Janey, holding up her dress and pulling aside her drawers, showed us her small unfledged cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Yours is far the nicest," said Gussy to me. "For yours has hair; we have none yet, but we shall bye-and-bye."<break time="100ms" />"How do you know?" asked Janey.<break time="100ms" />"Because I have often seen men bathing, and they all had hair about their pricks, as they call them."<break time="100ms" />"But what of women; you've never seen them bathing?"<break time="100ms" />"No, but I have seen nurse's, and she has plenty. One night, about a year ago. she was giving me a warm bath, and when she was drying me, she began tickling my little cockey; I was ashamed, but she said it was nothing to mind, that I would soon be proud enough of it, and that then I would be wanting to stick it into the chink that women have at the bottom of their belly. I coaxed her to let me feel hers. She did. And let me see it too."<break time="100ms" />"What was it like, Gussy?"<break time="100ms" />"Just like a great mouth with a beard all around it. I could nearly put my hand up into it, it was so big."<break time="100ms" />It was quite funny to see how the boys' pricks stiffened up as they felt and examined my cunt. Janey too looked on eagerly and frigged her own little slit with the handle of a battledore.<break time="100ms" />"But," said Johnny, "you have no place for getting into you here, like nurse."<break time="100ms" />"Yes, she has. See! I can push my finger up."<break time="100ms" />"Stop, Gussy, you are hurting me."<break time="100ms" />"Well, let me put my prick in. That won't hurt, I am sure."<break time="100ms" />"Do let him," cried John and Janey. "It will be such fun."<break time="100ms" />"You may try if you like," I said.<break time="100ms" />He then knelt between my open thighs, and pushed his prick about the lips of my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, he can't get it in," said Janey, "what a pity."<break time="100ms" />I began to grow excited, so I put down my hand and held his prick at the right entrance, while with my other hand on his bottom I helped to push him in.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, now It's going in, every bit of it; does it hurt you Nelly, does it hurt?"<break time="100ms" />"No dear, it feels very nice; that's the way."<break time="100ms" />Gussy, impelled by nature, shoved eagerly in and out, John and Jane laughed, but Gussy began to breathe hard, his face flushed, his eyes sparkled. "Oh!" he cried "what's going to happen, hold me Nelly," and he fell forward on my breast, as he poured forth for the first time his maiden treasure.<break time="100ms" />After that we never lost an opportunity of playing with each other's privates. Janey and I used to frig and suck the boys' pricks, and they tickled and kissed our cunts; but Gussy and I always ended with a fuck, for he had a wonderful tool for so young a lad, and enjoyed the sweet exercise thoroughly.
    </voice>
</speak>
