<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Dearest Victoria, pity my passion. How can I help loving those killing eyes, and luscious pouting lips. That very fact of its being wrong makes my determination the greater to enjoy you the first opportunity. It is useless to resist our fate: Why has the God of Love given me such a chance as this?"<break time="100ms" />She turns away her head with affected prudery; but not a blush rises to assert her horror at his speech. One hand presses her fingers to his lips; but where is the other? Under her clothes. He first touches her ankle, and slowly steals it up her leg. She fidgets on the seat, but he is impetuous, and soon has possession of her most secret charms. Her languishing eyes are turned on him, and in an instant, he is on his legs, and pushing her clothes up, displays a lovely pair of legs in white silk stockings, beautiful blue garters with gold buckles, her thighs encased in rather tight-fitting drawers, beautifully trimmed with Valenciennes lace. His lips are glued to hers at the same instant, and his hands gently part her yielding thighs, as he placed himself well between them. It is but the work of an instant. He places her hand on the shaft of love, which he has just let out, and it is guided into the haven of love. Both are evidently too hot and impetuous, for it seems to be over in a minute.<break time="100ms" />She hastily kisses him, and puts down her clothes as she says: "How awful; but I could not resist Your Grace without disordering all my dress. It's been quite a rape, sir," with a smile. "Now, let's make haste back before we are missed." He kisses her, and makes her agree to an assignation, somewhere in South Belgravia, for the morrow, to enjoy each other more at leisure, and then they were gone.<break time="100ms" />It would be impossible to describe the agitation of my partner during this short scene; Lothair seemed to shiver and shudder with emotion, I was also all of a tremble, and nestled close to him, my arm designedly touching the bunch in his trousers, always so interesting to me; I could feel it swell and seem ready to burst from its confinement; he nervously clasped my hand, and was speechless with emotion all during the scene which I have described; as soon as they were gone he seemed to give a gasp of relief, and led me out of our hiding place. "Poor girl," he said, "what a sight for you, how I trembled for my own honour, lest the scene should make me lose my self-control. Ah! wretched woman, to betray your husband so!" Then looking at me for the first time he said, "Do you not think it is best for a man never to marry?"<break time="100ms" />Used as I had been to such things, his terrible emotion made me quite sympathize with him, and my own agitation was quite natural, as I replied, "Ah! my Lord, you little know the ways of the world; I saw a more awful scene than what we have witnessed, only last night, enacted by men sworn to perpetual celibacy, and you yourself were mentioned as a victim to their infernal plot."<break time="100ms" />"My God! Lady, pray tell me what it was," he ejaculated. "Not now, we shall be missed, do you know any place where I can have a private conference with your lordship? If so, meet me to-morrow afternoon at two o'clock, in the Burlington Arcade. I shall come disguised," I answered.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />A Jew who wanted to get hold of a Miss Bacon, said:<break time="100ms" />If I took but a slice,<break time="100ms" />Of pig's flesh, so nice,<break time="100ms" />Our rabbis would bluster and take on.<break time="100ms" />But I'd brave all their damns,<break time="100ms" />For a touch at the hams,<break time="100ms" />Of this delicate red and white Bacon.<break time="100ms" />When Molly the housemaid, who lived at the "Blue Boar," at York, was married to John the Ostler, her mistress gave the poor couple a bedchamber, in a garret, to celebrate their nuptials. But Robert and Harry, who had long well known all Poor Molly's in and outs, were seriously anxious to know the result. They crept to the door, and at last heard Molly exclaim: "Ah! Johnny dearest, you are where man never was before!" "Zounds, Harry!" whispered Robert; "he must have got into her arse."<break time="100ms" />How lovely did Venus at first seem to be,<break time="100ms" />When her birth she received from the spring of the sea;<break time="100ms" />As red as a rose looked her cunt's lovely rim,<break time="100ms" />And the foam slowly dripped from the hairs of her quim!<break time="100ms" />Her belly was whiter than marble, I ween,<break time="100ms" />And above it her bubbies like snow balls were seen;<break time="100ms" />But Venus was still discontented, alas,<break time="100ms" />She wanted a prick and two balls at her arse!<break time="100ms" />Her thighs were so pure, so graceful and round,<break time="100ms" />None fairer and lovelier e'er could be found;<break time="100ms" />But her cunt, I dare say, great pleasure it sips,<break time="100ms" />With a stiff-standing penis to part its red lips!<break time="100ms" />Oh, poking is a pleasure, we all must enjoy.<break time="100ms" />Tho' I had it for ever, it never would cloy;<break time="100ms" />To any young man on the grass I would fall.<break time="100ms" />And if cunt would allow it, take bollox and all!<break time="100ms" />What dull and senseless lumps we'd be,<break time="100ms" />If never of felicity<break time="100ms" />We tasted; and what bliss is there<break time="100ms" />To equal that of fucking rare?<break time="100ms" />An age of grief, an age of pain,<break time="100ms" />I would endure and ne'er complain;<break time="100ms" />To purchase but an hour's charms,<break time="100ms" />While wriggling in a maiden's arms!<break time="100ms" />And hugging her to heavenly rest,<break time="100ms" />My hand reposing on her breast!<break time="100ms" />Her arse my own, her thighs my screen.<break time="100ms" />My penis standing in between!<break time="100ms" />My bollox hanging down below.<break time="100ms" />And banging 'gainst her arse of snow;<break time="100ms" />Or else grasped firmly in her hand,<break time="100ms" />To make my yard more stiffly stand.<break time="100ms" />How soon the blood glows in the veins,<break time="100ms" />And nature all its power now strains;<break time="100ms" />The belly heaves, the penis burns.<break time="100ms" />The maiden all its heat returns,<break time="100ms" />Till passion holds triumphant sway.<break time="100ms" />And both the lovers die away.<break time="100ms" />When wishes first enter a maiden's breast.<break time="100ms" />She longs by her lover to be carest;<break time="100ms" />She longs with her lover to do the trick,<break time="100ms" />And in secret she longs for a taste of his prick!<break time="100ms" />Her cunt it is itching from morning till night,<break time="100ms" />The prick of her lover can yield her delight;<break time="100ms" />She longs to be fucked, and for that does deplore,<break time="100ms" />For what can a young maiden wish for more?<break time="100ms" />If fever or sickness her spirits doth shock,<break time="100ms" />Why, we know what she wants, 'tis a stiff-standing cock!<break time="100ms" />Give her a prick, it will soon make her well,<break time="100ms" />Though perhaps in the long run, her belly may swell!<break time="100ms" />She'd like very well to be laid on the grass.
    </voice>
</speak>
