<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"I declare she has taken nearly half of it in; what a mouthful she has; she is sucking it, just as you are sucking mine. How nice it feels to have one's prick sucked. Oh! Nelly, I can't go on, let it out, it's just coming," and he tried to draw it away, but I was enjoying so much the taste of his prick in my mouth, and, at the same time, had such a wonderful feel in my cunt that I would not let it go, so holding the cheeks of his bottom I moved him backward and forward, and made him fuck me in my mouth. His prick swelled, I felt it throb, and then a hot stream of sperm spurted into my mouth and flowed down my throat. We soon heard Uncle leaving Lizzy's room, then Gussy went too and all was quiet.<break time="100ms" />Uncle went to her room nearly every night, and though, during the day they were most particular in their conduct towards each other, and she, with her large blue eyes, looked the very picture of innocence, yet at night they gave themselves up to the most unbounded license. He fucked her in every conceivable attitude and way. He made her use every amorous term, even words that are generally thought vulgar and coarse. He used to lie on the rug before the fire on his back, when she, all naked would straddle over him, and with her cunt resting on his mouth, would stoop down and suck his prick. Then, when she had it standing up stiff and strong, she would place its head between the lips of her cunt, and sitting down would force it up. Then he would place his hands under her bottom, and help her to rise up and down. At other times he would lean back in the armchair, and she would sit in his lap, her naked bottom rubbing against his belly, while his prick was soaking in her cunt, and her hands on his balls.<break time="100ms" />I heard her say she liked this plan best, as his prick seemed to get further into her cunt.<break time="100ms" />Gussy and I watched them with the greatest interest, as long as my visit lasted, and tried to follow them in their various evolutions, frigging, sucking, fucking, holding the chamber pot for each other to make water; and every possible idea we could think of to vary the fun.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. T. T., wife of a lawyer; she had first been the wife of Dr. F., another lawyer.<break time="100ms" />Some moments in life, I could wish very long,<break time="100ms" />Because as the monkey said, pleasant but wrong;<break time="100ms" />'Tis sweet to remember some frolics I've had,<break time="100ms" />Though the angel who suffered them cries out, "Too bad."<break time="100ms" />Yes, grant me that angel, another man's wife,<break time="100ms" />She is by law, but to me she is life;<break time="100ms" />That rich feast of pleasure, that rapture, I'd call it,<break time="100ms" />That devil that tickles my intellect's palate.<break time="100ms" />I'm well read in woman, I seldom can find,<break time="100ms" />One that brings a new relish of joy to my mind;<break time="100ms" />But she's quite a treat, one that never can pall,<break time="100ms" />Think all you can think, she surpasses it all.<break time="100ms" />Oh would that I had her! -and had her just now,<break time="100ms" />I can make love much better, than verses, I vow;<break time="100ms" />Her, I ardently covet, and love, and esteem,<break time="100ms" />I saw but last night, in a sweet Golden Dream.<break time="100ms" />The dress that she wore, fitted close as her skin,<break time="100ms" />'Twas of Paradise fashion, ere fig leaves came in;<break time="100ms" />Her smooth birthday suit, all of flesh colour'd buff,<break time="100ms" />With a furbelow too, a divine little muff.<break time="100ms" />But a creature so fair's a mere victim for evil,<break time="100ms" />So she straightway received an address from the devil;<break time="100ms" />He came drest like a lawyer, so grand and severe,<break time="100ms" />And assured her she suited him, just to a hair.<break time="100ms" />O how could she bear such a lifeless old lover,<break time="100ms" />She who palpitates warm with excitement all over;<break time="100ms" />She who throbs like my heart, on the ravishing stretch,<break time="100ms" />How could she endure such a cold-blooded wretch?<break time="100ms" />She smiled at his pleadings - and then she saw me.<break time="100ms" />It was just before tasting the wit-giving tree!<break time="100ms" />And the barrister prim, a great man in his college,<break time="100ms" />Was to introduce her to the fair tree of knowledge.<break time="100ms" />But alas; with that knowledge, came misery too,<break time="100ms" />And the Eve of my vision, evanished from view;<break time="100ms" />The devil soon died, but the very next glimpse,<break time="100ms" />Betrayed she had now married one of his imps!<break time="100ms" />To escape the dull phiz of this crabbed attorney,<break time="100ms" />She to Italy flew, on a classical journey;<break time="100ms" />Next I met her, more lovely, though after twelve years,<break time="100ms" />In her dear little parlour, so private, up-stairs.<break time="100ms" />There knee pressing knee, and kind eyes within eyes,<break time="100ms" />Our converse still broken, with fluttering sighs;<break time="100ms" />We talked about books, and the way to improve,<break time="100ms" />But our tremors confessed the sweet fever of love.<break time="100ms" />Ah! would that we both had had wisdom at will,<break time="100ms" />Though it might have prevented us kissing our fill!<break time="100ms" />Those blisses are short, that most heavenly seem,<break time="100ms" />I woke, and behold, it was merely a dream!<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />PART III.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)<break time="100ms" />Alice led me by the hand, having closed the door behind us; a cold shiver passed over my frame, but plucking up courage, I never faltered, and we soon found a little green baize door, bolted on our side. "Hush!" she said, "this opens into quite a dark corner, behind the confessional box," as she gently withdrew the bolt, and we then noiselessly entered the chapel into a little kind of passage, between the box and the wall, and fortunately protected from observation by a large open-work screen, which completely hid us, but afforded quite a good view of the interior of the chapel. Guess our astonishment when we beheld both Lady St. Jerome and her niece in earnest conference with the two priests and overheard what passed.<break time="100ms" />Father Coleman. - "Well, Sister Clare, the Cardinal has ordered that you are to seduce Lothair, by all the arts in your power; every venial sin you may commit is already forgiven."
    </voice>
</speak>
