<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />He told me that he had seen his father fucking a girl in the hayfield, after the labourers had gone home. She had come back to look for something. Uncle met her, drew her behind one of the cocks, tossed up her clothes, and made her lie on her back with her legs up. He then unbuttoned his trousers, took out his prick, and kneeling between her thighs, shoved it into her cunt.<break time="100ms" />"It was at the other side of the hedge, and I heard him saying, 'Come here. Maggy, I want to give you something.'<break time="100ms" />"Thanks, sir, you are very good."<break time="100ms" />"But I want a kiss in return,"<break time="100ms" />He kissed her loudly. Then she said: "Oh, but, dear sir, you need not push your knee between my thighs. Ah! stop, you'll make me fall."<break time="100ms" />"Be quiet, Maggy, and I'll give you something more when I have done."<break time="100ms" />"I had been searching for an opening in the hedge, and at length between the bushes I caught sight of them just as he had got her on her back, with her belly and legs all exposed. When I first saw his big red-headed prick standing out stiffly from the hair at its base, I did feel ashamed to look, but I was so eager to see Maggy's cunt, and to observe how a real fuck was performed, that I would not for the world have turned away my eyes."<break time="100ms" />"He soon got his prick in, and drove it up her cunt. She seemed used to the sport, and as he went on fucking she heaved up and down, crying, 'Give it me, dear sir, give it me, hard and strong, oh! oh!'<break time="100ms" />'That's right, Maggy, give tongue, lift your arse, and tickle my balls.'"<break time="100ms" />"Maggy called out prick, cunt, arse, at every push, and their bellies smacked together, until giving one tremendous lunge, Father darted his prick into her cunt pressed her in his arms, and kissed her in great delight."<break time="100ms" />"Then he gave her something, and when she had arranged her dress, she stole quietly away."<break time="100ms" />"You should not be talking of these things, Gussy."<break time="100ms" />"No more I do, only to you, and you know I tell you everything."<break time="100ms" />About this time a new governess arrived. She was a pretty flaxen-haired girl named Lizzy. I soon remarked that Uncle was very attentive to her, and was always bringing her flowers and small presents.<break time="100ms" />She slept in a room next mine, and separated from it by a wooden partition, the two having formed but one apartment. I could hear every stir she made. I knew when she got out of bed, when she took her bath, and even when she sat on the chamber pot. I observed one day that in one spot the paper over the boards had cracked, and that there was a small open slit between them. On putting my eye close I could see into Lizzy's room quite plainly. A few nights after, when I was in bed, I heard whispering in her room. I got up softly and went to the slit. By the light of her fire, I saw Uncle with his arm round Lizzy, and heard her saying:<break time="100ms" />"Mr. C., do go away. Oh, my! Where are you dragging me? I won't sit on the bed with you. What do you mean by pushing me back. Don't attempt to raise my clothes. Oh! Where are you putting your hand? Take it away, you are very nasty. Don't lift my legs. I won't let you. You'll ruin me. You are hurting my hands."<break time="100ms" />"Well, take your hands out of the way. Here; put them on my prick if you like. Open. Open more. I tell you to keep quiet, or you'll waken Nelly."<break time="100ms" />"I won't let you put it in. You must not do it."<break time="100ms" />"Do let me, love - only just a moment. There, let it in. What's the use of all this struggling?"<break time="100ms" />"You'll kiss me. I'm so tired. What is it you want?"<break time="100ms" />"Only to fuck you my darling. To put my prick in here - into your sweet cunt and fuck you. There! There! It's getting in. Don't you feel it going up-up! How hot your cunt is. Isn't it nice?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, that's very nice. I like that. You may fuck me now. Push it in well. Oh. yes; push. Oh!"<break time="100ms" />"Push what in, my love?"<break time="100ms" />"Your prick! Your prick; dear Mr. C."<break time="100ms" />"Where do you like me to push my prick?"<break time="100ms" />"Into my cunt! Into my cunt!"<break time="100ms" />"What is my prick doing in your cunt, Lizzy?"<break time="100ms" />"Fucking me! Fucking me! Oh! so nicely. You may fuck me as hard as you like. Oh! Oh!"<break time="100ms" />Uncle had placed her on her back with her bottom projecting over the edge of the bed, her clothes were all up, her thighs stretched wide open, and her legs resting on his shoulders. He had let down his trousers, and tucked up his shirt, so I could see his great muscular rump working vigorously back and forward, driving his stiff moist prick in and out between the hairy lips of her cunt.<break time="100ms" />I felt greatly excited, and my cunt seemed burning with heat. I could not help putting my hand on it, and squeezing the lips as hard as I could.<break time="100ms" />Just then I felt someone's arm stealing round me, and a hand placed on my mouth to stifle my cry.<break time="100ms" />Gussy whispered in my ear: "It's me. Don't say a word. Feel my prick, how stiff it is. I'll put it into your cunt this way, and fuck you from behind, but keep watching, and tell me all they are doing. What do you see?"<break time="100ms" />"I see your father fucking Lizzy. She is on her back with her bottom over the edge of the bed, her legs up on his shoulders. I can see her cunt."<break time="100ms" />"What is it like?"<break time="100ms" />"A large hairy mouth sucking his prick."<break time="100ms" />"Is he fucking still? Go on, dear Nelly; it's just coming."<break time="100ms" />"He is heaving backward and forward, faster and faster. Now he is stooping over her, clutching her in his arms. How he drives his prick into her cunt! How she bounds to meet it. There! He is done! Push, Gussy! Hold me, or I shall fall! Oh! what a nice fuck! You have a darling prick, Gussy. Now let us rest, and I'll suck it for you to make it strong again."<break time="100ms" />After a while we heard them whispering again.<break time="100ms" />"Now," said Gussy, "let us change places. Sit here with your back to the partition, and you can play with my prick, while I look through and tell you all they are doing."<break time="100ms" />I took the head of his soft little tool in my mouth, and played with his balls and bottom while he looked through the opening.<break time="100ms" />"He is kneeling down and kissing and sucking her cunt; there, he has opened wide the lips, and is looking into its deep red chink; now he is licking round it with his tongue, while he rubs his nose against the hair-listen."<break time="100ms" />"What a delicious cunt you have, Lizzy; it smells so sweet, and has such thick round full lips, and although so large, the entrance itself is as tight as possible, and holds my prick like a glove. Now lie along the edge, put your hand on this poor fellow, and pet him a little before we try another bout."<break time="100ms" />"Now he is standing up, and she has her arm round his hip so as to reach his balls from behind, with her other hand she holds his prick; she is drawing up and down the soft skin, now she places its rosy head to her lips.<break time="100ms" />"Take it in your mouth, my love."
    </voice>
</speak>
