<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Or the State restrict the God-like Sex's privilege to whore?<break time="100ms" />Since clandestine harlots will in spite of Statutes lure.<break time="100ms" />In spite of all espionage to keep the men secure;<break time="100ms" />Methinks the Act is faulty, in not finding means to know<break time="100ms" />The Article that's warranted, from her that is not so.<break time="100ms" />A list should be placarded conspicuous to see,<break time="100ms" />Or some special Chignon ordered, for the Girls we guarantee.<break time="100ms" />And since on Prostitution 'tis resolved to legislate<break time="100ms" />(Like Cab fares and Pawnbroking, and the sale of bread by weight);<break time="100ms" />Methinks 'twere only logical to extend the Act's protection,<break time="100ms" />And not limit our paternal care to personal infection.<break time="100ms" />Why not advance another step, extortion to put down,<break time="100ms" />And regulate the charges of women of the town?<break time="100ms" />A Commission might be ordered, a scale of fees to draw,<break time="100ms" />Composed of the supporters of this Sanitary Law<break time="100ms" />(These Bishops, Deans and Doctors, who have found a new vocation<break time="100ms" />In preaching up the doctrine of the right of Fornication.)<break time="100ms" />How early that Commission could assemble every morn.<break time="100ms" />Taking evidence from Regent Street, the Argyle and Cremorne,<break time="100ms" />Making curious calculations, how to regulate aright<break time="100ms" />The charge for short engagements, and engagements for all night.<break time="100ms" />Meditating from the Cab rules, of suggestions the adoption.<break time="100ms" />A charge for work done, or by time, at the Engager's option.<break time="100ms" />For reference the Reverends their Bibles might turn over.<break time="100ms" />To see the charge of Tamar to her Israelitisch lover;<break time="100ms" />And ponder if the object of the Heaven-inspired Narrator<break time="100ms" />Was suggestions for the guidance of each future fornicator?<break time="100ms" />While all Schoolmasters - Bishops, who had on the subject brooded,<break time="100ms" />Could advise them whether birching should be extra or included.<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />Part III.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)<break time="100ms" />He hastily wrote the assignation on his tablets, and we made haste to return to the saloons from which we had been absent quite twenty minutes. A little while after, as I was sitting by the side of Alice, whispering my adventure in her ear, Lady Montairy, to whom I had previously been introduced, came and seated herself by my side. "Ah!" she said, with a sly look, "you're in a fair way to carry off the great prize; my sister Corisande will stand no chance."<break time="100ms" />"I've only danced one set with him," I replied, demurely.<break time="100ms" />"Ah!" she laughed, "it was not the Lancers I referred to, but your quiet stroll into the recesses of the conservatory. You had quite a lover's tete-a-tete."<break time="100ms" />"But we did not indulge in a Pas Sett!, as you did with His Grace," I laughed, enjoying her confusion.<break time="100ms" />She was speechless with surprise, her eyes fairly started with affright, and I hastened to reassure her, "I'm your friend, dear Lady Montairy, your secret is safe with me, and I hope you will not make any remarks in connection with myself and Lothair."<break time="100ms" />She squeezed my hand nervously, and asked, "Do you remember Fred's birthday? I was not there, but my brother Bertram was with his cousins the Vavasours, and passed as their brother Charlie, who happened to be too ill to go with them. I'm initiated into your society. We shall meet again," she added with a smile; "I must go now to keep my engagements."<break time="100ms" />The supper was a fairy feast, except for its substantial reality, and we returned home to Lady St. Jerome's charmed with everything, and especially with the fine prospect we seemed to have of future enjoyment.<break time="100ms" />Next day I made an excuse to go out alone to pay a visit to an old schoolfellow, and two o'clock found me sauntering through Burlington Arcade. Lothair was there to the minute, and gently whispered in my ear, as I was looking in a doll-shop.<break time="100ms" />"Now, this is really kind of Your Ladyship, and proves you can be depended on; I have made a most excellent arrangement, we have only to step across the road to the Bristol Hotel in Burlington Gardens, where I have ordered luncheon for myself and cousin, in a private apartment, and they know me too well to pry into my affairs."<break time="100ms" />The chamber-maid attended me in the bedroom, and as soon as I had laid aside my cloak, hat, andc, I rejoined Lothar in the adjoining apartment, where a sumptuous luncheon was set out.<break time="100ms" />Lothair, whose shyness of the previous evening seemed considerably dispelled, most gallantly insisted upon my partaking of refreshment, before a word of my communication should be uttered. "Besides," he said, "a little champagne will give you courage, if it is at all disagreeable; the scene last night was such a shock to both of us that if you now prefer to be silent I won't press you about what you mentioned in the excitement of such a moment."<break time="100ms" />His conversation was very lively all through the repast, and when we had nearly finished I asked him to ring for a little milk, which was brought to me; he was at the moment abstractedly examining the debris of a pate de foie gras. I poured part of the milk into two champagne glasses, and slyly added about ten drops of tincture of cantharides, with which Alice had provided me, to his portion. "Now, my Lord," I said, "I challenge you to pledge me in a glass of my favourite beverage, champagne and milk, I think it is delicious," pouring out the fizzing wine, and handing him the glass, which I first touched with my lips.<break time="100ms" />His eyes sparkled with delight as he drained it to the bottom, and flung the empty glass over his shoulder, exclaiming, "No one shall ever put their lips to that again, it was indeed a challenge, Lady Beatrice, after which nothing but the reality will satisfy me," then rising, he persisted in claiming the kiss I had, as he alleged, challenged him to take.<break time="100ms" />"Now," he continued, drawing me to a sofa, "let us sit down and hear the awful communication you hinted at; who were those wretched men?"<break time="100ms" />"Monsignore Berwick and Father Coleman," I replied; "did you ever hear of a secret sisterhood of St. Bridget, the nuns belonging to which devote both soul and person to the service of the Church?"<break time="100ms" />"No, never, go on," said Lothair, so I continued: "These nuns are all aristocratic ladies, who devote themselves, as I said, implicitly to the interests of Holy Mother Church, to satisfy and appease the lusts of her priests, as well as marry any influential man they think they can lead by the silken tie of matrimony; such, my Lord, are Lady St. Jerome and Miss Arundel."
    </voice>
</speak>
