<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />As to ourselves, we were indeed intoxicated with success, so that I shall never forget the goings on of that last night at school, how the girls rushed about to each other's rooms, and revelled in every kind of lasciviousness one with another. Sleep was banished from our eyes, and nothing but the advent of breaking-up day put an end to our orgie of sensuality.<break time="100ms" />Miss Flaybum was not visible next day, and the only reference she ever made to our memorable scene of retributive justice was an enormous charge for damaged glass in my school bill.<break time="100ms" />This will end my letter for the present, but, dear Nellie, when I return from my tour, perhaps I can tell you a little more of my experiences.<break time="100ms" />Your affectionate friend. ROSA BELINDA COOTE. (To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />When Lucy's fine rump was first bared to the twigs.<break time="100ms" />She was finely cut up and her flesh torn in shreds;<break time="100ms" />She cried out for mercy in her dire distress.<break time="100ms" />Promising amendment as we lowered her dress.<break time="100ms" />She had been most naughty, and a bad rude girl.<break time="100ms" />Who presumed the hair on her fanny to curl;<break time="100ms" />But the birch reached her quim as well as her bum.<break time="100ms" />The height of her agony was glorious fun.<break time="100ms" />Her frightened looks, and deep blushes of shame.<break time="100ms" />Set our hearts pit-a-pit, and our senses in flame;<break time="100ms" />The old cockolorums our cunnies would grope.<break time="100ms" />Then tossed us on sofas and had a fine stroke.<break time="100ms" />So all those slow coaches, who a rise scarce can get;<break time="100ms" />Come, pay your respect to Our Lady St. Bridget;<break time="100ms" />She'll warm up your blood till it boils in your veins,<break time="100ms" />And your penis all his pristine vigour regains.<break time="100ms" />Let the birch be your love, St. Bridget your saint,<break time="100ms" />Never flinch from the rod, nor think of a faint;<break time="100ms" />Swish - swish - let it fall, till the glow of desire.<break time="100ms" />Will run thro' your senses, and set them on fire.<break time="100ms" />Ah! then you can fuck! and fuck, ah! so well!<break time="100ms" />That my Muse quite fails your joys to foretell;<break time="100ms" />But with oceans of spending, the fuck never ending,<break time="100ms" />Your ecstasy goes on, for a long time extending.<break time="100ms" />An old Ballad upon the proposed Extension of the Contagious Diseases Acts to the Civil Population.<break time="100ms" />[The memorial to the Government for the extension of these Acts was signed by several Peers, six Bishops, ten Deans and Canons, forty-two Clergymen and Ministers, twenty-four Heads of Colleges and Masters of Public Schools, fourteen Professors of different Universities, nineteen Mayors, ten Chairmen of Quarter Sessions and Boards of Guardians, twenty-nine Sheriffs and Magistrates, andc.]<break time="100ms" />Vide letter of Messrs. J. B. Cuyenven and Berkely Hill to the Daily News, March 8th, 1871.<break time="100ms" />It was certain Holy Bishops, Noble Lords and bold M.P.'s.<break time="100ms" />Deans, Rectors, Heads of Colleges, and numberless M.D.'s<break time="100ms" />They met in solemn Council, to discuss in grave debate,<break time="100ms" />And solve a weighty question, they thought worthy of the State.<break time="100ms" />It was not Education, it was not Irish Church.<break time="100ms" />The Ballot and Permissive Bill, were both left in the lurch.<break time="100ms" />There may be other evils, but said they, the greatest evil is.<break time="100ms" />That a man can't have a woman, without the risk of Syphilis;<break time="100ms" />Said they, the state takes measures that tradesmen shall not cheat,<break time="100ms" />In selling meat, or fish, or fruit, that isn't fit to eat;<break time="100ms" />It supervises Mutton, and is down on faulty weight,<break time="100ms" />So to guarantee safe Harlots is the duty of the State.<break time="100ms" />(Now the women had no voice, or else they might have said.<break time="100ms" />"If you regulate the sale of Human flesh, like meat and bread<break time="100ms" />You should grant to us the tradesman's right, by action to recover<break time="100ms" />The wages of our labour against a bilking lover.")<break time="100ms" />So a noble Act was passed, the Preamble whereof ran,<break time="100ms" />"Whereas to fornicate is the right of every man.<break time="100ms" />"And whereas in exercise of that right are oft contracted<break time="100ms" />"Disagreeable reminiscences! Be it hereby enacted:<break time="100ms" />"That a special force of Peelers, henceforth each city pay.<break time="100ms" />"To apprehend all women, they suspect of being gay;<break time="100ms" />"Who if they don't disprove the charge before some worthy Beak.<break time="100ms" />"Shall by this Act, be Speculumed in batches, once a week;<break time="100ms" />"That in every Town a Surgeon, be appointed to the Post,<break time="100ms" />"With Speculums provided at the British Nation's Cost;<break time="100ms" />"And five hundred pounds per annum, to be quarterly paid down,<break time="100ms" />"To guarantee the soundness of the women of the Town."<break time="100ms" />Then happy were the Peelers of that sanctified Division,<break time="100ms" />That was specially deputed to this female supervision;<break time="100ms" />Thieves, Drunkards, and Garrotters, no longer were their care,<break time="100ms" />But they played the spy on women who were volatile and fair;<break time="100ms" />If they saw a flaunting Petticoat that showed too much of calf,<break time="100ms" />Or a naughty Girl, responding to an Ogle with a Laugh,<break time="100ms" />If she wouldn't let the Peeler have a cut in with the Swell,<break time="100ms" />Or tip from her earnings, the Justice not to tell,<break time="100ms" />Straightway the injured Peeler's virtuous conscience was relieved<break time="100ms" />By yielding to the Justice information he'd received;<break time="100ms" />And such unhappy damsels as a Peeler might select,<break time="100ms" />For reasons of his own, to be pronounced "suspect,"<break time="100ms" />Were all served with a Summons to disprove it to the Beak.<break time="100ms" />Or submit them to be Speculumed in batches once a week;<break time="100ms" />Then cried every youthful student, "That examining M.D.,<break time="100ms" />With £500 per annum, would be just the Post for me.<break time="100ms" />No wealthy wife with Coach and Pair, or Patients, would I seek<break time="100ms" />But I'd Speculum the ladies at £9 10s. per week!"<break time="100ms" />And thus began the era of Sexual legislation:<break time="100ms" />To man alone the State allows Free-trade in Fornication;<break time="100ms" />Diseased or sound - no matter - let him riot fancy free.<break time="100ms" />And gaily pox the ladies that the Peelers guarantee;<break time="100ms" />Is not Man the Nobler sex, for whom was Woman made?<break time="100ms" />And shall harassing Inspections his liberties invade?<break time="100ms" />For Man alone, the Bill of Rights, and Magna Charta passed;<break time="100ms" />And shall Free-born Fornicators be with dirty Harlots classed?<break time="100ms" />The sauce that suits the Goose, o'er the nobler Gander pour?
    </voice>
</speak>
