<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />For any young maiden it can do the trick.<break time="100ms" />Oh, joys there are plenty, but nothing like prick!<break time="100ms" />Air - "Gee, ho Dobbin."<break time="100ms" />Oh, Maidenhead-taking's a very great bore,<break time="100ms" />It makes cunt and prick so confoundedly sore;<break time="100ms" />But fucking the third time's like heaven above.<break time="100ms" />For your prick then glides in as you draw on a glove!<break time="100ms" />Gee up, Roger.<break time="100ms" />Wag up, Roger,<break time="100ms" />Roger's a thing that all women admire!<break time="100ms" />Oh, give me a damsel of blooming fifteen,<break time="100ms" />With two luscious thighs and a mouse-trap between,<break time="100ms" />With the fringe on the edge, and two red lips I say.<break time="100ms" />In her cunt I'd be diving by night and by day!<break time="100ms" />Gee up, andc.<break time="100ms" />That woman would be a disgrace to our land,<break time="100ms" />Who would not take a prick, when it stiffy does stand;<break time="100ms" />And when it droops low as if it were in dread,<break time="100ms" />She must tickle the balls, till it lifts up its head!<break time="100ms" />Gee up, andc.<break time="100ms" />Cunt is a treasure which monarchs admire,<break time="100ms" />Cunt is a thing that my theme doth inspire;<break time="100ms" />Cunt is a mighty temptation to sin,<break time="100ms" />But cunt is a hole that I'd ever be in!<break time="100ms" />Gee up, andc.<break time="100ms" />Prick is its friend, its first cousin, I ween,<break time="100ms" />Tho' prick I confess is a rare go-between;<break time="100ms" />Prick to a woman much joy can impart,<break time="100ms" />And prick is a thing that she loves in her heart!<break time="100ms" />Gee up, andc.<break time="100ms" />Then here's to the female who yields to a man,<break time="100ms" />And here's to the man who'll fuck when he can,<break time="100ms" />For fucking creates all our joy on earth,<break time="100ms" />And from fucking you know, we all date our birth.<break time="100ms" />Gee up, Roger,<break time="100ms" />Wag up, Roger,<break time="100ms" />Roger's a thing that all women admire.<break time="100ms" />Here lies the amorous Fanny Hicks,<break time="100ms" />The scabbard of ten thousand pricks,<break time="100ms" />And if you wish to do her honour,<break time="100ms" />Pull out your cock, and piss upon her.<break time="100ms" />Home they brought the warrior, fed<break time="100ms" />To repletion more than just;<break time="100ms" />And the servants, chuckling, said.<break time="100ms" />"He must shit or he will bust."<break time="100ms" />Then they gave him castor oil.<break time="100ms" />Pills and drugs of many a sort;<break time="100ms" />Yet despite their loving toil,<break time="100ms" />He would not be taken short.<break time="100ms" />Stole a maiden to the spot.<break time="100ms" />And emetics, laughing, dared;<break time="100ms" />Yet in vain she held the pot,<break time="100ms" />For he only belched and glared.<break time="100ms" />Came a nurse of ninety years.<break time="100ms" />An enema huge she bore;<break time="100ms" />Shoved it up amidst their jeers,<break time="100ms" />And he shat for evermore.<break time="100ms" />If anxious Venus, beauty's queen!<break time="100ms" />Your empire should endure.<break time="100ms" />Borrow Cecilia's face and mien,<break time="100ms" />Our homage to ensure.<break time="100ms" />Though perfect all the charms may seem,<break time="100ms" />That famed Apelles drew.<break time="100ms" />Not half so sweet are they, I deem.<break time="100ms" />As fair Cecilia's Cu.<break time="100ms" />The feelings of my faithful heart<break time="100ms" />My mouth shall still express,<break time="100ms" />Upon that Cu-, delicious part.<break time="100ms" />In rapture's wild caress.<break time="100ms" />Oh! ye, who ne'er disquiet felt,<break time="100ms" />Nor aught but virtue knew.<break time="100ms" />Whence is it? But your eye ne'er dwelt<break time="100ms" />Upon Cecilia's Cu.<break time="100ms" />Cecilia, think not, from my brain,<break time="100ms" />The souvenir can remove,<break time="100ms" />Of thy sweet Cu, 'twill there remain,<break time="100ms" />Imprinted fast by Love!<break time="100ms" />But if my thread of life should break,<break time="100ms" />Expire thy lover true.<break time="100ms" />May I flight 'mid kisses take,<break time="100ms" />Imprinted on thy Cu!<break time="100ms" />Tom brought home some friends,<break time="100ms" />And not finding his dear,<break time="100ms" />But only young Harry,<break time="100ms" />Who look'd rather queer.<break time="100ms" />(Papa) Hush, Harry! What nonsense!<break time="100ms" />Run, call your Mama!<break time="100ms" />(Boy) Mama and de Captain<break time="100ms" />Are gone to Ca-Ca.<break time="100ms" />(Papa) Hush, Harry! What nonsense!<break time="100ms" />Just hear the child talk!<break time="100ms" />(Boy) Captain pull down his breeches,<break time="100ms" />Ma pull up her frock!<break time="100ms" />A farmer and his wife, who had been to church one Sunday morning, were walking home through a country lane, when John said, "Excuse me, my dear, for a minute or two, I want to get over the hedge to do something for myself." After rather a long interval his loving wife, who had walked on a little, returned to look for him, and could hear her good man on the other side of the hedge, blasting, swearing, and damning at an awful rate. She managed to get over to him, and then seeing him stooping down as if troubled by a very hard motion, exclaimed, "John! John! how can you swear so, don't you remember what the parson said about the patience of Job?"<break time="100ms" />"Blast that damned Job," exclaimed the furious John, "he never had his balls caught in a rabbit trap! Why don't you make haste to help me?"<break time="100ms" />The poor fellow stooping down to ease himself, had really been caught, and his wife had to release him and help him home.<break time="100ms" />RESULT OF THE WHORING HANDICAP.<break time="100ms" />Syphilis... 1<break time="100ms" />Chancre ... 2<break time="100ms" />Bubo ... 3<break time="100ms" />Immediately the flag dropped Gonorrhea began making the running for Injection (a brown colt out of Syringe). Coming round the Chordee Bend, Poultice showed well to the front, but when once in the Straight was soon left behind.<break time="100ms" />They passed the Grand Stand in the following order: Syphilis first, Chancre second, Bubo third, and Suppuration a bad fourth, closely followed by Unction. Black Wash, Lint, and Copaiba. Testicle pulled up much distressed, Capsules bolted. Doctor's Bill (extra weight) came in last.<break time="100ms" />The Sporting Prophets say that if French Letter had not been scratched she would have altered the result of the race.<break time="100ms" />There was a young man of Berlin.<break time="100ms" />Whome disease had despoiled of his skin;<break time="100ms" />But he said with much pride.<break time="100ms" />"Though deprived of my hide,<break time="100ms" />I can still enjoy a put in."<break time="100ms" />There was a young woman of Cheadle,<break time="100ms" />Who once gave the clap to a beadle.<break time="100ms" />Said she, "Does it itch?"<break time="100ms" />"It does, you damned bitch,<break time="100ms" />And burns like hell-fire when I peedle."<break time="100ms" />There was an old Chinaman drunk,
    </voice>
</speak>
