<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I am glad my dearest wife got safe home, and without being whipped, for I should be very jealous if anyone should peep into Nannette's backside but myself. I assure you when I have got you once more in my arms, I'll so belabour it I'll make it black and blue, and cram it full of my elixir to nourish young Lord Tunbridge. Adieu my soul's life; think of your own.<break time="100ms" />FIELDING.<break time="100ms" />To my better-half,<break time="100ms" />The Countess of Fielding.<break time="100ms" />At Waddon.<break time="100ms" />THE TWO WOLVES.<break time="100ms" />"What a nasty smell there is in this den," said one wolf to another; "have you shit yourself?"<break time="100ms" />"No," said the other.<break time="100ms" />"Then," said the first wolf, "I must have done so myself." So he had. The moral of this fable is that though ever ready to spy into the defects of others, we are apt to overlook our own imperfections.<break time="100ms" />THE DOG AND THE COCK.<break time="100ms" />"What a large fellow you are!" said the Cock to the Dog. "I can fuck half-a-dozen hens, while you are getting halfway in."<break time="100ms" />"Very likely," said the Dog, "but when I am in I stay there fancy; look at my prick compared to yours. I don't call yours fucking at all, it's over before it's well begun." This fable teaches that I like a long prick best.<break time="100ms" />THE MONKEY AND THE DILDOE.<break time="100ms" />A pet monkey who had watched his mistress fill her dildoe with cream, waited a chance when she had ceased using it, being called away for a few minutes. "Now," said he, "I will have my fill of cream," so he sucked away, but unfortunately the lady had contracted syphilis, and the monkey died in convulsions. The moral of this fable is, that you should never suck dildoes.<break time="100ms" />THE FOX AND THE GANDER.<break time="100ms" />"You want a good stiff prick up your arse," said the Fox, when he found he could not catch the Gander.<break time="100ms" />"I've got one; I always wear it there," said the Gander, chuckling. "Sold again! Yah! Bloody Fool!" The Fox slunk off abashed. This shows that the same repartee does not suit everyone.<break time="100ms" />It has been suggested to the Editor of THE PEARL that there is a great necessity for a club where gentlemen might get their greens much cheaper and better than at present.<break time="100ms" />Women are so dear, and at the same time so deceptive in appearance, that one often pays heavily and yet only gets a stinking article for his generous outlay.<break time="100ms" />To obviate this, it is proposed to start a club, where at least twenty pretty governesses would be engaged at salaries of £100 per annum; there would be French, English, German, Russian, Italian, and even Zulu and Hottentots, so as to assimilate to every variety of taste. These ladies would accommodate the members whenever they might visit the club, and everything in the shape of dress and generous living and indulgence would be extended to these houris, to make them as agreeable as possible, and happy and contented with their fucktious situations.<break time="100ms" />Gentlemen members would have to pay a subscription of £1 per week, wines and refreshments of course being extra, but supplied at the lowest possible prices compatible with economy and efficiency.<break time="100ms" />Gentlemen desirous of submitting their names for admission as members, should do so at once to the Editor, Pearl Office, Cock Lane, London, E. C, as the number will be strictly limited to one hundred.<break time="100ms" />If a husband came home and found his wife being had by another man, what would he do?<break time="100ms" />That depends on his disposition.<break time="100ms" />The Polite husband would beg him not to draw until he'd spent.<break time="100ms" />The Considerate husband would offer soap, towel, and warm water, as soon as he drew.<break time="100ms" />The Funny husband would cry "Boh!" and tickle his arse with a feather.<break time="100ms" />The Good-Natured husband would remark that he liked buttered buns.<break time="100ms" />The Ceremonious husband would wait for an introduction.<break time="100ms" />The Just husband would sneer at the size of his balls.<break time="100ms" />The Modest husband would think his balls looked larger than his own.<break time="100ms" />The Refined husband would pull his shirt over his bottom.<break time="100ms" />The Cautious husband, with a large family, would ask if he had on a French Letter, and if not, request him to spend outside.<break time="100ms" />The Jealous husband would be annoyed, although he had on a French Letter.<break time="100ms" />The Suspicious husband would make his wife wash afterwards.<break time="100ms" />The Excitable husband would begin to frig himself.<break time="100ms" />The Shy husband would blush and walk away.<break time="100ms" />The Avaricious husband would want to charge for it.<break time="100ms" />The Mean husband would look to see if he'd used his cold cream.<break time="100ms" />The Epicurean husband would gamahuche his wife immediately afterwards.<break time="100ms" />The Conscientious husband would fear that he had neglected his wife.<break time="100ms" />The Cynical husband would be surprised that anyone should care to fuck his wife.<break time="100ms" />The Prompt husband would be up his arse before he could say, "Jack Robinson."<break time="100ms" />A poet, whose water taps had been stolen, as well as those of his landlady and another neighbour, affixed the following to a board in his front garden:<break time="100ms" />My landlady's cock has been stolen away;<break time="100ms" />As well as my own, and also my neighbour's.<break time="100ms" />Let us hope in contentment they lay,<break time="100ms" />Released for a while from their watery labours.<break time="100ms" />Bad luck to the rascal that cut off our cocks;<break time="100ms" />Surely one was sufficient his water to pass.<break time="100ms" />The bugger deserves to be stuck in the stocks.<break time="100ms" />With a cock in each eye, and the third up his arse.<break time="100ms" />Thou heavenly sun whose golden light<break time="100ms" />Displays the hills with verdure bright;<break time="100ms" />Sink thee, oh sink thee, in the west.<break time="100ms" />And bring the hour I love best.<break time="100ms" />This evening shall my bosom prove,<break time="100ms" />The richest ecstasies of love.<break time="100ms" />Soon as thy glorious light retires.<break time="100ms" />I look for her my heart admires;<break time="100ms" />A matron she of sober grace,<break time="100ms" />With wisdom printed on her face.<break time="100ms" />This evening shall my bosom prove,<break time="100ms" />The richest ecstasies of love.<break time="100ms" />And is my heart then grown so cold,<break time="100ms" />As to be pleased with matrons old;<break time="100ms" />When I might feast on younger things,<break time="100ms" />Ah, no! a lovely girl she brings!<break time="100ms" />This evening shall my bosom prove,<break time="100ms" />The richest ecstasies of love.<break time="100ms" />To war her soldier son has hied,<break time="100ms" />She offers me his blooming bride;<break time="100ms" />And if the girl my taste should please,<break time="100ms" />Her husband I advance with ease.<break time="100ms" />This evening shall my bosom prove,<break time="100ms" />The richest ecstasies of love.
    </voice>
</speak>
