<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Mrs. White (with tears in her eyes). - "Oh! Oh! Miss Coote, my dear young lady, don't be too hard on the children. Cut me to pieces rather."<break time="100ms" />She is soon tied by her wrists to the ladder, but left as she is, in all her clothes, for the present. Then they strip little Minnie and Lucy, and expose their pretty plump figures to our gaze. Mademoiselle takes Lucy on her knee, and I have the youngest, Minnie, only nine years old. The little creatures are all blushes, and quite crimson with shame as we turn them on our laps bottom upwards. They are evidently quite unused to inspection by strange ladies.<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote (to Minnie). - "How you do blush, my dear; are you afraid I shall hurt you so much? What a lovely little bottom, does your mother often slap it?" giving two or three fair spanks, which very much improve the lovely colour of the firm flesh, and makes the little thing twist about beautifully, as she feels the smart.<break time="100ms" />Minnie. - "Oh! Oh! Pray don't! How you hurt! I can't bear it, Miss Coote," beginning to cry, and the pearly tears dropping on my lap.<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle. - " So you little girls sold the fruit for your mother; did you, Lucy?"<break time="100ms" />Lucy. - "Father gave it to us to carry home."<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle. - "The old story of Adam and Eve. One tempted the other. So it was all father; mother quite innocent, eh?"<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote. - "I think I can make Minnie tell us a different tale to that, Mdlle. Fosse. They are little story-tellers as well as thieves," giving Minnie a good slap with her open hand. "Just try my plan, Mademoiselle."<break time="100ms" />Minnie shrieks and kicks about in pain as Miss Coote slaps away, and Mademoiselle does the same by Lucy, till both their bottoms are as rosy as peaches. Both little girls screaming loudly for mercy; laying the blame first on father, and then mother, as they find it is no use to deny it.<break time="100ms" />"Now, Jane," says Miss Coote, "hand us a couple of light birches. We must thoroughly cure them before they are let off." Then taking hold of the birch, she directs Jane to tie both little victims to the whipping post, and puts a tight pair of drawers on each to hide their blushing rumps.<break time="100ms" />Jane ties them up, side by side, by their wrists, the arms well stretched above their heads, and their toes only just reaching the floor. Then she produces two little pairs of very thin lawn drawers almost as delicate as muslin, so that the rosy flesh was slightly perceptible through the material. They were, if anything, rather too small, and fitted quite tightly (the youthful bottoms are so finely developed, considering the age of their owners) and leave a space of nearly six inches wide behind, where they gave a delightfully seductive view of the pink roseate flesh and the cracks of the anus; altogether their shamefaced confusion and distress, as they gracefully lift their little legs, one by one, into the drawers, and go through all three positions Jane manages to put them in, as she fastidiously arranges them for sacrifice, was a most delightful sight to me, gloating as I was in the anticipation of the pleasure the whipping would be sure to afford.<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote. - "Now, Mademoiselle, will you assist me in the whipping? I will do all the talking."<break time="100ms" />The mother here is so distressed at the sight of her children tied up for whipping that she tries to fall on her knees, but soon remembers herself, when her hands being tied up prevent her intention. "Oh! Oh! Miss Coote, do have mercy on my little girls," she sobs. "To think I should bring this on them. Oh! Oh!" trying to wring her hands.<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote. - "Hold your foolish noise, woman. I'm just going to begin. How do you like it, Minnie? How is it, Lucy?" beginning to switch them finely, soon making a lot of thin red marks all over their backs and bottoms. "Will you ever take my fruit again, you little hussies? Warm their bottoms well for them, Mademoiselle. Take the thieving impudence out of their posteriors."<break time="100ms" />The victims shriek in a series of shrill screams, their faces are scarlet, and the tears roll in a little stream down their pretty pitiful faces, and they beg and pray to be let off. "Oh! Oh! we will be good, andc."<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote and her friend are delighted; the sight is so stimulating, their blood rushes through their veins and raises their voluptuous feelings of sensuality to the highest pitch, the cries of pain are so much music to their ears, and they cut the little bottoms dreadfully till the blood starts from the weals; the poor agonized mother is another spirit, which only adds to their enjoyment, as although only a spectator she seems to feel every blow, and cries and sobs as if her heart would break.<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle. - "Look at the silly woman, you'll have something to cry for presently, Mrs. White."<break time="100ms" />The thin drawers are cut up, and torn into rags, the birches almost worn out, and the two flagellatrices would never have stopped, but Jane interposes, for little Minnie has fainted, and Lucy seems likely to go off too.<break time="100ms" />They untie them, and with a little water and pungent smelling salts soon revive the little one, then both mother and children are refreshed by some champagne, slightly dashed with a most stimulating liqueur.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. White, who had also been released, nurses her children on her lap. Caressing and kissing them, crying and hysterically sobbing over their sore bottoms. "Poor little dears; oh! Miss Coote, you have been cruel to the innocent things,"<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote. - "How dare you say innocent things when you taught them to steal. I'll make you confess your guilt, you bad woman."<break time="100ms" />Mrs. White, all of a tremble. - "Oh! My heart bleeds for their poor rumps, I can't help what I say."<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote. - "Take them away, and let Mary see to their bruises, then come back and help us to cheer up the mother a little; she's dreadfully depressed, poor thing," laughing ironically at Mrs. White.<break time="100ms" />Jane soon returns, and begins to prepare the mother for her punishment.<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote. - "Stretch her properly on the ladder; she's the worst of the lot, first tempting her husband, and then making the children help to steal."<break time="100ms" />Mrs. White. - "Oh! I didn't think you cared about the garden-stuff, it would have been spoilt."<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote. - "Then why didn't your husband ask me what to do with it? Did you not use the money to buy ribbons and dresses?"
    </voice>
</speak>
