<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"A better donkey never trod,<break time="100ms" />Here lies beneath this friendly sod,<break time="100ms" />My Ass!"<break time="100ms" />How oft I've sworn to Caroline,<break time="100ms" />The world no sight can show,<break time="100ms" />To match her locks, her lips divine,<break time="100ms" />Her bosom's hills of snow.<break time="100ms" />But oh! I find myself forsworn,<break time="100ms" />Two lips I have beheld;<break time="100ms" />Still lovelier, on this happy morn,<break time="100ms" />A mount that those excell'd!<break time="100ms" />For chance has shewn me all that lies<break time="100ms" />Beneath her virgin zone;<break time="100ms" />Sure never seen by any eyes<break time="100ms" />Of man, save mine alone!<break time="100ms" />As o'er my face the swing I drove,<break time="100ms" />As wider flew her thighs;<break time="100ms" />The opening heaven itself o' love<break time="100ms" />Met my delighted eyes!<break time="100ms" />Her bosom boasts no swell so fair<break time="100ms" />No tints that these eclipse;<break time="100ms" />Her head has no such auburn hair,<break time="100ms" />Nor such enchanting lips!<break time="100ms" />Yes I've beheld the mossy mount,<break time="100ms" />Where all the graces centre;<break time="100ms" />I've seen the rosy, nectar'd fount,<break time="100ms" />Where he she loves shall enter!<break time="100ms" />While from within her petticoat,<break time="100ms" />A warm and savoury breeze,<break time="100ms" />Full in my face, would sweetly float,<break time="100ms" />Loaded with ecstasies!<break time="100ms" />Then be not wrath my matchless maid,<break time="100ms" />Nor blush so deep with shame;<break time="100ms" />Nor I attack'd nor you betray'd,<break time="100ms" />Let chance then bear the blame!<break time="100ms" />Oh pardon me, and I'll confess,<break time="100ms" />That henceforth when I gaze<break time="100ms" />Upon the beauties of thy face,<break time="100ms" />My fancy elsewhere strays!<break time="100ms" />Then if a reddy conscious blush,<break time="100ms" />Thy angel forehead warms;<break time="100ms" />Upon our souls the hour shall rush.<break time="100ms" />That shew'd thy inmost charms.<break time="100ms" />When John Scott was minister of Dundee, he reproved Alick Anderson for ill-treating his wife; Alick tried to justify his conduct, but the minister observed, "Ou Alick mon, there must be something wrong on both sides!"<break time="100ms" />"True very true," cried Alick, "she has neither bubbies nor buttocks!"<break time="100ms" />There was a young lady of Harwich,<break time="100ms" />Who said on the morn of her marriage:<break time="100ms" />"I shall sew my chemise,<break time="100ms" />Right down to my knees,<break time="100ms" />For I'm damned if I fuck in the carriage!"<break time="100ms" />In a series of Letters to a Lady Friend.<break time="100ms" />LETTER VII<break time="100ms" />My Dear Nellie,-<break time="100ms" />In my last letter you had an account of some pretty everyday larceny, but in this you will read about a pretty young lady who was also a thief by nature, not from any necessity; in fact, it was a case of what they call in these degenerate days Kleptomania; no wonder when downright thieving is called by such an outlandish name that milk-and-water people have almost succeeded in abolishing the good old institution of the rod.<break time="100ms" />Miss Selina Richards was a cousin of Laura Sandon, my old schoolfellow and first bedfellow at Miss Flaybum's; bye-the-bye, can you explain or did you ever understand how girls can be fellows, but I know of no other term which will apply to the relationship in question. Is there no feminine to that word? It certainly is a defect of the English language.<break time="100ms" />Well, being on a visit to Laura when I was about eighteen, she mentioned the case to me, saying that her cousin Selina was such an inveterate thief her family were positively afiaid to let her go anywhere from home for fear she should get into trouble, and that her parents were obliged to confine her to her room when they had visitors in the house, as the young thief would secrete any trifles, more especially jewelry, she could lay her hands upon, "and you know, Rosa, what an awful disgrace it would be to an the family if she should ever be accused of such a thing."<break time="100ms" />Rosa.- "But have they never punished her properly, to try and eradicate the vice?"<break time="100ms" />Laura.- "They confine her to her room, and often keep the child on bread and water for a week, but all the starving and lecturing in the world won't do any good."<break time="100ms" />Rosa.- "Have they never tried a good whipping?"<break time="100ms" />Laura.- "It never seems to have entered the stupid heads of her father and mother; they are too tender-hearted for anything of that kind."<break time="100ms" />Rosa.- "Laura, dear, I don't mind confessing to you I should dearly love to birch the little voleuse; ever since I left school our last grand seance at the breaking-up party has quite fascinated me - when I think over the beautiful sight of the red bleeding posteriors, the blushes of shame and indignation of the victims, and above all the enjoyment of their distress at being so humiliated and disgraced before others. We often enjoy our old schoolbirchings in private, and a little while ago I administered an awful whipping to our gardener's wife and her two little girls for stealing my fruit, etc., and effected quite a cure, they are strictly honest now. You are coming to see us soon, can't you persuade your uncle and aunt to entrust Selina to your care, with the promise that I am to be thoroughly informed of her evil propensity; on second thoughts I think you should say you have told me, and that I offer to try and cure the girl, if they will only give me a carte blanche to punish her in my own way. You will have a great treat, we shall shock the girl's modesty by stripping and exposing her, you win see how delightful the sight of her pretty form is added to the distressing sense of humiliation we will make her feel; the real lovers of the birch watch and enjoy all the expressions of the victim's face, and do all they can to increase the sense of degradation, as well as to inflict terrible and prolonged torture by skilful appliance of the rod, and placing the victim in most painful, distended positions to receive her chastisement."<break time="100ms" />Laura.- "What an ogress of cruelty you have become Rosa!"<break time="100ms" />Rosa, kissing her.- "So will you my dear, with a little more experience, you are much older than me, but really younger in that respect; by judicious use of the rod a club of ladies could enjoy every sensual feeling of pleasure without the society of men. I mean to marry the birch (in fact I am already wedded to it), and retain my fortune as my independence."<break time="100ms" />Laura.- "What a paragon of virtue, do I really understand you pander to your sensuality without intercourse with men?"<break time="100ms" />Rosa.- "Come and see, that is my only answer to such a dear sceptic, only manage to bring the pretty voleuse with you, and you will have every reason to be satisfied with your visit."
    </voice>
</speak>
