<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Lady St. Jerome had an extraordinary gift of contraction in her vagina, it took hold of my cock, like a delicately soft hand with a frigging motion, as she wriggled and met my thrusts, of the most delicious kind. I grasped and moulded her lovely breasts with both hands, for she held me convulsively to her body, and I had no necessity to clasp her myself. Our conjunction was so exciting that I spent again immediately, under the touches of what I called her invisible hand, then steadying myself I revelled in love and lubricity for more than half-an-hour, both the dear ladies gasping, sighing, and sometimes when they spent giving vent to subdued shrieks of pleasure and dearment. Clare seemed quite as excited as her aunt, who I found was frigging her bottom-hole, and rousing all her lustful propensities to the utmost, with a disengaged hand, as soon as she found I was so safely rooted in herself that one arm could hold me.<break time="100ms" />"I can't tell you how we finished, for there seemed to be no end to it; however, about eleven o'clock we apparently awoke from a kind of delicious lethargy, into which we had all fallen, and we soon sufficiently composed ourselves to ring for the carriage and start for town; on the plea of keeping out the chilly night air, the windows were put up, and I had one or the other of them astride of my lap and spitted on the shaft of love till the noise of granite pavement under the wheels of the carriage warned us of the near approach to St. James' Square.<break time="100ms" />"I have promised not to marry, but expressed my wish to be received into the Church by the Holy Father himself soon after Christmas, when I will visit Rome on purpose; this will give me plenty of time to carry on my game, and prove to the Jesuits that I am now quite equal to the tricks they played on me, when they had me down at Vauxe before, and imposed on the weak senses of a poor boy, quite green to the ways of the world. I can love Clare, when I don't think of it, but if I do I should hate her even in the midst of our love transports."<break time="100ms" />Our time in town was getting short, so at my suggestion Bertram and St. Aldegonde arranged an early day with Lothair, for his initiation to the Paphian Circle.<break time="100ms" />We were still at Crecy House, and this time the affair was managed under cover of a small private party at the Duke of Brecon's, where we dismissed our carriages, and then drove out in those of his Grace for a country excursion, which of course only extended to Cheyne Walk. Everything was in readiness, and Lothair being admitted as usual, we quickly appeared in the garb of Madre Natura as before.<break time="100ms" />Partners were drawn for the first dance, my lot fell to the Duke of Brecon, whilst Lothair was drawn by Alice, and Lady Corisande presided at the piano, where her brilliant execution helped to add to the excitement engendered by the lascivious motions of the dance, in which, when the gentlemen and ladies changed partners as they went through the figure, they gave our bottoms a fine smarting spank, which we repaid by sharp little slaps on their extended cocks, soon getting tremendously warm and excited over our quadrille, and at the conclusion could scarcely restrain ourselves sufficiently to allow Lothair to give the usual kiss all round to our palpitating cunnies.<break time="100ms" />I noticed Lady Bertha very busy whispering to everyone, and soon found out that she was proposing a little bit of extra fun for us, of which the novice was of course to be the victim, whilst both pleasure and profit would accrue to the Paphian Circle.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Let those who never tried, believe,<break time="100ms" />In woman's chastity!<break time="100ms" />Let her who ne'er was asked, receive,<break time="100ms" />The praise of modesty!<break time="100ms" />Again I've been at Church to-day,<break time="100ms" />And eyed that angel stranger;<break time="100ms" />Whose yielding glances seem to say,<break time="100ms" />"I love, but dread the danger."<break time="100ms" />Too truly sung the Indian sage,<break time="100ms" />That "Father, Brother, Son,<break time="100ms" />To her who feels the sexual rage<break time="100ms" />Are lawful - all are one."<break time="100ms" />Tho' woman's virtue's true as steel<break time="100ms" />Before you touch her soul;<break time="100ms" />Still let it once the Magnet feel<break time="100ms" />'Twill flutter tow'rds the Pole!<break time="100ms" />Oh, jealous Cotterill, why so warm?<break time="100ms" />Because your congregation,<break time="100ms" />In spite of all you preach and storm,<break time="100ms" />Persist in fornication.<break time="100ms" />And so you think a ball-room dress<break time="100ms" />Unfitted for a pew,<break time="100ms" />And fain would check the wantonness<break time="100ms" />That gives the breasts to view.<break time="100ms" />"Indecent" is a cruel word<break time="100ms" />To use to strict church-goers,<break time="100ms" />It's very awful by the Lord<break time="100ms" />To call us rogues and whores.<break time="100ms" />In pews, like sheep in pens we sit,<break time="100ms" />While you indulge in barking,<break time="100ms" />If sheep will cast sheep's eyes a bit<break time="100ms" />It is not worth remarking.<break time="100ms" />The ball-room and the play-house gay<break time="100ms" />In India are so rare,<break time="100ms" />That church for those who play or pray<break time="100ms" />Is crowded by the fair.<break time="100ms" />Poor Cotterill - why then should he grieve<break time="100ms" />Because our glances roam?<break time="100ms" />He merely wants us all to leave<break time="100ms" />Our "Hearts and Souls" at home.<break time="100ms" />I joy the lecherous girl to squeeze,<break time="100ms" />I joy thy rage to see,<break time="100ms" />So first I sin myself to please<break time="100ms" />And next to anger thee.<break time="100ms" />The silliest goose that swims the lake<break time="100ms" />Is known to be the Dotterel,<break time="100ms" />That spelling must be a mistake.<break time="100ms" />The name I'm sure is Cotterill!<break time="100ms" />(A statue in the Florentine Gallery.)<break time="100ms" />Genius of woman, glorious form<break time="100ms" />Of perfect loveliness,<break time="100ms" />I worship thee, with beauty warm,<break time="100ms" />Released from every dress.<break time="100ms" />Oh smile on him to Thee who bows,<break time="100ms" />Who worships Thee alone;<break time="100ms" />And pays his deep impassioned vows,<break time="100ms" />At none but Beauty's throne.<break time="100ms" />And bless thou Her whose pencil gave,<break time="100ms" />Thy dazzling limbs to light,<break time="100ms" />Naked, as rising from the wave,<break time="100ms" />They shone all rosy bright.<break time="100ms" />It was a homage due to Thee,<break time="100ms" />By grateful Chloris paid;<break time="100ms" />For Thou with every conquering charm,<break time="100ms" />Has't blest the golden maid.<break time="100ms" />And every touch her pencil gave,<break time="100ms" />To each alluring part;<break time="100ms" />Has bound in firmer spells the slave,<break time="100ms" />Of pleasure, love, and art.<break time="100ms" />Oh sacred, fervent, silent be,<break time="100ms" />Our worship at Thy shrine;<break time="100ms" />No eye profane shall ever see,
    </voice>
</speak>
