<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Miss Coote is quite exhausted with her exertions, and sinking on a sofa, fondly embraces her friend Laura, describing to her all the thrilling sensations she has enjoyed during the operation, which the flushed cheeks and sparkling soft large blue eyes of Laura show she is beginning to duly appreciate.<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle Fosse and the servants lay Selina on the floor, and sprinkle her face with water, whilst one of them uses a very large fan most effectively; her lacerated bottom is sponged with strong salt and water, and she soon shows signs of regaining animation. Sighing and sobbing, "Where, where am I? Oh! I remember, Miss Coote's cut my bottom off. Oh! Oh! Ah! How it smarts and burns!" They pour a little liqueur down her throat, and she is soon quite conscious again, and cries quite hysterically over her pickled state.<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle.- "Now for the finishing touch. Mary, fetch that pot from the kitchen, and bring the bag of feathers."<break time="100ms" />Selina (piteously).- "Oh, haven't you done yet? What have I to suffer?" wringing her hands in apprehension.<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle.- "Here it is. We won't keep you in suspense," taking the brush from a pot of warm tar, held by Mary. "This will heal your bruises, and prevent the flies getting at your sore bottom, this warm weather."<break time="100ms" />They make her stand up, and Mademoiselle paints all over her posteriors, and the lower part of her belly inside her thighs, and even the crack of her bottom, with the hot stuff, regardless of the great pain she is inflicting.<break time="100ms" />Selina (shrieking in fearful distress and shame at this degradation).- "Ah! This is worse than all, you're actually scalding me; my skin will peel off," dancing about in excruciating agony.<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle (laughing).- "My dear, it is to heal and keep your skin on. We're going to cover you with nice warm feathers. You never felt so comfortable in your life as you will presently."<break time="100ms" />The ceremony was both amusing and exciting, but it would be impossible to describe the poor girl's misery and dreadful shame. Her shrieks and appeals of "Oh! Ah! It will never come off," especially as they lift her up and roll her bottom and front in a great heap of feathers, taking care to shove them in everywhere, so as to thoroughly cover all the tar.<break time="100ms" />This is the finale, and she is led from the scene of her punishment and degradation; but that was not all; every day for nearly three weeks she had to strip and exhibit her feathery bum for inspection and laughing remarks. I need scarcely say the ordeal she went through effected a radical cure of the Kleptomania.<break time="100ms" />Do you not think, dear Nellie, my plan would cure the Kleptomaniacs of the present day? It would be well worth a trial.<break time="100ms" />Yours affectionately, ROSA BELINDA COOTE.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Sweet is the memory of the scenes<break time="100ms" />In boyhood I enjoyed,<break time="100ms" />Hot vigour thrilling in my veins,<break time="100ms" />By no fruition cloyd.<break time="100ms" />So innocent a child I seem'd<break time="100ms" />That Catherine, Jane, Eliza,<break time="100ms" />Would treat me as a girl, nor dream'd<break time="100ms" />That I was e'er the wiser.<break time="100ms" />I many a naked frolic spied,<break time="100ms" />Nor seem'd a whit to care,<break time="100ms" />With changeless glance serene I eyed<break time="100ms" />Their sexual members bare.<break time="100ms" />All fear'd the strict severities<break time="100ms" />Of Mistress and of Master,<break time="100ms" />Who thought to crush propensities<break time="100ms" />That only throve the faster.<break time="100ms" />But when I was thirteen I grew<break time="100ms" />Too big a boy for this,<break time="100ms" />The girls grew timid - well they knew<break time="100ms" />I might do more than kiss.<break time="100ms" />No longer Jane would offer me<break time="100ms" />The clean shirt nice and warm,<break time="100ms" />And turn me up and cuddle me,<break time="100ms" />Without supposing harm.<break time="100ms" />And Catherine never called me now<break time="100ms" />The bathroom door to keep,<break time="100ms" />The while she bathed, lest any came<break time="100ms" />And say, "You must not peep."<break time="100ms" />Nor Harriet, when she climb'd the trees,<break time="100ms" />Would let me now stand under,<break time="100ms" />All seem'd to guard their modesties<break time="100ms" />With care that made me wonder.<break time="100ms" />But fostering Venus kindly led<break time="100ms" />Her young disciple still,<break time="100ms" />Although I kept my maidenhead<break time="100ms" />Sorely against my will.<break time="100ms" />For though from British blood I sprung<break time="100ms" />Yet born in India's land,<break time="100ms" />I felt while callow, raw and young<break time="100ms" />Cythera's guiding hand.<break time="100ms" />And night by night, when fast asleep,<break time="100ms" />Wits, nerves upon the stretch,<break time="100ms" />My melting heart I could not keep,<break time="100ms" />I was an amorous wretch.<break time="100ms" />One day I chanced to climb outside<break time="100ms" />My cousin's bathing room,<break time="100ms" />And found a hole through which I spied<break time="100ms" />The place I'd used to roam.<break time="100ms" />I sigh'd to think how oft the girls<break time="100ms" />Had idly let me in,<break time="100ms" />"It's nobody but little Charles,<break time="100ms" />No matter though he's seen."<break time="100ms" />Yes, I was their sole favourite,<break time="100ms" />No other boy was suffer'd<break time="100ms" />To share in many a luscious sight<break time="100ms" />To me so freely offer'd.<break time="100ms" />"Those joys (thought I) are now no more!"<break time="100ms" />I started - at that minute,<break time="100ms" />Dear Kate came to the bathroom door,<break time="100ms" />She lock'd herself within it.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, do I dream, or is it true?<break time="100ms" />And is she going to bathe,<break time="100ms" />And treat me to the fullest view<break time="100ms" />Of all above, beneath?"<break time="100ms" />She dropt her gown, and one by one<break time="100ms" />She stript her of her clothes,<break time="100ms" />Her smock is all she now has on,<break time="100ms" />"Oh, will she nought expose?"<break time="100ms" />There now it's off- and Catherine stands,<break time="100ms" />In utter nudity,<break time="100ms" />And neither of her rosy hands<break time="100ms" />Conceals her modesty.<break time="100ms" />I saw her right before my eyes<break time="100ms" />Naked, stark naked stand,<break time="100ms" />The blooming centre of her thighs<break time="100ms" />As naked as my hand.<break time="100ms" />What see I now! what see I not!<break time="100ms" />Is Kate a woman grown?<break time="100ms" />She was a little girl I thought,<break time="100ms" />But lo, she's fully blown:<break time="100ms" />Oh look at her sweet fie for shame,<break time="100ms" />With pouting lips so red.<break time="100ms" />Oh look at her dear frisky game,<break time="100ms" />Her open maidenhead!<break time="100ms" />For Ravishing Margaret Edson, a child under the Age of 12 Years, at York Assizes, March 31st, 1775.
    </voice>
</speak>
