<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The sight of our red smarting bottoms and bursting pricks was too much for Annie and Rosa, and they were inflamed by lust, so throwing themselves backward on the bed, with their legs wide open and feet resting on the floor, the two dear girls presented their quims to our charge, as with both hands they held open the lips of their delicious cunts, inviting our eager cocks to come on. We charged them at once, under the impulsive urging of the rods, gave a few delightful fucking motions, then withdrew and trotted round the room again, this we constantly repeated to prolong our enjoyment, till at last the dear girls could stand it no longer, their arms clasped us firmly, whilst the rods cut away with extra force to make us complete their pleasure; it was a most luxurious finish, we all spent with screams of delight, and lay for a few moments in a delicious state of lethargic exhaustion till we awoke to find Sophie, Polly, Emily, and Louisa all rolling on the floor in the delights of gamahuching.<break time="100ms" />After this the two dear girls begged, with tears in their eyes, that Frank and Walter would make women of them, so that they might really taste the wildest delights of love.<break time="100ms" />"Then, dears," said Rosa, with a sly laugh, "you must kiss them, and make their exhausted cocks stiff again, and then we will lend the two boys to you."<break time="100ms" />We sat on the bed by the side of our late fucking partners, who we kissed, fondled and frigged, whilst Emily and Louisa, kneeling between our knees, sucked our pricks up to standing point, as their hands drew back our foreskins or played with our balls. Stiff and rampant as we were we entreated them to go on for a little longer, till feeling ourselves almost at spending point, Polly and Sophie arranged two bolsters and some pillows on the floor in the most advantageous manner, the sisters were each placed with two pillows under their bottoms, whilst their heads rested on the bolsters. Annie and Rosa then conducted us to the victims, who impatiently awaited their immolation to the god of love with open legs and longing cunts. The two mistresses of the ceremonies took our pricks in hand, and directed them to the path of bliss. Emily was my partner again; she threw her legs over my back and heaved up to meet the fatal thrust which was to be the death of her troublesome virginity.<break time="100ms" />I had no time to see how the others progressed, but heard a smothered shriek of agony from Louisa, as no doubt Frank achieved her fate for her; my partner was more courageous, she glued her lips to mine, sucking in my tongue in the most ardent manner imaginable, even whilst my prick was tearing through her hymen; my spending deluged her wounded quim, and we soon lost all thoughts of pain when we recommenced a lovely fuck, moving slowly at first, till her rapid motions spurred me on to faster plunges, her deliciously tight cunt holding me like a hand, in fact so tight that I could feel my foreskin drawn backwards and forwards at every shove.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! you dear fellow, push on, kill me with delight!" she screamed in ecstasy, as we came again together, and I was equally profuse in my words of endearment.<break time="100ms" />As we lay still after it was over her tight-fitting cunt seemed to hold and continually squeeze my delighted prick so by its contractions and throbbings that I was ready again directly, and we ran another thrilling course before she would let me try to withdraw.<break time="100ms" />Frank and Louisa had been equally delighted with each other, and thus the two sisters each lost her maidenhead almost at the same moment.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Was given me by my cozen SC of Kempston, and written in a Tarpaulin style.<break time="100ms" />Madame,-<break time="100ms" />Premising you are safe returned to Towne, I made bold to acquaint you that Mr. F- is lately arriv'd art ye haven of Matrimony; He had been long in ye middle state of Purgatory between ye Church and ye Ladyes Chamber; ere she with ye advice of her mother, and some other experienced Ladyes, was lanced forth into ye marriage bed. The Vessell had been 14 years and three months on Building, that it is thought she will care well under Sail. It is a fine smooth ship, I will promise you, and one of ye first-rate; and likely to doe ye King good Service if ably and well man'd. The only fault there is (if any) she is too narrow in ye Poope. She hath a fine shroud, and all difficulty soone vanish'd saving only ye maine yard may prove too burly for the middle Deck. The Capt. it is thought this night will goe on board or her; hee is bound for ye Straites Mouth, and cannot come off without blood-shed: Nay worse; 'tis fear'd if opposition be made, hee may be forced to spend his provision in ye channell, and soe returne without doeing ye Kingdome a penny worth of service.<break time="100ms" />By the Rev. Mr. Bray, on the Death of his favourite Donkey<break time="100ms" />How well do I remember yet<break time="100ms" />How very proud I used to get<break time="100ms" />When, like a little king, I'd sit,<break time="100ms" />Upon my Ass!<break time="100ms" />When seated in his nice warm back<break time="100ms" />My tiny, little whip I'd crack,<break time="100ms" />And with my youthful hand I'd smack<break time="100ms" />My Ass!<break time="100ms" />And when we galloped o'er the lea<break time="100ms" />I shouted with delight and glee,<break time="100ms" />For all the girls came out to see<break time="100ms" />My Ass!<break time="100ms" />With him my frugal meals I'd share<break time="100ms" />And nurture him with greatest cafe,<break time="100ms" />And dally with the long, soft hair<break time="100ms" />Upon my Ass!<break time="100ms" />In meadows green he'd love to play<break time="100ms" />And, when tired out, at close of day,<break time="100ms" />You then, of sweet delicious hay,<break time="100ms" />Could smell my Ass!<break time="100ms" />And when through dirty lanes we'd scud<break time="100ms" />And get bespattered o'er with mud,<break time="100ms" />I'd get some water when I could.<break time="100ms" />And wash my Ass!<break time="100ms" />But someone served him such a trick-<break time="100ms" />At first they hit him with a stick,<break time="100ms" />And then with heavy boots did kick<break time="100ms" />My Ass!<break time="100ms" />One day he got beyond my reach,<break time="100ms" />Into a pond, I gave a screech,<break time="100ms" />For a blood-thirsty, hungry leech<break time="100ms" />Did suck my Ass!<break time="100ms" />And oh! his fate I do bewail,<break time="100ms" />He backed one day against a rail,<break time="100ms" />And a long, pointed, rusty nail<break time="100ms" />Stuck in my Ass!<break time="100ms" />Alas his end I soon did see;<break time="100ms" />A woodman cutting down a tree,<break time="100ms" />Did slip, and, barely missing me,<break time="100ms" />Did axe my Ass!<break time="100ms" />I saw him die, I watched the gore<break time="100ms" />Run from the wound as home they bore<break time="100ms" />My dearest friend - my wounded, sore,<break time="100ms" />And bloody Ass!<break time="100ms" />My grief for him was most sincere,<break time="100ms" />The pain was more than I could bear,<break time="100ms" />So now, kind friend, come shed a tear<break time="100ms" />Upon my Ass!<break time="100ms" />Perhaps this epitaph is odd-
    </voice>
</speak>
