<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Mary Edson stated: I am the child's mother. On the Friday before New Year's Day, I perceived my daughter was ill, I asked her what she had done to herself (as she had trouble in making water), if she had fallen and hurt herself; she said no. On Sunday, the 1st January, when I stripped her I saw her shift very much daubed with what had come from her, which gave me a great shock.<break time="100ms" />Q.- What colour was it?<break time="100ms" />A.- A yellow colour mixed with red. When I saw her in that condition, I said if you do not tell me what you have done with yourself I will take the skin off your backside. As she would not tell me I got a birch rod, and twining her over my lap gave her bum a sharp tickling, when she said that Captain Powell sent for her brother and her, and he gave her brother a halfpenny to buy some sweets. After the boy went out the Captain barred the door, and then he put his finger up her body and hurt her very much. I was much surprised, and sent for Mrs. Nurser, a neighbour, who advised me to send for Dr. Lee, who lives at Knaresborough. In the afternoon too we asked her what Captain Powell did to her, and she then said Captain Powell unbuttoned his breeches and took out his cock and put it into her. I asked her if she felt anything come from him. She said she thought he made water in her. She said he sat in his chair and took her before him, and she shewed the motion he made in the chair, then he took her upstairs and did the same again.<break time="100ms" />Q.- From the appearance of the colour on the shift did you think it had the same appearance as that which comes from a man on those occasions?<break time="100ms" />A.- To the best of my judgment I thought it was. Mr. John Lee, a surgeon, said that Mr. Edson, the father of the child, making application to him to examine his daughter, he attended at his house, when he inspected the child, and found her private parts much inflamed and swelled, which convinced him she had received some injury; there was likewise a discharge from the parts, which made him afraid it was venereal. He attended and administered to her about six weeks.<break time="100ms" />Q.- Did it appear to you there had been any violence used by a man's penis?<break time="100ms" />A.- I cannot say I formed any judgment as to the cause.<break time="100ms" />Q.- Suppose a man had introduced his private parts, would it have occasioned this?<break time="100ms" />A.- Yes it would.<break time="100ms" />Q.- Would a finger being put there occasion the excoriation?<break time="100ms" />A.- Yes it might. If a man had entered the vagina of the child and entered into her body, I should have thought it would have had a different appearance. It would have brought away blood, but I observed none.<break time="100ms" />Margaret Edson (the child).<break time="100ms" />COURT.- What age are you?<break time="100ms" />A.— Ten-and-a-half<break time="100ms" />Q.— Do you tell lies?<break time="100ms" />A.— No.<break time="100ms" />Q.— Will you tell me the truth?<break time="100ms" />A.— Yes.<break time="100ms" />Q.— Do you know Captain Powell? Look round and see if he is here.<break time="100ms" />A.— There is Captain Powell, pointing to the prisoner.<break time="100ms" />Q.— Now tell us what Captain Powell did to you.<break time="100ms" />A.— I and my brother was at Mrs. Raper's playing with her little boy; we did not stay long. My brother and I were going home, and Captain Powell said, "Come hither, Peg, come hither." My brother went with me to Captain Powell, and he gave my brother a halfpenny to go and buy sweets. My brother went, and then Captain Powell bolted the door.<break time="100ms" />Q.— What did he do after that?<break time="100ms" />A.— He put one hand round my waist and turned up my clothes.<break time="100ms" />Q.— Where was he?<break time="100ms" />A.— He was sitting in a chair.<break time="100ms" />Q.— How was you standing?<break time="100ms" />A.— On the floor before him, between his legs.<break time="100ms" />Q.— What did he do?<break time="100ms" />A.— He unbuttoned his breeches and took his cock out.<break time="100ms" />Q.- How did you know it was his cock?<break time="100ms" />A.— I saw it; I saw him take it out.<break time="100ms" />Q.— What did he do after that?<break time="100ms" />A.— He put his cock in my arsehole.<break time="100ms" />Q.— Tell us that again?<break time="100ms" />A.— He unbuttoned his breeches, took out his cock, and put it in my arsehole.<break time="100ms" />The jury did not wish to hear any more, and he was indicted at the next assizes for a common assault, and found guilty.<break time="100ms" />The wife of a City gentleman one day found in his pocket a billet from a ladylove of his, asking him to come that evening to supper, and that she had fowls and pickled pork.<break time="100ms" />The husband came home at his usual time, and told his wife that he had some particular business to transact that evening, which would keep him out rather late.<break time="100ms" />"Very well, dear, but you can't go out in that soiled shirt, come upstairs and change it," responded his tender better half.<break time="100ms" />She went with him to their bedroom, and with her jokes and larking soon gave him such a cockstand that he tossed her on the bed and had a good fuck.<break time="100ms" />Proceeding to finish dressing she again interrupted him with the remark that "he could not go out with such dirty stockings, now John let me pull them off and put on a clean pair for you."<break time="100ms" />This led to further dallying, especially when she remarked, "how silly his cock looked with its head hanging down, how she had taken the life out of it; la, I wonder if it can stand again dear," as she played with and kissed his limp concern. This led to another loving fuck, which ended by her giving him a rapturous kiss, as she exclaimed, "I believe, John, you have made me a baby at last. Now, my dear, I don't mind if you go and have the 'fowls and pickled pork.'"<break time="100ms" />But the husband declared "he would be damned if he did now."<break time="100ms" />N.B.- The Editor of THE PEARL would advise married ladies not to trust too implicitly in the belief "that if they fuck their husband well before he goes out, they may safely trust him." Our experience is that it only tends to make the men more excitable; we once knew a person (not ourself of course), who would have three different women on the way home from business, and then fuck his wife well when he went to bed, which he would not have thought of otherwise.<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />PART IV.<break time="100ms" />I must now return to my liaison with Lothair; he had promised to meet me again in a week, when I hoped to hear the particulars of his drive to Richmond.<break time="100ms" />We lunched again at the Bristol Hotel, and without having recourse to the tincture, I found him almost as hot and impulsive as before. "Ah! Beatrice," he said, as we lay exhausted on the sofa, after a series of delicious encounters, "I cannot express half the gratitude and devotion I ought to have; for you, not satisfied with making me happy yourself, quite unselfishly advised me how to enjoy the two nuns. But first tell me of that Society of Love, which you promised to introduce me to, and then you shall have my adventure."
    </voice>
</speak>
