<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />For they a' do't, andc.<break time="100ms" />The goulocks an' the snails do't<break time="100ms" />The cushie doos and quails do't,<break time="100ms" />The dogs, the cats,<break time="100ms" />The mice, the rats,<break time="100ms" />E'en elephants an' whales do't.<break time="100ms" />For they a' do't, andc.<break time="100ms" />The wee bit cocks an' hens do't,<break time="100ms" />The robins an' the wrens do't,<break time="100ms" />The grizzly bears,<break time="100ms" />The toads an' hares,<break time="100ms" />The puddocks in the fens do't.<break time="100ms" />For they a' do't, andc.<break time="100ms" />The boars an' kangaroos do't,<break time="100ms" />The titlins an' cuckoos do't,<break time="100ms" />While sparrows sma',<break time="100ms" />An' rabbits a'<break time="100ms" />In countless swarms an' crews do't,<break time="100ms" />For they a' do't, andc.<break time="100ms" />The midges, fleas, and bees do't,<break time="100ms" />The mawkes an' mites in cheese do't,<break time="100ms" />An' cauld earthworms<break time="100ms" />Crawl up in swarms,<break time="100ms" />An' underneath the trees do't,<break time="100ms" />For they a' do't, andc.<break time="100ms" />The kings an' queens an' a' do't,<break time="100ms" />The Sultan an' Pacha do't,<break time="100ms" />An' Spanish dons - loup off their thrones,<break time="100ms" />Pu' doon their breeks, an' fa' to't.<break time="100ms" />For they a' do't, they a' do't<break time="100ms" />The grit as weel's the sma' do't,<break time="100ms" />Frae crowned king<break time="100ms" />To creeping thing,<break time="100ms" />'Tis just the same - 'they a' do't!<break time="100ms" />Her clear melodious voice sounding distinctly through the apartment had such a thrilling effect that we all joined in the chorus at the end of each verse, and never before felt so excited or saw such a scene of delicious wantonness as was displayed on every side, till at last exhaustion compelled us reluctantly to give up the engagement, and after a short rest we returned in the carriages to the Duke's mansion, as if we had only had an afternoon's drive.<break time="100ms" />This was altogether a memorable day, for as soon as we got back to Crecy House, Corisande whispered to me that as the gentlemen had all been fairly used up, her sisters had resolved to have an evening to ourselves whilst the gentlemen were in Parliament or at their clubs recruiting their enervated abilities by wine, smoke and cards. We might be sure of them till six A.M. at least, and the afternoon had left us all in such a burning unsatisfied state that they had impressed into our service four handsome young fellows, two footmen and two pages, who had never yet been admitted to any freedom with their mistresses, but Lady St. Aldegonde had already sworn them to secrecy as to what they might see in the evening, and given her instructions to have everything prepared in her own private drawing-room, so as to be ready as soon as the rest of the establishment had retired for the night.<break time="100ms" />It was past ten o'clock when we arrived home, but Bertha was so clever, it was all devised and ordered in a few minutes, the footmen, and pages little suspecting the scene they were to be introduced to when taking their oaths of secrecy. Everything promised a deliciously enjoyable affair, especially as we had to undertake to seduce them to our purposes.<break time="100ms" />In less than an hour-and-a-half, it was all ready; the Duchess was still keeping her room, so Bertha dismissed all except John, James, Charles and Lucien (the latter a fine handsome French page) as well as two pretty lady's-maids, Fanny and Bridget. There were five of us ladies who sat down to a game of cards, for which the party was ostensibly designed, all of us very lightly attired in the most neglige style as if quite indifferent to any little exposures we might make of our charms.<break time="100ms" />"My luck is dead this evening," exclaimed Lady Montairy, throwing her cards down; "I shall be ruined if I sit here; what do you say to a dance; let's get the servants to join us for fun; come Lucien, have a waltz with me round the room, I feel so low spirited I don't care what I do to drive it away."<break time="100ms" />"Fie, sister! how you make the boy blush, but I wouldn't mind a dance myself if it were not for the thing getting known," replied Corisande.<break time="100ms" />"Let's have a downright spree for once, John, James, and all of you will keep it secret, I should so like to know how you enjoy yourselves downstairs," laughed Bertha.<break time="100ms" />"Your Ladyship's slightest wish is binding upon us," replied John, most respectfully, speaking for the others, "and I am sure none of us would betray such a secret, when ladies condescend to a little familiar fun with their domestics."<break time="100ms" />Bertha seated herself at the piano, and everything was cleared out of the way for a waltz. Lady Montairy led off with Lucien, I proposed to Charles, a very handsome youth of seventeen, whilst Alice and Corisande had the two good-looking footmen, John and James for partners, Bridget and Fanny making a female couple.<break time="100ms" />What fun we had, how flushed and excited our partners looked as we clung to them in the voluptuous evolutions of this inspiriting waltz, as the strains of Lady Bertha's talented execution seemed to thrill through our souls; the young fellows quite delighted us by their easy graceful motions and manners, having evidently profited by their everyday experience in seeing their superiors conduct themselves in society.<break time="100ms" />At last we stopped from sheer exhaustion, Lady Montairy giving Lucien quite an amorous kiss, as she led him to a sofa, pretending she did it to put him at his ease, and we all followed her example, my partner excitedly returning my embrace with ample interest and ardour, his hot burning lips sending a thrill of desire through my frame.<break time="100ms" />Pretending to wish to cool myself a little I walked him into the next room, which was only lighted by the brilliant moon, and we opened the window, which looked out over a lovely garden, and then sat in a rather dark recess to enjoy the slight breeze which was loaded with perfume of flowers and had a soft sensuous effect on my excited nerves. I longed to enjoy my young partner, but did not exactly like the idea of being the first of the party to break through the slight barriers that still existed in favour of decency, although I knew perfectly well it was intended to be done by Lady Bertha and her sisters; still they seemed so slow in arriving at a thorough explanation with their company that I could wait no longer. "Charles," I whispered, "do you know what love is, have you ever had a sweetheart?"<break time="100ms" />"No, my Lady, I never had a chance yet, as I look at all the beautiful creatures, and think how hard it is that I dare not kiss one of them. Dear Lady, did you but know the intense pleasure your lips afforded me just now you not would think that kiss was thrown away, as I expect you did it in fun," he responded with emotion.
    </voice>
</speak>
