<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />In the morning when I awoke Rose was sitting up in the bed, looking with anxious eyes on the now diminutive, shrunken instrument which the night before had ripped open the entrances to her virginity, robbing her of her maidenhead. When she perceived that I was watching her she threw herself into my arms and hid her face in my bosom.<break time="100ms" />Gently raising and reassuring her, I made her take hold of it, and began dallying with her breasts, tickling her, pressing them, sucking their rosy nipples, while the touch of her hand renewed in me the fires which were already springing into flame. Rose had the pleasure to see the small shrunken thing she first took into her hand spring up into a magnificent rod, smooth and polished as ivory, its large uncapped head red and glowing with the heat that was raging in it. I determined that she should reap the reward of her labour, and gather into her storehouse the rich harvest of love that was awaiting her.<break time="100ms" />Gently laying her down, and placing a pillow under the firm half-moons of her backside, she stretched open her legs to the utmost, exhibiting to my gaze the gaping lips of her cunt, ready open to receive the delicious morsel which, panting and throbbing like a high mettled courser, raised his foaming head erect against my belly.<break time="100ms" />Laying myself down on Rose I made her take hold of my prick to put it in, but so firm and erect was it that she could barely bend its head down to the entrance. So magnificent was the erection that with all the stretching her cunt had received the night before it would not enter. Drawing myself back to wet the head within the lips, and slowly shoving it into her, she could not move, but lay quietly till I stirred her up so powerfully that we soon melted away, making her feel the pleasures more sensibly, and giving her the full enjoyment of that which she had but tasted the night before.<break time="100ms" />We had barely recovered ourselves when we were aroused by a knocking at the door. Slipping on a loose robe de chambre I immediately opened it, and Raoul and Manette came in. I led them up to the bed, and pulling off the coverlet showed them the blushing Rose, more beautiful in the morning from the fatigues she had undergone the night past.<break time="100ms" />I called their attention to her, saying, "Behold her chemise; see how it is dyed by the juice and crimson tide, which flowed from the parent stem after I had plucked la rose d'amour from my lovely Rose."<break time="100ms" />My cousin Raoul now congratulated me. He said that he was "overjoyed that he had been in a manner instrumental in procuring for me such a delicious rose as Rose turned out to be." That he was sincerely glad he had been partially the cause of my being thus happily initiated into the mysteries of the divine art of love, and at the same time of my having had a virgin partner in my delicious combats.<break time="100ms" />Manette, too, congratulated her sister.<break time="100ms" />"How pleased she was to learn that she had secured such a lover as M. Louis, how happy you will be together now you have once tasted the supreme joys to be obtained in each other's embraces, sipping of the pleasures of which I am sure you will never tire."<break time="100ms" />I now spent all my nights with Rose, sometimes in her own chamber, again in my own, and not content to wait for the night I would sometimes get her into my room in the day, and enjoy myself with her.<break time="100ms" />One day, while in my room with Rose, she stretched across the foot of the bed, her clothes raised up, and exposing to my view all her beauties, I standing between her legs with my prick (which was a very large one, few men being able to boast of one as large), in my hand, Manette suddenly entered the room, I having neglected to lock the door.<break time="100ms" />She got a fair view of my prick, and stood looking at it, apparently amazed at its being so big, but seeing the manner in which I was engaged, she retired.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />As a brother of old, from his lodge was returning,<break time="100ms" />He called on his sweetheart, with love he was burning,<break time="100ms" />He wanted some favours, says she,<break time="100ms" />"Not so free," Unless you reveal your famed secrets to me."<break time="100ms" />"Agreed - 'tis a bargain - you must be prepared,<break time="100ms" />Your legs well exposed, your bosom all bared."<break time="100ms" />Then hoodwinked and silent, says she, "I'll be mum,<break time="100ms" />In despite of the poker you'll clap on my bum."<break time="100ms" />To a chamber convenient his fair charge he bore,<break time="100ms" />Placed her in due form, having closed tight the door,<break time="100ms" />Then presented the point of his sharp Instrumentis,<break time="100ms" />And the Lady was soon made an "entered apprentice."<break time="100ms" />His working tools next to her gaze he presented,<break time="100ms" />To improve by them seriously she then consented,<break time="100ms" />And handled his jewels his gavel and shaft,<break time="100ms" />That she in a jiffey was passed "fellow craft."<break time="100ms" />She next wanted raising, says he, "There's no urgency,"<break time="100ms" />She pleaded that this was a case of emergency,<break time="100ms" />His column looked to her in no particular way,<break time="100ms" />But she very soon made it assume perpendicular.<break time="100ms" />He used all his efforts to raise the young elf,<break time="100ms" />But found he required much raising himself;<break time="100ms" />The task was beyond him. Oh! shame and disaster,<break time="100ms" />He broke down in his charge, and she became master.<break time="100ms" />Exhausted and faint, still no rest could betide him,<break time="100ms" />For she like a glutton soon mounted astride him,<break time="100ms" />"From refreshment to labour," says she, "let us march.<break time="100ms" />Says he, "You're exalted - you are now royal arch."<break time="100ms" />In her zeal for true knowledge, no labour, no shirking,<break time="100ms" />His jewels and furniture constantly working,<break time="100ms" />By night and by day, in the light or the dark,<break time="100ms" />With pleasure her lover she guides to the mark.<break time="100ms" />The Lady and the Eel.<break time="100ms" />A young lady was frigging herself with a small live eel, when it slipped from her fingers and disappeared in her cunt; making its way into the womb, it entered, and stretching out its head said, "I am much obliged to you Madam, for finding me so warm and comfortable a residence; I shall make myself quite at home." This fable teaches how much better it is to use large eels which could not enter.<break time="100ms" />The Discontented Crab.<break time="100ms" />A crab who had for some time lived very happily on the person of a very dirty whore, one day became discontented. "How much nicer would it be to live with some cleaner and more reputable person," he thought, so watching his opportunity he effected his escape on to the person of a well-dressed and delicately clean young gentleman. "This," said the crab, "is something like," but to his disgust the gentleman took a warm bath after leaving his late mistress, and spying him out cracked him.
    </voice>
</speak>
