<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />At this we all burst out into a loud laugh, and thoroughly enjoyed poor Lucretia's shame and confusion.<break time="100ms" />Miss Coote.- "Cheer up, Sister Lucretia, you have only to do what we call stepping the ladder, someday you will have a chance of revenge, but you will find Louise Van Tromp quite as cruel as I am, when she uses the birch in her skilful style on your half-cooked bum. Come Jane, I think she is ready for the second edition of her punishment."<break time="100ms" />Louise Van Tromp.- "Ah! trust me, Sister Rosa, to do my duty, she has not half confessed to us yet," taking up and switching a fine birch rod, making it fairly hiss through the air, to the evident terror of the victim.<break time="100ms" />Lucretia, with sobs and tears running in streams down her cheeks.- "Oh! Oh! how horrible, will you never have mercy; my bottom is so sore I really can't bear it to be touched," shrinking back as Jane tries to draw her to the ladder. "Oh! No! Not again on that awful thing!"<break time="100ms" />Louise brings down her rod with a tremendous whack across the poor girl's bare shoulders, exclaiming, "What are you hanging back for, look sharp, quick, or I'll cut your shoulders again," looking with delight on the red marks her cut has left on the white flesh of the victim.<break time="100ms" />Lucretia.- "Oh! Oh! I will! I will!" holding up her wrists for Jane to secure them, which is quickly done.<break time="100ms" />Louise.- "Now, step on the rungs of the ladder one at a time, as I call out the number beginning at the bottom, if you take two at once you must do it over again. Now, one"- giving a terrible whack on the victim's bruised rump—<break time="100ms" />"Ah-r-r-r-re!" shrieks Lucretia, in terrible agony as the birch cuts into the already lacerated skin, but careful only to take one step.<break time="100ms" />Louise, making her birch flourish through the air with a hissing noise.- "Pretty well, now - now - now," keeping her in trembling suspense. "Two - three," giving a couple of crashing strokes with a good interval between them, to make the victim feel the effect as much as possible.<break time="100ms" />Lucretia gives a fearful shriek at each cut, and sobs out hysterically, "Ah! How dreadful, the skin of my bottom will burst, it's getting so tight."<break time="100ms" />Louise.- "Glad you enjoy it so, dear, I'm sorry to hurt you much," looking delightedly round at the other members. "Now - now - now" - with another flourish - "four - five," each blow draws the blood afresh from the already crimsoned surface, and puts the spectators into a flutter of excitement.<break time="100ms" />Lucretia fairly groans, but only once makes a false step, which she corrects before Louise can find fault. "Only two more," she sighs, as if calculating the steps yet to be done.<break time="100ms" />Louise.- "Steady, keep your bottom well out," switching her lightly underneath so as to tickle the exposed pussey, then another grand flourish. "Six - seven," these are awful crackers, but the victim keeps herself steady, and her pluck is greeted by clapping of hands all round. Jane takes advantage of the opportunity to secure the victim's ankles so that she is fixed in a most inviting attitude for further flagellation.<break time="100ms" />Louise.- "Thanks, Jane, very thoughtful of you. Now, Sister Lucretia, before you are let off you must tell us all about yourself and young Aubrey. Miss Coote did not half get it out of you," whisking the tightly bent bottom in a playful way with her rod, but the victim is evidently so sore that even light strokes make twinges of pain pass across her scarlet face.<break time="100ms" />Lucretia.- "Oh! Oh! Pray don't begin again. I told you he took liberties with me, what more can I say? Oh! Oh! Don't touch me; the least whisk of that thing gives awful pain."<break time="100ms" />Louise.- "Then, you silly girl, why do you persist in keeping back the truth? Did you not encourage him?" making the victim writhe under her painful touches, which, although not very heavy, seem to have great effect on the raw bottom, in such a tightly bent position.<break time="100ms" />Lucretia, in great shame and confusion, and seeming to crimson all over at the thoughts of her degradation before them all.- "Oh! Oh! Spare me! If you know all, have mercy, consider my feelings, how painful such a confession must be. Ah-r-r-rre! You are shameful girls to enjoy my pain and shame so," sobbing as if her heart would break.<break time="100ms" />Louise.- "Come! Come! It is not so bad as that. Make a clean breast and be one of us in future. You will enjoy such scenes yourself when the next novice is admitted; but I can't play with you. There - there - there!" cutting three brisk strokes on the bent bottom.<break time="100ms" />Lucretia.- "Ah! Oh! Oh! I shall faint again. It's like burning with red hot irons. Ah! You know he seduced me, and - I must confess I did not resist as I ought. Something tempted me to taste the sweets of love, and your President's birching brought all the thrilling sensations back to me, and, when I fainted my dream was all about the bliss enjoyed in my lover's arms."<break time="100ms" />Louise, still lightly using her rod.- "A little better, and getting nearer the truth, but you still prevaricate so in trying to excuse your own fault. Now, did you not seduce the youth instead of his taking advantage of you?"<break time="100ms" />Lucretia.- "Oh! Pity me. I saw him lying asleep on the grass in a secluded part of the garden; he was so sleepy that I failed to wake him, but I since believe he was shamming. Noticing a lump of something in his breeches, I gently pressed it with my fingers to see what it was, when it gradually swelled under my pressure and became like a hard stick throbbing under the cloth; my blood was fired; I can't tell how I did it, but presently, when he opened his eyes and laughed at me, I found myself with his exposed shaft in my hand. He jumped up, sprang upon me, and taking advantage of my confusion, I own he had an easy conquest. But something of the sort will happen to every loving girl at some time or other. Now I have told you all, have pity and let me go," sobbing and looking dreadfully confused and distressed.<break time="100ms" />She was let down, and we all crowded round her, giving affectionate kisses and welcoming her to be a real sister of Lady Rodney's Club.<break time="100ms" />The poor girl was very sore, and sobbed over her poor bruised bottom. "Oh! Oh! I can't sit down, it will be weeks before I can do anything with comfort. Ah! You pretend to be kind now after all that dreadful cruelty. I only wish we could get Aubrey and give him a good thrashing, it would do the impetuous boy good." We had another laugh at this, but assured her our rules didn't provide for admitting any of the opposite sex to the seances of the Club; but in my next you shall see what happened, and how Lucretia tricked us by introducing young Aubrey as a young lady novice desirous of admission to our Society. I remain, dear Nellie,<break time="100ms" />Yours affectionately<break time="100ms" />ROSA BELINDA COOTE.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />PART IV.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)
    </voice>
</speak>
