<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />What delightful sensations I experienced, my prick feeling all the spasmodic contractions of her vagina, and having my bottom well dildoe-fucked at the same time, I spent again under the influence of this accumulated excitement just as my partner was coming round under the influence of some cordial which had been poured down her gasping throat, whilst strong smelling salts had been applied to her nostrils. She opened her eyes, giving a violent sneeze at the same time, which vibrated on my delightful prick, who instantly began gently to bestir himself in her tight scabbard; this roused her little by little, till throwing her arms round my neck, and returning my hot kisses with all the ardour of her nature, she cried and laughed by turns, as she begged me to make haste and complete her happiness.<break time="100ms" />By a side glance I could see Frank was in Mrs. Leslie's bottom, Annie in him with a dildoe, and Sophie doing the same to her sister, in fact, a perfect string of pederastic branchings from my own violated bum. It was such a scene as I had never seen before, and added additional fury to my already maddened lust. I came again and again before we finished, each spend more ecstatic than the last. The chocolate had so invigorated us, that we went through an almost interminable series of spendings, till at last nature could stand it no longer, we rolled on the floor in a confused heap, and wound up in a mutual gamahuche; Mrs. Leslie secured the blood-stained quim of little Polly, which she sucked till she had enjoyed the last drop of ensanguined spunk she could extract from the wounded slit of her young friend, who writhed in delight under the soothing touches of such a lascivious tongue.<break time="100ms" />It was between eleven and twelve o'clock, when just as we were recovering from a state of lethargic oblivion, and thinking of some reinvigorating refreshment, the sound of carriage wheels on the gravel drive up to the house, and then, rat-a-tat-tat on the loud knocker made us all start to our feet and rush for our clothes.<break time="100ms" />"The Colonel, by all that's unfortunate," exclaimed Mrs. Leslie, "make haste or he will catch us; who would have thought of his arriving this time of night."<break time="100ms" />The prudent Vishnu, pretending to be awaking out of his first sleep, so bungled and delayed opening the front door, that we were tolerably presentable by the time the Colonel made his appearance, and whatever his suspicions may have been, he went through the formality of introduction in the most friendly way possible, the presence of so many young ladies evidently quite disconcerting him for the moment.<break time="100ms" />I afterwards learnt from his wife that under promise of secrecy she had confessed all to him, and vastly amused her husband by an account of our doings; but, at any rate, it stopped our fun at the time, and next day I was obliged to return to town, and thus brought to conclusion "My Sport amongst the She-Noodles," anything but "Noodles" after I had so enlightened them, in fact quite as knowing as Adam and Eve after they found out they were "Naked," having tasted the "Tree of Knowledge," which, in my humble opinion, meant found out "L'Arte de faire l'amour."<break time="100ms" />FINIS.<break time="100ms" />Nine years ago I Betsy knew,<break time="100ms" />When she was but thrice five;<break time="100ms" />With eyes that flash'd in amorous glow,<break time="100ms" />The prettiest girl alive!<break time="100ms" />Behold her now! a married dame,<break time="100ms" />Huge, burly, fat and coarse;<break time="100ms" />With a plump, lusty, dumpy frame.<break time="100ms" />Hind quarters of a horse!<break time="100ms" />She then was light, and slim, and fresh,<break time="100ms" />Rosy, and light'ning ey'd;<break time="100ms" />She then was Spirit - now - O Flesh!<break time="100ms" />How are thou finished!<break time="100ms" />SECOND PART.<break time="100ms" />Her sister Athenais sits<break time="100ms" />Beside her in the pew;<break time="100ms" />I wonder if that lass forgets,<break time="100ms" />What I once used to do?<break time="100ms" />She then was nine; I put my hand,<break time="100ms" />Into her frock behind;<break time="100ms" />And strok'd her, you will understand,<break time="100ms" />Just as I felt inclin'd.<break time="100ms" />She giggled and she winc'd about,<break time="100ms" />But liked the picked rudeness;<break time="100ms" />She eyes me kindly - she no doubt<break time="100ms" />Remembers all my lewdness.<break time="100ms" />Yes - eyes me most luxuriously,<break time="100ms" />With glances bright beseeching!<break time="100ms" />How pleasantly the moments fly,<break time="100ms" />While Mr. Cotterill's preaching!<break time="100ms" />I see she feels the amorous smart,<break time="100ms" />She muses on the men,<break time="100ms" />Comprising in her virtuous heart,<break time="100ms" />The thoughts of now and then.<break time="100ms" />Papa and Mamma, Arabella and I,<break time="100ms" />Were sitting at supper with nobody by;<break time="100ms" />Now because they believe me a cozy old fellow,<break time="100ms" />They want to induce me to wed Arabella.<break time="100ms" />I like the girl well, but I don't choose to wed,<break time="100ms" />Fair Bella perceives I'm not easily led;<break time="100ms" />But while Papa told me some prosy old fable,<break time="100ms" />She was scratching her marrowbones under the table.<break time="100ms" />She look'd in my face, and on our eyes catching,<break time="100ms" />I just turn'd my head to see what she was scratching;<break time="100ms" />She had got her right ankle upon her left knee,<break time="100ms" />Up to her left garter I fairly could see.<break time="100ms" />She look'd in my face without shame or aversion,<break time="100ms" />While scratching her nakedness for my diversion;<break time="100ms" />While I sat electrifyd stuck like a fool,<break time="100ms" />She put down her petticoats easy and cool.<break time="100ms" />And ten minutes after she did it again,<break time="100ms" />Though knowing I look'd and saw it quite plain;<break time="100ms" />Come - there was a prank for a delicate virgin,<break time="100ms" />Who thought an old bachelor wanting some urging!<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Johnson, going into the cellar one day, caught her husband fucking the servant girl. A short time after, finding that Kate was packing her boxes to leave, she enquired the reason.<break time="100ms" />Kate.- "I couldn't think of stopping mum, after what you saw in the cellar."<break time="100ms" />Mrs. J.- "Go along girl, do you think I mind? Perhaps with what you do in the cellar, and I do upstairs, we may keep the old whoremonger at home between us."<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
