<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"'Look, darling,' he continued, as he rose to his feet, 'I thought a few delicate kisses would revive you if properly bestowed in the most sensitive place, but I don't mean to have you there; this book will show you the most delightful avenue of bliss, and open up to your ravished senses heavenly bliss you have hither had no conception of.'<break time="100ms" />"Keeping my clothes up, and making me retain hold of his priapus in one hand, he showed me a series of splendid little drawings in the book, all illustrating the way to enjoy bottom-fucking. He could see I was tremendously excited, so lost no time in placing me on my hands and knees on the sofa, then anointing my tight little bum-hole with some ointment from the box, and putting some also on the shaft of his prick, he made me push my bottom well out behind, with my legs wide apart so as to give him every facility, but 'Ah! Ah! No, no, I can't bear it!' I exclaimed, the tears fairly starting to my eyes as I felt the first advance of his lovely engine, forcing its way through the tightened orifice; the pain was like a number of needles pricking the part all at once. I can describe the sensation as the sphincter muscle gradually relaxed in no other way. He frigged me deliciously in front all the while, pushing so firmly and getting in in such a gentle manner behind that I seemed to love him more and more every moment, and long for him to accomplish his task, and complete my enjoyment, as the very pain seemed a percursor to some extraordinary bliss, nor was I disappointed; the pain was soon succeeded by the most delicious sensations as his movements stirred me up to the highest pitch of excitement, and he never withdrew till we had spent thrice in rapturous ecstasies, screaming with delight and almost losing our lives from excess of enjoyment.<break time="100ms" />"Thus my mission was successful, and his lordship became a Member of Parliament."<break time="100ms" />This tale had worked us all up, so that we were mutually groping each other's privates, and as soon as Bertha had finished we seized Fanny and Bridget, but too much of the same thing being rather tedious to read I will only say that John and Charles took their virginities in splendid style, when the girls really found no more nonsense would be tolerated.<break time="100ms" />This was my last adventure in town, and in the next part I shall go on to relate what happened after my marriage with Lord Crim-Con, which took place shortly afterwards.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />A few young sages one bright day<break time="100ms" />(Such conduct is not becoming)<break time="100ms" />Disputed, doth an old tale say,<break time="100ms" />Which is the prettiest part of women:<break time="100ms" />And this, the cause of the affray is.<break time="100ms" />Some said the cheeks, and some the eyes,<break time="100ms" />And so they sought the beauteous Lais,<break time="100ms" />And asked her to award the prize.<break time="100ms" />The lady said, perhaps displeased,<break time="100ms" />These thoughts I cannot understand.<break time="100ms" />If you could have them where you pleased,<break time="100ms" />I wonder where you'd put your hand?<break time="100ms" />'Twould be, you would see,<break time="100ms" />On their K.U.N.T.<break time="100ms" />Translated from the Hindustani.<break time="100ms" />Oh when shall I behold, love,<break time="100ms" />Thy noble manly face?<break time="100ms" />O when thy neck enfold, love,<break time="100ms" />Within my close embrace?<break time="100ms" />All young, and warm, and willing,<break time="100ms" />O when shall I receive<break time="100ms" />Those raptures, fierce and thrilling,<break time="100ms" />Which man alone can give?<break time="100ms" />As the thirsty pearl shell opes, love,<break time="100ms" />To imbibe prolific showers,<break time="100ms" />All, all my bosom's hope, love,<break time="100ms" />Expect thy vigorous powers;<break time="100ms" />My dreams are full of pleasure,<break time="100ms" />Naught else my heart employs,<break time="100ms" />Come kiss me without measure,<break time="100ms" />Thou source of all my joys!<break time="100ms" />A contributor wishes to remonstrate against the practice of a very nice young lady friend of his, who treats her quim as if it was a baby's arse. He says, "A nice cunt is a delicious thing to suck, but damn the violet powder, which dries up all the natural juiciness!"<break time="100ms" />A nigger in fair St. Domingo,<break time="100ms" />Being blase, and worn, said "By Jingo,<break time="100ms" />Blast all women and boys,<break time="100ms" />I'll try some new joys,"<break time="100ms" />So he went out and fucked a flamingo.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
