<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />This was most favourably received, and I soon found out that Lady Clara was at the bottom of a plot for introducing the male element into our society. I hastily closed the seance, and never knew how or what means they used to ease his sore bottom, but next day, by advice of Mdlle. Fosse, I intimated to them all a dissolution of the Club, as I could not possibly join in or allow my house to be used for birching orgies in connection with the opposite sex. My next and last letter on this subject will relate more nearly to myself.<break time="100ms" />Yours affectionately, ROSA BELINDA COOTE.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Said good Mrs. Besant,<break time="100ms" />To make things pleasant,<break time="100ms" />If of children you wish to be rid,<break time="100ms" />Just after coition,<break time="100ms" />Prevent all fruition,<break time="100ms" />And corpse the incipient kid.<break time="100ms" />To do this completely,<break time="100ms" />Securely and neatly,<break time="100ms" />That your conscience may suffer no twinge,<break time="100ms" />Before having connection,<break time="100ms" />Procure an injection,<break time="100ms" />Likewise an elastic syringe.<break time="100ms" />Then after the "coup,"<break time="100ms" />All the ladies need do<break time="100ms" />Is to jump out of bed on the spot,<break time="100ms" />Fill the squirt to the brim,<break time="100ms" />Pump it well up her quim,<break time="100ms" />And the kid trickles into the pot.<break time="100ms" />A little lady who was, and we believe is, a great speaker at the Quakers' meetings, was once asked by Mr. Bright in his young days, "if she did not find the spirit inspired her with thoughts of marriage?" "No," she answered, "but I frequently find my struggling with the flesh does."<break time="100ms" />Written in London 12th January, 1837, on Fraulein Theresa Schmidt, an opera dancer, as Columbine.<break time="100ms" />Night after night I've fed my eyes,<break time="100ms" />On sweet "Theresa Schmidt, Fraulein,"<break time="100ms" />And marvell'd how cold Northern skies<break time="100ms" />Could mould so fair a Columbine.<break time="100ms" />No verse, no rhyme could tell my mind,<break time="100ms" />To vent the praise my heart would breathe,<break time="100ms" />But she's an English girl I find,<break time="100ms" />And bears the vulgar name of Smith.<break time="100ms" />But whatso'er her name may be,<break time="100ms" />No Roman dancer could surpass,<break time="100ms" />The way she shows her open C,<break time="100ms" />And flourishes her jutting arse.<break time="100ms" />Yes - whatso'er the name she bear.<break time="100ms" />No graces, no celestial nymphs,<break time="100ms" />Can grant to men a sight more fair,<break time="100ms" />Of paradise a clearer glimpse.<break time="100ms" />Let others rave of Taglioni,<break time="100ms" />Dancers from Florence or from France,<break time="100ms" />But give Theresa for my money,<break time="100ms" />She shines the goddess of the dance.<break time="100ms" />The sculptor modelling naked truth,<break time="100ms" />Array'd in Eve's celestial dress,<break time="100ms" />May find her here in blaze of youth,<break time="100ms" />In all her native loveliness.<break time="100ms" />Pure English are the parts she shews,<break time="100ms" />Although she's call'd Theresa Schmidt;<break time="100ms" />What's in a name? A bright moss rose<break time="100ms" />By any other name's as sweet!<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />PART IV.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)<break time="100ms" />My partner was far too impetuous to heed my faint remonstrances, and in spite of all I could do to keep my thighs closed his venturesome hand soon took possession of my heated cunny. "If I die I must have you, darling lady," he whispered in my ear, as he suddenly forced me quite back on the sofa, and tried to raise my clothes.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! No! No! I shall faint. How your violence frightens me!" I sighed, trying to smother my desires by simulating helplessness, and then feigning unconsciousness I promised myself a rare treat by allowing him to think I really had fainted, which, no doubt, would urge him to take advantage of the moment to riot unrestrained in the enjoyment of my most secret charms.<break time="100ms" />It was almost dark in the shadowy recess where the sofa on which we were was situated. "She's quite gone, the darling!" I heard him say to himself, as he gently parted my relaxing thighs, "I'll kiss it first." Then I knew he was kneeling between my legs, and I felt his fingers gently parting the lips of my cunt. "How I must have excited her, she's been spending!" he went on, then I felt his lips right between the nymphre as he kissed me rapturously just on the excitable little clitoris. What a thrill of desire it sent through my frame, as it made me literally quiver all-over with emotion, so that I could scarcely refrain from clasping his head with my hand, or nipping his dear face between my thighs.<break time="100ms" />This only lasted a few moments, which seemed awfully long in my excitable state, my cunt was spending and throbbing under the voluptuous titillations of his velvety tongue. Heavens how I wanted to feel his prick inside of me! and could not have feigned my fainting state another instant, but the moment my lips were in the act of parting to implore him to fuck me at once he started to his feet, pushing my thighs as wide apart as possible, and directly I felt the hot head of his cock placed to the mark; slowly and gradually he pushed his way in, as contracting my usually tight affair I made it as difficult as I could for him to achieve possession. How he kissed my lips, calling me, "Darling lady, dear Beatrice, oh, you love, what pleasure you give me!"<break time="100ms" />I felt him spend a torrent of his warm essence right up to my vitals, and then lay still upon me exhausted for the moment by the profuseness of his emission.<break time="100ms" />Still apparently in the state of inanimation, and without opening my eyes, I made my cunt nip and contract on his throbbing prick as it was soaking within me, in such a manner that he was almost immediately aroused from his delicious lethargy, and recommenced his movements, exclaiming to himself, What a love of a girl, even in her fainting state, the love pressure of her cunt responds to the action of my prick. What pleasure it would be if I could but arouse her to sensibility!" as he kissed me over and over again rapturously, quickening his stroke till my blood was so fired I could no longer impose upon him, so I suddenly threw my arms around the dear boy's neck, whilst my amorous kisses responding to his silently assured him of the delight he was affording me.
    </voice>
</speak>
