<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />In a moment Caroline reduced me to a state of pure nature; far from resisting, I imitated her eagerness; the new beauties which discovered themselves to our view extorted a cry of admiration, and suspended our burning caresses.<break time="100ms" />Our hands, which for an instant seemed to have respected so many charms, wander with fresh delirium. Caroline takes me in her arms, drags me on to the ottoman, and obliges me to assume the attitude of Algae! I recline with my head resting on one of my arms, the right foot on the ottoman, the knee raised, whilst the left leg, unsupported, gently balances itself.<break time="100ms" />My chere amie, not less curious than Venus, takes the same posture, and places herself exactly in front of the throne of felicity, one of the beautiful knees rests on a cushion, the other serves for a footstool. Caroline, at her ease, contemplates the object of her dearest desires. Her delicate hand opens the rose, and the new Sappho exclaims with transports of joy, impossible to describe, "She is still a virgin! Good God, what a source of pleasure!"<break time="100ms" />I confess I could never have imagined this discovery of such great value to her; virgin or not, what need she care? But we cannot account for the eccentricity of the passions, and doubtless the most singular of all is to find one female amorous of another.<break time="100ms" />Love! thou who inflamed Caroline with the most ardent fires for one of her own sex, lend me thy burning pencil that I may worthily describe this voluptuous scene, as even in forcing us to give way to thy caprices, thy only object is to render us happy!<break time="100ms" />Caroline rises transported, presses me in her arms, giving a thousand kisses, then resuming her first attitude, contemplates anew the prettiest of bijous. "Yes," she exclaims, "that flower is untouched. What colour! What freshness! Similar to the bee, I will extract the ambrosia! I will intoxicate myself with its delicious juice. I will drain it with pleasure!"<break time="100ms" />Then by a thousand means, which I dare not describe, but which occasioned me the most delicious sensations, Caroline made me attain the last period of delight. Her design was not merely to procure me delight; the skilful bee, wanting in the natural engine necessary to extract the honey from the rose, made use of her lascivious tongue to draw down my ambrosial tribute to love, titillating and sucking in such a rapturous manner that her face was almost drowned by my impetuous emission, as I went off into a most delicious state of almost unconscious lethargy. Expressions would vainly endeavour to give an idea of Caroline's excitement; she seemed to have lost her reason as the source of life, her words were as incoherent as her conduct was extravagant. But what do I say? Was she not more sensible than ever, since all she said, everything she did, only tended to increase our intoxication, and add to its fury. Caroline, whose desires no longer knew any restraints, in order to satisfy them, made me pass through all the gradations of pleasure. I tasted in the same evening all those indescribable enjoyments which I should not have been acquainted with until after a long novitiate, had not the extraordinary passion I inspired her with induced her to initiate me at once in the most secret mysteries.<break time="100ms" />What charming pictures could I describe were I permitted to give the reins to my pen.<break time="100ms" />My imagination, exalted by these enchanting souvenirs, longs to retrace the image! But, alas! I must confine in my bosom the secret ready to escape, and deprive the most beautiful half of the human race of a fruitful source of pleasures and voluptuousness, of which the experience alone can conceive the extent!<break time="100ms" />Ten little niggers did a farting match design,<break time="100ms" />One got excited and died, so there were nine;<break time="100ms" />Nine little niggers layed his body straight,<break time="100ms" />One chanced to touch his prick, then there were eight;<break time="100ms" />Eight little nigger boys took a trip to Devon,<break time="100ms" />One fucked a peasant girl, and then there were seven;<break time="100ms" />Seven little niggers got fooling with their pricks,<break time="100ms" />One got his foreskin back, and then there were six;<break time="100ms" />Six little niggers a frig loop did contrive,<break time="100ms" />One overspent himself, and then there were five;<break time="100ms" />Five little nigger boys each picked a whore,<break time="100ms" />One had his in the arse, and then there were four;<break time="100ms" />Four little nigger boys for a prize did pee,<break time="100ms" />One pissed himself away, and then there were three;<break time="100ms" />Three little nigger boys had connection with a Jew.<break time="100ms" />The Chief Rabbi caught one, and then there were two;<break time="100ms" />Two little niggers were gamahuched for fun,<break time="100ms" />One got his prick bit off, and then there was one;<break time="100ms" />The last little nigger met a Countess at a ball,<break time="100ms" />Married her, got the pox and died, and now that is all.<break time="100ms" />In a series of Letters to a Lady Friend.<break time="100ms" />LETTER IX<break time="100ms" />My dear Nellie,-<break time="100ms" />I have been looking over some of my grandfather's papers, and found the following curious little bit written by his brother Dean Coote, "Remarks on the influence of Female Beauty":-<break time="100ms" />I shall reverse the general practice, and instead of beginning with the head, commence with the leg, and hope to get credit for so doing. A pretty face, sparkling eyes, rosy cheeks, delicate complexion, smiles, dimples, hair dark; auburn or blonde, have all, it is acknowledged, great weight in the business of love; but still let me appeal to every impartial and unprejudiced observer, which he is most curious to behold, the legs or the face of his favourite lady.<break time="100ms" />Whether does the face or the legs of a pretty girl that is clambering over a style, or mounting a ladder, most attract our notice and regard?<break time="100ms" />What is it that causes my lord to smack his chops in that wanton lecherous manner, as he is sauntering up and down the lounge in Bond Street, with his glass in hand, to watch the ladies getting in and out of their carriages? And what is it that draws together such vast crowds of the holiday gentry at Easter and Whitsuntide, to see the merry rose-faced lasses running down the hill in Greenwich Park?<break time="100ms" />What is it causes such a roar of laughter and applause when a merry girl happens to overset in her career, and kick her heels in the air?<break time="100ms" />Lastly, as the parsons all say, what is it that makes the theatrical ballets so popular?
    </voice>
</speak>
