<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />On retiring for the night, my mistress informed me that she had an engagement with our host's wife. That she intended to drug a glass of wine for her husband on going to bed, which would ensure her freedom for at least ten hours, and that as soon as her husband was fast asleep she would go to her room.<break time="100ms" />Telling Celestine to undress and get into my bed, I went into the room prepared for her, and stripping myself perfectly naked, awaited in darkness the coming of the charming hostess.<break time="100ms" />After waiting for an hour I heard a light step advancing towards the room, the door opened, and she entered, and whispering Rudolph, the name Celestine had taken, advanced to the bed. Slipping the bolts in the door, I caught her in my arms, and found she was as naked as myself. In kissing her she knew immediately by my whiskers that I was not the person she expected to meet, and fearing she had made a mistake in the room, she gave a slight scream, and struggled violently to free herself.<break time="100ms" />But I retained a firm hold of her naked waist, and drawing her to the bed, explained everything to her. How that my page Rudolph was my "chere amie," accompanying me in this disguise.<break time="100ms" />After calming her fears I lighted a taper that stood on the table and kissed everything, especially a dear hairy little cleft at the bottom of her belly, I found her to exceed the expectations I had formed at the supper table. She could not resist my handling her person, but freely gave herself up to my touches.<break time="100ms" />The game was getting too exciting to stand dallying very long, so turning her on her back, I plunged my weapon into a bath of hot juicy flesh, and gave her a luxurious feast of the fruit of which she had had before but a very slight taste.<break time="100ms" />Five times that night did I put her through the manual exercise of love, and five times did she die away in the most ecstatic enjoyments, the pleasures of which she declared she had only known in imagination.<break time="100ms" />It was with sincere regret that Madame le Maire parted from me at dawn of day, to join her sleeping husband, to whose brows had just been added a pair of horns. They were short to be sure, but there appeared every prospect of their branching out into large antlers.<break time="100ms" />Before leaving me she made me promise to stop on my return.<break time="100ms" />After breakfast in the morning I returned my host my sincere thanks for his hospitality, assuring him that the entertainment I had received in his house was far beyond my expectations.<break time="100ms" />I ordered my carriage, and followed by my page, took the road to Vienna.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Sally, the servant-maid of Mr. A-, was accustomed to walk in her sleep. She one night came into her master's room, went into his bed, laid down and slept between him and his wife.<break time="100ms" />In the morning Mr. A- got up according to his usual custom, a little after five o'clock, after having performed (as he thought) the part of an affectionate husband, not suspecting that there was anybody in bed with him but his wife.<break time="100ms" />He had not got downstairs before Mrs. A- awoke, and accosted Sally, whom she mistook for her husband, in the following terms: "My dear Mr. A-, indeed I am not surprised that we have no children, since you are so lazy. Come closer, my dear, pray my dear, come. I am sure I am young and vigorous and perform my part as well as any woman in the kingdom."<break time="100ms" />Here Mrs. A- paused a few minutes, waiting for an answer, but receiving none from the imagined husband (who lay all the time in a cold sweat, fearing a discovery, for she thought Mrs. A- was her gallant the shopman, who laid with her every night, as she was afraid to sleep by herself; but they never spoke to each other during their amorous interviews for fear of being overheard).<break time="100ms" />"Fellow, do you think me worthy of an answer; I'll be revenged - I'll never get into bed with you again!"<break time="100ms" />Here her breast swelled so with anger that she could not utter another word.<break time="100ms" />Fortunately it was not yet light, so Sally jumped out of the bed and ran up to her gallant; to whom she imparted the whole affair.<break time="100ms" />This was the first time they had ever broken silence during their amours, and they were overheard by another maid who slept in the next room. She watched for the shopman's coming out of Sally's chamber, and made him go into hers to gratify those desires which I leave the reader to guess.<break time="100ms" />They all arose at their usual time, and Mrs. A- being informed that breakfast was ready, went downstairs into the parlour, and had just seated herself when Mr. A- entered the room, and accosted her in the following words:<break time="100ms" />Mr. A.- "Well, my dear, what do you think of me now?"<break time="100ms" />Mrs. A.- "That you are as incapable as a eunuch."<break time="100ms" />Mr. A.- "Nay, my dear, I thought you seemed so much pleased with our gambols this morning that we should have been very great friends all the day, but, alas, I find there is no satisfying a woman!"<break time="100ms" />Mrs. A.- "I'll tell you, fellow, I'll have a divorce. Not even answer me, scoundrel. Did I not make a man of you? Had it not been for me, you would have had to carry your cod-piece to a beggar woman ere this - whilst I know by your unnatural abstinence you have a gay woman in keeping - some painted little bitch or flaghopper. Not a civil answer when I offer you my love? You shall repent it, sir, you old whoremonger, thus to neglect your virtuous wife" (clapping her hands in fury).<break time="100ms" />Mr. A.- "My dear, I did. As I love my money, will you have it cut off and preserved like a snake in a bottle - or do you want it twice before breakfast?"<break time="100ms" />Mrs. A.- "Your money is my money, and so ought your - to be, but you take it elsewhere, you old adulterer!"<break time="100ms" />Mr. A. - "Nay, nay, my dear, but I believe you're too loving, my jewel, as soon as breakfast is over I'll lock the door and we will-"<break time="100ms" />Mrs. A.- "Now, indeed, my dear, you speak like a man of mettle, and I forgive all that is past."<break time="100ms" />When breakfast was over he performed his promise. Madam was pleased, and harmony once more reigned in their loving abode. Sally also was equally happy in having escaped from her dangerous predicament, her fellow servant in having gotten a gallant, and the shopman two fine girls to play and toy with at his pleasure.<break time="100ms" />Moral. - "It's an ill wind that blows nobody any good."<break time="100ms" />A merchant of Genoa leaving wife at home;<break time="100ms" />Kiss'd a little whore, in the town of Rome;<break time="100ms" />"You, my dear;" said he, "tried full many a nation,<break time="100ms" />Then say who had the longest tool of generation?"<break time="100ms" />Said the merry girl, "Oh, that's soon decided,<break time="100ms" />You, who cross the sea, are the best provided;<break time="100ms" />What a length of tail, though the seas you roam,<break time="100ms" />Your spouses never fail, to bear you babes at home!"<break time="100ms" />In a series of Letters to a Lady Friend.<break time="100ms" />LETTER X.<break time="100ms" />My dear Nellie,-
    </voice>
</speak>
