<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"'And what's this little slit?'<break time="100ms" />'"My cunt.'<break time="100ms" />"'Would you like to see the prick going into Jane's cunt again, and nicking it?'<break time="100ms" />"'Oh, yes, I would very much.'<break time="100ms" />"'Well, Jane, my love, let us have another turn before we go, my prick is awfully excited.'<break time="100ms" />"He laid her back, and opening her legs, made me look at her cunt. I had often seen it before when she was bathing, but had never looked into it until now. I was surprised at its depth and extent. He put my hand on it, and said: 'See these fine thick lips, how they swell out. That's the sort of cunt a man loves to fuck. And this deep chink, how red and hot it is. Put your fingers in.'<break time="100ms" />"Three fingers entered easily. The soft warm folds inside closed on my fingers, and seemed to suck them in.<break time="100ms" />"Just like your own cunt, May. Oh! how hot it is! and how it throbs! And mine is throbbing too. Let us have a mutual suck before I proceed with my story."<break time="100ms" />I readily agreed, for my cunt felt all in a flame. We threw off our shifts, and lay naked on the bed. She got over me, and lifting up my thighs, sucked eagerly at my cunt, and twining her arms round my hips, tickled my bottom.<break time="100ms" />My tongue was equally busy about her sweet orifice, and as she felt it penetrating the heated parts inside, she wriggled about, and pressed her bottom on my face.<break time="100ms" />We were soon partially relieved by a copious discharge from our founts of pleasure.<break time="100ms" />Susey then resumed her exciting narrative:<break time="100ms" />"John knelt between Jane's thighs, and made me direct his prick into her open cunt. I held it by the root as it passed quickly up. He told me to stir his balls and pinch his bottom.<break time="100ms" />"Meanwhile, I watched the operation with the greatest interest and delight.<break time="100ms" />"As the prick went in, the lips enclosed it with a kind of eager suction, and when it came out they seemed to follow it, as if loath to part with such a pleasant morsel.<break time="100ms" />"John put his hands under her, and raised her up. As he warmed to the work, his great muscular bottom heaved backward and forward with increasing rapidity, making his prick plunge in and out of her hot receptacle.<break time="100ms" />"'Are you pinching him, Susey? Pinch hard.'<break time="100ms" />"I pinched his bottom, and tickled the hole there with my finger.<break time="100ms" />"'Push it in, Susey, oh, that is so nice. Tell us what you see, dear.'<break time="100ms" />'"I see your bottom heaving backward and forward and your prick rushing in and out between the thick hairy lips of Jane's cunt.'<break time="100ms" />"'What else do you see, Susey?'<break time="100ms" />'"I see the bag below your prick, and feel two round things in it.'<break time="100ms" />"'Stir them, Susey. What else do you see?'<break time="100ms" />'"I see the round hole of your bottom.'<break time="100ms" />"'Move your finger inside, Susey. Oh! Oh!!' he cried, as he drove his prick with great force into her cunt, and banged his balls against her bottom, while she clasped him in her arms."<break time="100ms" />All this time Susey had been frigging my cunt with her fingers, and now she sprang on top of me, and pounded her cunt against mine, until our cunts again overflowed with love's sweet juice, and we lay back to rest.<break time="100ms" />The next time I went to Mr. T-, after the usual preliminaries of petting, sucking, andc, he said he wished to try a new mode of enjoyment which he had seen in a picture. So he first set up a large mirror before us, and then sitting on the edge of a sofa, he lifted me up backwards, and placed my bottom on his belly. Then putting his hand under my thigh, he raised my knee up to his breast. So that, in the glass, we had a most exciting view of my open cunt, and his upstanding prick nestling its rubicund head between the hairy lips.<break time="100ms" />I rested my foot on his knee, and then pressing down, watched it slowly disappearing in the pouting gap. As I rose up, the sweet instrument of pleasure again appeared, all red and shining with the moisture of my cunt, and when I pressed down it hastily returned, leaving nothing outside but the balls in close contact with the hairy lips.<break time="100ms" />Mr. T- smiled, as he saw his tool absorbed in the crimson recess of my greedy cunt, and said:<break time="100ms" />"How beautifully plump and pouting your cunt is; my sweet May. With what delicious pressure it sucks in my bounding prick, while the soft cheeks of your bottom rub sweetly against my belly. But let us not hurry, it is so pleasant to talk together while my prick is soaking in your cunt. I want you to tell me something about your friend Susey. Does she know much of these matters?"<break time="100ms" />"Indeed, she does, everything in fact."<break time="100ms" />"Do you speak out the names? Prick, andc?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, she talks freely of pricks and cunts, and of fucking too."<break time="100ms" />"Was she ever fucked, do you think?"<break time="100ms" />"I think not, but she has often seen it done."<break time="100ms" />"How was she able to manage that?;'<break time="100ms" />I told him how she had seen her sister fucked by her intended before their marriage.<break time="100ms" />"Do you often pet each other's cunts?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, nearly every night."<break time="100ms" />"How?"<break time="100ms" />"When we are stripping for bed, she often asks me to lean back; and then she kisses and pets my cunt, and I do the same for her."<break time="100ms" />"Has she a nice cunt?"<break time="100ms" />"It is a nice little cunt, much tighter than mine; the lips are very plump, and well covered with light red hair. The skin round it is white, and smooth as satin, and the inside a bright pink."<break time="100ms" />"Why, May, you have quite excited me. Would you be awfully jealous if you saw me fucking her?"<break time="100ms" />"No, I would not be such a fool."<break time="100ms" />"May, you are the dearest girl, and have the sweetest cunt in the world. But I must take out my prick now. Hold it in your hand. There - see - how it spouts."<break time="100ms" />Before leaving I consented to let him hide in my wardrobe the following evening, that he might hear and see how we got on together.<break time="100ms" />When the time came I detained Susey in the schoolroom, until I was sure that Mr. T- was safely ensconced in his hiding place. Then we went to our room, and having carefully fastened the door, commenced undressing as usual right opposite my wardrobe. I stopped her as she was putting on her nightdress, and said:<break time="100ms" />"Susey, the night is warm, let us have some sport before we go to bed. And first give me a good peep at your nice little cunt."<break time="100ms" />I stretched open her thighs, as she leaned back on the bed, that Mr. T- might have a better view.<break time="100ms" />I opened the soft pouting lips, and said:<break time="100ms" />"Your cunt is very red to-night, have you much feeling in it?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, it is all aglow. Oh! pinch the clitoris - rub your finger - there - you may push it in if you like."<break time="100ms" />The door of the press opened a little further.
    </voice>
</speak>
