<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />And supple his wrist,<break time="100ms" />And he handled the Rod,<break time="100ms" />With a terrible twist,<break time="100ms" />But muscles grow weary,<break time="100ms" />And arms lose their powers,<break time="100ms" />There's an end for all nice things,<break time="100ms" />For floggings - like flowers.<break time="100ms" />Shrieks Frank Fane, "I'm dying!"<break time="100ms" />Says Redgy," You a'nt,<break time="100ms" />And if you go off<break time="100ms" />In a bit of a faint,<break time="100ms" />We'll soon thrash you back<break time="100ms" />Into living again,<break time="100ms" />You've not done with swishing<break time="100ms" />Just yet - Master Fane!"<break time="100ms" />Now the whipping is over,<break time="100ms" />And the culprit is free,<break time="100ms" />I don't think he'll sit down,<break time="100ms" />This evening for tea!<break time="100ms" />And when in a fortnight<break time="100ms" />He's turned down once more,<break time="100ms" />I fancy he'll find<break time="100ms" />His bottom still sore.<break time="100ms" />From an unsophisticated Manuscript found amongst the old lady's papers, after her death, supposed to have been written about A.D. 1797.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER 1.<break time="100ms" />When I was sixteen years old I was a pupil teacher at the N. School. I had a bedroom to myself, but I always chose one of the elder girls to sleep with me. My favourite, Susey P-, was about my own age, and of a warm friendly disposition. We soon became very intimate, and promised to tell each other all our secrets.<break time="100ms" />We were both exceedingly curious to know all about the secret pleasures of love, and often talked over the subject at night, all the time fondling and playing with each other's cunts.<break time="100ms" />"Did you ever hear any name for this little chink, May?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, dear, cunt. One of the girls wrote it the other day on her slate. She said that was what the boys called it."<break time="100ms" />"And what do they call their own things?"<break time="100ms" />"Pricks."<break time="100ms" />"Why do they call them pricks?"<break time="100ms" />"I suppose it is because they prick our cunts."<break time="100ms" />"Would you like to have your cunt pricked?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, I think, I would like it now, for my cunt feels so very hot."<break time="100ms" />"So it is, and mine is just the same. O May! if my cunt could be turned into a prick what fun we would have."<break time="100ms" />She then got over me, and rubbed her cunt against mine, while I held the cheeks of her bottom and pressed her in between my thighs.<break time="100ms" />"May, did you ever notice the lump between the legs of Mr. T-, the resident tutor?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, dear, that's his prick, every man has that, though some have it larger than others."<break time="100ms" />"O yes, I know that, but have you seen it swell out when he talks to us girls, and leans over us to make us hold our pens right?"<break time="100ms" />"Perhaps he is then thinking of our cunts."<break time="100ms" />"I am sure of it, and especially of yours, for you are his favourite. If he were here now I know what he would like to do."<break time="100ms" />"What?"<break time="100ms" />"Just to get on top of you, and shove his prick into your cunt, and fuck you."<break time="100ms" />I only laughed, and we soon fell asleep.<break time="100ms" />On Sunday, a short time after, having a headache, I remained at home. I was not aware that anyone was in the house, until happening to pass Mr. T-'s room, he suddenly sprang out, caught me in his arms, drew me in, and closed the door.<break time="100ms" />"Oh Mr. T-. Please let me go."<break time="100ms" />"Dearest May, let me tell you how dearly I love you." And while he half smothered me with kisses, he gently drew me towards the bed.<break time="100ms" />"No, I won't sit down - let me up - don't attempt to put your hands under my clothes."<break time="100ms" />But he forced his hand up, and I felt his eager fingers exploring all my secrets there.<break time="100ms" />"Mr. T-, take your hand - I cannot allow such liberties - let me up, or I'll scream."<break time="100ms" />"Don't, my pet, for there is no one to hear."<break time="100ms" />"Do let me up, and take your hand - oh my! how dare you lift my clothes."<break time="100ms" />He held me down, and soon, in spite of my struggles, he uncovered all my belly and thighs, and my cunt lay bare and exposed to view.<break time="100ms" />It was the first time it had been seen by man, and I felt horribly ashamed. But a peculiar sensation of pleasure quickly turned the idea of exposure into a source of delight.<break time="100ms" />His face flushed, and his eyes sparkled as he looked down, and exclaimed, "What a lovely cunt you have, May; this rising mound is covered with such a profusion of rich brown hair, and the swelling lips, how deliciously they pout, while the glowing red chink between is most luxurious and inviting. I must kiss it. Oh! how sweetly it smells."<break time="100ms" />He stooped and warmly kissed my cunt.<break time="100ms" />Then opening the lips he sucked the clitoris and pushed his tongue into the hot recess.<break time="100ms" />The touch of his mouth made my cunt thrill, and when I felt his tongue moving around the clitoris, and penetrating the sensitive folds inside, I could not help opening my thighs and raising myself a little, so as to afford him a freer access to that pleasurable spot.<break time="100ms" />When he stood up I saw that his trousers were down, and that his prick was sticking out pointed towards me, and nodding its great red head as if in proud defiance.<break time="100ms" />Holding it in his hand, he said, "Look at this poor fellow, May, he craves your kind indulgence, and only asks to hide his blushing head for a moment in this sweet nest; won't you take him in your hand?"<break time="100ms" />"O, for shame! Mr. T-. Put that horrid thing away. I won't look at it, or touch it. I won't let you put it in." And I covered my cunt with my hand. He pulled my hand away, and placing it on his prick, forced my fingers round it. It felt deliciously smooth and soft, but at the same time firm and stiff.<break time="100ms" />"Mr. T-, let me up. What do you mean?"<break time="100ms" />"I mean that I am going to fuck you May; to put my prick into your cunt and fuck you."<break time="100ms" />"I will never let you. It would harm me, and hurt me."<break time="100ms" />"No, my love, it will neither hurt you nor harm you. Let me put it in, do, my sweet pet."<break time="100ms" />He pushed the head of his prick in between the lips of my cunt, and moving it up and down the furrow, said, "There, that does not hurt you, I am sure." He then placed it at the inner opening, and with a sudden push forced it in.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! Mr. T-. Take it out. Oh! it is hurting me. You said you would not hurt me."<break time="100ms" />But he only pushed harder, then something gave away inside, and I felt the whole prick rush up into my belly. It had a startling effect at first, and almost took away my breath, but when he went on to work his tool in and out, and I felt it rubbing with a most delicious friction against the throbbing folds of my cunt, the feeling became one of overpowering delight. I twisted about and heaved to meet his thrusts.<break time="100ms" />"There, darling, now don't you like that?"
    </voice>
</speak>
