<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Susey, my pet, I want to see you make water. I'll hold the pot between your legs, and you can do your pee into it." I did so, and soon the hot piss came gurgling out. I heard a stir in the press behind me.<break time="100ms" />"Now, May, it is my turn to see you perform, and I will hold the pot for you." I spread my thighs and fired away.<break time="100ms" />"Lean back May, and let us tip cunts, for want of something better."<break time="100ms" />She got in between my thighs, and pushed hard against my cunt. Mr. T- must have had a grand view of her peach-like bottom, as she heaved it up and down.<break time="100ms" />The door of the press opened further, and I could see the head of a prick sticking out.<break time="100ms" />"Tell me, May, once again, how you felt the first time you were fucked?"<break time="100ms" />"Well, you know, he pushed me back on the bed, pulled up my clothes, and in spite of all my efforts, laid bare my cunt. Then he forced himself in between my thighs, and with his naked prick standing up. He made me take it in my hand and rub it up and down. He praised my cunt, and sucked it, which I thought very nice, though I wondered at his doing it."<break time="100ms" />"I don't," said Susey. "I love to suck your cunt, darling May, but go on, tell me more."<break time="100ms" />"He said he wanted to fuck me. I said he shouldn't, but he forced the head of his prick into the mouth of my cunt. Then giving a great heave he drove it up. It smarted me a good deal at first, but when it got in altogether, and he commenced to work it in and out, the pleasure was so great that I could not help telling him, when he asked me, that I liked his fucking very much, and that his prick felt very nice in my cunt."<break time="100ms" />Here Susey commenced bounding between my thighs. "Oh! May! how I long for a prick. How I do wish that Mr.- was here. I could almost ask him to fuck me, my cunt is so burning hot."<break time="100ms" />The press door opened, and Mr. T- stepped out perfectly naked. In a moment he was behind Susey, poking his prick against her cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Here I am then, ready and delighted to gratify each of my sweet pets."<break time="100ms" />Susey started, but when she looked back and saw Mr. T-, and felt the head of his prick in her cunt, she hid her blushing face in my neck, and resigned herself to his amorous attack.<break time="100ms" />I laughed and held her buttocks open while he drove his prick into her maiden cunt.<break time="100ms" />It did not hurt her much, as she had enlarged the opening when frigging it with her finger.<break time="100ms" />After a few strokes I asked her how she liked the feel of a prick in her cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Oh May," she replied, "why do you ask me. You know well yourself how a prick feels."<break time="100ms" />I slipped my hand between them, and felt her hot clitoris clinging to his prick, as it plunged in and out. While at every push she got behind, her belly and breasts heaved against mine.<break time="100ms" />Mr. T- was too much excited by all that he had seen and heard to be able to prolong his fuck, so he had to draw out his prick to avoid harm.<break time="100ms" />I held it in my hand, as he rubbed it in the furrow between the cheeks of her bottom, and I soon felt the emitting spasm, as it poured a stream of hot sperm over her back.<break time="100ms" />Susey seemed disappointed, however, and asked why he took it out.<break time="100ms" />"Just because I would not injure you."<break time="100ms" />Then he explained how that unless the seed was injected on the mouth of the womb, which lay at the end of the passage, there was no danger of any woman being put in the family way. And though the pleasure of both parties is lessened by the withdrawal of the prick at the moment of highest enjoyment, yet a man must be a selfish brute if on that account he would run the risk of doing such a grievous wrong to any girl whom he respected and loved.<break time="100ms" />He now placed his pendant tool in Susey's hand, and said if she would pet it a little that it would soon be in working order again.<break time="100ms" />She raised it up, and regarding it with interest, drew back the soft movable skin, and uncovered its rosy head.<break time="100ms" />"Kiss it Susey," I said bending her down.<break time="100ms" />She kissed the end of his prick, as she gently worked it up and down. Then as it gradually stiffened she let its head pass into her mouth, while her roving hands wandered over his bottom and balls.<break time="100ms" />Then he laid her back that he might inspect and kiss her pretty love chink.<break time="100ms" />"Is not this soft red hair very nice?" I said, passing my hand over her swelling mound.<break time="100ms" />"Yes it is exceedingly nice and exciting," and he buried his mouth in the pouting slit, while I caressed his prick and balls.<break time="100ms" />Rising up, he presented his prick, which had now regained its former size and strength, and asked, "Which of you will take it in?"<break time="100ms" />Susey said, "Fuck May, Mr. T-. I would so like to put your prick into her cunt, and see you fuck her."<break time="100ms" />He leaned over me as I lay back on the bed, and Susey, looking up between his legs, popped his tool into my cunt, and held his balls as he pushed it up.<break time="100ms" />Then, at his request, she laid down beside me, with her thighs up, and her pretty little cunt open before him. He leaned over and kissed it, at the same time softly working his prick in and out of my cunt, and not being so hot as before, he was able to prolong the pleasant exercise. After a minute or two he stopped and said, "I must take it out now, as I feel it coming. Hold it in your hand Susey, and you will soon see what a man's seed is like."<break time="100ms" />She held it over my belly, while he pressed his balls against my cunt. And the white seed, like fluid starch, spouted in spurts from his excited tool.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! isn't it funny," she said, stooping down, and touching with her lips the tip of his prick, when a fresh spurt darted into her mouth.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! there is very little taste. Will it do me any harm in my mouth?"<break time="100ms" />"None whatever, not even if you swallowed it all, indeed, it is considered most invigorating."<break time="100ms" />He told us afterwards how greatly he enjoyed seeing us playing together, and especially doing our pee, for, he added, nothing excites a man so much as seeing a woman doing her pee, the water streaming out of her hairy chink is most suggestive of love's delights.<break time="100ms" />We spent many nights after this when we sported and fucked in every possible way. His great delight was to have one of us sucking his prick and tickling his bottom, while he sucked and frigged the cunt of the other. He loved to make us spend in his mouth, at the same time that we swallowed his seed.<break time="100ms" />We let him fuck us in our bottoms too.
    </voice>
</speak>
