<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Yes, I like it now, that's very nice."<break time="100ms" />"Now say its name."<break time="100ms" />I whispered, "Prick."<break time="100ms" />"Say it out."<break time="100ms" />"Prick."<break time="100ms" />"And yours?"<break time="100ms" />"Cunt."<break time="100ms" />"And doing this?"<break time="100ms" />"Fucking."<break time="100ms" />"Go on, say what it is you like."<break time="100ms" />"I like to feel your prick fucking my cunt."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, go on, it's just coming."<break time="100ms" />"Prick - cunt - fucking - belly - bottom."<break time="100ms" />Then, drawing his prick suddenly out of my cunt, he poured a torrent of hot seed over my belly, and up to my very breasts. After this Mr. T- and I lost no opportunity of performing the sweet rites of Venus, and he soon initiated me into all the various ways and modes of enjoyment. I found that I could fully trust him, as he was very discreet, and particularly careful to avoid doing me harm.<break time="100ms" />Susey and I too became more and more confidential. I acknowledged to her that I had been fucked, but did not name Mr. T-.<break time="100ms" />One night I prevailed on her to give me full particulars of some love scenes between her elder sister Jane and her intended, Mr. John C-.<break time="100ms" />"They used to take me out to walk with them. They generally went to a wood, where they had a favourite resting place, well sheltered among the trees. But when there they always sent me away to gather blackberries or flowers.<break time="100ms" />"I often saw him kiss her, and sometimes when no one was looking, push his hand up under her petticoats. This aroused my curiosity, and I resolved to watch them.<break time="100ms" />"So the next time when I went off with my basket, I made a circuit, and entered the wood behind them. I crept through the trees until I could both hear and see them plainly.<break time="100ms" />"He was lying on his back, his trousers all open, and a long fleshy thing with a purple head was standing up. She was stooping over it moving it up and down with her hand. Then she kissed it, and took it in her mouth and sucked it.<break time="100ms" />"'How nicely you suck my prick, Jane. Kneel up now, I want to see your beautiful bottom and cunt at the same time.'<break time="100ms" />"As she did so he threw up her clothes over her back, uncovering the two round cheeks of her bottom, and the thick lips of her cunt jutting out like a huge hairy mouth between.<break time="100ms" />'"My darling, you have a splendid backside, the sight of it would bring to life the prick of a dying man. Keep as you are, I'll fuck you this time from behind, in what is called dog fashion.'<break time="100ms" />"He then got up, and knelt between her legs, and drawing apart the white cheeks of her bottom, pushed his prick into her cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Then holding her hips, he worked his article rapidly in and out, telling her to push back her bottom to meet each thrust of his prick.<break time="100ms" />"She panted and pushed, while he grunted out, 'Do you feel it Jane? Do you feel my prick?'<break time="100ms" />"'Yes, dear John, I do feel your prick, ever so far up my cunt - that's right - drive it in hard. Fuck-fuck-fuck.'<break time="100ms" />"Then they fell together on the grass, and I ran away."<break time="100ms" />"How did your cunt feel, Susey, when you saw his prick, and watched them fucking?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, it used to get very hot, and then I would rub it and squeeze it as hard as I could."<break time="100ms" />"Did you often see them doing it, Susey?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, many a time, and in every kind of way. Would you believe it, I saw him once fuck her in her bottom, and she did not mind it a bit."<break time="100ms" />"Did they ever find you out, Susey?"<break time="100ms" />"They did. I'll tell you how. One day I crept up very close to them, she was standing with her back against a tree, holding up her clothes. He was kneeling between her legs kissing her cunt. He looked up and she said:<break time="100ms" />"'Well, to please you - there - watch.'<break time="100ms" />"And a stream of amber fluid spurted out with a hissing noise from between the hairy lips of her cunt. She had scarcely done before he kissed it again, and sipped up the drops that hung about the hairs.<break time="100ms" />"'Now, John, it's my turn to see you spouting.'<break time="100ms" />"'Well, if you hold my prick I'll try.'<break time="100ms" />"She held it while he pissed, rubbing it all the time, as if she was milking a cow's teat, and when he had done, she kissed and sucked it.<break time="100ms" />'"Your prick is in grand order to-day. Look how stiff it is.'<break time="100ms" />"She bent it down, and let it go, when it sprang up erect as before.<break time="100ms" />"'Lie on your back, John, and I'll get over you, I know it is a way you like.'<break time="100ms" />"So he lay down, his fine prick standing up in full erection.<break time="100ms" />"'Now tuck up, and turn your bottom to my face.'<break time="100ms" />"She did so, and straddling over him with her great white bum jutting out, she stuffed his prick, neck and shoulders, into her gaping cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Then she bounded up and down like a jockey riding. When she rose up I could see the prick standing up, all red and inflamed. Then heaving down, the prick rushed up into her cunt, and her bottom came flap against his belly.<break time="100ms" />"This scene excited me greatly. I envied Jane. She seemed to enjoy it so thoroughly. And not thinking what I was doing, I forced my middle finger right up my cunt, the sudden pain made me cry. 'Oh!' They started, and quickly drawing aside the branches, saw me, my clothes up, and my finger in my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"'Holloa, Susey! is that you?' cried John.<break time="100ms" />"'You wicked little minx,' said Jane, 'how dare you steal upon us in that manner?'<break time="100ms" />"I said nothing, but covering my face with my hands, began to cry.<break time="100ms" />'"Don't scold her, perhaps she could not help it. Come here, Susey, sit down and dry your tears. Now promise you will never speak of anything you may have seen.'<break time="100ms" />"I sat down, and earnestly promised all that they desired.<break time="100ms" />"John, passing his hand up under my clothes, and pinching the lips of my cunt, said: 'You have already given me a glimpse of this little nook, Susey. I want a closer and fuller view. Lean back. Open your legs. There. There. Hasn't she a nice innocent looking little cunt, Jane? I think the cunt of a young girl before the hair grows over it is particularly pleasant to look upon, and to kiss too,' he said, as he held up my bottom with his hands, and buried his face between my legs.<break time="100ms" />"I felt his whiskers brushing my thighs, and his soft tongue pushing into my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"'Yes,' replied Jane, 'you may pet and kiss Susey's little plaything as much as you like, but remember that is all.'<break time="100ms" />"'Tell me, Susey, what did you see?'<break time="100ms" />'"I saw you pushing something into Jane.'<break time="100ms" />"He drew out his prick, and putting my hand on it, asked, 'Was this what you saw?'<break time="100ms" />"'Yes.'<break time="100ms" />"'Do you know what it is called?'<break time="100ms" />"'Yes, I heard Jane call it prick.'
    </voice>
</speak>
