<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The seven (no longer virgins) now washed the king and queen, and then themselves, after which all were refreshed and reinvigorated by stimulating wines and viands. Esther again excited her Royal spouse, till his pego was as a bar of iron; she made him enter the bottoms of all her maids, but without spending his Royal seed, till at last presenting her own lovely buttocks, she received the weapon of love in her anus, and kept him there till he rewarded her devotion by another copious emission.<break time="100ms" />Thus she became queen, and, as the king said when he presented her to the nobles of the Court, she surpassed in virtue and loveliness all the women of his realm.<break time="100ms" />The Marriage Morn.<break time="100ms" />Tune — The Merry Dance.<break time="100ms" />The marriage morn I can't forget,<break time="100ms" />My senses teem'd with new delight;<break time="100ms" />Time, cry'd I, haste the coming night,<break time="100ms" />And Hymen, give me sweet Lisette:<break time="100ms" />I whisper'd softly in her ear,<break time="100ms" />And said, "The God of Night draws near."<break time="100ms" />Oh, how she look'd! Oh, how she smil'd! Oh, how she sigh'd!<break time="100ms" />She sigh'd - then spent a joyful tear.<break time="100ms" />Now nuptial Night her curtain drew,<break time="100ms" />And Cupid's mandate was, "Commence<break time="100ms" />With ardour, break the virgin fence."<break time="100ms" />Then to bed sweet Lisette flew,<break time="100ms" />'Twas heav'n to view her when she lay,<break time="100ms" />And hear her cry, "Come to me, pray."<break time="100ms" />Oh, how I feel! Oh, how I pant! Oh, I shall die-<break time="100ms" />Shall die before the break of day!<break time="100ms" />Soon Manhood rose with furious gust,<break time="100ms" />And Mars, when he lewd Venus view'd,<break time="100ms" />Ne'er felt his pow'r so closely screw'd<break time="100ms" />Up to the standing post of Lust;<break time="100ms" />But when the stranger to her sight,<break time="100ms" />Sweet Lisette saw in rampant plight,<break time="100ms" />Oh, how she scream'd! Oh, how she scream'd! Oh, how she scream'd!<break time="100ms" />She scream'd - then grasp'd the dear delight!<break time="100ms" />Now lustful Nature eager grew,<break time="100ms" />And longer could not wanton toy;<break time="100ms" />So rushing up the path of joy,<break time="100ms" />Quick from the fount Love's liquor flew;<break time="100ms" />At morn, she cry'd, "Full three times three,<break time="100ms" />The vivid stream I've felt from thee;<break time="100ms" />Oh, how I'm eas'd! Oh, how I'm pleas'd! Oh, how I'm charm'd!<break time="100ms" />I'm charm'd with rapt'rous three times three!"<break time="100ms" />Lady Pokingham, or They All Do It.<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />PART V.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)<break time="100ms" />The Earl was as good as his promise. "My Robert," as I called him in our loving intercourse, was so well schooled that he was quite equal to the assertion of all his rights as a husband by the time Lady Cecilia returned home.<break time="100ms" />After dinner, on the evening of her arrival from the country, he found me sitting alone in the conservatory, and sitting down by my side, whispered in my ear how delighted he was at being able to have a last word of advice with me before retiring to rest with his, no doubt, rather expectant spouse.<break time="100ms" />"You have so drained me, last night and early this morning, dear Beatrice," he said, putting his arm round my waist, and meeting my ready lips in a long breathless kiss, and then continued, "Nothing but some extraordinary excitement will enable me to do justice to her expectations. I must fuck her at least three or four times after such a long absence; how shall I be equal to the occasion?"<break time="100ms" />"Have me first," I replied, "whilst she is seeing the children put to bed, there is plenty of time; it will give you zest for the fun to come, the idea of taking the virginity of her maiden bottom-hole will excite you enough, and the more she resists and gets indignant, the more you will enjoy it."<break time="100ms" />I had been gently stroking his prick outside his trousers; my touch was magical, it stiffened immediately, and when I let the impatient prisoner out of his confinement, I thought I had never before seen his priapus so distended and inflamed with lust as at that moment.<break time="100ms" />Rising up, I first stooped to give the engine of love a warm kiss, and keeping it in my hand, raised my clothes; and turning my bottom to his belly, spitted myself on the loving object, opening my legs and straddling over his lap, so as to get the very last fraction of its length into my heated cunt. We sat still for a moment or two, enjoying the mutual sensations of repletion and possession so delightful to each of the participators in a loving fuck, before commencing those soul-stirring movements which gradually work our heated desires to that state of frenzied madness which can only be allayed by the divinely beneficent ecstasy of spending, and mingling the very essences of our nature.<break time="100ms" />The idea that I was robbing his hated wife of her just expectations added such piquancy to our loving conjunction that I literally moaned or whined with delight, as I twisted my head round in the act of emission, so as not to lose the luscious kiss which is such an extra pleasure in those supreme moments of our happiness.<break time="100ms" />He did not come at the same time, but stopped and rested a moment or two, then rising, and keeping me still impaled on his dear prick, without losing place even for a single second, he laid my body face downwards on a little table which stood handy, and then recommenced his delicious moves, with his hands under me in front, frigging and tickling my cunt, till I almost wrenched myself away from him by the violence of my convulsive contortions. Suddenly drawing quite out, with another plunge he drove the head of his tool into the smaller orifice, which is so delightfully near and convenient when in the position in which he had me.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! Oh-oh-oh-oh-o-o-o-oe!!" I screamed, swimming in lubricity as I felt him so gorging my bottom, whilst his busy fingers were adding to my erotic madness by the artistic way in which they groped within my spending cunt. "Oh, heavens, Robert, Robert! Do, do Come darling! There, ah-re, I feel it, how deliciously warm!" I murmured excitedly, as his flood of boiling seed inundated the gratified and sensitive sheath which enclosed him so tightly. After recovering from our transports, we conversed about how he should proceed with his wife, his prick all the while as stiff as a policeman's truncheon, till at last fearing Lady Cecilia might surprise us, I went into the drawing-room and played the piano whilst he smoked his cigarette amongst the flowers in the conservatory outside the window.<break time="100ms" />Her Ladyship pretending fatigue (we knew what she was in a hurry for), the family retired rather earlier than usual to rest, but I took care to be at my peephole before Cecilia and Robert entered their bedroom.
    </voice>
</speak>
