<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"What's that to me, you've got to suck it, so go on, my dear, without all those wry faces, which only add to my fun, it's rare sport to make you submit to my fancies. I find I've been a fool ever since I was married, not to have asserted my right to do as I please with every bit of your person, cunt, arse, mouth, or bubbies; they can all afford me intense pleasure, without getting in the family way. Now go on, and I will fuck you with a fine large dildoe. Mind you must swallow every drop of my spendings when it comes."<break time="100ms" />He forced his prick between her reluctant lips, all slimy and soiled as it was from the previous enculade, then producing an enormous dildoe, nearly twelve inches long, and big in proportion, he put a little cold cream on it, and presented the head to her notch, trying to force it in.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! No! no! that's so awfully large!" she almost screamed, but the head was partly in, and despite her sobs: and moans of pains, he soon succeeded in passing at least ten inches of it into her distended vagina.<break time="100ms" />Her cunt was exposed towards me, so that I could see how gorged it was with that big india-rubber tool, and the sight of her slit so stretched to its utmost capacity caused quite a thrill of desire to shoot through my veins; it was almost impossible for me to prevent myself making some kind of demonstration. How I longed to be with them and join in the orgie of lust. Each shove of that tremendous affair now seemed to afford her the most intense delight. She sucked his prick in a kind of delirium, her highly wrought feelings banishing every sense of delicacy, shame, or disgust that might have previously deterred her from doing so. I frigged myself furiously, they screamed and spent, till at last both spectatrix and actors were thoroughly exhausted.<break time="100ms" />When I awoke next morning, and applied my eye to the peephole, it was just in time to see Her Ladyship awake. First she felt her cunt to see if it was all right, and not ruined by the giant dildoe she had taken in the previous night. Her eyes sparkled with desire, and she repeatedly blushed as I suppose the recollection flashed through her mind. Presently throwing the sheet entirely off her husband's body, she handled his limp affair for a few moments, then putting her face down, took the head of his prick in between her lovely lips, and sucked away with evident relish, till she had him in a glorious state of fitness, and was about to treat herself to a proper St. George, when Robert, who had only been feigning sleep to see what his randy wife would do, suddenly woke up, and insisted upon her applying it to her arse-hole instead of her cunt, wetting it with spittle.<break time="100ms" />Slowly but surely she achieved its insertion, although to judge by her face it was evidently a painful operation. But when once in how they enjoyed that glorious bottom-fuck. Even after he had spent she rode on till he met her again, and both seemed to come at the same time, kissing each other in a frenzy of erotic madness.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />The New Patent Fucking Machine.<break time="100ms" />Dear Mary, I promised to write directly when to school I returned.<break time="100ms" />But I think when this letter is finished 'twere better by far it were burned;<break time="100ms" />For a girl has just now returned to us, and bought while in town she has been<break time="100ms" />The last improvement in dildoes - the new patent Fucking Machine.<break time="100ms" />At night when we go to our bedrooms, we go in for a jolly good spree,<break time="100ms" />And first I perform upon Fanny and then she performs upon me.<break time="100ms" />It beats the old "flatcocks" a long way, you know the old game that I mean,<break time="100ms" />Oh! mustn't a man be galoptious if he beats the new Fucking Machine?<break time="100ms" />It beats fingers by far too - a long way, its shape is just like a tool,<break time="100ms" />The girl who owns it is good-natured, she has fucked, I believe, the whole school;<break time="100ms" />She has it herself much too often, and is getting most awfully lean,<break time="100ms" />And her pussey's quite tender with using the patent new Fucking Machine.<break time="100ms" />It gives a delightful sensation, your breath comes too quickly to speak,<break time="100ms" />Whilst Fanny was doing it for me I bit a piece out of her cheek;<break time="100ms" />And when you feel yourself spending and clasp it your legs in between,<break time="100ms" />Oh! I should die if it ever got broken, God preserve the new Fucking Machine!<break time="100ms" />A new girl arrived, dearest Mary, and slept during last night with me;<break time="100ms" />When I put the machine to her "cunny," she said, "None of that sort for me!"<break time="100ms" />She turned up her nose at our patent, and said we were "awfully green,"<break time="100ms" />To injure ourselves with such habits, and not have the real Fucking Machine.<break time="100ms" />That the men are all dying to have us, if only we'll give them the chance;<break time="100ms" />She was herself had in the carriage, coming home from the Lord Mayor's dance.<break time="100ms" />Now directly I get home next Xmas, I'll spoon my young cousin Jack Green,<break time="100ms" />And I swear he'll be only too ready, to lend me his Fucking Machine.<break time="100ms" />Anecdote of Kate Santley.<break time="100ms" />One night, at the Alhambra, amongst a shower of bouquets from the boxes, a carrot was thrown from the gallery. She coolly gathered an armful of trophies, and after bowing again and again to the boxes, looked up with a smile at the gods, as she said, "Excuse me taking your carrot, now I have the flowers," and tripped off the stage amidst a storm of applause.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
