<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"No fear, Tom," I replied, stretching out to one side, when my foot slipped, and I came sliding down, just over him, so that his head passed up between my thighs.<break time="100ms" />He caught me in his arms, and as he held me for a moment I felt him kiss my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Miss, are you hurt?"<break time="100ms" />"Not much, only a little stunned. Carry me into the summer-house."<break time="100ms" />He took me in his arms, his hand still resting on my naked bottom, and laid me on a seat.<break time="100ms" />"Shall I call anyone, Miss? You seem very faint."<break time="100ms" />"No Tom. I shall be all right in a few mintues; it is only my knee."<break time="100ms" />I lay on my back with one leg up. He was kneeling on the ground at my side. I saw him peeping up under my dress.<break time="100ms" />"Is it here, Miss?" Putting his hand on my knee, "May I rub it?" "Yes Tom, thank you, that makes it better."<break time="100ms" />He rubbed my knee, he touched my thigh above the stocking, he moved his hand gradually higher and higher, until at last he slightly touched the hair on my cunt. He looked up at my face. I lay with my eyes closed.<break time="100ms" />He grew bolder, he pressed the lips, he felt the chink between, he rubbed the clitoris.<break time="100ms" />"Tom, where are you putting your hand?" I said in a languid tone.<break time="100ms" />"Oh Miss, I can't help it. You are so beautiful."<break time="100ms" />He convulsively grasped my cunt, and pushed his fingers into its glowing slit.<break time="100ms" />"Tom, I cannot allow this, let me up."<break time="100ms" />"Darling Miss May, don't be angry."<break time="100ms" />He forced his head under my clothes, and rapturously kissed my cunt.<break time="100ms" />I trembled with delight as I felt the touch of his lips, and the soft probing of his tongue, yet for appearance' sake, I cried, "For shame, Tom, let me up, you are making me very angry."<break time="100ms" />I raised myself on my elbow, and saw that his prick was out and standing in fine condition.<break time="100ms" />"Tom, how dare you expose yourself in that manner. Go away." "Miss May, I can't help it, indeed I can't."<break time="100ms" />He still kept his hand on my cunt, opening and closing the lips, and pinching the clitoris.<break time="100ms" />He drew me across the wide seat, and getting in between my thighs, pushed the head of his prick against the lips of my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Sweet Miss May, do let me put it in, oh do."<break time="100ms" />"No Tom, I won't allow it. Let me up now, perhaps I may some other time."<break time="100ms" />He pushed again, the head entered, it passed up, the whole prick was in, it filled my cunt.<break time="100ms" />My hungry cunt, with what eagerness it sucked in a morsel so delicious! Oh! there is nothing to be compared to a standing prick for gratifying a girl who knows and understands the supreme delights of fucking.<break time="100ms" />So I lay back and let him work away. "Tom, what are you doing?"<break time="100ms" />"I am only - fucking - fucking your cunt - Miss May. Oh! how good you are - ain't that nice!" he said, as he drove up his prick with most thrilling effect.<break time="100ms" />"It is, dear Tom, press up to my heart."<break time="100ms" />"Do you like my fucking you, Miss?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, Tom, you have a very nice prick, but take care or you may do me harm."<break time="100ms" />The dear fellow understood me, and just before he spent drew out his prick. I took it in my hand, and held it while it poured forth a torrent of love's juice.<break time="100ms" />I need not say that after this many happy love scenes were enacted in the summer-house.<break time="100ms" />Tom proved very docile and prudent. He had a wonderful prick, always ready for its work, and eager for a fuck. He knew well how to use it with effect, and I soon found that he was no tyro in the art of love.<break time="100ms" />He told me many curious things; among others, that papa was in the habit of fucking our milk-maid Sarah in the hayloft. It was she herself told him, for he had been the first to open her maiden channel.<break time="100ms" />He offered to place me in a position where I could safely witness all that passed between them.<break time="100ms" />"Meet me early to-morrow morning. For it is after Sarah brings in the milk, and while Robert the groom is at his breakfast, that the master comes out."<break time="100ms" />So the next morning Tom conducted me to the hay-loft. He covered himself and me lightly with the hay.<break time="100ms" />We had not long to wait, for we soon heard papa talking in a low voice to Sarah as they came up the ladder.<break time="100ms" />They came down near us.<break time="100ms" />Papa then said: "Take him out, Sarah, I have been longing for a fuck all night."<break time="100ms" />She unbuttoned his trousers and drew out his prick. It was in good order, with a fine large ruby head.<break time="100ms" />The sight of my father's prick had a curious effect on me. At first I did not like to look at it, but at length the amorous feeling overpowered every other; and I almost<break time="100ms" />envied Sarah as she held it admiringly in her hand, slowly moving it up and down. Then she took out his balls, and putting her hand underneath pushed it on to his bottom.<break time="100ms" />He had meanwhile pulled up her coats, and uncovered a fine thick-lipped cunt, which pouted in fleshy luxuriance.<break time="100ms" />"What a splendid affair you have, Sarah! It is the most lascivious cunt I ever looked at. Now tell me, who fucked you last?"<break time="100ms" />"La, sir, why do you ask me that?"<break time="100ms" />"Just because it excites me more to hear you tell. You know I don't care who fucks you, provided you hide nothing from me, and keep yourself from harm. Did not Robert fuck you last evening? Your face was so red when I met you after leaving him."<break time="100ms" />"Well, to tell the truth, sir, he did." "Tell me how it happened."<break time="100ms" />"I went into the stable to borrow a lantern, he caught me in his arms and kissed me. Then he forced me back on a heap of straw, pushed his hand under my petticoats, and got hold of my cunt. I scolded him, and boxed his ears. He did not mind, but squeezing in between my thighs, he thrust his big tool into my cunt, and fucked me like mad."<break time="100ms" />"Has he a big tool, Sarah?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, it is very big and strong, but he does not use it as nicely as you do, he is always in too great a hurry."<break time="100ms" />Papa now got over her, she held his prick, and with his hand directed it into her cunt. He pushed it slowly up until his balls pressed her bottom. She grasped his buttocks, an vigorously heaved up to meet every thrust he gave, saying at every heave, "Dear sir, oh, how nice - push it in - drive it home - that's the way - how your prick fills my cunt - fuck me fast - fuck me hard."<break time="100ms" />I was leaning forward on the hay, and Tom over me, his prick and balls resting on my naked bottom; but as soon as papa commenced fucking Sarah, he lodged his prick in my cunt.<break time="100ms" />He then timed his strokes, so that each time papa pushed I felt Tom's prick driving up my cunt, and his hair tickling my bum.
    </voice>
</speak>
