<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"If you were really fond of me you would not come to me in this way - don't - I pray you leave me - oh, my! - how can you be so nasty - take your hand off me - I don't like it - no, it is not nice - let my hands go - I won't hold it - I won't move it up and down - don't separate my thighs with your knee - what are you getting over me for? What are you pushing into me?"<break time="100ms" />"My prick, darling Kate. There, don't struggle, my pet, let it in, don't be frightened, I won't harm you in any way. Open your thighs, that's the sweet girl. Now I'll push it in as gently as possible. There, it is in, it is all the way up."<break time="100ms" />Then the bed began to creak, and the clothes to rustle.<break time="100ms" />"Put your arms around me, my love. Heave up your dainty little bottom. That's right. Do you know what doing this is called?"<break time="100ms" />"No sir."<break time="100ms" />"It is called fucking. Isn't fucking very pleasant?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, it is now. Do I heave up right?"<break time="100ms" />"My darling, you heave as if you had been fucking all your life. Pinch my bottom. May I pinch yours?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, as hard as you like."<break time="100ms" />"Now place your hand here. Hold my prick. Hold it tight. Oh! there it comes."<break time="100ms" />And rolling off her he lay panting at her side.<break time="100ms" />I felt greatly excited, and crept into the room, close up to the bed. I heard them kissing.<break time="100ms" />"Did I hurt you, my love?"<break time="100ms" />"You did a little at first, but when your prick was well in, and you commenced fucking, there was no feeling but pleasure. Would you like me to pet your prick now?"<break time="100ms" />"I would, darling, rub it up and down, this way, put your other hand on the balls, move your fingers further back, still further, there."<break time="100ms" />"Have you much feeling there?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, there is great feeling behind the balls; don't you feel the root of the prick extending back to the little hole? That's a dear girl, the touch of your finger there is delicious. Push it in a little, my sweet pet. Kate, did you ever look at May's cunt?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, I have seen it when she was in the bath; it looks well covered with hair."<break time="100ms" />"I am sure if you made free with her you would have great fun together, for, unless I am greatly mistaken, she has a very randy disposition. Promise to try to- morrow night, and tell me next day all that you have succeeded in finding out."<break time="100ms" />She promised to carry out his wishes.<break time="100ms" />"But now that you have worked up my prick we must have another fuck. Lie over me this time."<break time="100ms" />I heard her getting over him.<break time="100ms" />"Now it's in, heave away my love. You must do all the fucking yourself." She panted as she worked her nimble bottom up and down over him. "Do you like it this way, my love?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, as a variety, but I like better to have you lying over me, and pushing in your prick."<break time="100ms" />He now prepared to leave, and I started for my own room, and was soon fast asleep.<break time="100ms" />I had several amorous dreams that night. I thought that Robert was flicking me in the loft, when papa came behind, pulled him off, and thrust his own prick into my cunt, and fucked me most delightfully. In my dream I felt no surprise at papa's fucking me; on the contrary, the idea seemed to add greatly to my enjoyment.<break time="100ms" />The next evening Kate offered to sleep with me. I could not repress a smile as I consented.<break time="100ms" />When we were undressing Kate said: "I would like to see you quite naked, May. You know we girls need not be ashamed of one another, and I will set the example."<break time="100ms" />She threw off her shift and stood before me, then pointing to my cunt she remarked that I had a great deal of hair there.<break time="100ms" />I replied that her dark hair was prettier, for it set off the whiteness of her skin.<break time="100ms" />She put her hand on my cunt, and asked me to let her feel it, "and you may feel mine if you like."<break time="100ms" />She touched the clitoris, and passing her finger down the slit pushed it up the passage, and said:<break time="100ms" />"Dear May, you are very open, were you always as open as you are now?" "No, I was not; but are not you very open too?"<break time="100ms" />She smiled as she said: "May, if you will give me your full confidence I will promise you mine."<break time="100ms" />"Agreed," said I.<break time="100ms" />"Did you ever see what a man has here?"<break time="100ms" />"I did, did you?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, do you know what it is called?"<break time="100ms" />"I have heard it called a prick, is that it?"<break time="100ms" />"It is. Had you ever a prick in here?"<break time="100ms" />"I have Kate, haven't you?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, dear. Now tell me how it happened, and I'll tell you about myself afterwards."<break time="100ms" />I related my adventure with Mr. T-, and how he was, so fond of kissing and sucking my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Would you like me to kiss it?"<break time="100ms" />"I would, dear Kate, and I'll kiss yours too."<break time="100ms" />"Well, lean back, lift your legs, open your thighs as widely as you can. There, do you like that?"<break time="100ms" />Holding my buttocks with her hands she sucked my cunt with great ardour, rolling her tongue round and round, and thrusting it up the passage.<break time="100ms" />After enjoying it for a while I said, "It is my turn now, dear Kate, let me pet and kiss your sweet cunt, while you are giving me the account you promised."<break time="100ms" />I sat on a stool between her thighs, and with my mouth buried in her open cunt, listened to her narrative.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />A Secret Revealed<break time="100ms" />or<break time="100ms" />The True Reason Why Queen Esther Pleased the King More Than All the Other Virgins.<break time="100ms" />From an Original Essay by I. van Meyen. Amsterdam, A.D. 1629. Text. - Esther, Chap. II, v. 2 to 17 inclusive.<break time="100ms" />The Jewish Rabbis have a tradition that it was entirely owing to the training Mordecai gave to his cousin Hadassah (or Esther), in order to prepare the young girl to be his own wife, that she was enabled to bear off the palm from all the competing virgins, when the whim of the Court suddenly causes her to be impressed for the royal pleasures, as well as hundreds of other beautiful girls throughout the kingdom, which of course at once quashes all her cousin's plans for his own future enjoyment.<break time="100ms" />Robbed of his prospective bride, Mordecai had the brilliant idea of making Esther's advancement the stepping stone of his own fortunes. He knew that kings regarded their numerous concubines as so many toys only to be cast aside, and perhaps never even looked upon again, when they had once submitted to the Royal ravisher, and his natural shrewdness and great knowledge of human nature made him reflect how cloyed and disgusted even a king must get with the sameness of the pleasure,* which the taking of hundreds of maidenheads from unresisting virgins could only afford him.
    </voice>
</speak>
