<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I spread my thighs and raised my bottom, Tom suddenly drew out his prick, and holding open the cheeks of my bottom, popped it in there. As it was well moistened with the juice of my cunt, it slipped in easily. I dared not speak, so had to let him have his own way.<break time="100ms" />He pushed it home, and bending his arms round my hip he frigged my cunt. After a few strokes, which were far from disagreeable, he administered a warm and soothing enema, just as papa with a grunt of satisfaction poured his libation at the shrine of Sarah's cunt.<break time="100ms" />He then got up and went away, after telling her to remain until he was out of the yard.<break time="100ms" />He had not gone many minutes when Robert popped up his head.<break time="100ms" />"Holloa, Sarah, so master has been just oiling your notch. I heard him fucking you, and all you said too. And now I'll have my revenge."<break time="100ms" />He seized her in his arms, threw her on the hay, and pitched her clothes over her head.<break time="100ms" />She struggled and kicked her legs about in the air, but Robert held her down while he gloated over her wriggling bum and inflamed cunt. It looked very red and open, while the rich juices of her previous fuck trickled down her bottom.<break time="100ms" />"So you say master fucks better than I do, and that I am always in too great a hurry. Well, I will be slow enough now."<break time="100ms" />He took out his prick, and held it in his hand, while he opened the lips of her cunt.<break time="100ms" />It was the largest prick I ever saw, and had a tremendous head. I was curious to see how she could take it in. He pushed it against her cunt. She plunged about.<break time="100ms" />"Be quiet," he shouted, giving her a slap on the bottom. "Keep your arse quiet, I say, and mind your fucking."<break time="100ms" />He forced the head in, and, to my surprise, it passed easily in. The huge prick must have filled her belly. He grasped the cheeks of her bottom on each side, and held her up, as he plunged his great prick with wonderful force in and out of her smoking gap.<break time="100ms" />I had seen many a fuck, but never a fuck like this. I admired the wonderful size and strength of Robert's prick, and could not repress a longing for a taste of its prowess.<break time="100ms" />Tom too was greatly excited by the scene, and fucked me in his best style. But it was the idea of Robert's prick that filled my mind.<break time="100ms" />The next afternoon, drawn by an irresistible attraction, I went into the stable.<break time="100ms" />"Robert, I have come to look after my mare, I think she wants to be clipped," and I stepped up.<break time="100ms" />"Take care, Miss," he said, putting his hand on my shoulder, "she is very restive just now."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, I am not afraid," and I began to pat her.<break time="100ms" />He made some kind of noise that caused her, I think, to plunge and kick.<break time="100ms" />"I told you so, Miss," he said, passing his hand down over my bosom, and drawing me towards him. "It is a mercy you were not killed." And he pressed me in his arms.<break time="100ms" />"Robert, let me go - where are you drawing me - you will make me fall. Oh! what do you mean - don't push your knees there - don't attempt to raise my dress. Robert, what are you about - I won't let you - take it away - you must not do it - Oh! oh!! - you are hurting me - Oh, my! what are you pushing in - yes, I do feel it - hold me in your arms - yes, I like that - you may fuck me, Robert, as hard as you like."<break time="100ms" />The monstrous prick was in my cunt. I felt it everywhere. He grasped my buttocks. He lifted me up. As he arose I clasped my arms round his neck, and crossed my legs over his back. He carried me around the stable, with his prick still embedded in my cunt. It seemed to penetrate to my very heart. Every nerve within me thrilled with rapture, as he shot into my vitals a stream of gushing sperm.<break time="100ms" />It was the first time I had ever received into my cunt the seed of man, and the feeling was intensely delicious.<break time="100ms" />"What have you done, Robert? Perhaps you have ruined me for life."<break time="100ms" />"Not at all, Miss, look here," and he showed me a large syringe, "and there happens to be warm water in this bucket. Let me syringe your cunt at once, it will remove all danger."<break time="100ms" />I lay back with my thighs widely extended, while he poured such a flood of water into my cunt as must have washed out every trace.<break time="100ms" />Robert then wiped and kissed it, after which he knelt by my side, and presented before me his prick once more in splendid condition.<break time="100ms" />"What a great fellow you have, Robert," I said as I chafed it in my hand, and uncovered its rosy head. I kissed it, and with difficulty took part of it in my mouth.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Miss May, you are very good, and you have the sweetest cunt I ever fucked, may I put it in again?"<break time="100ms" />"Not this time, Robert, I would rather pet this fine fellow, while you are tickling my cunt."<break time="100ms" />So keeping its glowing head in my mouth, with one hand I frigged the shaft, and with the other stirred his balls and touched his bottom, while he was equally busy about my seat of pleasure, deliciously frigging with his fingers each sensitive orifice.<break time="100ms" />And just as I felt my cunt flooded with love's effusion, he shot into my mouth such a torrent of seed that I could not swallow it fast enough, and it squirted out on each side of my mouth. It was pungent and pleasant to the taste.<break time="100ms" />Before I left him he swore on his oath never to speak of what had just happened, and he proved loyal and true.<break time="100ms" />I had now two esquires both able and willing to gratify me at any time, or in any way. And although I soon found out more of papa's secret amours, yet I myself exercised the greatest care and circumspection.<break time="100ms" />A few days after this adventure papa told me that as he considered I must be very lonely so much by myself, he had asked a young lady named Kate L- to come and stay with us for some time.<break time="100ms" />In due course she arrived. She was a nice, pleasing girl, with dark hair and eyes, and three years older than I was. I found her amiable and obliging, and ready to enter into my plans and share in my amusements.<break time="100ms" />Papa paid her particular attention, and I observed she did not seem at all averse.<break time="100ms" />They were often alone together, and I guessed something was going on, but she never told me anything.<break time="100ms" />Her bedroom was separated from mine by a bathroom, into which both our rooms opened.<break time="100ms" />One night, when we went upstairs, I sat for some time with her, and after bidding her good night, I passed through the bathroom, leaving the doors slightly opened. When I had undressed I put out my candle, and sat by the fire to warm my feet before going to bed.<break time="100ms" />I had not sat long when my curiosity was excited by hearing whispering in Kate's room.<break time="100ms" />I crept softly to the open door and listened. "Oh, sir, why have you come into my bed?" "Because I am so fond of you, my darling."
    </voice>
</speak>
