<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />This question hit the mark, and seeing how shame-faced and blushing they both were, I went on: "No doubt, examining to see which one showed most signs of hair on her little pussey. Let me see Annie," as I suddenly caught the bottom of her nightdress and in an instant had it reversed over her head, so as to cover up her face and expose all the rest of her beautiful little figure. "Why, the impudent little thing hasn't a hair to boast of! Give her bottom a good slapping, Patty!"<break time="100ms" />Patty was only too pleased to do it, and the slaps fairly echoed through the room, mingling with Annie's piteous cries to let her go.<break time="100ms" />My blood was up. The sight of her beautiful bum, all flushed and rosy under the sharply administered slaps, made me fairly lust to take further liberties. So I let the little victim go, whispering in her ear, and her tearful eyes were brightened in a moment. She darted at Patty and sooner than it takes to write was dragging her about the room fully exposed, with her head and arms secured in her reversed night- dress.<break time="100ms" />I amused myself by slapping poor Patty's pretty posteriors till they were almost black and blue, regardless of her sobbing and crying for mercy.<break time="100ms" />At last we let her go, and I took her on my lap to kiss away her tears. She soon smiled again and nestled herself to my body quite lovingly. This seemed to make her companion almost jealous as she appealed to me with a flushed face to kiss her also, which I readily did in the most loving manner, and I asked her to fetch a decanter of wine and some glasses from a cabinet, saying I felt so dull and sleepless I must have something to cheer me.<break time="100ms" />"Ah, my dear lady," exclaimed Patty, kissing me again and again, "you don't know how we all love you and feel for you, being left alone and unhappy. There is nothing we wouldn't do to bring a smile to your pale face."<break time="100ms" />"Then we'll sleep together and have a romp on the bed. Only mind, you are good girls, and never tell your mistress's doings," I replied, taking a glass of wine, and ordering them to do the same.<break time="100ms" />A second and a third glass seemed to open their eyes immensely; the least touch or joke sent them into fits of laughter. They blushed and seemed quite excited. In fact Patty, who had remained on my knee, was almost ready to faint with emotion as she caressed my face and bosom, the cause being a hand I had managed to slip under her nightdress, so that one finger had been tickling and playing with her almost hairless slit and gradually working her up to a state of excitement she was at a loss to comprehend.<break time="100ms" />"Let us all be naked. Throw off every rag, my dear ones, I want to feel your soft warm flesh next to mine, to cuddle you and feel you all over. Shall I read a pretty little piece of poetry about a potter who married your namesake, Patty?" I said, and seeing they were ready for anything, told Annie to bring me a manuscript called "The Haunted House" from a drawer in the cabinet.<break time="100ms" />"Now listen to 'The Tale of a Potter' and don't laugh till it is finished. You will find it rather free but nothing more than big girls like you ought to know." Then I commenced:<break time="100ms" />Young Hodge, he was a worthy wise,<break time="100ms" />A potter he by trade;<break time="100ms" />He fell in love with Martha Price,<break time="100ms" />She was a parson's maid.<break time="100ms" />This Hodge worked amongst his pans,<break time="100ms" />His pots, his mugs, his delf;<break time="100ms" />He said: "A sad fate is a man's<break time="100ms" />When he is by himself.<break time="100ms" />Now soon I'll marry Martha Price,<break time="100ms" />A nice snug home I've got;<break time="100ms" />The parson soon the knot shall splice,<break time="100ms" />And we'll both piss in one pot."<break time="100ms" />Then Hodge he made a pretty pot,<break time="100ms" />And took it to his love;<break time="100ms" />Said he: "I've brought this pot to show,<break time="100ms" />I mean your love to prove.<break time="100ms" />Now name the day, the happy day,<break time="100ms" />Whose night shall bring me bliss;<break time="100ms" />When your sweet cunt and my stiff prick<break time="100ms" />Shall mingle in this their piss."<break time="100ms" />They married were within a week,<break time="100ms" />And Hodge he was in luck;<break time="100ms" />He took sweet Patty's maidenhead<break time="100ms" />With his first vigorous fuck.<break time="100ms" />Then in her arms he fell asleep,<break time="100ms" />But started with affright;<break time="100ms" />And in the middle of the bed<break time="100ms" />He sat up bold and white.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, love! oh, love! I've had a dream,<break time="100ms" />A dream to cause me fright;<break time="100ms" />I dreamed we both were in my shop<break time="100ms" />And there I hugged you tight.<break time="100ms" />I dreamed I went your cheek to kiss,<break time="100ms" />We romped with hugs and squeezes;<break time="100ms" />When down I knocked the pots and pans<break time="100ms" />And broke them all in pieces."<break time="100ms" />Then Martha answered with a laugh:<break time="100ms" />"No pots you've broke, good man;<break time="100ms" />But much I fear this very night,<break time="100ms" />You've cracked a Patty Pan."<break time="100ms" />And from that night unto this day<break time="100ms" />Hodge in that crack would pop,<break time="100ms" />A prick as thick as any brick,<break time="100ms" />But the crack he cannot stop.<break time="100ms" />So maids beware, heed well your pans.<break time="100ms" />With this my tale is ended;<break time="100ms" />If your pan's cracked by prick of man,<break time="100ms" />It never can be mended.<break time="100ms" />Throwing down the manuscript, I had a finger in each of their cracks sooner than it takes to write. "What darling little pans each of you has! I long to throw you on the bed and kiss them. What do you think of mine with its soft curly hair? Only it's a broken pan, you know, my dears, as I've of course had my husband."<break time="100ms" />"La, and was that really so nice, dear lady? Oh, I love you so, do let me look," exclaimed Patty, slipping off my knee and kneeling between my legs to get a better sight of the object of her curiosity, which she first kissed most lovingly, and then, parting the hair, put a couple of fingers light up my cunt. This so tickled and delighted me that I leant back in the chair and pulled Annie close to my bosom as I hugged and kissed her, whilst I still had a finger in her little slit, as far as it would go. My legs also mechanically opened to facilitate inspection, as Patty exclaimed, "How deep my two fingers can go right up and it is so warm and moist. It makes me feel I could eat it!"<break time="100ms" />In a few minutes we were all tossing on my bed in a state of nature. They laughed, screamed and blushed as I excitedly examined and kissed their respective cunnies. How my tongue revelled around their budding clitorises till they rewarded me with those first virgin emissions which are always so deliciously thick and creamy. How lovingly they both repaid all my caresses, Patty paying the most ardent attentions to my cunt, which delighted her more and more every moment, whilst Annie seemed to prefer sucking my bubbies as I gamahuched her.
    </voice>
</speak>
