<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Now, Nina, be kind and you'll be my pet, and I will give you all sorts of pretty things - there, let me feel it, that's a sweet girl, open your legs more, lean against this tree, hold up your dress, give me your hand, place it here, close your fingers round it. That's the way. You have a dear little cunt, very fat and plump. But I wonder you have much hair on it. How old are you, Nina?"<break time="100ms" />"Just fifteen, sir."<break time="100ms" />"Now then, press out in front. Hold my prick, while I push it - there it's in - put your arms round me - press my bottom. How do you like the feel of my prick in your cunt?"<break time="100ms" />"It feels very nice, push it in more."<break time="100ms" />I heard them kissing and panting as they shoved together, and then they rested in each other's arms.<break time="100ms" />She soon left him, after promising to go out at that same hour that day every week.<break time="100ms" />I often followed him out now, and found he always had one of the slave girls with him.<break time="100ms" />I then learned all the terms and ways of enjoyment, for he was fond of variety, and loved to make them talk, and say all manner of words while he fucked them. And I was astonished to hear how freely they spoke of pricks, cunts, arses, frigging, fucking, pissing, etc.<break time="100ms" />Joe had been sent to school and my cunt, not having been entered for a long time, was in an aggravated state of longing and desire.<break time="100ms" />So, when Nina's turn came next, the thought flashed upon me, why not personate her for one occasion.<break time="100ms" />I was about her height and size, and my cunt was now pretty well furnished with hair. So when the hour came, I set her to a task which would occupy her for some time, and said I was in a hurry to have it done.<break time="100ms" />Then, going out in the dark I quietly strolled up the walk. Someone met me, put his arm round me, and pushed his knee in between my thighs.<break time="100ms" />"How is your sweet cunt tonight?"<break time="100ms" />I said nothing but only pressed against him as he lifted my dress and felt my cunt.<break time="100ms" />Moving his finger about, he said: "It's very hot and juicy tonight. I am sure it is longing for a fuck. Put your hand here, my love."<break time="100ms" />I felt his firm upstanding prick. I moved the loose skin up and down as Joe had taught me. I put my other hand below and felt the two soft balls in their hairy bag.<break time="100ms" />"Take it in your mouth, dear, for a moment."<break time="100ms" />I had gone too far to recede now, so I stooped and sucked its glowing head while I tickled him behind the balls.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Nina, that's delicious! Now lie back on this moss bank, raise your legs, open your dress, that I may press your soft bubbies, while my prick is in your cunt."<break time="100ms" />He knelt between my uplifted thighs. He leaned over me. He opened the lips of my cunt. He introduced his prick. He moulded my breasts. He kissed me and darted his tongue into my mouth.<break time="100ms" />"Say you like it, Nina, my love!"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, yes dear sir!" I whispered heaving up my bottom. "I feel your prick in my cunt - fucking - fucking - oh! so - deliciously!"<break time="100ms" />The rapturous feeling increased. He pushed and panted. I heaved and gasped: "Oh, yes, push, fuck, oh! oh! oh!"<break time="100ms" />He lay over me, his face on my shoulder and his prick buried in my cunt.<break time="100ms" />After a while he said: "I don't know how it is, Nina, but I never enjoyed fucking you so much before, your cunt closes on my prick with such a hot compression, and you nipped the head of my prick when I drove it home as you never did before, and which only a few women can do. Oh! there! I feel it now!"<break time="100ms" />(Here I interrupted Kate by asking: "What do you mean by nipping the head of his prick?"<break time="100ms" />"Well, my dear, I'll teach you. When you feel the entire prick driven in as far as it can go, draw up your bottom inside, as hard as you can. If you do it right you will squeeze the head of the prick as it rests on the mouth of your womb. Try it now while I have my finger in. Yes, that's the way."<break time="100ms" />"Well, go on, what did he say next?")<break time="100ms" />He asked me: "Is Miss Kate kind to you?"<break time="100ms" />"She is," I whispered in reply.<break time="100ms" />"Don't you attend her in the bath?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes."<break time="100ms" />"Does she let you see her cunt?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, I dry it and sometimes kiss it."<break time="100ms" />"Is it a nice little cunt?"<break time="100ms" />"Very nice."<break time="100ms" />"Do you think she has any longing to have it fucked?"<break time="100ms" />"I am sure she has, it is always red and hot."<break time="100ms" />"I guessed as much. Indeed, I often think of it when I observe her swelling hips. How I would enjoy fucking her, if I could only do it without letting her know who it was."<break time="100ms" />"Perhaps I could manage it for you. Come to my bed tomorrow night and I'll prevail on her to take my place. I'll tell her I expect a young fellow who will take her for me, and give her the greatest pleasure but without doing her any harm. If you find the door of my room unlocked you will know I succeeded."<break time="100ms" />Next evening, papa did not go out at all and I saw he was regarding me with a peculiar look in his eyes. He was also more affectionate and made me sit on his knee when I was bidding him good-night and he pressed my bottom and thighs in the warmest way.<break time="100ms" />Nina readily agreed to my taking her place for the night when I told her I had been restless of late and thought a change of my bed would do me good.<break time="100ms" />About midnight someone entered the room and felt his way to where he heard me breathing. He quietly put off his clothes, and slipped into bed. He put his arm over me and felt my cunt. He opened the lips and rubbed about the clitoris and then tried to push his finger up.<break time="100ms" />I held his hand.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, you hurt me!"<break time="100ms" />"Why, you are not my Nina at all."<break time="100ms" />"No, I am only Nina's friend."<break time="100ms" />"Well, whoever you are, you have a sweet cunt. Put your hand on this, it won't hurt you."<break time="100ms" />"But it will do me harm."<break time="100ms" />"No, trust me, my pet, I won't harm you."<break time="100ms" />He then got over me and began to push his prick against my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, no, I can't, I am afraid. Oh, pray don't, it is too big!"<break time="100ms" />I held him by the hips and pushed him back.<break time="100ms" />"I can't bear it - it will kill me!"<break time="100ms" />Every time he pushed the head of his prick at the entrance, I shrank from him.<break time="100ms" />He begged me. He prayed me just to let it in and he would be so very gentle.<break time="100ms" />He got it in a little way inside the entrance.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, push easily, or you'll kill me. Oh! Oh!"<break time="100ms" />"There, now - it is quite in. My precious, I shall not hurt you any more."<break time="100ms" />He moved his prick very slowly in and out, in and out. I began to heave and twist.
    </voice>
</speak>
