<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I then concluded the bargain for the purchase of Ibzaidu, and for the first three I had chosen.<break time="100ms" />After settling with Ali, I told him that he must let me have the use of a part of his house, including the harem, during my stay, so that I should be able to guard safely my slaves and to have for them proper attendance. Also, that he must instantly purchase for me six or eight mutes and eunuchs, which he immediately set about, whilst I returned to my house to get my money, jewels, etc., and also to bring away Caroline and her companion.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Dr. Tanner's Fast of Forty Days.<break time="100ms" />A correspondent in New York writes to the Editor of THE PEARL, to say that, for the last three weeks of the terrible experiment, the Doctor's penis, which in its normal condition would be eight and a half inches when in a state of erection, was shriveled up to less than an inch in length, and no handling or frigging could induce either stiffness or emission.<break time="100ms" />Julien's Concert.<break time="100ms" />Now music being the food of love I thought that I would go<break time="100ms" />To Julien's concert; for I heard the price was very low.<break time="100ms" />It being nearly eight o'clock, so in I toddled quick,<break time="100ms" />To hear the quadrille and see great Julien shake his pr-<break time="100ms" />The little staff about, and I've been told by jokers<break time="100ms" />That the ladies they do all agree that he's the prince of pokers.<break time="100ms" />The ladles they were highly dressed - naked, almost stark,<break time="100ms" />Their muslin being thin enough to see the watermark;<break time="100ms" />I gazed on one, a beauteous maid, her smile was bright and sunny,<break time="100ms" />She'd a nice small mouth and golden hair and a fine full open cunny.<break time="100ms" />Being so, I introduced myself to her so gentle,<break time="100ms" />She said, she'd come there for an hour with something instrumental.<break time="100ms" />I gently sat down by her side while glowing like a fire;<break time="100ms" />The smile she gave I must admit I really did admire.<break time="100ms" />Said she: "The band is going to play." Said I: "'Twill shake the walls."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, no," said she, "that's only when great Julien shakes his ball—<break time="100ms" />My bunch of rosy locks, his staff so well displayed is,<break time="100ms" />He knows full well a good long piece is sure to please the ladies."<break time="100ms" />The names of all the instruments she then enquired about<break time="100ms" />Especially of that long brass-thing that kept sliding in and out.<break time="100ms" />The fingering of the double-bass she thought was rather slack,<break time="100ms" />And wondered Julien should engage a man who'd got the clap-<break time="100ms" />Pers they were an awful bore, and still she would insist on<break time="100ms" />Me telling her who'd get the horn, and who the cornet a piston.<break time="100ms" />She said she liked the clarinet, likewise the German flute-<break time="100ms" />You know all well such instruments the ladies always suit;<break time="100ms" />The forty parts they were so off they almost made us start,<break time="100ms" />And the ophicleide would come in just like a thundering fart<break time="100ms" />Or peal of thunder, but not so far as India;<break time="100ms" />And the French horn would pop in, to join those things so windy<break time="100ms" />The place got overpowering; our ears were tired of drumming;<break time="100ms" />Said she: "I feel I'm going, you'd better be a-coming."<break time="100ms" />She took my arm, we left the place, I acted as conductor;<break time="100ms" />I called a cab, and on the road I freely furnished her with my ideas of Julien's improvements,<break time="100ms" />And so wound up with a grand duet with many pleasing movements.<break time="100ms" />My Grandmother's Tale or May's Account of Her Introduction to the Art of Love.<break time="100ms" />From an unsophisticated Manuscript found amongst the old lady's papers, after her death, supposed to have been written about A.D. 1797.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER II.<break time="100ms" />KATE'S NARRATIVE.<break time="100ms" />You know I am a native of the West Indies. I was born in Santa Cruz, where my father had a plantation, and lots of slaves.<break time="100ms" />The little boys and girls were naked until they were eight or nine years old: I remember being greatly struck with the fine little cocks of the boys, and wondered why they differed so from girls.<break time="100ms" />The son of our overseer was just my age, about ten. He was a smart intelligent boy, and we used to play together. His name was Joe.<break time="100ms" />One day I caught him piddling and looking at his cock. I laughed and told him he ought to cut it off, it was so ugly.<break time="100ms" />He said he would be sorry for he would much rather be a man than a woman, "and when I grow to be a man," he said, "this will grow big."<break time="100ms" />"How do you know?" I said, putting my hand on it.<break time="100ms" />"Because I have often seen men naked. Do you know what a man calls it?"<break time="100ms" />"No. What?"<break time="100ms" />"He calls it a prick."<break time="100ms" />"Oh?"<break time="100ms" />"And do you know what he does with it?"<break time="100ms" />"He piddles with it, I suppose, like yourself."<break time="100ms" />"Ah!" he said, looking very sly, "he does more than that."<break time="100ms" />"What?"<break time="100ms" />"He can put it into a woman between her legs, in that queer little slit you girls have."<break time="100ms" />"There's no room for it there," I said.<break time="100ms" />"Yes there is; I'll show you if you'll let me, may I?" he said, lifting my frock.<break time="100ms" />"You may, just for a minute."<break time="100ms" />He put his fingers into my cunt and felt about for the opening. At last he found it, and, to my surprise, pushed his forefinger up.<break time="100ms" />"Stop," I cried, "that hurts."<break time="100ms" />"I won't hurt you bye-and-bye," he said, with his sly look.<break time="100ms" />"How, what do you mean?"<break time="100ms" />"I'll tell you, but mind, it's a great secret. You know Jim who has the cat and flogs the slaves when they misbehave. Well, when the women are sent, he flogs their backs; but when girls are sent he flogs their bottoms. I was near the place when a fine plump girl came from your papa with a note, which I saw afterwards. It had only these words: 'Give this girl twelve lashes. -E. L.'<break time="100ms" />"Jim brought her in and shut the door but I stole round to a window on the other side and peeped in. He had her kneel on a bench and tied her hands to the block. Then he threw up her petticoat, uncovering her shining black bum, and took out his cat.<break time="100ms" />"He said: 'Be quiet, Norry. If you let me have my will of you I won't hurt you, but if you won't I'll give it you.'<break time="100ms" />"He opened his pantaloons and out started, oh! such a big one, it would have frightened you as he pushed it against her bottom. She cried more than ever.<break time="100ms" />"He brought down the cat with a smart stinging blow on her bottom.<break time="100ms" />"She jumped and yelled.<break time="100ms" />'"Be quiet now or you'll get more.'
    </voice>
</speak>
