<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"She stopped, while he separated her legs as widely as he could. Then stooping, he looked up into her slit, which he kept open with his fingers. I could see that it was very red inside, had plenty of black woolly hair on it.<break time="100ms" />"Then he put in the head of his prick, and giving a great push, it went in every bit of it. Then he withdrew it out all wet and red looking, and putting his arms round her hips he went on pushing in and out with all his might.<break time="100ms" />"She did not mind but only poked out her bottom as if to get more of it.<break time="100ms" />"Then he stopped suddenly, and pressed in hard against her.<break time="100ms" />"After which he untied her, and giving her a kiss, sent her away."<break time="100ms" />"That's very odd Joe. It must have hurt her very much."<break time="100ms" />"Indeed it didn't. She liked it beyond anything. I know it by the way she stuck out her bottom. Will you just try and you'll feel how pleasant it is."<break time="100ms" />My amorous feelings were aroused, so I did not object to his having a trial. I kneeled on the seat, as he told me, and jutted out my bottom.<break time="100ms" />He tried to get his cock into my slit, but failed. I put down my hand and kept the lips open, but whether from my immaturity or his inexperience, he could not succeed.<break time="100ms" />A few days afterwards he came running up to me in great glee, crying out: "I can do it now, Katie, I can do it now!"<break time="100ms" />"Stop your noise. What do you mean?"<break time="100ms" />"Stay, Katie, and I will tell you. You know father and I live in the cottage. He has, however, generally one or two of the slave girls with him in the evening. They like to come to him for they get plenty of rum, and are sure of a half holiday next day.<break time="100ms" />"He sends me to bed and then produces the rum, sugar and water. Last night he had three with him. He sent me off to bed as usual, but I hid behind the door.<break time="100ms" />"They soon became very merry over the drink and capered about in style. He threw up their petticoats, slapping their bottoms and tickled their cunts, while they pulled out his prick and handled his balls. Then he made them undress and chased them naked around the room. Whenever he caught one, he felt her cunt, and making her kneel would stick his prick into it from behind while the others tickled his balls and bottom. In the midst of the fun, one of them suddenly opened the door, and spying on me, seized me, and dragging me into the room, cried out: 'Oh, here's massa Joe playing bo-peep. What shall we do with him?'<break time="100ms" />"'Let's strip him,' cried another, 'and we will make him fuck Fanny. She is the youngest and her cunt will fit his little prick best.'<break time="100ms" />"My father only laughed and said: 'All right, he'll be man enough for any of you some of these days.'<break time="100ms" />"So I was stripped, nothing loath, and placed over Fanny, who was lying on the floor. She had her legs wide apart and with her fingers kept the lips of her cunt open while one of the others, after kissing and sucking my little cock, pushed it in. Then they clapped my bottom, and sat around to watch the performance.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Katie, you can't think how easy my prick slipped into her cunt. And I felt it growing bigger when it got in; she was so hot inside. She then hugged me in her arms and jerked up her bottom, while I worked and pushed as I had seen father do until the nice warm feeling came and I nearly fainted with pleasure.<break time="100ms" />"I was then glad to get away and creep off to bed, for I was tired and sleepy.<break time="100ms" />"Look at it, Katie, isn't it larger and stronger than before?"<break time="100ms" />He held it in his hand and drew back the skin until its head stood up round and red as a cherry.<break time="100ms" />"Put your hand oh it, Katie. Feel how firm it is!"<break time="100ms" />I took it in my hand and rubbed it up and down.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, Joe, it is larger and stronger. You may put it in if you like."<break time="100ms" />He laid me back, lifted my dress and looked at and felt my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Yours is much prettier and nicer than Fanny's, Katie. These soft round white lips are beautiful. Hold them open like a dear girl while I push it in."<break time="100ms" />I put my hands down and opening the lips with one while with the other I directed the head of his prick to the right spot and told him to push. He did so. It entered. He pushed harder. It got in more and more until it was all enclosed and I felt its head far back.<break time="100ms" />Oh, sweet sensation! Nothing can exceed the pleasure of feeling one's cunt for the first time filled up with a throbbing heaving prick!<break time="100ms" />His eyes sparkled and his breath came hard and fast as I hugged him in my arms, and told him to push in his prick and fuck me very well.<break time="100ms" />Having now ascertained for ourselves the wondrous power we each possessed of conferring pleasure on the other, our play always turned on the practice and enjoyment of love.<break time="100ms" />We were never tired of examining and petting each other's privates.<break time="100ms" />And our senses being now fully aroused, we were always the watch to enlarge our experience of the ways and means enjoyment.<break time="100ms" />My father had several slaves almost white, and most of them good-looking. These were all retained in the house and never sent into the fields.<break time="100ms" />One pretty little girl named Nina was assigned to me as my waiting-maid. She always attended me in my bath, and used to dry me when I came out. She was particularly attentive to my little slit, on which the hair was just beginning to grow. She used to perfume it, and comb it, and kiss it.<break time="100ms" />"You have a beautiful cunt, Missy, the sight of it would set any young fellow wild!"<break time="100ms" />"I suppose it is much the same as other girls', your own for instance. Show it to me, Nina."<break time="100ms" />She lifted her dress, and opening her thighs, gave me a full view of her cunt. It was a pretty little mouth, with a full rosebud clitoris, and the lips covered with brown silky hair. I put my hand on it, and pushing up my finger, said: "Did this ever set any young fellow wild?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Missy, you must not ask me such questions, or I will have to tell you lies."<break time="100ms" />"Nina, if you want me to be your friend you will tell everything. But this will do for the present."<break time="100ms" />My father was in the habit of walking in the garden after sunset when it was nearly dark, to smoke his cigar, and I found out that he always had with him one or the other of the white slaves.<break time="100ms" />One night I missed Nina, and guessing where she was, I threw on my shawl and went out softly into the garden. I heard voices in a sheltered walk, and as it was almost dark, I was able to get within range of hearing without being seen.
    </voice>
</speak>
