<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />They raised her up whilst cleaning her of the blood that dyed her thighs and buttocks, I took up the consecrated cushion and its bloody covering and directed one of them prepare the bed for us. I - but no. I determined to give her a little rest, and ordering the girls to prepare a cold supper, told them to awake me in two hours, and we fell asleep in each other's arms.<break time="100ms" />After sleeping for some time, Laura awoke much refreshed, but still feeling sore from the severe battering she had received.<break time="100ms" />The table being laid alongside the bed, we reclined on it, the others sitting around the table on cushions.<break time="100ms" />Not feeling much inclined to eat, I commenced dallying with my bedfellow, railing her on the feelings she experienced while I was taking her maidenhead, till the spirit began to wax powerful within me, whereupon I laid her down flat on her back and fell with my face downward upon her, and thence followed what the spirit moveth. Yes, verily, we did mighty deeds of fucking that night, and it was not until after the sixth operation, or moving of the spirit, that we lay exhausted in each other's arms and fell asleep.<break time="100ms" />In a few days after there arrived at the mouth of the creek a fine large steam-brig, which dropped anchor and sent a boat ashore with the captain, who delivered me a letter from my banker, stating who and what the officers and crew were and upon what terms they had been engaged.<break time="100ms" />I immediately walked down to the creek and going into the boat with the captain, we pulled on board. I examined her decks, masts, etc., and then descended to the cabin, which extended my most sanguine expectations, so magnificently was it fitted up. The cabin contained six staterooms, very large and splendidly fitted up, equalling in style and ornament the most elegant boudoir I had ever seen in Paris.<break time="100ms" />I questioned the captain, who was English, as well as the whole crew, in regard to the men on board.<break time="100ms" />He said that he and his men had been employed to serve me in any way I might think proper, so long as I did not command him to commit piracy. That he and the crew were paid enormous wages, and that they were bound and felt ready and willing to follow me to "heaven or hell," if I but showed them the way.<break time="100ms" />On questioning the stewards, I found the brig to be well stored with all the luxuries that could be procured.<break time="100ms" />I ascended to the deck with the captain, and passing the word forward for all hands to come aft, I had a crew of most hardy and devil-may-care looking fellows around me in a trice, standing respectfully hats in hand.<break time="100ms" />I made them a short address, laying open to them my intentions, and stating the service I required of them.<break time="100ms" />I gave the captain his orders to be in readiness to sail in two days and I returned to the chateau.<break time="100ms" />Summoning the steward I directed him to prepare everything for our voyage, as I determined to start in two days for Constantinople.<break time="100ms" />I then directed a page to send the women to me. On their entering, I made them all strip to the skin and examined the cunts and several charms of each of them with a critical eye, endeavouring when all were most lusciously beautiful to select one as my compagnon de voyage; but not being able to choose among so many loves I left it to chance.<break time="100ms" />Taking up a dice-box, I made each throw in her turn. La Rose D' Amour and my fair Russian, Caroline, made the highest throws and I determined to take both.<break time="100ms" />After they had cast their dies, I informed them what my object was. Whereupon, Laura, my last love, who bye-the-bye, was a great libertine, fell on her knees before me weeping, and begged me to take her with me.<break time="100ms" />It was impossible for me to take more than two, I told her; it was no use to grieve about the matter as she could not go, but that I would pass all my remaining time with her.<break time="100ms" />Leaving the chateau in the care of my trusty stewards and followers, I embarked, taking with me over one million in francs in gold, for the purpose of purchasing slaves in Constantinople.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER V.<break time="100ms" />After a pleasant voyage of about two weeks, I arrived at the capital of the Turkish Empire.<break time="100ms" />At the earliest opportunity I presented my letters to some of the most wealthy and influential foreigners under a fictitious name.<break time="100ms" />I soon became acquainted with many wealthy Turks and among them three or four slave-merchants.<break time="100ms" />I then hired an interpreter, and paying a visit to one of the merchants, engaged him as an agent to find out and procure me a lot of the handsomest females to be found in the market. And knowing that the poor class of the inhabitants were in the daily habit of selling their daughters, such as were handsome enough to grace the harems of the rich and lustful Turks, I directed him to send out some of his emissaries to search out all the families among the poor quarters who had beautiful girls and who would be apt to exchange them for gold.<break time="100ms" />In the course of a few days my agent called on me, stating that he was about to go on a three days' trip from the city to the house of an old broker-merchant of his who was continually in receipt of girls from the interior of the kingdom, and occasionally of a few from Circassia. That for certain reasons he never came to the city, but on receipt of any new beauties he always wrote, and he, my agent, went to his place of residence and either bargained for or took the females to Constantinople and sold them on commission.<break time="100ms" />He said that when I first called on him he wrote to his correspondent in the country, who replied that he had several very fine girls, one in particular whom he named Ibzaidu, who, he said, was fit to adorn the harem of the Grand Sultan.<break time="100ms" />I told my agent, Ali Hassan, to start immediately and to bring the lot, if they were beautiful, to the city.<break time="100ms" />In the interim of his absence, attended by my interpreter, I sauntered day and night through the streets and bazaazs, endeavouring to spy out some of the beauties of the place; but all in vain. I could not catch even a glimpse of a female face.<break time="100ms" />On the evening of the ninth day from his leaving me, Ali called on me, saying that he had brought with him seven slaves, who were safe in his harem, and invited me to call at his house in the morning and examine them.<break time="100ms" />He ran perfectly wild in his praises of Ibzaidu, whom he pronounced to be more beautiful than a houri, the nee plus ultra of Circassian beauty. About eleven o'clock the following day, I went to Ali's house, and immediately entered on business.<break time="100ms" />He retired for a few minutes to give orders for the slaves to prepare for my visit.<break time="100ms" />In the course of half-an-hour a eunuch entered, made a salaam to his master, and retired.<break time="100ms" />Ali arose, and inviting me to follow, led the way into a large and elegantly furnished apartment in his harem.
    </voice>
</speak>
