<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Darling, this is exquisite! Your cunt is delightfully tight, and its soft pressure most delicious. Put your arms round me, my love! I only once before had such a fuck as this."<break time="100ms" />I pressed him in my arms, thrust up my bottom to meet every thrust of his prick. I raised my thighs and crossed my legs on his back.<break time="100ms" />He ran his prick with delightful friction in and out of my throbbing, heaving, panting cunt. I felt a soft hand on my bottom and soft fingers playing about my cunt. I knew they were Nina's, I did not mind. I was intoxicated with pleasure. I squeezed in my bottom to nip his prick.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! That's grand, who taught you that sweet trick - do it again. Oh! That's splendid!"<break time="100ms" />Nina got into the bed and pressed against his bottom.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Nina you are just in time. Let me get on you that I may spend in your cunt."<break time="100ms" />He drew out his prick, saying to me: "You know I promised not to harm you; but Nina does not mind the risk for she knows she will be well taken care of. Let us get outside the clothes and take off everything, the night is so warm."<break time="100ms" />He then got between her uplifted thighs, and resting on her breast, told me to put it in.<break time="100ms" />I felt her cunt, it was very hot and flowing. I took his prick and rubbed its throbbing head between the soft lips, placed it at the entrance. He pushed, it passed in. I went behind him and holding him around the hips rubbed my cunt against his bottom while he fucked.<break time="100ms" />He discharged immediately and soon afterwards he bid us good-night and went away.<break time="100ms" />Nina begged me to excuse her. She said she heard all that passed and got so excited that she could not help coming in to us.<break time="100ms" />I asked: "Did papa know who your friend was?"<break time="100ms" />She said she was not certain but thought he did.<break time="100ms" />There was something peculiar about papa's manner the next morning. He put his arms around me several times, called me his sweet girl, his darling pet. He told me he was making arrangements to send me to England, to have my education completed there. He told me that he had taken my passage in a sugar-brig which was to start in a few days, and which was commanded by a friend of his, a Captain Lemberg, who would take good care of me.<break time="100ms" />I said I would like it very much but would be sorry to leave him and put my arms round his neck kissing him.<break time="100ms" />He enfolded me in his; he lifted me off the ground, carrying me to a sofa and laid me down. He sat by me and slipping his hand under my dress put it on my naked bottom.<break time="100ms" />"My darling," he said, "let me pet you, I feel so fond of you and I won't have you long."<break time="100ms" />"Dearest papa, you may do anything you please with me, I love to give you pleasure."<break time="100ms" />He kissed me warmly, turned me on my back, lifted my dress, opened my thighs, and looked at my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"You are beautifully made here. Tell me, my darling, was it you in Nina's bed last night?"<break time="100ms" />"It was I, dearest papa; was I very wicked?"<break time="100ms" />"No, my darling, you gave me the sweetest pleasure I ever had in my life. Did you enjoy what I did to you then?"<break time="100ms" />"I did indeed, it was most delightful."<break time="100ms" />"Might I do it to you again?"<break time="100ms" />"You may, dear papa, if you like."<break time="100ms" />He drew me to the end of the sofa, made me raise my legs and open them as widely as possible. Then kneeling on the floor, he kissed my cunt. He praised its shape and colour. He opened the lips, put in his tongue and licked the inside round and round. He introduced his prick, pushing it slowly up, and fucked me most delightfully.<break time="100ms" />I tried all I could to increase and intensify his pleasure. I asked if he was enjoying it much.<break time="100ms" />"Do you like it, papa?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, my sweet pet, your cunt is perfection itself. I envy the man who gets you for a wife."<break time="100ms" />I now ventured on a request I had long in mind.<break time="100ms" />"Dear papa, I have one thing to ask you for."<break time="100ms" />"What is it my pet? I would do anything in the world to gratify you."<break time="100ms" />"Will you give Nina her freedom and send her to England with me?"<break time="100ms" />"Surely, my pet, I will do more; if she marries with your consent and approbation I will allow you to present her with a £50 dowry, and besides, you may order whatever dress she may require for the voyage."<break time="100ms" />Need I describe the response I made to these kind words, how I clung to him, how I tightened the pleasure girths within, what a glowing reception I gave to his prick as it darted into my quivering cunt, or how he grunted his satisfaction: "Oh, Katie! Oh! Katie, my pet!"<break time="100ms" />Nina was overjoyed when she heard that she was to have her freedom. She thanked me on her knees and promised to be the most faithful of servants.<break time="100ms" />Now, dearest May, I have told you more than ever I told anyone else, because I find in you a kindred soul and I want someone to sympathize with me. Don't judge me too harshly; I was little more than a child and alone, my father has been a widower ever since I could remember. Do you love me less?<break time="100ms" />"No, dearest Kate, I love you a hundred times more for your confidence and affection; but go on and tell me about the voyage and how you first met papa."<break time="100ms" />"I will dearest; but not to-night. I am tired and sleepy. Kiss me, my love, good night."<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />That interesting old roadside public-house, "The Cock," at Kennington, has lately been redecorated. The sign-post was surmounted by an effigy of Chanticleer, who shone resplendent in new gold-leaf. Enters Mr. Robinson, a neighbouring pawn-broker, who thus addresses the bar-maid: "Your house now looks charming, my dear! Will you tell the painter who gilt your gov'nor's cock to come and gild my balls?" The bar-maid broke a wine-glass in her blushing confusion.<break time="100ms" />Flunkeyania; or Belgravian Morals.<break time="100ms" />BY CHARLES.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER I.<break time="100ms" />It is understood a useful, and it certainly is a commendable, practice, that in bringing a book before the public, the author should say a few words by way of introduction, and of excuse, I presume, for his writing the book at all. But as I have very little to say about my antecedents and even that not of a very exalted or interesting character, I shall plunge at once in medium res, and beg the reader to follow me into the study of the Earl of Pomeroy, who was in the act of investigating my character previously to engaging me in the somewhat anomalous, not to say duplicate, role as his own confidential secretary-valet and body-footman to the Countess.<break time="100ms" />This, I am aware, is unusual in high families, but it is not without its special utility as I very soon had occasion to find out.
    </voice>
</speak>
