<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"What a treat it would be to see you both lose your maidenheads at once," I exclaimed.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! couldn't the pages do it for us, dear lady? I do love that Charlie so!" appealed Patty without consideration in her excitement.<break time="100ms" />"I'll try and manage it; but we must be careful not to let them into our secrets before I can find out how they are disposed," I replied.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, I know Charlie is a rude, bold little fellow, wicked enough for anything if he had the chance. What do you think, I once actually caught him handling his affair in the pantry when he thought no one was looking and when I happened to enter suddenly; it was sticking out straight and red-looking at the top. His face was quite red and he seemed rather short of breath; but the impudent fellow, like the dare-devil he is, shook it fairly in my face as he asked me to give him a kiss, saying: 'What do you think of this, Patty? That's how it gets, when' - oh, mistress I can't tell you all he said."<break time="100ms" />But I pressed her and at last she told me: "It was when we had been waiting on his mistress. 'Oh, Patty,' he said, isn't she lovely, such mouth and teeth and loving eyes, I feel as if I could jump at her, I do!'"<break time="100ms" />"Very well, Master Charlie," I laughed, "perhaps I shouldn't so much mind if you did, when we are alone someday I will give him the chance and let you two dears know all about it. But I will first read you another song from 'The Haunted House' and to-morrow I will give you a copy, and I expect both to be able to sing it soon."<break time="100ms" />"LIVE AND LEARN." Tune:- Drops of Brandy<break time="100ms" />When I was little and good,<break time="100ms" />A long time ago 'm afraid, Miss;<break time="100ms" />A stiff prick was not understood,<break time="100ms" />I was a quiet little, shy little maid, Miss.<break time="100ms" />I knew but one use for my cunt,<break time="100ms" />I knew not what joy 'twould afford me.<break time="100ms" />The sight of a cock would affront,<break time="100ms" />And talk about fucking have bored me.<break time="100ms" />But now, oh, much wiser I've grown!<break time="100ms" />I'll stretch my legs open for any,<break time="100ms" />My modest shy feelings have flown.<break time="100ms" />And fucks, why, I can't get too many!<break time="100ms" />I like a stiff prick up my arse.<break time="100ms" />Though too much of that makes you bandy.<break time="100ms" />When I look at my quim in the glass,<break time="100ms" />It always pouts red and looks randy.<break time="100ms" />I like a fuck - morn, noon, and night,<break time="100ms" />On every weekday and Sunday:<break time="100ms" />If I'm fucked on the Sabbath, all right!<break time="100ms" />But I want to be buggered on Monday.<break time="100ms" />Oh! Let it be hot or be cold,<break time="100ms" />I'm always alive for a cock, Miss;<break time="100ms" />Men, fair, dark, young or old,<break time="100ms" />Here's a hole that'll take in their jock, Miss!<break time="100ms" />I can spend for an hour at a time.<break time="100ms" />My cunt is as hot as fire, Sir;<break time="100ms" />The man that says: "Fucking is crime,"<break time="100ms" />I say to his face, he's a liar, Sir.<break time="100ms" />Then give me a prick in each hand,<break time="100ms" />Turn my arse north, my cunt to the south;<break time="100ms" />And get an your jocks well to stand,<break time="100ms" />One in each hole and one in my mouth;<break time="100ms" />I'll fuck and I'll suck and I'll frig,<break time="100ms" />Until you're all quite bloody well spent, Sir!<break time="100ms" />Then I'll take in the lodgers again,<break time="100ms" />And never once ask them for rent, Sir!<break time="100ms" />Hurrah! for my cunt, my best friend.<break time="100ms" />Hurrah! for a cock to kiss, Sir;<break time="100ms" />I'll fuck till this life comes to end,<break time="100ms" />I hope too, there's fucking in bliss, Sir!"<break time="100ms" />When we awoke in the morning it was too late for a repetition of our tribadism, so I made them get up quickly and bring in breakfast, promising to look after Master Charlie during the day.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Overheard at the Aquarium.<break time="100ms" />Swell.- "Damn it! all the same flaghopping faces, not a fresh bit of cunt here, I'd give anything if I could fuck the Princess Amuzulu, and bugger the "Old Man of the Woods!"<break time="100ms" />Just as we were going to press an anonymous correspondent in board Admiral Seymour's ship at Ragusa has favoured the editor with the following:<break time="100ms" />A Propos of the Naval Demonstration.<break time="100ms" />Who'll bugger the Turk?<break time="100ms" />"I," said Gladstone, "as Chief of the Nation,<break time="100ms" />And Premier of England, to gain reputation.<break time="100ms" />I'll bugger the Turk,<break time="100ms" />And ne'er let him shirk<break time="100ms" />My prick's Grand Demonstration!"<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
