<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Come, none of that, sir!" I reply. "I meant as to legs; simply as to legs."<break time="100ms" />And to return to my subject. The decidedly manly look of the young lady's legs, taken in conjunction with her dress, her style altogether and the peculiar nature of the caresses exchanged between her and the Countess, all these little incidents put together, I repeat, produced strong suspicions in my mind as to the sex of our young passenger.<break time="100ms" />But I need not have troubled myself to have entertained any suspicions at all. At any rate, they soon became certainties. For presently, I took upon myself to ask Robert the coachman where he was driving? And why was he driving so horribly slow?<break time="100ms" />To my first enquiry he replied that he was going to drive along St. John's Wood-Road, and in the second place affirmed that he was too compassionate a disposition to two handsome creatures that had never done him harm.<break time="100ms" />I stared at him, for I presumed he referred to the handsome pair of chestnut horses. But when he followed up his remark by gravely saying that it did not matter at what pace he drove for there was "nobody in the carriage," I thought at first he must be mad or drunk, but on turning my head round, the whole truth flashed upon me at once!<break time="100ms" />Sure enough, the carriage was supposed to be empty, for all the blinds were closed!<break time="100ms" />"Don't you know the peephole," said my friend John. "Our coachbuilder made it on purpose to please me, or I ought to say, Lord Pomeroy. He put me up to it and sometimes rides on the box with me and says it's far more pleasure to see his wife fucked by a fine young fellow than to have the trouble to do it himself."<break time="100ms" />"You don't mean that," I replied.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, no humbug between ourselves! Old Pom only cares for page-boys, lady's-maids, or some other man's wife or daughters. 'Nothing like breaking the Ten Commandments' is his favourite saying. You'll find that hole in the roof. A little bit slides back just behind you."<break time="100ms" />Eager to see something of real life, the slide was noiselessly pushed back, till I could see every part of the interior of the brougham. There sat my lady billing and cooing with Miss Courtney. How flushed they looked as their impassioned kisses too plainly told the depth of their feelings.<break time="100ms" />They were sitting side by side, and the first act of their little love-drama was evidently just over, but the curtain had not yet fallen for the Countess's dress was raised to her navel and I could see the jewelled hand of Miss Courtney groping between her lovely thighs. But that was nothing to the sight of the manly root with which that young lady was furnished at the bottom of her belly, which although rather drooping, was still glistening with the cream of love, as the Countess continued to caress it in her milk-white hand, gently uncovering the fiery-looking red head of her delight, as the motion of her fingers seemed to make a mute appeal to its further gallantry. My curiosity was quite satisfied and we let them enjoy themselves in peace for the rest of the drive.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Lady Pokingham, or They All Do It.<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />PART V.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)<break time="100ms" />My peephole afforded me the sight of many more luscious scenes between Lady Cecilia and her husband before I left town to take up my residence at Hastings for the benefit of my health.<break time="100ms" />My agent had secured and furnished for me a pretty little detached residence of thirteen or fourteen rooms, surrounded by gardens and orchards, so as to be delightfully free from the prying curiosity of my neighbours.<break time="100ms" />The household consisted of a cook and housekeeper, both young persons, not exceeding twenty-four or -five years of age, the latter being the daughter of a decayed merchant, a most pleasant and intelligent companion, but up to the time I engaged her, strictly prudish, virtuous.<break time="100ms" />Being naturally fond of young boys and girls, we had also two very pretty page- boys of about the age of fifteen or sixteen and two beautiful young girls about the same age, instead of housemaid and lady's-maid.<break time="100ms" />At first I felt considerably enervated by the little excesses I had been a party to, or witnessed, whilst staying with the new Earl, but the soft bracing air of the southern coast soon made me feel more like myself again, and long to indulge in the delicious dalliances of love, to which my warm temperament made me always so inclined.<break time="100ms" />The result was that I determined to seduce every member of my virgin household, each one of whom I believed to be thoroughly virtuous up to their entering my service.<break time="100ms" />The two youngest girls, as my special attendants, slept in the next room to mine, and had a door of communication by which the two rooms entered into the other without the necessity of going into the corridor.<break time="100ms" />I had quite a passion come over me to gamahuche these two pretty young things, and make them thoroughly subservient to my purposes.<break time="100ms" />You may be sure I was not long in putting my plans in operation as soon as I had sketched them all out in my brain. That very same evening, after my two pretty demoiselles had put the finishing touches to my toilet and left me sitting in my chemise de nuit, in front of a cosy fire with my feet resting on the fender, as I pretended to be reading a thrilling romance.<break time="100ms" />"Leave that door open, my dears," I said, as they respectfully bid me good night. "I feel so dull perhaps I shall call for you to keep me company, if I feel that I cannot go to sleep."<break time="100ms" />In a few minutes I heard them tittering and laughing.<break time="100ms" />"Now, girls," I cried, "come here this moment. I want to know what you are having such fun about. Come just as you are, no putting anything more on or waiting to hide your blushes. Annie! Patty! Do you hear?"<break time="100ms" />Afraid of making me angry, the two girls came blushing into my room just as they were, in their nightgowns.<break time="100ms" />"Well now, what is it that is amusing you so?"<break time="100ms" />"Please, my Lady, it was Patty," said Annie with a wicked look at her companion.<break time="100ms" />"Ah, no, you fibber! My Lady, it was Annie began it," retorted the other, looking quite abashed.<break time="100ms" />Nothing could be got out of them, each saying it was the other.<break time="100ms" />At last I said: "I can guess pretty well what you two girls were amusing yourselves about; now tell me truly, were you looking at each other's privates in the glass?"
    </voice>
</speak>
