<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Well, dear, it is hard to give an opinion. Most women like to have a man all to themselves and as a rule they are satisfied with one; but in cases where either party has led a free life before marriage, I can quite understand that such an arrangement would be expedient and wise. But you may have an opportunity of judging for yourself as your papa intends inviting them here as soon as Carle returns from his present voyage."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, that will be delightful. I am longing to see Hilda and we may have Mr. T- also, for he says he can't wait any longer for me and he has written to papa. But go on, dear Kate, and tell me what happened next.")<break time="100ms" />Just this: The following day Carle told the Captain of his engagement with his niece and that he had promised to marry her as soon as they arrived in port.<break time="100ms" />The Captain replied: "All right, old fellow, I congratulate you. She is a thorough good girl and will make a jolly wife. But you may have her at once so far as I am concerned, if you sign the marriage contract in my presence, which you know has legal force in Danish law."<break time="100ms" />Carle jumped at the idea. So the contract was drawn up and signed by Hilda and himself, the Captain and I adding our names as witnesses.<break time="100ms" />"Now," said the Captain, "I pronounce you man and wife together, etc. Have at her as soon as you like, my boy! And as we have witnessed the wedding it would be only fair that we should witness the bedding too."<break time="100ms" />Carle found her in his arms and placed her on his knee. The Captain caught hold of me and moving his leg under me, said: "Kate, you will have to be my niece now." And in spite of my struggles he forced his hand up between my legs.<break time="100ms" />Carle was not slow in following his example, and soon amidst many "Ah, Carle," "Stop Charlie" our cunts were taken in full possession of by exploring hands while two standing pricks boldly upreared their rosy tips.<break time="100ms" />Finding that they were bent on enjoying us openly, we saw no use in further resistance and so let them have their way.<break time="100ms" />The Captain smiled when he saw how skillfully and lovingly Hilda caressed Carle's noble tool, and under cover of a kiss placed my fingers on his own. "Now, Carle, lay her on the locker and don't spare her maiden-trap. Kate will guide the bird into the nest and I will look on, and see fair play and no favour."<break time="100ms" />Carle laid her back and tenderly lifting her dress uncovered her belly and thighs. Then raising her legs, he spread her thighs widely apart and paused to admire her cunt, fringed with golden hair, and cosily placed himself between her luxuriant thighs. He then leaned over her so as to place his prick upon its opened lips.<break time="100ms" />"Kate, now pop it in and hold it firmly."<break time="100ms" />I stooped forward and taking hold of Carle's bounding tool pushed its head into her soft recess. In doing so my bare bottom became exposed to the Captain's view.<break time="100ms" />He caught me round the hips and cried: "Oh, lovely arse!" He kissed it and I felt his warm pliant tongue playing in and about my cunt and penetrating my bottom-hole itself. Then quickly rising up he thrust his rampant prick into my cunt and fucked away all the while leaning over my back, watching Carle and crying out at every thrust: "That's the way, fellow! Send it home - rattle your bullocks against her arse! - fuck - fuck - fuck - ah, oh!" And we all fell together, our cunts overflowing with the discharge from their excited pricks.<break time="100ms" />After lying over her for a few moments Carle began to heave his bottom again and gave her the benefit of a second fuck, without taking out his prick.<break time="100ms" />This pleased the Captain greatly. He stooped over his niece and kissing her asked how she liked being fucked.<break time="100ms" />She smiled, and stretching out her hand took hold of his prick, now soft and hanging down.<break time="100ms" />Carle laughed to see her frigging her uncle's prick and went on slowly driving his own in and out of her cunt.<break time="100ms" />The Captain's prick began to stand; he pushed it towards her face. She drew it to her lips and calling me, raised my clothes and placed Carle's hand on my cunt, then looking up she said: "Now we are quits."<break time="100ms" />He kissed her and said: "Darling Hilda, you are the best and sweetest of wives, you will never regret it."<break time="100ms" />Then bending down he asked me to lean back and open my thighs. He kissed my cunt and sucked the clitoris all the while with a slow and measured stroke, fucking Hilda's cunt.<break time="100ms" />"What are you doing to Kate, Carle?"<break time="100ms" />"I am sucking her sweet cunt while I am fucking yours. And what are you doing to the Captain?"<break time="100ms" />"I am sucking his prick and squeezing yours in my cunt."<break time="100ms" />The Captain now heaved his great heavy bum and worked his prick in and out of her mouth, just as Carle with increasing vigour drove his prick in and out of her cunt. She heaved up and down, and in the height of her excitement, grasped one of the cheeks of my bottom and at every thrust of Carle's prick gave me such a squeeze that I could hardly suppress a shout.<break time="100ms" />But I felt nearly as excited as herself, for the action of Carle's lips and tongue in my cunt was almost as exciting as that of his prick in hers, while the view of his fine bottom rising and falling between her wide-spread thighs, and the Captain's tool darting in and out of her mouth, caused me fully to share in the general form of excitement.<break time="100ms" />The Captain feeling the tide of pleasure rising to the flood, cried: "Fuck her, Carle - fuck her cunt."<break time="100ms" />Carle replied: "Suck him, Hilda - suck his prick."<break time="100ms" />Whilst I, I pressed my cunt against Carle's mouth and spent on his tongue, called out the names - prick - cunt - arse - frigging - sucking - fucking - oh!<break time="100ms" />Carle went on deck and the Captain soon after tumbled into his berth. Hilda and I retired to our cabins and were soon fast asleep.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />The Good Nobleman.<break time="100ms" />Air - "There was a Little Man."<break time="100ms" />Respected near and far,<break time="100ms" />There was a noble Mar-<break time="100ms" />quis, and Wallsend was the title that he bore, bore, bore,<break time="100ms" />Who left his brother-swells<break time="100ms" />To follow little girls,<break time="100ms" />And tell 'em not to do it any more, more, more.<break time="100ms" />Said he: "A man's affair<break time="100ms" />Isn't meant to go in there!"<break time="100ms" />And his Lordship put his finger on the spot, spot, spot;<break time="100ms" />But the wicked girls appalled<break time="100ms" />The nobleman, and called<break time="100ms" />On God to paralyse each limb they'd got, got, got.<break time="100ms" />"Your private parts, or cunny,<break time="100ms" />Should not be let for money,<break time="100ms" />They're only meant to pee with," did he preach, preach preach,<break time="100ms" />His ears he almost doubted,<break time="100ms" />When the little creatures shouted:<break time="100ms" />"God blind us into bloody corpses, each, each, each!"
    </voice>
</speak>
