<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"You always should endeavour<break time="100ms" />To stop a young man ever<break time="100ms" />On any grounds from creeping up behind, hind, hind."<break time="100ms" />And this noble thought he dreamed,<break time="100ms" />When the little creatures screamed:<break time="100ms" />"God strike us deaf, lame, dumb and blind, blind, blind!"<break time="100ms" />"You dissembling, bleeding, rotten,<break time="100ms" />Bloody, cankered, misbegotten<break time="100ms" />Lump of shit, rubbed over with a little spend, spend, spend!"<break time="100ms" />The little children cried,<break time="100ms" />For a cockstand they espied<break time="100ms" />Within the noble breeches of their friend, friend, friend.<break time="100ms" />They were tearing down his breeches,<break time="100ms" />And his bitter cries and screeches,<break time="100ms" />And his blushes would have melted hearts of snow, snow, snow.<break time="100ms" />And the little creatures found,<break time="100ms" />When they dragged him to the ground,<break time="100ms" />That, while lecturing, he'd shot his noble roe, roe, roe.<break time="100ms" />Flunkeyania, or Belgravian Morals.<break time="100ms" />BY CHARLES.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER II.<break time="100ms" />It was rather late in the afternoon when we arrived home, and I was in my apartment making some slight alteration in my attire before attending my lady at the dinner table, when enters Justine! Without tapping or giving any other intimation of her approach.<break time="100ms" />I remonstrated with her, with mock gravity on her great impudence, representing to her that under the present circumstances my attire was grossly disarranged and that there was a great possibility that she might have found me in a state totally unfit to be seen by any young woman whatever.<break time="100ms" />To which the saucy girl replied that she did not know what state that was, unless I was sewn up to the neck in a strong sack; and even then, she continued, she thought that loving woman with a sharp pair of scissors might overcome the difficulty and make me a presentable member of society - fit to be seen by herself anyway.<break time="100ms" />I think I was going to put this experiment to the practical test, and that without the adjuncts of the sack and the scissors, when Justine stopped me by saying that she had a very particular message for me from Her Ladyship.<break time="100ms" />This appeared to be that I was not to mention to anyone, least of all to the Earl, the circumstances of the Countess's having taken "Miss Courtney for a drive."<break time="100ms" />"For a ride" said I, correcting her with all possible gravity.<break time="100ms" />"Well, then, for a ride, if you like, you saucy boy," replied the sweet girl, giving me a slight box on the ear. "You know a great deal too much, sir; but you will promise not to tell Ernest, darling, won't you?"<break time="100ms" />Now, I was resolved to tease her a little. So I said that really I considered Miss Courtney a very fine girl. That she had given me a couple of sovereigns when she got out of the carriage. That she was just the sort of a girl that I was sure His Lordship would like: tall and long-legged, in fact exactly like a young fellow in girl's clothes. He's very fond of boys and would be delighted in finding Adam's needle instead of Eve's bit of old hat, when he put his hand up her clothes - and I was chafing away at a great rate when my pretty visitor stamped her foot with vexation, and then began to cry!<break time="100ms" />Of course upon this there was only one thing to do, and that was to comfort my young lady in every way that I could, and I succeeded so well that from sobbing, pouting, pushing me away and calling me a tantalizing, cross wretch, she began to return my kisses after the most approved fashion. Then she clasped me round the neck, sighing on my shoulder and murmuring incoherently all the loving epithets that suggested themselves on the spur of the moment, yielding herself as she did so to the loving clasp of my arms.<break time="100ms" />Almost undressed as I was, my natural feeling got the better of my discretion. It was too plain what the Countess's soubrette sighed for at the moment, and could any young fellow refuse such an appeal to his gallantry, especially that engine of love which knows no conscience was burning with impatience.<break time="100ms" />My hands raised her clothes as I threw her back on the edge of my bed and for a few minutes we revelled in the delights of love.<break time="100ms" />When we were getting more composed and able to converse like reasonable beings, I gave Justine willingly enough the promise her mistress had told her to get from me. While she informed me that the Earl was particular, almost to jealousy, of anyone using his beautiful chestnuts, unless they who used them belonged to the family.<break time="100ms" />I could not help wondering if he would be equally jealous of anyone "using" his beautiful chestnut-haired wife! And whether I was to be considered "one of the family"?<break time="100ms" />I could not help hinting something to this effect to Justine, in as discreet a way as the object admitted of. And to my surprise instead of being exposed to a lecture, for my brazen impudence, for daring to entertain such ideas, or a storm of jealous reproaches for my cruelty in so thinking of anybody but herself, after what had just passed between us - and that not for the first time - instead of this I received from the faithful femme de chambre no slight encouragement.<break time="100ms" />She told me that she was sure the Countess was very fond of me. That she had questioned her (Justine) about my private habits, how I looked when in dishabille.<break time="100ms" />"You see, Ernest," said the arch girl laughingly, "that she supposes that I know all about it."<break time="100ms" />Then she told me that the Earl, although not at all an unkind husband, was habitually neglectful, and that, as the girl very shrewdly remarked, ladies considered even worse. That they will bear with a great deal of flirting, infidelity, and other bad conduct on the part of their lovers or husbands, as long as they themselves are not neglected. But that the one offence not to be forgiven.<break time="100ms" />I do not mean to say that Justine expressed this sentiment precisely in these words, but this was the sense of what she said, and very good sense, too.<break time="100ms" />The upshot of her conversation was that I was to be ready and bold; but not too knowing or forward. To look my best, and to watch for a favourable opportunity which she felt sure my Lady would afford me when she could. Indeed, Justine went on to say that the present occasion would not be at all an unfavourable one, when I could take the opportunity of assuring my mistress of my inviolable secrecy as to the "Miss" Courtney transaction, and my eternal devotion to her service.<break time="100ms" />"But," said Justine, "I dare say my Lady may feel rather fatigued with the exercises she has taken today - and as for you, sir; it is, or ought to be entirely out of the question!"
    </voice>
</speak>
