<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I got up, opened the panel and peeped in. Her lamp was burning. I could see that he had drawn her to the edge of her berth, over which her naked bottom projected. Her legs were raised up and resting on his arms while his large prick was darting in and out of her open cunt. I could see that she was beginning to enjoy it for she wriggled her bum and threw her arms around his neck.<break time="100ms" />"Press it, dear Uncle! You make me like it in spite of myself."<break time="100ms" />At every thrust he banged against her rump, crying: "There, there, you have it all."<break time="100ms" />Before he left I heard him talking of me and telling her to show me some books and pictures.<break time="100ms" />The next day, coming suddenly out of my cabin I caught her sitting in Mr. Carle's lap. He had his arm round her and was kissing her. They started and blushed when they saw me and he got up and went on deck.<break time="100ms" />She then told me that they were engaged to be married at the end of the voyage. "And do you know, Kate, though I am fond of Carle I dread it."<break time="100ms" />"Why?", I asked.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, don't you know what a man does to a woman when they are in bed together?"<break time="100ms" />"No," I said, looking very innocent, "What?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, you must know that he has something that he puts into her stomach."<break time="100ms" />"What is it like, Hilda? Tell me about it."<break time="100ms" />"It's a thing called a prick, eight or nine inches long, with a purple head. It hangs between his legs and when it stiffens he can push it into our slits, which are called cunts, you know. Then after working it in and out, something comes out, and it makes the child."<break time="100ms" />"How queer! Did you ever see it, Hilda?"<break time="100ms" />"I have often seen pictures of it. Uncle has curious books with pictures, that tell all about it. Would you like to see it? I was looking over his books and I came upon a secret drawer which was open, and there I found them; come, I'll show them to you."<break time="100ms" />We went into his cabin and on opening the drawer saw a number of books full of coloured pictures of the most lascivious evolutions of love.<break time="100ms" />There were naked men and naked women with their cunts and pricks and bottoms displayed in every kind of attitude and position. They were frigging, sucking and fucking in all varied positions.<break time="100ms" />There were some large French prints also. One depicted a beautiful girl with her bare shoulders and legs, seated on the lap of her lover. Between her voluptuous thighs her cunt is seen delightfully gorged with his standing prick. Her arms are round his neck and her face is turned up, beaming with the satisfaction she experiences in her well-filled cunt.<break time="100ms" />Another showed a fat nun with her frock up and her breasts bare, stretched on a couch before a large mirror; she had been working a dildoe, that is, an artificial prick, into her voluptuous cunt. She has obtained an emission and is now lying back in delicious languor, while two randy monks, peeping round the; curtain, and beholding the luscious scene reflected in the glass, have pulled out their pricks and contend who shall be the first into her lustful orifice.<break time="100ms" />Then there was a scene in a cafe in Paris: a number of naked men and women dancing together. As they circle round, their pricks and cunts are presented in most exciting points of view; one is pressing the soft buttocks of his partner, while she holds with loving grasp his standing prick. Another squeezes the breasts of his beloved, while she supports his pendant balls. Another couple falls, but they so manage that he falls between her extended thighs and his eager prick soon finds lodgement in her expectant cunt. Some are lying their partners, nothing loath, upon the surrounding couches and relieving their excitement by plunging into their melting cunts. While others again regale their senses of taste and smell between the voluptuous thighs of their delighted fair ones.<break time="100ms" />These pictures excited me greatly. I had never seen anything like them before. "Oh, Hilda," I muttered as I pressed together my thighs, while she pointed out each lascivious detail.<break time="100ms" />"But we must not remain here," she said. "Let us take some of these books into your cabin and there we can observe them at our leisure."<break time="100ms" />So, taking three, we shut the drawer and made off.<break time="100ms" />When we had comfortably settled ourselves on a little sofa at the side of my cabin, we opened the first. It contained a thrilling description of a doctor's exploits with a buxom young widow. How he gained her confidence and then excited her amorous feelings, eyes on the ripe beauties of her voluptuous form. The next depicts her standing thus at his side with her splendid cunt protruding its full rounded lips from the midst of a thick covering of crisp curling hair, while the crimson line between gives promise of a warm reception to his prick.<break time="100ms" />He has put her hand on his standing prick, which she looks at with shy pleasure as she draws the skin down from its glowing red head.<break time="100ms" />In the next plate she is seen lying across his lap, her beautifully rounded bottom with its milk-white globes is turned up to meet his amorous gaze. He pats the cheeks and titillates the furrow between, while his prick is luxuriating in the soft folds of her melting cunt.<break time="100ms" />In another plate she is represented as astride of him, her bottom rubbing against his belly as he leans back. By the sweet suction of her mouth she has restored his prick to vigorous life, and, as it now stands up between her widely separated thighs, she presses it warmly against the lips of her longing cunt.<break time="100ms" />"How would you like to be in her place, Kate? And to feel a fine lusty prick pressing against your cunt and then pushing up into it filling you with rapture and delight?"<break time="100ms" />"I am sure it would be very pleasant if it were the prick of one I loved."<break time="100ms" />"No doubt that would vastly increase the pleasure; but don't you feel when your cunt gets excited that any prick, if it were in the right condition, would give you pleasure? How does your cunt feel now? Would you mind my putting my hand on it, Kate?"<break time="100ms" />"Not in the least, Hilda, if you want to."<break time="100ms" />"Lean back, dear, open your thighs. Might I see it?"<break time="100ms" />"I have no objection."<break time="100ms" />I now became aware that the sliding panel was slightly open and though I saw something like an eye peering through the slit, I pretended to take no notice. I replied: "You may, Hilda, provided you let me see yours afterwards."
    </voice>
</speak>
