<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I begged to assure Justine that she was never more mistaken in her life, for the taste of love she had just given me only whetted my appetite for a fuller feast, which was perfectly true; for what, with the girl's beauty before me, and the peep which I had had that afternoon into the closed carriage, the warm blood throbbed in my veins so that between reality and imagination I was in a highly efficient state; and all of this I might have given Mademoiselle Justine another and immediate proof of, had not the Countess's bell rung just at this juncture.<break time="100ms" />Our tete-a-tete was interrupted, Justine exclaiming: "Let me go directly, you dear, naughty fellow - don't you hear my Lady's bell? I promised her to be back in five minutes, and here I've been five and twenty! How you have tumbled my dress, to be sure! Do get along with you! But I must kiss the dear boy first, who has given me such a proof of his vigour!"<break time="100ms" />Her hand was under my shirt in a moment, and grasping the reanimated object of her desires, she stooped and took it in her mouth for a moment or two, tickling the ruby head with her lascivious tongue as her cherry lips pressed deliciously around it. But just as I felt the crisis coming on, she suddenly rose from her stooping position and, slapping my posteriors with no light hand, exclaimed with a laugh: "Ah, would you, sir? I know what you are going to do!" and bounced out of my room, saying as she closed the door, to be ready for Her Ladyship's commands in half-an-hour.<break time="100ms" />Reader, what could I do in the excited state in which she left me, but pass my hand two or three times up and down on my bursting affair, till the seed spurted over the floor satisfied my raging lust for that moment.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Lady Pokingham, or They All Do It.<break time="100ms" />Giving an Account of her Luxurious Adventures, both before and after her Marriage with Lord Crim-Con<break time="100ms" />PART VI.<break time="100ms" />After luncheon I ordered Charles to take several shawls and a floor-stool into the summer-house of the garden, as I wished to take a nap, and was sure the open air was more conducive to refreshing sleep than the close atmosphere of a room on a warm sunny day.<break time="100ms" />Annie and Patty exchanged significant glances as I gave the order, but my uplifted finger stopped any further manifestation of intelligence.<break time="100ms" />We had a fine large garden at the back of the house, in some parts beautifully shaded by umbrageous elms of a venerable age, especially on the banks of a small circular pond about twenty yards in diameter, where, facing the south, the summer- house stood under the trees by the side of the small lakelet.<break time="100ms" />I followed Charles as he carried out my orders, and arriving at our destination, ordered him to spread the shawls over a sofa which stood there, for fear the leather might be damp. Then he fetched a pillow, and placed the foot-stool at my feet.<break time="100ms" />I had nothing on but a loose morning-wrapper, with my chemise and drawers underneath.<break time="100ms" />"How very oppressive it is," I exclaimed, as I languidly sank back on the couch as soon as he had prepared it, allowing as I did so, a most negligent exposure of my neck and slight glimpse of the orbs of love beneath.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! Oh, oh! My goodness; the dreadful cramp!" I almost screamed, as bending down in great apparent pain, I pulled the robe to rub the calf of my right leg. "Ah, oh! what torture!"<break time="100ms" />Charles was on his knees at my feet in a moment.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, my Lady, is it so very bad? Let me bend up your toes!"<break time="100ms" />"No, no, not there, rub the calf, as hard as you can, Charles, there's a good boy!" I replied, my face wincing under the pain. "Higher, rub along my leg, the foot's no use!"<break time="100ms" />Somehow the toe of my bad foot touched his trousers just outside the most interesting part of his anatomy; the slipper had fallen off and I could feel his prick quickly harden and throb under my toes, whilst his face flushed all over, and I thought quite a perceptible tremor passed through his frame, as he went on rubbing my leg below the knee, and I need not say how my own lustful temperament was affected by the contact.<break time="100ms" />My robe had opened down the front so that he had a full view of legs, drawers and bosom, perhaps the wrinkle of love itself.<break time="100ms" />My blood was in a boil and I could no longer resist the impulse to enjoy such a beautiful Adonis.<break time="100ms" />"Get up, Charles, it's better now." I said in a low voice, "and pray don't tell what you've seen by accident. That cramp threw me into such an awful agony I did not know how I tossed about!"<break time="100ms" />"Dear Lady, your secrets are always safe with me." he replied, looking down bashfully as he rose to his feet. "I could kiss the ground under your feet to prove my devotion!"<break time="100ms" />"No, you are such a kind boy that just for this once, Charles, only this once, mind, I will give you a kiss myself instead. Come closer to me! What a fine boy you are. Now don't be bashful, really I mean to kiss you, if you promise never to tell."<break time="100ms" />"Ah, Madame, how kind of a great lady to a poor page-boy like me! I shall never forget such a favour and would die for you any time!" he said with bashful excitement.<break time="100ms" />"Come then," and I took his handsome face between my hands and kissed him repeatedly. "Why don't you kiss me, Charles?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, lady, and may I take that liberty?" he asked, his warm lips almost sucking the breath from me, so earnest his kissing.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, yes," I murmured, "you may kiss me now, dear boy! And would you be faithful, Charles, if I trusted my life, my honour to your keeping?"<break time="100ms" />"Those kisses have made me your slave forever, dear Lady. Nothing could ever wring a secret of yours from me."<break time="100ms" />"Then, Charles, I will tell you I'm in love with your figure! I know you must be a perfect Cupid, and should you like to strip quite naked, that I may enjoy the sight of a living statue? Will you do so, no one will ever know?" I asked.<break time="100ms" />His face was crimson and I could see that he actually trembled under my gaze. "Now Charles, make haste, and if you do that for me I'll give you a sovereign and a new suit of clothes."<break time="100ms" />Slipping off his jacket I began to unbutton his trousers. Turning them down, my eager hands wandered under his shirt, feeling the firmness of the ivory-like flesh of his deliciously rounded buttocks whilst my eyes did not fail to detect how his linen stood out in front and was saturated with spendings.<break time="100ms" />He seemed to understand me now and almost quicker than I can write it, he was naked as Adam in Paradise.<break time="100ms" />My roving hands took possession of his beautiful little prick, quite six inches long, and ornamented round the tight looking balls by just a shade of curly brown hair.<break time="100ms" />"What's this, Charles, are you often wet like this?" as I called his attention to the glistening sperm on my fingers. "What a big fellow this is, quite enough for a man. Did you ever make love with a girl?"
    </voice>
</speak>
