<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I raised her up and had her put into a warm bath and after drying her I again put her to bed. After giving her some wine and taking some myself, I found that again I was in trim for another bout.<break time="100ms" />With a spring I placed myself between her thighs. I entered her, not without a good deal of hard work.<break time="100ms" />God of voluptuous love, what a heat reigned through her body!<break time="100ms" />How lusciously did the sweet flesh clasp around my rod!<break time="100ms" />A few thrusts and a few moves in and out awaken her to a sense of pleasure.<break time="100ms" />She moves up to me, she catches the fever that runs through me. Quicker, quicker she heaves up to me to meet my fierce lunges as I drive my foaming steed through her gap into the rich pasturage. She clasps me in her arms, and throws her snowy thighs around my back, the bounces of her bottom fairly spring me off her. I feel she is coming. Ah, my god, she comes - she spends! The sperm comes from her in a shower. I, too - I again - I spend! It runs from me. Great God! It's too much! I die! Oh-h! And then I breathed my spirit away in a sigh soft and gentle as a zephyr.<break time="100ms" />My God, how voluptuous, how luscious was the beautiful Circassian! What warmth! With what fire, what energy did she meet all my efforts at procuring and dispensing pleasure! How lusciously did she squeeze me when in her! How plentifully did she let down the milk when the agony of pleasure seized her!<break time="100ms" />We swam in a perfect sea of voluptuousness totally indescribable. Man cannot imagine, pen cannot describe it, it was an intoxication of delight - pleasure wrought up to agony, bliss inexpressible, more exquisitely delicious than that enjoyed by the houris of Paradise when in the arms of true Mohammedans, or that enjoyed by the spirits of the Elysian fields.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />My Grandmother's Tale or May's Account of Her Introduction to the Art of Love.<break time="100ms" />From an unsophisticated Manuscript found amongst the old lady's papers, after her death, supposed to have been written about A.D. 1797.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER IV.<break time="100ms" />KATE'S NARRATIVE CONTINUED; THE VOYAGE; CAPTAIN LEMBERG AND HIS NIECE<break time="100ms" />HILDA.<break time="100ms" />On the next occasion that May and her friend Kate were snugly stretched in bed, their arms fondly circling one another and their hands tenderly plucking the hair of each other's cunt, they soon grew so excited that she, throwing off everything and May reversing her position, lay over her friend and gamahuched her most lovingly, Kate's tongue returning those fiery kisses of love with such interest that in a few minutes both were dissolved in a balmy emission.<break time="100ms" />As soon as they were recovered a little and more composed, May said softly: "Now, dear Katie, proceed with your most interesting and exciting narrative."<break time="100ms" />Well, when the time came, papa brought me word to board the brig, and after taking a most affectionate leave he left me in charge of Captain Lemberg and his niece, Hilda. I was delighted to have her as a companion for she was a merry, spritely girl, and had made the voyage before.<break time="100ms" />I had a little cabin adjoining hers and opening on the salon.<break time="100ms" />Nina was accommodated in the forepart of the ship and was with a soldier's wife, a Mrs. S and her sister Jenny. The vessel sailed early the next morning and soon began to pitch and roll. The motion made us all sick. Nina was not able to leave her berth and Hilda was nearly as bad. As for me I never felt so bad in my life.<break time="100ms" />About noon the Captain came into my cabin. I was lying down, only half dressed and so sick that I did not care what was done to me.<break time="100ms" />He said he was so sorry to find me so bad; but that if I would allow him to prescribe for me he knew what would be sure to give relief.<break time="100ms" />I said I would take anything he gave for I could not be worse than I was.<break time="100ms" />He went out and soon returned with a tumbler of hot brandy and water. When I tasted it I said: "I cannot take this, it is too strong."<break time="100ms" />"All the better, my dear, it will do you more good. Come, trust an old sailor."<break time="100ms" />He put his arm round me and supported me while I gulped it down. Then he laid me back. It relieved the sickness but threw me into a stupor.<break time="100ms" />Before he left he arranged my dress and was very particular in setting it over my breast. Seeing I did not move he passed his hand down over my stomach and pressed the mound at the bottom of my belly. Then he lightly kissed my forehead and went away.<break time="100ms" />After a short time he returned and finding me tossing about, but still in a state of stupor he softly rubbed my stomach over my chemise, bringing his hand lower and lower, until he reached my cunt. Finding I did not mind him, he passed his hands up under my chemise and boldly grasped my cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Captain," I muttered, but could say no more.<break time="100ms" />He pushed his hand between my thighs so as to feel the lips. He separated my thighs more and felt them round about. Indeed I don't know what he did, I was so stupefied, but I think he kissed it.<break time="100ms" />In the evening the sea calmed down and I felt much better.<break time="100ms" />He brought me a cup of coffee, which roused me up. He supported me with his arm while I was drinking and then stooped to kiss me. I could not refuse him my lips, he so kind.<break time="100ms" />In a few days I recovered from the effects of my sickness, and I began to feel at home in the vessel.<break time="100ms" />Hilda brought me about and showed me everything.<break time="100ms" />At the opposite side of the salon the Captain and the mate, Mr. Carle, occupied cabins corresponding to ours.<break time="100ms" />Mr. Carle was a young man, good-looking and very agreeable. He was most attentive to Hilda and did not mind me much. But the Captain was unremitting in his attentions to me. He got into the way of kissing me every night and used to squeeze my bottom when I passed near him.<break time="100ms" />With Hilda he was still more free, but then she was his niece.<break time="100ms" />In arranging my cabin I found there was a sliding panel between Hilda's cabin and mine which, when open, gave a full view either way.<break time="100ms" />The Captain generally kept the first night-watch and remained on deck until after twelve; then he would come down, take grog, and turn in.<break time="100ms" />One night I was awakened by talking in Hilda's cabin and I heard her say "Now behave yourself, I won't have you coming this way into my cabin at night. Ah, stop, I will call out, if you don't let me alone."<break time="100ms" />"Hildy, my pet, let me, just a moment."<break time="100ms" />"No, you mustn't put your hand there - you mustn't raise my shift - you mustn't open my thighs. Oh, Uncle, do - take it away. You are a terrible man, why don't you go and fuck Kate? What would Carle say if he knew you did this to me?
    </voice>
</speak>
