<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Volume 15
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />It has been suggested that this work be split into multiple pages.<break time="100ms" />If you'd like to help, please review the style guidelines and help pages.<break time="100ms" />La Rose D'Amour.<break time="100ms" />Or the Adventures of a Gentleman in search of Pleasure. Translated from the French.<break time="100ms" />PART VII.<break time="100ms" />(Continued.)<break time="100ms" />I FELT CONSIDERABLY ENERVATED FOR A DAY OR TWO AND REFRAINED FROM AGAIN ENTERING THE LISTS OF VENUS UNTIL I HAD FAIRLY SET SAIL ON MY PROJECTED CRUISE IN SEARCH OF LOVE AND BEAUTY IN THE HESPERIAN CLIMES, WHERE I HOPED FOR THE MOST EXQUISITE PLEASURES IN THE ARMS OF THE ARDENT LADIES OF CUBA AND SPANISH MAIN.<break time="100ms" />I coasted round and put into Bordeaux for the purpose of giving the sailors a chance of getting themselves girls.<break time="100ms" />In two days they were all mated, and we put off for Havana, intending to stop there a short time, as I had heard much of the beauty of the women of the island.<break time="100ms" />Arriving at Havana, I took some rooms at one of the best hotels, giving orders to the Captain to keep the brig in sailing order so as to be able to sail at a moment's notice.<break time="100ms" />At the table d'hote I noticed a handsome, vivacious brunette, evidently an inhabitant of the island. Her eyes were fairly hidden under a mass of deep black hair which overshadowed them; but I could perceive whilst at the table, she was continually glancing at me, and the moment my eyes met hers she would suddenly drop her eyes on the plate or look in another direction. From this I augured favourably and deemed success certain, thinking that I had made a conquest.<break time="100ms" />In the evening I attended the theatre accompanied by the Captain, and both of us well armed. I there saw the lady in a box in company with a couple of elderly gentlemen.<break time="100ms" />The one whom I took to be her husband was a cross-grained, ugly looking fellow.<break time="100ms" />I followed her home with the intent to win her.<break time="100ms" />In the morning I got an introduction to Senor Don Manuel Vasquer, the husband of Donna Isabel, my lovely vis-a-vis at the table.<break time="100ms" />I told him I was a gentleman of rank and fortune, traveling for the pleasure with a vessel of my own, and invited him down to the harbour to look at the brig.<break time="100ms" />He accepted the invitation and was very much pleased with the neat cleanliness of everything on deck, and with the luxury displayed in the fittings of the cabin.<break time="100ms" />I had a lunch set out and plied him well with champagne so that when he left the vessel, he was in very high spirits. On reaching the hotel he invited me up to his apartment and introduced me to his wife and a couple of other ladies we found with her.<break time="100ms" />I endeavoured as well as my looks could express to let her see that I had taken particular notice of her, and was much smitten by her charms.<break time="100ms" />After conversing for a short time I retired to my room to dress for dinner and penned a declaration to the Donna Isabel, declaring my passion for her and imploring her grant me an interview, as I had read in her eyes that I was not disagreeable to her.<break time="100ms" />After dinner I joined her and her husband and slipped my note into her hand, which she immediately hid in the folds of her dress. I then went to my room to wait for an answer, which I felt sure would soon be sent to me. Nor had I to wait long, for in a couple of hours a negro-wench opened the door, poking her head in to ascertain if I was in the room, threw a note to me, and shutting the door without saying a word, retired.<break time="100ms" />I hastily picked up the note and opening it found my expectations confirmed!<break time="100ms" />She granted me an interview. Her note stated that her husband would go out to his plantations the next day and that at three o'clock in the afternoon she would be alone taking her siesta.<break time="100ms" />The evening, night and morning hung heavily on me, and after dining, I retired to my room, laid my watch on the table and sat gazing at the dial to see the weary hours pass away; but as the minute-hand pointed to three; the same black wench again opened the door, poked her head in, looked round and drew back, leaving the door open.<break time="100ms" />I jumped up and followed her to the rooms of her mistress.<break time="100ms" />Here I found Donna Isabel reclining in an elegant dishabille, on a sofa. She held out her hand to me in welcome, which I took and pressed to my lips.<break time="100ms" />She invited me to be seated and I placed myself on a foot-stool at her side. Taking her hand between mine, I disclosed my passion for her, imploring her not to refuse my love. At first she pretended to be much surprised that I should make a declaration of my love to her and appeared half angry. But as I proceeded with my tale of love and pressed her for an answer favourable to the passion which was consuming me, she appeared to relent, and rising from her reclining position made room for me to sit beside her on the couch.<break time="100ms" />As I sat down by her side I dropped an arm round her waist and drawing her to my bosom I implored her to grant me her love - even to leave her husband and fly with me to some remote corner of the earth where we could while away our years in the soft dalliance of love.<break time="100ms" />I told her that her husband was an old man with whom she could not enjoy life, and from whom a young woman like herself could not receive those tender attentions, and the soft and real pleasure which she could enjoy in the arms of a young and devoted lover.<break time="100ms" />She sighed and hung her head on her breast, saying she never knew what it was to receive those delicious and tender pleasures from her husband that I had just spoken of. That from the time of her marriage to the present moment, her whole time was taken up with drinking and gambling. That he left her to amuse herself as best she could in the house, he was so jealous that he would never allow her to go out except in his company. She sighed again and wished that heaven had given her such a man as myself.<break time="100ms" />I know not how it was, but when she stopped, I found one of my hands had opened the front of her dress and slipped beneath her shift and was moulding one of her large hard breasts, and my lips were pressed on hers.<break time="100ms" />My leaning against her had insensibly moved her backwards till, without our knowing it, her head was resting on the cushion of the sofa and I was lying on top of her.
    </voice>
</speak>
