<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I rather suspect that putting the Countess to bed was a longer business than usual, and I am afraid that Justine found me a nuisance rather than otherwise, for I was so proud of my newly invested privileges and other important offices, which I considered myself entitled to, that I insisted on acting the part of a chambermaid to a somewhat indefensible extent. And the beauty of it (in every sense of the word) was that the Countess rather backed me up in my vagaries than otherwise, until at last Justine lost all patience and vowed that if I did not retire into the anteroom and leave her alone with her mistress for a few minutes, I should go back to my own room as I deserved.<break time="100ms" />"Now, she's jealous, throw her on the bed, Ernest," ordered the Countess, "and do her over at once. I shall be delighted to see two such handsome persons playing the Adam and Eve game: besides, I've got a little tickler here to increase the fun and add to our enjoyment."<break time="100ms" />My affair was again in prime condition. So, throwing Justine over the edge of the bed I was into her in a moment. "Ah! ah! oh! Pray don't, my Lady!" I called out almost in a scream, as one, two, three slashing cuts of a heavy birch rod warmed my bottom behind. Justine held me to herself like a vice and I could hear the Countess laugh as she plied the merciless rod, till presently such a beautiful glowing sensation added to an extraordinary bursting stiffness in my piston-rod, drowned all sense of pain as I shot such a profuse emission into my sweetheart that I almost fainted from excess of emotion.<break time="100ms" />And here it was my intention to draw the veil, or more correctly speaking, to drop the curtain and to balk the necessity of my friends by giving no further record of the proceedings of that delicious night; but I think in common gratitude to my beautiful Lady Pomeroy I ought to acknowledge that I was in a state of exquisite bliss and I may say with vanity that my lovely companion owned to something very like that enviable state herself.<break time="100ms" />We were both a little too happy, for when Justine came to call me in the morning I was almost exhausted. And the faithful girl could only rouse me by insisting that her mistress was faint, that I must leave the room while she administered restoratives.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />The Old Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />Tune— "The Mistletoe Bough."<break time="100ms" />The beds were all made in the bawdy house fine,<break time="100ms" />And the whores were rejoicing in gin and wine;<break time="100ms" />And the old bawd herself, dressed out so gay,<break time="100ms" />Was making them drunk on Xmas day.<break time="100ms" />And there was "Peg Watkins" the brothel's delight,<break time="100ms" />Got lewd on a cove, as was there that night.<break time="100ms" />And said she to herself: "If I don't have a go.<break time="100ms" />I'll content myself with the old Dildoe."<break time="100ms" />Chorus- Oh! the old Dildoe, oh, the old whore's Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! I am weary of lashing," Peg now did cry,<break time="100ms" />"Come upstairs with me Joey, and let's have a shie."<break time="100ms" />But Joey determined to stick to the gin,<break time="100ms" />And wouldn't leave his liquor to have put in.<break time="100ms" />And Peg cursed him and told him to go to hell;<break time="100ms" />But drunk as a fart, from the chair he fell.<break time="100ms" />So away she ran with her blood in a glow;<break time="100ms" />Determined to try the old Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />Chorus- Oh! the old Dildoe, oh! the old whore's Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />To the old bawd's bedroom at once she went,<break time="100ms" />To seize upon the implement.<break time="100ms" />She looked in the cupboard, she looked in the pot,<break time="100ms" />She searched high and low but found it not.<break time="100ms" />She rushed to the couch, she searched the bed,<break time="100ms" />Underneath the pillow she spied its head.<break time="100ms" />She seized it and cried: "Full well I know,<break time="100ms" />Far better than Joe's the old Dildoe."<break time="100ms" />Chorus- Oh! the old Dildoe, oh, the old whore's Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />She flew with the treasure into her room<break time="100ms" />(Its size was the handle of a broom).<break time="100ms" />Oh! what ecstatic moments she passed there,<break time="100ms" />As she threw up her legs on the back of a chair.<break time="100ms" />Through each vein in her body the fire lurked,<break time="100ms" />Surely and quickly the engine worked;<break time="100ms" />Face her, back her, stop her no! no!<break time="100ms" />Faster and faster flew the old Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />Chorus- Oh! the old Dildoe, oh! the old whore's Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />Minutes soon passed and the hours flew by,<break time="100ms" />When there suddenly came a fearful cry,<break time="100ms" />Which was followed at once by a fearful scream,<break time="100ms" />Which awoke the whores from their drunken dream.<break time="100ms" />They all jumped up in a hell of a fright,<break time="100ms" />In an empty gin-bottle they stuck a light;<break time="100ms" />And the old whore herself away did go<break time="100ms" />To look after the safety of the old Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />Chorus- Oh! the old Dildoe, oh! the old whore's Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />But the old whore very soon did return<break time="100ms" />With a look of agony and deep concern;<break time="100ms" />For her heart was filled with dire remorse,<break time="100ms" />As she told the whores of her fearful loss;<break time="100ms" />She questioned them all and implored them to tell,<break time="100ms" />Where the treasure had gone that she loved so well;<break time="100ms" />When one of them said: "I think I know,<break time="100ms" />Peg Watkins is using your old Dildoe."<break time="100ms" />Chorus- Oh! the old Dildoe, oh! the old whore's Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />Away they all flew to Peggy's room.<break time="100ms" />But, ho! 'twas filled with smoke and fume,<break time="100ms" />And a terrible stench came forth from the bed,<break time="100ms" />Where poor Peggy lay all burnt and dead.<break time="100ms" />Sad, sad, was her fate, when, instead of a fuck,<break time="100ms" />With the old Dildoe she had tried her luck;<break time="100ms" />And when at the short digs she so hard did go,<break time="100ms" />It caught fire with the friction - the old Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />Chorus- Oh! the old Dildoe, oh! the old whore's Dildoe.<break time="100ms" />* * *<break time="100ms" />An old and favoured servant of two maiden ladies had been frequently reprimanded by them for his free behaviour with the female servants. Caught one day in flagrante delicto, he was summoned to their presence, and while the girl was sacked, he was told that if he did not do better and turn over a new leaf, much as they valued him - his next escapade would be the last. He promised amendment and matters went on very well for a time. One evening, he was not to be found when wanted, and on a search being made, was discovered in the beer-cellar, buggering the page boy.<break time="100ms" />"How now," he was asked, "is this your amendment? You promised to turn over a new leaf."<break time="100ms" />"So I have" said he, "only I have begun at the bottom of the page!"
    </voice>
</speak>
