<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"But would not any other prick do you as well as his," she asked, all the while frigging my cunt until she had it in a glow.<break time="100ms" />"Well, Kate, you have so excited my cunt with your finger that I could enjoy being fucked by most any prick."<break time="100ms" />"Well dear, your finger has done the same for me. Let us try to relieve each other and as the night is hot let us get outside the clothes. Come, lie over me."<break time="100ms" />And placing herself on the edge of the bed with her feet on the floor, she put me astride over her, my breast and belly resting on hers, and my bottom turned out. Then she threw her arms around me and thrusting her tongue in my mouth held me firm. I felt something touch my bottom and then a soft round stiff thing poked against my cunt. I spluttered "Let me up, Kate, I am sure there is someone behind us."<break time="100ms" />"Nonsense," said Kate, "it is only your own overheated imaginative mind."<break time="100ms" />"I tell you it is no imagination. Oh! - it is pushing in - let me up - there is someone fucking me. Oh, Kate, I feel his prick, my cunt is filled with it, do let me up."<break time="100ms" />But she held me tighter than ever.<break time="100ms" />"Don't be foolish, keep your bottom quiet. It is only my finger."<break time="100ms" />"No, it is a prick, I feel its head - in - ever so far. Oh!"<break time="100ms" />"What is it doing?"<break time="100ms" />"It is fucking, fucking, fucking, fucking. Oh, there the feeling comes, how delicious!" And I lay motionless on her bosom. Then the prick was suddenly drawn out and must have been thrust into her for I felt a belly with hair on rubbing against my bottom as the prick was worked in and out.<break time="100ms" />Then a pair of strong arms clasped us both together and after holding us for a moment, quickly withdrew.<break time="100ms" />After we had returned to our usual places in the bed I asked: "Who was it, Kate?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, never mind, let me go on with my story."<break time="100ms" />"Both the Captain and the mate had good voices and they sometimes sang for us when taking their grog in the evening.<break time="100ms" />"Our custom was to sit reclining on the broad stern locker which was well covered with cushions. Carle was generally between Hilda and me, and with a hand on each of our cunts. I would be occupied petting his prick and balls while she would be similarly engaged with the Captain. The latter while sipping his grog would strike up one of his favourite ditties in a bold rollicking tone, and Carle would quickly follow suit. After which there would be a general fuck such as I have already described.<break time="100ms" />"I only remember two of their songs, which I will repeat you as specimens if you like."<break time="100ms" />"Do please, I would like to hear them."<break time="100ms" />THE CAPTAIN'S SONG.<break time="100ms" />I care not what squeamish lovers may say,<break time="100ms" />The maiden that best suits my mind<break time="100ms" />Is the sweet girl that will meet me half way;<break time="100ms" />And while she is free, be as kind.<break time="100ms" />With her rich beauties I never am cloyed,<break time="100ms" />Fresh pleasures I find at her side;<break time="100ms" />I don't love her less because she's enjoyed<break time="100ms" />By many another beside.<break time="100ms" />Shall I try to describe all her merit,<break time="100ms" />I feel that I'd never have done;<break time="100ms" />She is brimful of sweetness and spirit,<break time="100ms" />And sparkles with freedom and fun.<break time="100ms" />It is bliss then to hold her and win her,<break time="100ms" />She never proves peevish or coy;<break time="100ms" />But the farther and deeper I'm in her<break time="100ms" />The fuller she fills me with joy.<break time="100ms" />She opens her thighs without fear or dread,<break time="100ms" />She points to her sweet little crack,<break time="100ms" />Its lips are so red, and all overspread<break time="100ms" />With hair of the glossiest black.<break time="100ms" />Reclined on her breast, and clasped in her arms,<break time="100ms" />With her my soft moments I spend;<break time="100ms" />And revel the more in her melting charms,<break time="100ms" />Because they are shared with a friend.<break time="100ms" />THE MATE'S SONG.<break time="100ms" />My Jamie is a lover gay,<break time="100ms" />He is so very funny.<break time="100ms" />When last we met to sport and play,<break time="100ms" />He took me by the cunny.<break time="100ms" />Then drawing out his sturdy prick,<break time="100ms" />Right in my hand he placed it,<break time="100ms" />And said 'twould be a jolly trick,<break time="100ms" />If in my mouth I'd taste it.<break time="100ms" />I kissed its bright and rosy head,<break time="100ms" />And then began to suck it;<break time="100ms" />He felt about my cunt, and said,<break time="100ms" />He wanted now to fuck it.<break time="100ms" />Down on the bed he laid me,<break time="100ms" />With bursting balls, and prick's round head,<break time="100ms" />Love's sweetest debt he paid me.<break time="100ms" />Let maidens of a tim'rous mind<break time="100ms" />Refuse what most they're wanting;<break time="100ms" />Since we for fucking were designed,<break time="100ms" />We surely should be granting.<break time="100ms" />So when your lover feels your cunt,<break time="100ms" />Do not be coy, nor grieve him;<break time="100ms" />But spread your thighs and heave your front,<break time="100ms" />For fucking is like heaven.<break time="100ms" />When Kate had repeated these songs she asked me what I thought of them.<break time="100ms" />I told her they were excellent, especially the mate's, and that I certainly should learn that one and sing it to Mr. Trevor. Kate then continued her narrative:<break time="100ms" />I ought to tell you that during our voyage my maid Nina had not been idle. She attended me every morning to assist in giving me a sponge-bath and in dressing me. She amused me by the recital of her adventures with the sailors who coaxed her to come to them at night in their hammocks. She said fucking in that position was quite new.<break time="100ms" />She had an adventure which I must repeat to you. Our passengers were a sailor, Jim Murphy, sent home on sick-leave, his wife and her daughter Jenny, a buxom damsel about twenty.<break time="100ms" />Now, Mrs. Murphy kept a sharp look-out on Jenny, with whom the boatswain soon fell in love, and he tried to find opportunities of being alone with her to press his suit, or in plain language, to get a fuck out of her.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Murphy had at times to be in her husband's cabin to give him medicine or attend to his wants, so she told Nina in her absence never to leave Jenny alone with the boatswain. Nina faithfully promised and kept her word in the following manner.<break time="100ms" />One evening Mrs. Murphy was sent for to attend to her husband and the moment she was out of sight the boatswain came and sat down by the side of Jenny and Nina and asked Jenny to sew a button on his shirt.<break time="100ms" />"Yes," said Jenny.<break time="100ms" />"Then come to my cabin and I will give it to you."<break time="100ms" />Nina said: "Yes, Jenny, we will both go."
    </voice>
</speak>
