<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />After we were out of sight of the city, I took the Captain aside and told him that towards night I wanted him to run the brig in towards the shore; and that I intended to seize the seven men and land them in a boat and make off with the women. I told him to go and speak to the crew about the matter and have them in readiness to obey my signal.<break time="100ms" />A little before dusk, we ran close in shore at a place where there was no plantation visible. I had ordered some lumber to be strewn about the greater deck and commanded the Captain to send the sailors to carry it away.<break time="100ms" />Sixteen stalwart fellows came aft and suddenly seized on the men and bound their arms and legs. I then told them what I intended to do, ordering the men at the same time to the women below. Their execrations and implorings for the girls who were their relatives, I would not listen to, but I had them put in a boat and sent ashore. They were unbound and and let loose. The boat returned to the brig and we set sail for France.<break time="100ms" />The girls did nothing but sob and weep for a day or two but I soon brought them to their senses. Immediately after setting their companions ashore I went into the cabin, and bringing Ibzaidu and Mary out of their hiding places, I introduced them to the company.<break time="100ms" />When supper was served they all refused to sit at the table and eat. But I told them if they did not comply with all my wishes that I would hand them over to the sailors to be used by them as they chose. This had its effect on them and they seated themselves at the table.<break time="100ms" />I rang a bell and two of the handsomest women belonging to the sailors entered stark naked, as I had ordered them to wait on the table.<break time="100ms" />The Spanish girls were all about to rise up, but putting on a fierce aspect, I threatened them the first who should rise should be passed forward to the men. This had effect on them and they sat still.<break time="100ms" />Whilst the servant was pouring out the coffee I arose and went to the side-table as if to fetch something, but in reality to pour a few drops of a certain liquid into each cup of coffee.<break time="100ms" />The quantity put in each cup was enough to set any woman's amorous and licentious desires on fire.<break time="100ms" />They all drank their coffee and in about half-an-hour the effect was very visible, as all the coyness of modesty had disappeared and they languishingly cast their lascivious glances at me, joking the servant-girls on their nudity, and whenever they came in reach of them, pinching, slapping them, etc., so great was the effect produced by the drug I put in the coffee.<break time="100ms" />When the supper was over and the tables were cleared, I commenced playing and tussling with them. Rolling them about on the floor and playing them a thousand amorous tricks which they repaid with interest - throwing me on floor, falling in a heap on top of me while I would catch a kiss from them, squeeze a fine bubby, slide my hand along a thigh, or slip it up under their petticoats and grasp a large calf or a well-turned knee. I ordered in some wine of a very strong quality, well drugged with the love-potion.<break time="100ms" />I plied them with the wine of which they drank very freely and in a couple of hours all reserve and modesty had left them.<break time="100ms" />I took the Senora - the wife I had seduced at the hotel and whose husband I had set ashore with the others - on one side and invited her to step into one of the staterooms with me, I then asked her if she could forgive me for robbing her from her old cuckold of a husband. She threw herself into my arms and with a fervent embrace and kiss sealed my pardon with her lips.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />* * *<break time="100ms" />It has without doubt been Truscott's ambition<break time="100ms" />To get the new Temple Bar in position.<break time="100ms" />He thought of it by day, dreamt of it by night,<break time="100ms" />And one morning woke in a terrible fright.<break time="100ms" />"I dreamt, my dear love, that this thing came to pass,<break time="100ms" />That the public had shoved Temple Bar up my arse;<break time="100ms" />That they greeted me loudly with hisses and calls<break time="100ms" />And the dragon grew lively and bit off my balls."<break time="100ms" />An Unfortunate Family.<break time="100ms" />Miss Jones, whose father was a wealthy alderman, and thought nobody but a rich city man was good enough for his daughter, took the precaution to allow young Brown to get her in the family way.<break time="100ms" />When the youngster was about three months on the road she one morning appealed to her papa to sanction their engagement and she asked for a speedy marriage:<break time="100ms" />"Egad! Do you think I'll ever have that penniless puppy?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, oh, Papa! But the puppy's had me and there's a baby coming!" sobbed Miss Jones, covering her crimson face with her hands.<break time="100ms" />"Well, I'm buggered!" exclaimed the alderman.<break time="100ms" />"Father! Father! Don't say that; we're such an unfortunate family!"<break time="100ms" />Hoar Frost.<break time="100ms" />A Yankee travelling on the London and North Eastern Railway the other day, had for his vis-a-vis a gentleman who had lost his nose. The disfigured countenance so fascinated his gaze that at last his fellow-passenger, getting impatient at what he considered an impertinence, exclaimed in a rage: "Really, sir, you are very rude and insulting to look at me so! Did you ever see a person before who had had the misfortune to have his nose frost-bitten?"<break time="100ms" />The Yankee apologized for his seeming want of manners, and reassured the annoyed person by informing him that he was going to alight at the next station. However, after leaving the train he continued to walk up and down the station-platform in seeming thought, till just as the train was on the move, his curiosity again came over him and thrusting his head through the carriage window with a meaning grin on his face, he said: "I guess, stranger, that must have been a darn sharp Hoar Frost!"<break time="100ms" />Lord E. T-e, when a youth, asked his mother the following question: "Mama dear," said he, "what is the meaning of the word bugger?"<break time="100ms" />"Bugger, my child? Why do you ask?"<break time="100ms" />"Because I heard my tutor call the coachman a damned bugger."<break time="100ms" />"Well, my child," replied the Marchioness, "a bugger is a person who does his fellow an injury behind his back."<break time="100ms" />-Cough.<break time="100ms" />My Grandmother's Tale or May's Account of Her Introduction to the Art of Love.<break time="100ms" />From an unsophisticated Manuscript found amongst the old lady's papers, after her death, supposed to have been written about A.D. 1797.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER II.<break time="100ms" />KATE'S NARRATIVE CONTINUED; THE VOYAGE; CAPTAIN LEMBERG AND HIS NIECE HILDA<break time="100ms" />I need not tell you that after all reserve was laid aside amongst us we certainly enjoyed ourselves amazingly.<break time="100ms" />Carle and the Captain seemed to delight in fucking us turn and turn about, but everything was done openly and by general consent.
    </voice>
</speak>
