<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The books and pictures were freely used and we tried to act the scenes depicted or described.<break time="100ms" />The Captain would lay Hilda on her back across the table. Then, placing me over her so that her face was between my thighs while my feet rested on the floor, he would produce his prick, and Hilda looking up, would pop it into her cunt and hold it while he fucked.<break time="100ms" />Carle would beat the other side of the table between Hilda's uplifted thighs, while I, stooping forward, would take his prick and stick it into her open cunt and then handle his bottom and balls. The Captain leaning over my back would watch the operation with great interest, and, waiting until Carle's prick was all absorbed within the hairy lips, would cry:<break time="100ms" />"Now, old fellow, let us make a fair start! Draw out first, and when I say one, push."<break time="100ms" />"ONE."- The two bottoms heaved, driving the two pricks into the deep recesses of our cunts.<break time="100ms" />"TWO."- Another energetic shove, making our breasts and bellies rub together.<break time="100ms" />"THREE."- A vehement push; the Captain's belly smacked against my bottom, and Carle's balls banged against Hilda's rump.<break time="100ms" />"FOUR."- The two excited pricks rushed with delicious force into our throbbing cunts, making us bound to meet them.<break time="100ms" />"FIVE."- We felt the pricks rammed home, they seemed to reach our very hearts.<break time="100ms" />"SIX."- A flood of boiling seed burst into our cunts and filled our reservoirs so that they overflowed and the hot sperm poured out, saturating pricks, ballocks, and cunts in love's sweet juice.<break time="100ms" />The next time that Hilda and I were alone she pointed to some whipping scenes among the pictures and suggested that we should make a trial of the boasted efficacy of the birch rod in producing emotion.<break time="100ms" />"But where shall we get a rod on board ship?" I asked.<break time="100ms" />She at once replied: "Oh, I know where there is a broom without a handle. I can easily abstract some of the twigs and tie up a rod with enough for our purpose."<break time="100ms" />So, that evening, when I was in my nightdress, Hilda came into my cabin and showed me a rod which she had prepared and neatly tied with ribbon.<break time="100ms" />I was a little frightened at the sight of it and said: "Won't it hurt?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, it may a little at first, but when one begins to get the feel, the pain will be turned into pleasure. However, begin with me, I am not afraid."<break time="100ms" />She then placed herself on the sofa with her naked bottom up, and making me tuck up my shift, she put her arm round my hip and told me to whip away.<break time="100ms" />I touched up her beautiful white posteriors while she played with my cunt. "You may hit harder than that, Kate," she said, wriggling her bottom about.<break time="100ms" />I began to enter into the sport and struck her so smartly that the cheeks of her bottom assumed a rosy hue like two blooming apples.<break time="100ms" />"Oh," she cried, as she rolled over, "my cunt is on fire - put your finger into it, Kate. How I would enjoy being fucked now. How I wish Carle was here."<break time="100ms" />"Well, you have your wish," he said, as he stepped in quite naked and holding in his hand his fine red-headed prick in stiff erection.<break time="100ms" />He seized her round the waist and making her stoop forward he plunged his prick into her cunt from behind.<break time="100ms" />"Stay a moment, Carle," she said. "Kate is to get her whipping now, and lest you should cover it with your hands let me tie them here."<break time="100ms" />And without asking my leave she secured my wrists and tied them firmly to the legs of the sofa, and then to keep my legs apart, she tied my ankles, too. I did not quite like my position but as I was helpless I only said:<break time="100ms" />"Remember, you must stop when I tell you."<break time="100ms" />Then she leaned forward and Carle introduced his prick into her cunt from behind.<break time="100ms" />They both laughed while she played away at my poor innocent bum. At first I tried to bear it as patiently as I could but Carle became more energetic in his strokes, and she imported more force to her blows. At last I said: "I say - Hilda - stop! Hilda, you wretch, what do you mean? You cruel girl, let me up, you are torturing me!"<break time="100ms" />My whole bottom felt in a flame. I made frantic efforts to release my hands and I began to sob. Just then she fell forward, and Carle pressing against her bottom discharged into her cunt. Then, coming to me, she untied my hands and laying her cheek against mine, said: "Forgive me, dear Kate, I was so excited. I am just burning!"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Hilda, you cruel girl, how could you? Oh, I am hot; I am just burning!"<break time="100ms" />"Where are you so hot, darling Kate?"<break time="100ms" />And I felt a hand slip up between my thighs and press the lips of my cunt. Looking up I saw the Captain's good-humoured cheery face.<break time="100ms" />"Never mind, Kate, we will punish her for this. Let me give you what relief I can."<break time="100ms" />Then, gently separating my thighs he pushed in his prick while Hilda kissed away my tears. The soft head of his prick had a most soothing effect on the terribly excited folds of my cunt and as it gradually passed up I forgot the pain of the whipping in the intensely amorous excitement I now experienced. I never felt anything more delicious than the sweet friction of the Captain's cock in my fevered cunt; it made every nerve thrill again with pleasure.<break time="100ms" />"Does not that repay you?" Hilda whispered.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, yes," I replied. "Push it in; drive it home, fuck me - fuck me. Oh, fuck - fuck - fuck!"<break time="100ms" />The Captain now declared that Hilda ought to be well whipped for her cruel treatment of my poor bottom.<break time="100ms" />"Very well," said Carle, "but as I am the real offender I will bear it in her place."<break time="100ms" />So putting the rod into my hand he leaned over the berth and stuck out his great fleshy rump, while Hilda sat below him, holding his prick and sucking it in her mouth.<break time="100ms" />"Now, Kate," said the Captain, "lay it on strongly; don't spare his impudent backside, hit him, hit him hard! Don't mind, he used to be flogged every day at school!"<break time="100ms" />I whipped away and soon his bottom began to glow, his balls were tightened up and his prick swelled and stiffened. He heaved gently so as to work it in and out of her mouth and then with a tremendous "Oh!" he spurted his seed down her throat.<break time="100ms" />Now, sweet May, that must do for the present. Good night, my love, good night.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER V KATE'S NARRATIVE CONCLUDED.<break time="100ms" />Before I resume Kate's narrative I must tell something that happened to myself the following night.<break time="100ms" />Kate was later than usual in coming and when she did I was in bed, my lamp out and the room quite dark. When she got into bed she put her hand on my cunt, and asked if I had ever any longing for a prick now. I told her I had but that I was waiting for my lover to come and then I should have plenty of fucking.
    </voice>
</speak>
