<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Stand aside, all of you," I said sternly, "and let me pay him the desserts for his impudence," advancing birch in hand.<break time="100ms" />He was a plucky little fellow and distained to cry out although I saw two or three big tears roll down his crimson face under my infliction, and I could also see that his cock was as stiff as a poker. He was released, and without even waiting to pull his breeches up, rushed forward to help us as we stretched his friend Peter on the ottoman, and then by my direction he sat on his back, whilst I gleefully let him have a due share of the birch till he begged hard to be let off.<break time="100ms" />When they thought to adjust their clothes we all began to laugh and joke them about the beautiful red weals we could see, pulling up their shirt-tails and taking such liberties that in a short time they were quite undressed and we had two youths in a state of nature with standing pricks to look at.<break time="100ms" />"Well, I wouldn't give much for those toys of yours if that is all you have to show the girls!" I said laughingly, as I switched the parts indicated with my rod. "Why Annie here has a better cock than any of you. We'll all strip and you shall see."<break time="100ms" />This was the expected signal and all further restraint on our impulsive passions was thrown aside in a moment.<break time="100ms" />I think those two handsome middies had never really had a girl before and that I really took their maidenheads. In fact, I indulged in my letch for having two pricks in my cunt at once, whilst Charlie fucked Miss Prude before our eyes, till she had hysterics from excessive lubricity.<break time="100ms" />We kept it up till nearly five o'clock, flicking, gamahuching and indulging in every fancy we could think of. I even made Charlie get into my bottom with Simpson in him. Peter Williams also postillioning her companion with his prick in his fundament, whilst Miss Prude and Patty tickled and helped to excite us the very best way they could.<break time="100ms" />At last they were obliged to leave us and I may say that was the last lustful orgy I was ever able to indulge in, for my constitution broke down rapidly even during my stay at Madeira and I returned to England in the following May, since when, dear Walter, you have been my constant and loving attendant, and seen how rapidly this consumption is carrying me to my grave. Oh! I would that I had strength to do it once more and that you were my manly champion in that combat of bliss which I shall never taste again. Would to Heaven I might die in spending as I felt your very soul shoot into my vitals, but, alas! it cannot be! Still, if there is bliss in the world to be, I feel assured of an everlasting fuck.<break time="100ms" />Amen! I am unable to hold my pen any longer.<break time="100ms" />CONCLUSION.<break time="100ms" />Sweet Polly.<break time="100ms" />Oh, do you remember sweet Polly, Ben Bolt,<break time="100ms" />Sweet Polly with a cunt soft and brown;<break time="100ms" />How she'd grin with delight when you gave her a quid,<break time="100ms" />And how quickly she'd fetch a prick down?<break time="100ms" />That girl has now gone to decay, Ben Bolt,<break time="100ms" />That soft, luscious quim is now dry;<break time="100ms" />And that lump of delight is now a bag of dry bones,<break time="100ms" />That wouldn't please you, Ben, or I.<break time="100ms" />Had she stuck to the Navy, I vow, Ben Bolt,<break time="100ms" />She'd alive be and kicking today;<break time="100ms" />But a bloody big soldier got round our poor girl,<break time="100ms" />And turned the poor mot into clay.<break time="100ms" />He gave her no coin, but he gave her the pox,<break time="100ms" />He whacked her while we were away;<break time="100ms" />He fucked her to death, and true to his set,<break time="100ms" />He often got in the back way.<break time="100ms" />Now she's gone dead, and he's off abroad,<break time="100ms" />And there the cuss had better stay;<break time="100ms" />For if he comes near me, my toe in his arse<break time="100ms" />Will remind him of his comrade's play.<break time="100ms" />The Burial of Sir John Thomas.<break time="100ms" />Not a sound was heard, but the ottoman shook,<break time="100ms" />And my darling looked awfully worried,<break time="100ms" />As round her fair form I a firm hold took,<break time="100ms" />And John Thomas I silently buried.<break time="100ms" />We buried him deeply at dead of night,<break time="100ms" />The tails of our night-shirts upturning;<break time="100ms" />With struggling raptures and fits of delight,<break time="100ms" />The night-lights dimly burning.<break time="100ms" />No useless French Letters enclosed his crest,<break time="100ms" />For ne'er in such rubbish we bound him;<break time="100ms" />But he went like a warrior taking his test,<break time="100ms" />With naught but his fur coat around him.<break time="100ms" />Few and short were the sighs we gave,<break time="100ms" />Though we oftentimes groaned as in sorrow,<break time="100ms" />As at each stroke for the joy we'd rave,<break time="100ms" />Ne'er giving a thought for the morrow.<break time="100ms" />But as yet he had not nearly done,<break time="100ms" />And ne'er had a thought of retiring,<break time="100ms" />When suddenly to groan we again had begun<break time="100ms" />Through John Thomas silently firing.<break time="100ms" />And we thought, as he came from his narrow bed,<break time="100ms" />As lifeless and limp as a willow,<break time="100ms" />How lowly he hung down his diminished head,<break time="100ms" />And how gladly he'd rest on his pillow.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
