<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />All our love-matters went on in much the same manner, until at last our brig reached London docks, when we wish Jenny and the boatswain good-bye, and with Nina and our luggage, Captain Lemberg took us to the hotel, where he usually put up when he returned from his voyages.<break time="100ms" />Captain Lemberg was very kind and chose a bedroom for myself and Nina next to his own, and both opened into a parlour intended for our mutual use.<break time="100ms" />Captain Lemberg decided I should remain a week or two at the hotel with him, to rest after the voyage and to see some of the sights of London, before I went to the school. In fact he told me he did not think I need go to school until he was obliged to return to the brig, which would be a couple of months, and I told him I would prefer to obey my father's wishes. So we decided I was to go to school in a week.<break time="100ms" />My father had given me a letter to hand to Madame Stewart, the school-mistress, who lived at Hampton Court.<break time="100ms" />Captain Lemberg took us to the theatres, which pleased me extremely, also to the Tower and Monument and British Museum.<break time="100ms" />The time passed very rapidly away in seeing the wonders of London by day and the theatres in the evening, and then we had nice suppers at our hotel and Nina and I retired to our bed, soon to be followed by Captain Lemberg to continue those loving fucking matches like those on the ship.<break time="100ms" />At last the week ended and Captain Lemberg took me in a coach to Madame Stewart together with Nina, who was to continue to wait on me as lady's-maid.<break time="100ms" />We had a little fucking in the coach and at last arrived at the school, which was a large house surrounded by ornamental grounds and gardens, enclosed by high walls. The grounds sloped down to the Thames, on the banks of which, of course, there was no wall.<break time="100ms" />Madame Stewart received the Captain and myself and Nina in a large drawing-room, and I handed her my father's letter and told her Nina was my servant.<break time="100ms" />She told Nina to retire for the present to the housekeeper's room.<break time="100ms" />Madame was a fine-looking woman of about fifty, with dark hair and eyes and a fine bust.<break time="100ms" />After reading the letter she kissed me and said she was acquainted with my father many years before and would try to make me happy, provided I obeyed the rules of her establishment.<break time="100ms" />Captain Lemberg then paid her £100 for one year's fees in advance and asked for a receipt.<break time="100ms" />Madame asked him to step into the next room with her as she kept her writing materials there, and she wished to ask him a few questions in private.<break time="100ms" />So pouring me out a glass of wine and giving me some cake and a book of pictures, they withdrew into the next room and shut the door.<break time="100ms" />You may be sure my eye was at the keyhole in a moment and I saw that the Captain had pulled out his prick! And I heard him say:<break time="100ms" />"Madame, I am entitled to the usual commission for bringing you a new pupil and I will take it in dog-fashion."<break time="100ms" />"Hush!" said Madame, "or the young lady will hear you."<break time="100ms" />"Nonsense - now get down on all fours so as not to derange your dress."<break time="100ms" />Madame did so and the Captain tossing up her clothes exposed her bottom, and standing behind her, leant over her back and fucked her in that position.<break time="100ms" />When this was over they each took a chair and I overheard the following conversation:<break time="100ms" />Madame S.- "Is this young lady a virgin?"<break time="100ms" />Capt. L.- "Yes, as much as you are!"<break time="100ms" />Madame S.- "Shall I read you the letter her father has sent me?"<break time="100ms" />Capt. L.- "I shall be delighted to hear it read."<break time="100ms" />Madame then read the letter aloud, and I heard every word that follows:<break time="100ms" />My Dear Madame Stewart:<break time="100ms" />These will be handed to you by my daughter Kate, a fine girl just over twelve years of age. Captain Lemberg has kindly undertaken to see her safely to your house, and I have authorized him to pay you for the first year's expense, one hundred guineas.<break time="100ms" />My daughter's education has been neglected in such matters as penmanship, grammar, drawing, and music. Be pleased to spare no pains in instructing her in these.<break time="100ms" />In some other things she is in advance of her years. On account of living all her life on a slave plantation she has always seen boys, girls and women in a state of nakedness, so the difference in sex is familiar to her. She has seen men and women in the act of coition.<break time="100ms" />You will please pay special regard to her religious duties, and also try to inculcate that modest demeanour which is such a characteristic to your own movements that I shall never forget being struck with on occasion of my last visit to your school some fifteen years ago when I had the felicity of watching you slowly strip naked at noon before a large mirror in your dining-room previous to your honouring my pego with a visit to your fine quim.<break time="100ms" />Alas! Madam, these remembrances quite overpower me and make me regret the distance that separates us!<break time="100ms" />I have sent a very fair mulatto-girl named Nina, to wait on my daughter.<break time="100ms" />From your obedient servant, Sebastian de Lorme.<break time="100ms" />P. S.- Nina is not a virgin although she is very tight in her cunny. She may be useful at your conversations. Neither Kate nor Nina have ever been birched."<break time="100ms" />Capt. L.- "What a very interesting letter. Do you use the birch still, Madame?"<break time="100ms" />Madame.- "Certainly, when my young ladies deserve it."<break time="100ms" />Capt. Lemberg then insisted on having another fuck, for reading my father's letter of his interview with Madame Stewart had given him a cockstand.<break time="100ms" />So they had another bout and the Captain said he must leave. So I hastened from the keyhole and was apparently absorbed in my book when Madame and Captain entered the room.<break time="100ms" />The Captain kissed me as he bade me good-bye and thrust his tongue into my mouth as he did so, bidding me obey Madame in everything and all would be well.<break time="100ms" />He promised to take me for a day's holiday before the brig sailed if Madame would kindly consent.<break time="100ms" />I promised to endeavour to please Madame, and with another kiss he departed.<break time="100ms" />Madame Stewart then had a long talk with me and urged me to be candid and truthful in my answers to her questions. She asked: "Have you ever seen the slave men quite naked?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes."<break time="100ms" />"And the slave women?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes."<break time="100ms" />"And is it true that neither of them ever have any hair on their private parts?"<break time="100ms" />"Do you mean their cocks and cunts, Madame?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, my dear."<break time="100ms" />"Then it is not true, because I have seen short curly hair on those places, and in the case of the men, quite as much as was on my dear father's prick."<break time="100ms" />"Do you mean to say you have seen your father's prick?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, Madame, and felt it too!"
    </voice>
</speak>
