<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I fell on my knees and offered the devotions of my tongue at her shrine of love, then followed that up by a most salacious sucking, till she was content and graciously dismissed me, in order that I might be in immediate attendance on the Earl, who summoned me, and as his guests had just arrived, I lost no time in waiting on my master.<break time="100ms" />As of course the new arrivals were at once shown to the apartments destined for them, it afforded a capital opportunity for my Lord to order me to follow him to his dressing-room. The private instructions and directions I there received were, as the reader will see, slightly different to the suggestions thrown out by Lady Pomeroy.<break time="100ms" />To begin with, His Lordship expressed his strong opinion that the Lady was guilty of infidelity and that the partner of her misdemeanour was no other than his most intimate friend, the Duke of Dashwood.<break time="100ms" />Of course, I knew better than this, but as I was supposed to know nothing, I said nothing.<break time="100ms" />I think His Lordship tried hard to persuade himself that the case was such, in order to try and make some small excuse for his conduct with regard to the Duchess.<break time="100ms" />This, indeed, he hardly tried to conceal.<break time="100ms" />He was far from entertaining the same opinion of Monsieur Duroque and Mademoiselle Juliette, the valet and femme de chambre of the Duke and Duchess, which was held by the Countess. Indeed he represented that couple as the most valuable and trustworthy of their class, especially recommending Juliette to my notice. She and I would, it appeared, be the means of communication between the Duchess and himself in the way of verbal messages, notes or otherwise, and therefore it was highly desirable that I should cultivate the young woman's acquaintance.<break time="100ms" />"You have my full permission to fuck her, and make yourself as agreeable as possible. Then I can depend upon you both. There's nothing like that to ensure discretion in love matters," he added.<break time="100ms" />This, from the estimate I formed of her character and judging from her personal appearance, I considered I should not have much difficulty in doing.<break time="100ms" />My final instructions were not to fail in my attendance on my Lady and to report to him anything worthy of notice, particularly between her and the Duke.<break time="100ms" />This I faithfully promised to do, feeling pretty confident that I should notice nothing in that quarter, and mentally solving that any other eccentricities of my Lady as developed in respect to myself should not be considered worthy of notice.<break time="100ms" />So far, so good. And when my services to Her Ladyship were concluded, little did he guess in what some of those services consisted, or with what pleasure they were given.<break time="100ms" />I was to attend His Lordship in his dressing-room as he would most likely require me.<break time="100ms" />Upon this I bowed and withdrew, and my Lady having a good deal of company to entertain at dinner, subsequently retired rather fatigued about eleven o'clock. I was at liberty to retire and repaired at once to my Lord's dressing-room. There I waited until nearly twelve when, making his appearance, he demanded if anyone had called there with a note for him.<break time="100ms" />I was in the very act of replying in the negative when a tap was heard at the door and opening it, entered Juliette.<break time="100ms" />She hesitated a little on seeing me, but on the holding out of his hand as if expecting something, she placed in it a small note. On reading it, he nodded his head and smiled, saying to the bearer, "Your mistress is retiring, I suppose?"<break time="100ms" />On receiving an answer in the affirmative he farther asked whether his Grace was in bed or making any preparations for going to bed?<break time="100ms" />To this the clever soubrette replied that she had just seen Duroque, who had informed her that the Duke had taken a good deal of wine and seemed quite disposed for bed and would probably sleep soundly.<break time="100ms" />Upon receiving this information, my Lord dismissed me, as there was little possibility of my services being required that night in the espionage department, and it is to be presumed that he could manage anything else perfectly well without my assistance.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER V.<break time="100ms" />Tired as I was, I was undressing myself very leisurely but had nearly concluded that operation, when, lo! the door of my room quietly opened.<break time="100ms" />I never locked it for fear of being suddenly and secretly summoned.<break time="100ms" />Who the opener might be, of course, I could not tell, but I certainly did not expect to see Mademoiselle Juliette.<break time="100ms" />Putting her finger to her lips as a sign of silence and secrecy, she informed me that the Duke was up and evidently bound on some nocturnal ramble, and that she, being in the Duchess's room, Lord Pomeroy (it is to be presumed that he was there too) had begged her to awake me, and desire me to look after his Grace as there was every reason to fear that his destination was the apartment of the Countess.<break time="100ms" />"So don't sit there staring like an owl in the sunshine," exclaimed the impudent black-eyed girl. "Get up and put your breeches on and I'll help you."<break time="100ms" />Now I beg to assure my kind readers that at this moment I was in that particular costume in which Charles Lever describes his hero, Harry Lorrequer, being discovered when the bell rang to draw up the curtain at some private theatricals: to wit, a shirt and silk stockings.<break time="100ms" />Nothing more, upon my honour!<break time="100ms" />And I leave it to any to say whether it was a delicate operation for a modest young man to undergo to be assisted in pulling on his breeches by an impudent black-eyed soubrette.<break time="100ms" />The chastest Joseph that ever lived must have yielded to the temptation, and the stupidest gawky of a piously brought up lout must guess what followed.<break time="100ms" />I picked up my trousers from the chair upon which they had been flung as I undressed, and pretending to bungle as I bashfully attempted to hide John Thomas, who at the barest idea of a bit of anything fresh, was in his usual unruly state.<break time="100ms" />"La!" she exclaimed as her hand touched my projecting shirt, "is it anything that will bite?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes love, but not anything to hurt a darling like you. Won't you stroke his pretty head? It's a pet with all the ladies," I replied, pulling up my shirt and presenting Vade mecum of pleasure to her eyes.<break time="100ms" />Juliette at once flushed crimson as she covered her face at the sight, ejaculating: "How dare you, sir? I'll tell the Countess!"
    </voice>
</speak>
