<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />So I told her all my history, at which she was delighted and wanted to look at my cunny. I complied and she complimented me on my rich growth of hair.<break time="100ms" />She told me I must never let a man's prick enter my cunny without her consent being first obtained as she was desirous of shielding me from harm whilst I was under her roof; but she promised I should have all the coition that was good for me at proper times if I was diligent in my lessons.<break time="100ms" />You may be sure, dearest May, I was pleased with this intelligence and gave the required promise, thinking what a wise and kind schoolmistress she was.<break time="100ms" />I told her my father had fucked Nina and sent her to be my waiting-maid, and as we were very fond of each other I hoped she would allow us to be together as much as possible. She agreed to this saying she quite understood from my father's letter that it was his wish Nina should be with me. She made me repeat the tale I had told her about my taking Nina's place in the garden with my father and also the scene with him just before the brig sailed.<break time="100ms" />Nina was then called into the room and I told her that Madame Stewart was a very kindly lady and was willing we should occupy the same room like we did at home.<break time="100ms" />Poor Nina was profuse in her thanks and asked permission to kiss Madame's feet as a token of her gratitude.<break time="100ms" />Madame then told us to follow her upstairs, and she took us down a long passage with bedrooms opening from both sides of it. Here she pointed out a room and told us it was ours, but shared with another girl, the daughter of a wealthy baronet, Sir Thomas Moreton.<break time="100ms" />The room had three narrow beds in it, as Madame said her rule was for each pupil to have a bed of her own.<break time="100ms" />Madame then kissed me and told me to read the rules, a copy of which was fastened on the wall. As nearly as I can recollect they ran as follows:<break time="100ms" />Rule I - Every pupil, before retiring to rest, must strip naked and wash her person in every part.<break time="100ms" />Rule II - No pupil may examine her secret part before the mirror.<break time="100ms" />Rule III - No pupil must occupy a bed that is not her own.<break time="100ms" />N.B. -The penalty for breaking either of these rules is one dozen stripes with the birch.<break time="100ms" />When Nina heard me read these rules she said: "But how will Madame know if we break them?"<break time="100ms" />I replied: "Perhaps the other girl will tell tales on us! Or, perhaps she will be a nice girl and we can do as we like."<break time="100ms" />"Hush!" said Nina.<break time="100ms" />And Madame entered our room with Miss Moreton, saying, "Let me introduce you young ladies, as you will occupy this room together. Miss Moreton has been in this establishment for two years, so she knows all the girls and all the customs. You will soon get acquainted."<break time="100ms" />Madame withdrew and Miss Moreton asked my age and who my father was and we were soon chatting away glibly.<break time="100ms" />She said she was sixteen and should leave the school next holidays. Her name was Alice. She asked me if I had ever had a lover. I told her yes - Captain Lemberg - and that my father had sent me in his ship from home to England.<break time="100ms" />"Oh!" said Alice, "then you had a fine time together, I know! Please tell me all about it."<break time="100ms" />I said I would someday, but now I wanted to know all about the girls at school as I was never at school before.<break time="100ms" />Alice was surprised at this but I informed her my mother died when I was young and my father would not part with me, but preferred teaching me himself.<break time="100ms" />Alice told me Madame was very strict with the new girls until she had the chance to whip them a few times, after which she was very indulgent.<break time="100ms" />She told me that Saturday evening was punishment time and she had found out that gentlemen were admitted to Madame's room to peep at the girls punished. I enquired how she knew that. She said I had no doubt noticed that the grounds reached the water's edge.<break time="100ms" />Well, said Alice, one Saturday Madame sent me into the garden to get some fruit the gardener had forgotten and I saw two boats stop at the boat-house. I hid behind some bushes and saw four gentlemen, muffled up in cloaks, walk up the path which leads to the side entrance of the house. They were admitted by Mrs. White, the housekeeper. My curiosity was excited, so I quickly brought Madame the fruit and ran into her private room, and crept under the sofa to listen, thinking I would be certain to find out something. Nor was I wrong in my conjecture, for in a few minutes Mrs. White ushers in the four gentlemen and two of them sit down on the very sofa I was under. They talked to each other about the superior manner in which Madame's establishment was conducted. Two of them said they had daughters at present in the school and hoped they would have broken some of the rules that week.<break time="100ms" />This remark astonished me but my surprise was greater when by the voice of the next speaker I recognized my own father, Sir Thomas Moreton! He had visited me that very morning, gave me a supply of pocket money, wished me good-bye and said he was going back home at once; and here he was in the same house!<break time="100ms" />The other speaker was the rector of the parish church, the Hon. and Rev. Algernon Stanley. I knew his voice, for in the course of the conversation he was addressed as Stanley by my father.<break time="100ms" />Evidently the party of four were acquaintances, for they all chatted away on good terms.<break time="100ms" />In a few moments I heard my father's voice:<break time="100ms" />"Well, gentlemen, I will bet you five pounds that when you see the punishment this evening you will allow my daughter's bottom to be the plumpest and most exciting of any you shall see tonight!"<break time="100ms" />RECTOR.- "But suppose your daughter is not birched tonight?"<break time="100ms" />SIR MORETON.- "Then we will let the bet stand over till some other Saturday when she is flogged and we all are here."<break time="100ms" />Here, dear Kate, was a revelation to me! My father and three other gentlemen evidently were here for the purpose of witnessing the punishments about to be inflicted on the schoolgirls' bottoms! And my father must have seen my bottom on some previous occasion, or how could he make this bet! I knew I was to be punished that evening for my name was on the blacklist.<break time="100ms" />How should I escape from under the sofa and reach the schoolroom? For my ambition was fired by my father's words of admiration about my plump bottom and I wanted him to win that bet!<break time="100ms" />Fortunately for my intentions, Madame came into the room and invited the gentlemen to adjourn upstairs.<break time="100ms" />Directly they were gone I crept from my hiding place and ran up to the schoolroom by the back staircase and seated myself at the piano and commenced practicing my exercises.<break time="100ms" />In a short time the German governess, Fraulein Hoffman, came to me and said: "My dear you must prepare for punishment."<break time="100ms" />"Yes, Fraulein," I answered.
    </voice>
</speak>
