<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I now live happily surrounded by the sweet creatures, but I hear someone calling me from my private bed. I am in good condition, having abstained for three days. I fly to her, I jump into her arms and drown myself in a sea of bliss, in the arms of La Rose d' Amour.<break time="100ms" />THE END.<break time="100ms" />The Blue Vein.<break time="100ms" />A True Welsh Story.<break time="100ms" />Ye fun-loving fellows for comical tales,<break time="100ms" />Match this if you can, truly current in Wales;<break time="100ms" />The Bible so old, and the Testament new,<break time="100ms" />Having none more authentic, more faithful or true.<break time="100ms" />Four frisky maidens, young, handsome and plump,<break time="100ms" />Who could each crack a flea on their bubbies or rump,<break time="100ms" />Took it into their heads just to bother the tail<break time="100ms" />Of Ned Natty, a groom, so they jalap'd his ale.<break time="100ms" />Now Ned on red herrings that evening did sup,<break time="100ms" />So he drank every drop of the gripe-giving cup.<break time="100ms" />Soon his guts 'gan to grumble and shortly Ned found<break time="100ms" />His bowels give way, and his body unbound;<break time="100ms" />The buckskin's gay leather, by gallus confin'd,<break time="100ms" />Could not be cut down till indecently lined;<break time="100ms" />This made Neddy's Pego, accustomed to sprout,<break time="100ms" />Shrink into his belly, and turn up his snout.<break time="100ms" />The time this damn'd jalap in Ned's belly lurked,<break time="100ms" />No post horse like Neddy was ever so worked.<break time="100ms" />Three nights and three days he lay squirting in bed.<break time="100ms" />And neither could hold up his tail nor his head.<break time="100ms" />The storm at length ceasing, purg'd Ned 'gan to think<break time="100ms" />On some revenge sweet for this damnable stink;<break time="100ms" />"For I'm damn'd," exclaimed Ned, "if these bitches shan't find,<break time="100ms" />That I'm cabbaged before, tho' I'm loosened behind."<break time="100ms" />'Twas early one mom, exercising his steed,<break time="100ms" />Ned saw an old gipsy-hag crossing the mead.<break time="100ms" />Straight he hailed her and said: "Woman, where do you hie?"<break time="100ms" />She replied: "To tell fortunes of females hard by."<break time="100ms" />Now these females Ned found were his japlaping friends,<break time="100ms" />So he thought it the season to make them amends.<break time="100ms" />Then he brib'd for the cant and the gipsy's old clothes.<break time="100ms" />Thus equipped, said Ned: "Trick for trick: damn me, here goes!"<break time="100ms" />First Molly, the cook-maid, he took by the hand,<break time="100ms" />From her greasy palm told her what fortune had plann'd.<break time="100ms" />She was soon to be married, each year have a brat.<break time="100ms" />"Indeed," cried the cooky, "how can you tell that?"<break time="100ms" />"I'll tell you the number," said Ned, "let me see<break time="100ms" />The blue vein that's low plac'd 'twixt the navel and knee."<break time="100ms" />When she pulled up her clothes, Ned exclaimed: "I declare<break time="100ms" />Your blue vein I can't see, 'tis so cover'd with hair."<break time="100ms" />Next dairy-maid Dolly, of lechery full,<break time="100ms" />Swore she was then breeding, for she'd had the bull.<break time="100ms" />To the gipsy, said Doll: "Can you, old woman, tell.<break time="100ms" />Whether bull or cow-calf makes my belly so swell?"<break time="100ms" />When he viewed her blue vein, he said, "Doll by my troth,<break time="100ms" />You must find out two fathers, for you will have both."<break time="100ms" />For the squire and the curate, when heated with ale,<break time="100ms" />Doll Dairy had milk'd in her amorous pail.<break time="100ms" />Now Kitty the housemaid, so frisky and fair,<break time="100ms" />Who smelt none the sweeter for carrotty hair,<break time="100ms" />Presenting her palm to the gipsy so shrewd,<break time="100ms" />Was candidly told that her nature was lewd.<break time="100ms" />While feeling the vein near her gold-girded nick,<break time="100ms" />Kate played the old gipsy a slippery trick,<break time="100ms" />So that Kate, who had ne'er been consider'd a whore,<break time="100ms" />Was told she'd miscarried the morning before.<break time="100ms" />Then came Peggy the prude, who no bawdy could bear,<break time="100ms" />Yet would tickle the lap-dog while combing his hair.<break time="100ms" />"Is the butler my sweetheart," said Peggy, "sincere,<break time="100ms" />And shall we be married, pray, gipsy, this year?"<break time="100ms" />Quoth the gipsy: "You'll have him for better or worse,<break time="100ms" />But you'll find that his corkscrew is not worth a curse.<break time="100ms" />So when you are wed, 'twill be o'er the town talk'd:<break time="100ms" />There goes Peggy, a bottle, most damnably cork'd."<break time="100ms" />Now Ned, thus revenged, bid the maidens good-day,<break time="100ms" />But, curious, they ask'd him a moment to stay.<break time="100ms" />"For," said Molly the cook-maid, "we all long to see,<break time="100ms" />If you've a blue vein 'twixt the navel and knee."<break time="100ms" />Ned pull'd up his clothes, sir, when, to their surprise<break time="100ms" />They beheld his blue vein of a wonderful size.<break time="100ms" />The sight, Kate the carrotty, couldn't withstand;<break time="100ms" />She grasped the blue vein till it burst in her hand.<break time="100ms" />So alarm'd the prude Peggy fell into strong fits,<break time="100ms" />Frightened cook and Doll Dairy went out of their wits.<break time="100ms" />Then carrotty Kitty to gipsy Ned spoke:<break time="100ms" />"We'll each give a guinea to stifle the joke."<break time="100ms" />But Ned swore that no money should silence his tongue,<break time="100ms" />That the tale should be told in a mirth-moving song:<break time="100ms" />"As a caution," cry'd Ned, "to all Abigails frail<break time="100ms" />That there's more fun in f-g that jalaping ale."<break time="100ms" />The story like wildfire o'er Cambria spread,<break time="100ms" />From the borders of Chester to fam'd Holyhead.<break time="100ms" />In a vein of good humor, the vein that is blue,<break time="100ms" />Will long be remembered by me and by you;<break time="100ms" />Then fill a bright bumper to honour this vein,<break time="100ms" />A bumper of pleasure to badger all pain;<break time="100ms" />So hear us, celestials, gay mortals below!<break time="100ms" />Drink c - t, the blue vein, wherein floods of joy flow.<break time="100ms" />My Grandmother's Tale or May's Account of Her Introduction to the Art of Love.<break time="100ms" />From an unsophisticated Manuscript found amongst the old lady's papers, after her death, supposed to have been written about A.D. 1797.<break time="100ms" />Nina got up and said: "And so I did keep close to Jenny and I have watched over her, and I it was who saw Mr. Boatswain's prick slip in and out of her cunt, and I have been watching her while he did it! What could be closer watching than that, Mrs. Murphy?"<break time="100ms" />"But he has promised to marry me," called out Jenny.<break time="100ms" />"Yes," said the boatswain, "I swear I will, but she must let me have a fuck every day until we are ashore."<break time="100ms" />Mrs. Murphy was obliged to give her consent as she saw the mischief was done.
    </voice>
</speak>
