<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />And, according to the custom, I retired to my bedroom, took off my form, skirts and corset and returned to the school-room in chemise, drawers and stockings, which was the regulation dress for punishment.<break time="100ms" />Three other girls were to be punished; one rebelled from Fraulein's order and had to be dragged to her room and undressed.<break time="100ms" />At last we heard a bell ring and each of us, the culprits, was escorted by a governess to the room especially used and fitted up for punishment. It was lighted from the roof and had ladders, Berkeley horses and other appliances, such as ropes from the ceiling, rings in the floor and ceiling to which to fasten refractory culprits.<break time="100ms" />On this occasion we were made to slowly take off our drawers and then kneel on a kind of table with our heads low down and our posteriors sticking well out, with our hands and ankles tied securely.<break time="100ms" />Next, our offences were read out to us by Madame as follows:<break time="100ms" />"Margaret Stanley, your offence is as usual peeing in bed. I give you notice that I intend telling the worthy rector, your uncle, of this most disgusting habit of yours.<break time="100ms" />"Emmeline Chesterfield, your offence is greediness in eating up the cake you brought from home, and not sharing it with your schoolfellows.<break time="100ms" />"Constance Le Ray, you were discovered viewing your naked person in the glass; such vanity must be checked by the rod."<break time="100ms" />And then Madame read my name.<break time="100ms" />"Alice Moreton, your offence is one against decency. It is that of having received a letter from a lover whom you obstinately refuse to name or give any information as to how you have carried on this clandestine correspondence.<break time="100ms" />"I will read it aloud to you, Miss Alice Moreton, and I hope your cheeks will blush with shame as much as the cheeks of your bottom will blush under the rod, presently. This is the horrid letter:<break time="100ms" />My Dear Alice:<break time="100ms" />How I do long for another kiss on the lips of your pussey! The last I had was delicious! I dream of you every night and sometimes fancy I am in one of those high pews at church with your naked bottom sitting in my face, so I can kiss and suck your pussey! At other times in my dreams you catch hold of me by the cock and sing: "I will not let thee go, unless you fuck me!"<break time="100ms" />You cannot wonder at these dreams, sweetheart, for they are only repetitions of the facts of the day!<break time="100ms" />Give my love to Madame and asked her to notice the beauty of your cunny!<break time="100ms" />From your devoted love,<break time="100ms" />Henry.<break time="100ms" />Madame having finished the letter told the governesses to commence flogging us, and to strike as she called out, One, Two, Three.<break time="100ms" />They were stationed close to our heads so they had to strike over our backs to reach our bottoms, which were turned towards the end of the room at which Madame was seated on a dais, raised up six steps above the level of the floor.<break time="100ms" />I remembered the conversation of the gentlemen and the bet of my dear father, and I had no doubt they were watching us from some secret peep-hole, or were perhaps under the dais. So at every blow of the rod I writhed and twisted my posteriors as much as possible, in order to display all its beauties.<break time="100ms" />Margaret received fifty stripes, Emmeline sixty, Constance eighty, and I, the greatest offender, received one hundred which caused me to faint away.<break time="100ms" />What do you think of that, Kate dear?<break time="100ms" />I told her I thought it was a great shame and asked if the gentlemen ever came again.<break time="100ms" />Alice said no doubt they did although she had never had an opportunity of proving it; still, on Saturdays occasionally she had slipped into the garden and found boats moored to the boat-house. "However, my dear Katie, I have told you all I know, perhaps someday we will make more discoveries."<break time="100ms" />Kate said she warmly thanked Alice for telling her all the circumstances, and they kissed and went to bed.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER IV.<break time="100ms" />A LETTER FROM SUSEY.<break time="100ms" />About this time I received a letter from Susey, who, when the vacation commenced, went to her uncle in Scotland, and I may as well give her adventures in her own words:<break time="100ms" />My Darling May:<break time="100ms" />You remember the morning you took leave of me, I had to walk a mile to meet the coach. John Cox, my sister Jane's intended husband, came to start me off, and he carried my box on his shoulder as we walked across the fields and down to the crossroads where the coach takes up passengers. John told me he and Jane were soon to be married, and he said her belly was so big that it looked beautiful. I asked him what made it so big and he laughed as he said: "Why, Susey, because I have made a baby inside of it to be sure, you little goose!"<break time="100ms" />John also said that he was now obliged to fuck Jane behind, because her belly sticking out quite prevented his approaching the front.<break time="100ms" />He told me that he had a special message from Jane to me which was to be sure to do my pee just before getting on the coach, as I should have to ride for many hours and it was very painful to be obliged to hold your water.<break time="100ms" />"So," says John, "you had better squat down at once, and I can see your little cunt at the same time."<break time="100ms" />So I got close to some bushes and had a good pee and John had a good look at my cunny, and afterwards kissed and sucked it. Just then we heard the guard's horn announcing the near approach of the coach. So I had only time to give John's prick a farewell kiss, and then we hurried to the little ale-house at the crossroads.<break time="100ms" />The coach was full inside so I had to take an outside seat, and as there was no ladder I climbed up as well as I could. But I felt John's hand on my thigh as he stood beneath me.<break time="100ms" />When the coach started I looked at my fellow passengers and saw there were two gentlemen - one evidently a clergyman and the other, from remarks made, was his son, apparently about my own age. He asked me how far I was going and I replied, to Scotland.<break time="100ms" />"Have you never been there before?"<break time="100ms" />"No, sir," I replied.<break time="100ms" />"They have some very curious customs in Scotland," he said.<break time="100ms" />"What are they?" was my enquiry.<break time="100ms" />"The wearing of the kilt, for instance," said he.<break time="100ms" />"I do not know what a kilt is," was my reply.<break time="100ms" />"I will show you a picture of a Scotsman dressed in his kilt," said he, taking a book from his coat-pocket, and turning over the leaves, he showed me the picture of a tall man with naked knees and a short petticoat which he explained was the kilt.<break time="100ms" />I laughed at the odd figure in the picture and asked: "Do the Scotch girls and women dress like that too? If so, they must be cold."<break time="100ms" />"I wish they did," said he, "don't you, father?"<break time="100ms" />"Well, my son, it would have a very delightful effect, no doubt," said the clergyman.
    </voice>
</speak>
