<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Not before you've enjoyed it, however, and then you can give me a reference for gallantry as well, which may do me a great service. You're in for it, now, Miss Juliette," I said shoving her towards the bed, and in spite of her resistance, I soon had her clothes up and got between as beautiful a pair of thighs as I ever saw (she had no drawers on). It wanted only the electric touch of Mr. Pego to make her surrender all discretion. Ah, what an engagement we had, yard-arm to yard-arm, as Jack Tar would say! In fact I fired into her porthole till she surrendered and went off into a faint of ecstasy.<break time="100ms" />I shall never forget it, short as the fuck was, it was one of the most enjoyable I remember. Time was precious and she soon kissed and forgave my boldness, for, of course, it was only what the young lady had hoped and expected, and so I trust she was satisfied. But now I had to attend to business.<break time="100ms" />Finding that the Duke had indeed left his room, I proceeded in search of his Grace, not in the direction suggested by Juliette, but in quite another direction than towards my Lady Pomeroy's apartments, to where the under-servants slept. Comfortable rooms enough they were, too.<break time="100ms" />Now I was perfectly aware that Sophy and Lucy, the two housemaids, slept in one room. There I thought would be my mark, and there, sure enough, I found his Grace evidently on the most affectionate terms with the two young women, whose charms, though not of the most aristocratic class, were by no means to be despised; for he was paying them very liberally in advance, and so I had to remain and see whether he fell into the snare which sometimes awaits the bad paymasters who pay in advance, or I should make but a poor report to my employers. But, no, I had the gratification of witnessing through the medium of the keyhole (after rather a tedious observation, however, for were there not two young women?) that "there is honour among housemaids" and that his Grace of Dashwood did not get his money's worth it as not the fault of Sophy and Lucy!<break time="100ms" />(To be continued)<break time="100ms" />Nursery Rhymes.<break time="100ms" />There was a young bride of Antigua,<break time="100ms" />Whose husband had said: "Dear me, how big you are!"<break time="100ms" />Said the girl: "What damn'd rot,<break time="100ms" />Why, you've often felt my twot,<break time="100ms" />My legs and my arse and my figua!"<break time="100ms" />There once was a young man of Bulgaria,<break time="100ms" />Who once went to piss down an area,<break time="100ms" />Said Mary to cook:<break time="100ms" />"Oh, do come and look,<break time="100ms" />Did you ever see anything hairier?"<break time="100ms" />A Curious Fact for Naturalists.<break time="100ms" />The Editor has received the following from a subscriber:<break time="100ms" />"One often hears: 'No standing pricks this weather,' or, 'It's a difficult thing to find it, etc., during a severe winter,' but one intensely cold morning, just as we were getting up, my wife looking out of the window, drew my attention to a poor cat which had been out all night, expressing her sympathy for the poor beast. Presently I looked into the back yard for myself, when, lo! there were two cats, the feminine rolling on her back in the most approved fashion of cat-courtship, when the lady is agreeable to the gentleman's attentions. The thermometer at twenty-six degrees below freezing made no difficulty with him. He was on to her and into her in a moment, the only difference being that he, and in fact both of them, were more ready than on a warm summer's night, when we all know to our cost, the long preliminary caterwauling, scratching, etc., necessary to bring Mr. Tom to the point."<break time="100ms" />N.B.- I suppose scratching with cats has the same effect as birching on human beings.<break time="100ms" />The Lover's Kiss.<break time="100ms" />"Give me, my love; that billing kiss,<break time="100ms" />I taught you one delicious night,<break time="100ms" />When, turning epicures in delight,<break time="100ms" />We tried inventions of bliss.<break time="100ms" />Come gently steal my lips along,<break time="100ms" />And let your lips in murmurs move;<break time="100ms" />Ah, no - again - that kiss was wrong,<break time="100ms" />How can you be so dull, my love?"<break time="100ms" />"Cease, cease," the blushing girl replied,<break time="100ms" />And in her milky arms she caught me;<break time="100ms" />"How can you thus your pupil chide?<break time="100ms" />You know 'twas in the dark you taught me!"<break time="100ms" />Amenities of Leicester Square.<break time="100ms" />Girl to Ponce:- Go along, you bloody Mary Ann, and tighten your arse-hole with alum.<break time="100ms" />English Whore to French Woman:- Yah, you foreign bitches can only get a man by promising them a bottom-fuck!<break time="100ms" />French Woman:- Yes, I do let the English gentlemen have my arse-hole but my cunt I do keep for my husband.<break time="100ms" />TOASTS.<break time="100ms" />Gent:- The first four letters of the alphabet - A Big Cunt Daily. Lady:- In with it, and out with it, and God work his will with it.<break time="100ms" />
    </voice>
</speak>
