<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I interposed: "But the poor man must feel very cold here."<break time="100ms" />"Not at all," said the clergyman. "When I was at college as a young man, I wore that dress once at a fancy ball a found it very comfortable."<break time="100ms" />"Did you waltz in your kilt?" I asked.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, certainly, and why not?"<break time="100ms" />"Because I should think the whirling motion of dancing would cause your kilt to fly up and expose your..." and I stopped suddenly - laughing.<break time="100ms" />"Bottom, you were going to say, my dear! And where would be the harm in that? Ladies like to get a glimpse at man's bottom sometimes," said he.<break time="100ms" />"I'm sure they don't," I replied.<break time="100ms" />"Oh," said the son, "you think the ladies would rather look at him before than behind, eh? Well, what do you say at this picture," and he moved aside the kilt, which was a separate piece of paper, and showed me the Scotsman's prick in full erection.<break time="100ms" />"That's more in your way, my dear," said he. Then speaking to the clergyman, he said: "Father, this young lady, evidently, from her blushes, thinks a man's prick is more beautiful than his bottom."<break time="100ms" />"I am very glad to hear it," said he, "for it proves that her education has not been neglected and that she has learnt from her catechism: 'What is the chief end of man?'"<break time="100ms" />(To be continued)<break time="100ms" />Flunkeyania; or Belgravian Morals.<break time="100ms" />BY CHARLES.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER III.<break time="100ms" />That I have not ere this alluded to the Earl of Pomeroy, by whom I was specially engaged and to whom my services were due as well as to the Countess, must be attributed to the fact that almost immediately on my entering upon my duties, as recorded in this veracious narrative, His Lordship had joined a shooting-party at the Duke of Dashwood's, with whom the Earl was particularly intimate. Indeed, common report went so far as to say that His Lordship was still more intimate with the Duchess and that his Grace seemed to be perfectly indifferent on the subject.<break time="100ms" />Report as a general rule is a sad liar, but I strongly suspect (indeed, I had reason subsequently to know) that in this instance there was a good deal of truth in the rumour. Be that as it may, their Graces, accompanied by their daughter, the Lady Georgiana, were making a return visit to the Earl and Countess of Pomeroy, both of whom (very sensibly, as they might have need of my services) took care to make me acquainted with certain peculiarities of their noble guests.<break time="100ms" />As the Countess's remarks and suggestions were by far the more concise, I shall take them first in order.<break time="100ms" />She commenced by saying that she hated them all three. Father, mother and daughter. His Grace she described as a great heavy man, fond of good eating, hard drinking and riding, and that in matters pertaining to women he was a gross sensualist.<break time="100ms" />People had even been kind enough to couple her name with his, which she need not say was a base fabrication.<break time="100ms" />"Of course, my Lady," I ventured to interrupt.<break time="100ms" />She then went on to say that nothing would induce her to have anything to do with such a brute and that she would leave him to his liaisons with chambermaids and housemaids, whom he had the bad taste to prefer and to whom he conducted himself in such a style as to render him a nuisance in any country-house where he happened to be staying.<break time="100ms" />"On the last occasion when he was here," my Lady continued, "he had the impudence to make improper advances to my maid Justine, but I very soon put a stop to that. Indeed, I think that Justine herself had too much good taste to permit such a thing."<break time="100ms" />Here I may notice, en passant, that while I cordially subscribed to Justine's good taste as far as I was personally concerned, yet I had my private doubts about that young lady resisting temptation, especially if a heavy bribe were offered.<break time="100ms" />But I am interrupting the course of the Lady's remarks.<break time="100ms" />"If his Grace condescends to make paramours about the girls' bedrooms, generally it's no business of mine, as long as the housekeeper does not call my attention to the degrading circumstances. If the girls get into mischief I am sorry for them and they must leave, that is all."<break time="100ms" />This was all my Lady had to say about his Grace of Dashwood, and pretty much too, you'll say.<break time="100ms" />The Duchess came next in consideration. She, it appeared, was very handsome, though dark. This was quite true, her Grace presenting a marked contrast in appearance to my mistress, who, as I think I have before noticed, had bright brown hair. The head and front of her offence was, in Lady Pomeroy's opinion, not only that she, the Duchess, kept up a constant and most undisguised improper intimacy with the Earl, but had the effrontery to presume to be on the most affectionate terms with herself, the Countess.<break time="100ms" />"Just as if," continued that indignant lady, "she could fancy me so stupidly blind as not to perceive what was going on almost under my very nose. Why, the very fact of not concealing it is an insult in itself!"<break time="100ms" />And I must say that I quite agreed with her there.<break time="100ms" />As to the Lady Georgiana, my mistress considered her a handsome aristocratic young lady, who had nothing but the accident of her birth to justify her excessive haughtiness and who affected to consider all other people, and the male sex in particular, as so much dirt under her feet.<break time="100ms" />"That part of the business," continued my Lady, "I am convinced is all sheer nonsense, and in reality she is as sensually inclined, body and soul, as either her father or mother; and that will be found out someday, I feel perfectly certain."<break time="100ms" />As the Countess emphasized the last remarks, I could not help fancying that she glanced at me in a peculiar way.<break time="100ms" />Could it be that she had designed me as the instrument for lowering the pride of the haughty Lady Georgiana?<break time="100ms" />As to the characters of the gentleman's valet and the lady's femme de chambre, she merely prymised that they were a trifle worse than usual among persons in their situations. The rest I might find out for myself.<break time="100ms" />Then reminding me of my pledge of secrecy and the peculiar bond by which she had secured my fidelity, we forgot for a few minutes our relative positions as Lady and servant.<break time="100ms" />I had been standing respectfully in front of Her Ladyship, but at the conclusion of her explanatory remarks on the virtues and vices of her guests, she motioned me to draw closer as she wished to ascertain for herself if I had been wasting on others that which I ought to keep so as to be always in readiness to minister to her requirements.<break time="100ms" />Opening my trousers with her own delicate hands, she pulled out my rapidly rising organ of pleasure, and drawing back the foreskin, exclaimed: "Ah! you have been good! I can easily tell if the prepuce is all red that you have been obliging someone else within five hours. But this jewel is pale and I see no traces of recent excitement."
    </voice>
</speak>
