<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I was glad to learn we had to stop one hour for dinner, but was amused at Charley telling the chambermaid I was his wife, and so accompanying me up to the bedroom where he actually produced the pot from under the bed and made me sit down and do my pee, while he, lying at full length on the floor with his head close to my belly, watched the waterfall, as he called it.<break time="100ms" />Then he went down the stairs with me to the dinner-table, where we all did justice to the repast and had some good wine.<break time="100ms" />My companions were all very attentive to my wants and paid my score between them.<break time="100ms" />We then resumed our places in the coach as before, the coachman telling us we should have another four hours without stopping at all.<break time="100ms" />I noticed the Parson and Squire soon felt the efforts of their wine and good feeding, for they were soon sound asleep and snoring.<break time="100ms" />Charley said he was glad of that as now he could have me all to himself. So we first had a mutual prick-and-cunt-sucking match, each trying to hold back the juice of love as long as possible.<break time="100ms" />Next, sitting in Charley's lap with his tool ensconced in my cunny, I gently rode up and down, till he was compelled to withdraw and spend all over my belly.<break time="100ms" />We tired ourselves out with our varied loving encounters and at last we both fell asleep and were only aroused by the guard's horn announcing our arrival at our destination in Edinburgh.<break time="100ms" />My uncle was waiting for me at the inn and after thanking my travelling companions for their polite attentions, I took my uncle's arm and walked with him to his home.<break time="100ms" />My uncle kept talking all the way and enquired the name of my late companions.<break time="100ms" />I answered truthfully and he was pleased to think I had been in such good respectable society: "For," said he, "now a-days there are so many villains about that a young girl might be ruined before she knew her danger."<break time="100ms" />I mentally resolved to act the part of an innocent girl in dear uncle's presence and also I determined to put in practice the instructions of Charley Stuart, who, being a medical student, told me many things about a woman's private parts that I did not know before. One thing he told me was to get a lump of alum and push it up in my cunny and keep it then all night. It would act as an astringent and make it as tight as a virgin's cunny. And he also advised me to use a solution of alum in water with a female syringe as often during the day as was convenient.<break time="100ms" />Dear May, I advise you to do the same. When you send a messenger to buy the alum you can say it is for a sore throat or to use in dyeing - as it is used for both those purposes. Only, dear May, let me give you a caution - don't let the piece of alum be very large, for I will tell you what a fright I had.<break time="100ms" />One night I put a lump as large as a hen's egg up my cunny and in the morning I could not get it out! It had caused such a contraction of the inside folds of my cunny that I could barely insert the tip of my finger so you may imagine m dilemma. At last I thought: "Why of course, hot water will dissolve it." So I sat over the bidet for nearly an hour an bathed my poor cunny with warm water and it gradually dissolved some of the alum, and I was none the worse for my fright.<break time="100ms" />Well, to resume, Uncle and I came at last to his house which was a bookseller's shop with rooms for residence over the shop and a milliner's shop on one side, and a dressmaker's shop on the other, while opposite was an inn called "The Royal Standard," and next door to that was a board-school for young ladies.<break time="100ms" />I mention these details because Uncle called my attention to them, saying they were all his best customers.<break time="100ms" />On arriving at Uncle's house he took me upstairs and introduced me to the housekeeper, who was going to leave to get married the following week, and I was to take her place in Uncle's household.<break time="100ms" />She took me to a comfortable bedroom, and kissing me, praised my good looks and enquired if I would like a bath after my long journey.<break time="100ms" />I replied it was the one thing I was longing for. So she opened a door leading from my bedroom and showed me the bath, saying she would be back in half-an-hour to help me dress and get ready for dinner.<break time="100ms" />Oh, May, how I enjoyed that cold bath! I splashed and dashed the water all over my naked body and took the opportunity of removing the alum Charley had considerately slipped into my cunny in the coach, for, said he, who knows how soon you may have to pass for a virgin?<break time="100ms" />I had just finished my washing and stepped out of the bath and was seated on a stool drying myself when the door opened and in came the housekeeper, Jemima, and rushing up to me, exclaimed: "Oh, Miss Susan, please stand before this pier- glass for a moment!"<break time="100ms" />I did so and found it was as tall as myself and reflected my figure as large as life.<break time="100ms" />Jemima now began to rub me with a towel, all the time praising my skin, my back, my belly, and my thighs, in such a loud voice that I began to fancy she intended someone in the next room to hear. However, I kept my thoughts to myself and only said: "Make haste, Jemima, and help me dress for I want my supper so badly."<break time="100ms" />At last she was obliged to leave off her rubbings and she brought me a clean smock and petticoat which she helped to put on. Then I sat on a low stool and drew on clean white stockings; but Jemima would help put on a new pair of garters, which fastened with a silver clasp. I was so pleased with them that I jumped up and stood before the mirror to admire my garters, and of course had to raise my smock rather high to do so.<break time="100ms" />"Those garters are a present from your uncle," said Jemima, "you will not forget to thank him presently."<break time="100ms" />"Of course I shall thank him," I said.<break time="100ms" />Jemima now put on me a very low-necked blue frock.<break time="100ms" />"And this also is your uncle's present," said she.<break time="100ms" />"Oh; what a dear, kind uncle he is! How much I love him already," I replied.<break time="100ms" />"Well," said Jemima, "now go down to supper and tell him so."<break time="100ms" />On entering the room downstairs I found supper on the table and Uncle in his dressing-gown and slippers sitting by a bright fire.<break time="100ms" />(To be continued.)<break time="100ms" />Drawing-Room Passe Temps.<break time="100ms" />Gent - Have you tried the new medicated paper for the water-closet?<break time="100ms" />Lady - It is so dreadfully expensive.<break time="100ms" />Gent - No, really I know a place where you can buy six packets for ten-and-sixpence.<break time="100ms" />Lady - It is so deliciously soft, I cannot think how I could have put up with old newspapers.<break time="100ms" />Gent - May I send you half a dozen?<break time="100ms" />Lady - Thanks very much.<break time="100ms" />Gent - What a very disagreeable smell, I think our vis-a-vis must have farted.<break time="100ms" />Lady - No, it's that conceited thing on your left. I saw her cough behind her hand and pull her dress out.
    </voice>
</speak>
