<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />And, to use a low phrase, stand my ground like a brick.<break time="100ms" />Stop, a few minutes you are able to spare,<break time="100ms" />A bit of my mind I intend to lay bare;<break time="100ms" />Tho' with my way of thinking you'll p'raps not agree,<break time="100ms" />I'll tell you a few things I don't like to see.<break time="100ms" />I don't like to see vulgar girls in the town<break time="100ms" />Pull their clothes up, and stand to be goosed for a crown;<break time="100ms" />Nor a man with light trousers, of decency shorn,<break time="100ms" />Stop and talk to young ladies while having the horn.<break time="100ms" />I don't like to see women wear dirty smocks,<break time="100ms" />Nor a boy of fifteen laid' up with the pox;<break time="100ms" />And I don't like to see, it's a fact by my life—<break time="100ms" />A married man grinding another man's wife.<break time="100ms" />Nor I don't like to see - you'll not doubt it, I beg,<break time="100ms" />A large linseed poultice slip down a man's leg;<break time="100ms" />Nor a gray-headed sinner that's fond of a find.<break time="100ms" />When a girl under twelve he is able to grind.<break time="100ms" />In church, too, believe me, I don't like to see<break time="100ms" />A chap grope a girl while she sits on his knee;<break time="100ms" />Nor a lady whose visage is allover scabs,<break time="100ms" />Nor a young married lady troubled with crabs.<break time="100ms" />Nor I don't like to see, through it's really a lark,<break time="100ms" />A clergyman poking a girl in the park;<break time="100ms" />Nor a young lady, wishing to be thought discreet,<break time="100ms" />Looking in print-shops in Holywell Street.<break time="100ms" />I don't like to see, coming out of Cremorne,<break time="100ms" />A girl with her muslin much crumpled and torn;<break time="100ms" />Arm in arm with a fellow who's had the mishap,<break time="100ms" />To forget, when he shagged her, to button his flap.<break time="100ms" />Nor I don't like to see, though some think it a treat.<break time="100ms" />A young woman scratching her thing in the street;<break time="100ms" />And a boarding-school miss, with no sense in her pate.<break time="100ms" />Sit and chalk a man's tool on the back of her slate.<break time="100ms" />I don't like to see, in the bright face of the day,<break time="100ms" />A man stand and piss in the public highway;<break time="100ms" />Nor a Newfoundland dog, without any disguise.<break time="100ms" />Tied fast to a bitch not a quarter his size.<break time="100ms" />Nor I don't like to see, little sisters and brothers<break time="100ms" />Get playing at what they call fathers and mothers;<break time="100ms" />And I don't like to see, though at me you might scoff,<break time="100ms" />An old woman trying to toss herself off.<break time="100ms" />I don't like to see - it's a fact that I utter -<break time="100ms" />That nasty word — written up on a shutter:<break time="100ms" />And I don't like to see a man, drunk as an Earl.<break time="100ms" />Getting into a lamp-post thinking it's a girl.<break time="100ms" />I don't like to see, 'cause my feelings it shocks.<break time="100ms" />Two girls busy playing with each other's c-;<break time="100ms" />Nor I don't like to see, though it may be a whim.<break time="100ms" />A hole like a pit-mouth in place of a q-.<break time="100ms" />But I fear I'm encroaching too much on your time,<break time="100ms" />So I'll put an end to my quizzical rhyme;<break time="100ms" />Though with my way of taste you'll perhaps not agree,<break time="100ms" />I've told you the things I don't like to see.<break time="100ms" />A' That and A' That.<break time="100ms" />Put butter in my Donald's brose,<break time="100ms" />For weel does Donald fa that;<break time="100ms" />I love my Donald's tartan hose,<break time="100ms" />His naked prick, and a' that.<break time="100ms" />For a' that and a' that,<break time="100ms" />And twice as mickle as a' that:<break time="100ms" />The lassie get a skelpit gnat,<break time="100ms" />But wan the day for a' that.<break time="100ms" />For Donald swore a solemn oath,<break time="100ms" />By his first hairy gravat,<break time="100ms" />That he would fight the battle there,<break time="100ms" />And fuck the lass and a' that.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For a' that and a' that, etc.<break time="100ms" />His hairy cock, both side and wide,<break time="100ms" />Hung like a beggar's wallet;<break time="100ms" />His prick stood like a rolling-pin,<break time="100ms" />She nicker'dwhen she saw that.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For a' that and a' that, etc.<break time="100ms" />And then she turned up her cunt,<break time="100ms" />And she bade Donald claw that;<break time="100ms" />The devil's dizzen Donald drew,<break time="100ms" />And Donald gave her a' that.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For a' that and a' that, etc.<break time="100ms" />Facetiae.<break time="100ms" />Boss returning from the wars,<break time="100ms" />Wearied out with wounds and jars,<break time="100ms" />Tells the tale of blood and strife,<break time="100ms" />Woe and suffering to his wife;<break time="100ms" />"Never mind, dear Boss," she said,<break time="100ms" />"Your tool is safe - let's go to bed."<break time="100ms" />Through my brain strange musings ran,<break time="100ms" />Deeply pondering: "What is man?"<break time="100ms" />Still the question I resolve,<break time="100ms" />Philosophic doubts to solve:<break time="100ms" />"What is man? I'll tell you true,<break time="100ms" />He's but a pizzle's dirty spew!"<break time="100ms" />Lines for Valentines.<break time="100ms" />What a fate this poor girl in her lovers befalls,<break time="100ms" />A prickless old man, and a youth without balls.<break time="100ms" />Boast not that you have won a rich wife,<break time="100ms" />Length of tool, not of purse, makes the comfort of life.<break time="100ms" />Your prick is so useless for love's pleasant game,<break time="100ms" />Your nose long and hooky and fuck of such muck,<break time="100ms" />Go, stick then your nose in the cunt of your dame,<break time="100ms" />And you'll have at one go both a blow and a fuck.<break time="100ms" />To his bed he went sleepy and drunk, oh, very!<break time="100ms" />He wanted to piss, felt about for the jerry,<break time="100ms" />Took up by mischance a big mousetrap instead,<break time="100ms" />Which snapped off, alas! his old gentleman's head!<break time="100ms" />Advertisements.<break time="100ms" />To Be Sold—A Bargain<break time="100ms" />A Maidenhead<break time="100ms" />(Slightly Soiled)<break time="100ms" />The owner being about to get married is willing to sell the above by auction. Further particulars will be announced in the next number of THE PEARL.<break time="100ms" />To the Lovers of Good Things.<break time="100ms" />Messrs. Rogers, Rosencrantz and Co., Importers of Foreign Females, and other Curiosities, beg to announce the arrival of a cargo per steamship Orient, direct from Zululand, of young girls of all ages from 8 to 16 years of age, all genuine virgins which will be offered for selection any time next' week. Terms - C.O.D.<break time="100ms" />N.B. - As this class of goods is extremely perishable buyers must remove their purchases at their own risk.
    </voice>
</speak>
