<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Volume 17
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />My Grandmother's Tale or May's Account of Her Introduction to the Art of Love.<break time="100ms" />From an unsophisticated Manuscript found amongst the old lady's papers, after her death, supposed to have been written about A.D. 1797.<break time="100ms" />"My dear father," said the young man, "we have the back part of the coach to ourselves and the guard is sitting with the coachman, so we are quite private here. Would it not be a good opportunity for letting this young lady look at your reverend prick?"<break time="100ms" />"Most certainly, my son," replied the clergyman, unbuttoning his trousers. "I am always ready to please the ladies."<break time="100ms" />So he pulled out his noble tool, fondly stroking it. "There, Miss, there is something for a man to be proud of, and I am proud to have such a father."<break time="100ms" />"I hope you may have just such another someday," I said.<break time="100ms" />"Thank you, my dear," said he, "I will show you what I have at present."<break time="100ms" />And he exhibited his own prick. I told him it was as big as he had any reason to expect, and he quite agreed with me and then regretted the fact that our being outside the coach would prevent his father and himself from looking at anything I would like to show them. "But," continued he, "the coach will stop to change horses in a few minutes' time, and then the passengers generally get down and go inside the inn for half-an-hour for refreshments. But my father, the rector, is well known to the landlord and we will ask for a private room and take our refreshments there; and then, Miss Susan, you will have the wished-for opportunity."<break time="100ms" />By the time he had finished speaking we arrived at the Royal George, and the parson and his son helped me down from the coach, and I soon found myself in an upstairs parlour with them. They told me their journey terminated there, as they had to drive in a gig to their home, five miles distant, and they both begged me to lose no time.<break time="100ms" />I replied: "I am in your hands, gentlemen! Only don't harm me."<break time="100ms" />They promised they would not, and the father then raised my clothes, called his son's attention to my white thighs and the pouting lips of my cunt.<break time="100ms" />Both father and son kissed and sucked it for a few minutes and then the father insisted on his son having a fuck before he had one.<break time="100ms" />By the time each had finished, the horn blew the warning to get ready. So hastily swallowing a glass of wine, I arranged my clothes and bade them good-bye.<break time="100ms" />They accompanied me to the coach and this time I was able to get inside, there being one place vacant, and the parson kindly paying the difference in fare.<break time="100ms" />With mutual farewells the coach started again and I looked at my fellow passengers and found one who appeared young, the other two being grey-haired gentlemen.<break time="100ms" />They all accosted me very politely and hoped we should have a pleasant journey together.<break time="100ms" />The young man enquired how far I was going and when I replied to Edinburgh, he expressed his pleasure that we should be going to the same city.<break time="100ms" />"What a fortunate circumstance," said he, "that you were not travelling by this coach last week."<break time="100ms" />"How so?"<break time="100ms" />"Because the notorious Dick Turpin and his gang stopped the coach just a little way from here and robbed the passengers, and used the ladies very cruelly."<break time="100ms" />"Oh! how you frighten me! Do tell me all about it," said I. The elderly gentleman opposite now spoke and said:<break time="100ms" />"I can give you the correct account, for I was one of the passengers and one of the victims; I may say."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, do tell me if there is any danger of Dick Turpin coming again today?" I asked.<break time="100ms" />"Not the slightest, " said the old gentleman, "and that is the reason why I am travelling again so soon. Besides, I am armed with my horse-pistols."<break time="100ms" />"Oh," said I, "don't show them to me, I am so terribly frightened! But tell me about the villains."<break time="100ms" />The old gentleman continued: "It was just about three in the afternoon when, as we were bowling along, as we are now, I heard several horsemen ride up on each side of the coach and call to the coachman to stop or he should be shot. And two shots were fired at him, and one wounded him, the other broke the lamp.<break time="100ms" />"Of course the coach was stopped and the robbers then called: 'Stand out and deliver your money and valuables, or you are all dead men.'<break time="100ms" />"There must have been ten or twelve men - some on foot, and some on horseback.<break time="100ms" />"I should mention that the inside of the coach was occupied by some girls going to York to school. There were four besides their mistress and outside there were four more girls - that makes nine ladies, and there were six men passengers besides the coachman and guard.<break time="100ms" />"I should say that two of the misses were my grandchildren, aged about thirteen and fourteen.<break time="100ms" />"Well, the villains first looked inside the coach and made the madame give up her gold watch and rings, then they made us men come down and stand in the road while they searched our pockets, one man standing with the muzzle of a pistol pressed close to my forehead while he searched my pockets.<break time="100ms" />"When this was done, they abused us for giving them so much trouble for so little money and declared they would be revenged on the women for it.<break time="100ms" />"I begged them to spare my poor grandchildren.<break time="100ms" />"'Point them out,' said one of the villains.<break time="100ms" />"I did so, thinking that he was going to listen to my requests, but no; to my surprise he tied their hands behind them and then lifted up their clothes and threw them over their heads, exposing their bodies from the waist downwards!<break time="100ms" />"I rushed forward to replace their clothing when two of the villains caught hold of me and tied my hands behind my back, and then to my indignation, they actually cut open my breeches in front and pulled out my prick."<break time="100ms" />"Horrible!" I exclaimed.<break time="100ms" />"Monstrous," said the young man.<break time="100ms" />"Yes," continued the old man, "and that is not all. There is something more horrible to tell."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, do tell," said I.<break time="100ms" />"Pray," said the young man, "continue."<break time="100ms" />"Well, the villains made me kneel down and kiss the slits of my two granddaughters and made me suck them and push in my tongue! Then they uncovered the poor girls' faces, and tying their clothes tight under their arms, ordered them to suck my cock! In vain they and I protested. A loaded pistol fired off close to our ears was the warning of what our fate should be if we disobeyed. So first one and then the other dear girl went through the task. And the villains made me say the sucking was pleasant!"<break time="100ms" />"And what did you say?"<break time="100ms" />"Of course I told the truth, that the sucking gave me pleasure."<break time="100ms" />"And what became of the other men who were passengers?"
    </voice>
</speak>
