<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Lady - I desire an article inserted and should like you to put it in for me.<break time="100ms" />Editor - Certainly, with pleasure, if you will first show it to me, so that I may see what it is like.<break time="100ms" />Lady - I wish a situation as a wet nurse and should like to get a good healthy boy.<break time="100ms" />(Editor prepares this advertisement and shows it to the Lady, who likes the look of it and wishes it to be put in at once, and asks the price.)<break time="100ms" />Editor - How often shall you want it put in?<break time="100ms" />Lady - Well, I cannot tell! That will depend whether it is taken or not; but what will you charge for inserting it three times?<break time="100ms" />Editor - One dollar for putting it in three times.<break time="100ms" />Lady - Oh, how dear! You might do it for me for less!<break time="100ms" />Editor - No, Madame, we have so many ladies to oblige, that is our lowest price for inserting three times such an article as you ask for.<break time="100ms" />Lady - Well, suppose you do not get me a baby in three times, how much will you charge me for three times more?<break time="100ms" />Editor - Why Madame, if you can manage to keep the affair standing after that, for one dollar more I will put it in as often as you like, till I get you a child; that is, of course, provided the ink continues to flow.<break time="100ms" />Flunkeyania; or Belgravian Morals.<break time="100ms" />BY CHARLES.<break time="100ms" />CHAPTER VI.<break time="100ms" />Honour amongst maid-servants, you would have thought so, had you but seen how Sophy and Lucy, after receiving the Duke's retaining fee, worked for his pleasure in hopes of getting a refresher when he retired.<break time="100ms" />Nor were their labours in vain. Yet, I verily believe he had stimulated himself by a dose of tincture of cantharides, phosphodyne, or something of that sort, for he was a perfect goat.<break time="100ms" />Lucy in her nightdress was sitting on the edge of the bed with a finger between her thighs, evidently trying to impress upon his Grace the necessity of another bit of flimsy for her bedfellow; and from what I could only partially hear, he made that depend on how they pleased him first.<break time="100ms" />Although I could not hear all that was said, what I saw will enable me to supply the dialogue.<break time="100ms" />Lucy now proceeded to business by suddenly throwing the bedclothes off Sophy, whose chemise she turned up, and began to smack her lily-white bum before she could very well help herself.<break time="100ms" />I could see the red marks flush on her tender skin at every slap. This seemed greatly to please the Duke, who did his best to prevent the helpless girl from getting up.<break time="100ms" />Sophy struggled desperately, looking both flushed and cross but afraid to call out for fear of making too much noise.<break time="100ms" />His Grace had gone on his expedition in slippers and dressing-gown. So when this slapping was over; he slipped off his only coverings, and dropping the slippers, had nothing but his stockings on as he jumped on the bed between the two girls, his great affair as stiff and ready as possible.<break time="100ms" />Sophy was the first to take possession of that red-headed prize. She was evidently excited by the rough usage of her posteriors and begged to be comforted at once.<break time="100ms" />"So you shall, my dear," said the Duke, "and let your bedfellow straddle over my face, that I can tickle her up with my tongue whilst you ride my cock."<break time="100ms" />This was a luscious sight and raised all my own lustful feelings quite to burst point, till, as they all seemed to come together, I actually emitted in my breeches.<break time="100ms" />After this, each of them sucked his prick and balls by turn, till he mounted Lucy and fucked her like a satyr; Sophy all the while kissing and fondling his testicles and working one finger in his arse-hole to excite him to the utmost.<break time="100ms" />Even this did not exhaust him, for he gamahuched them by turns, and even did the "La Rose" trick of the French women, by frigging their bottoms with his long tongue, which seemed to drive them almost mad. They got his prick in a glorious state again, and at his request, both knelt down on hands and knees, presenting their bottoms to him. What a surprise I had, for he buried that great bursting prick of his in each arse-hole in turn, and then for a change, in their cunts. He made it last awfully long and I could see plainly by their wriggles of delight and the subdued ejaculations of pleasure which I heard, such as: "How nice - lovely - delicious. How you do make me come. Oh, do spend into me," etc., as each girl was also busy frigging herself as well.<break time="100ms" />At last it was over. I saw him taking the second fiver out of his dressing-gown. So, turning from the keyhole, I retraced my steps. Everyone to his taste, I reflected, as I quickly and cautiously descended the stairs on my homeward journey. And yet again, I thought, a man might do worse; and if I had not been so exceptionally fortunate, as I am, I might be very glad of two such buxom lasses as Sophy and Lucy.<break time="100ms" />These reflections brought me to the door of the Duchess of Dashwood (quite in another part of the house from that of the Duke) and here I essayed to make my knocking with my knuckles.<break time="100ms" />But whether Juliette was in the arms of Morpheus or of one of our young footmen, or of M. Duroque, or of all three, I cannot tell; but at any rate, I could not obtain admittance, until I heard the bolt withdrawn and the voice of the Earl, my master, telling me to come in.<break time="100ms" />I entered accordingly and made a full report of what I had seen, much to the pretended surprise of His Lordship, but not at all to the surprise of the Duchess, who declared with considerable emphasis, "It was just like him!"<break time="100ms" />She, then totally oblivious of my presence, as it seemed and of her own dishabille, which might be charming but was somewhat remarkable for her own peculiar situation, that is to say, a married woman comfortably in bed with another woman's husband - totally forgetful of all these trifles as it seemed - she began to expatiate upon the enormities perpetrated by his Grace of Dashwood.<break time="100ms" />Of the valuable impulse he had given to the population in his neighbourhood through the medium of the farmers' daughters and pretty cottage-girls; that she never could keep a decent-looking chamber-maid or housemaid in the castle - that in London he was worse, if possible - that she suspected him of improper conduct with Mademoiselle Juliette, the best soubrette she ever had, and was getting on at a great rate, when the Earl politely reminded her that my presence in the room was no longer required and suggested that I should be allowed to retire, which her Grace cordially agreed to, commenting at the same time upon my manners and general appearance in a style which I may be forgiven for not repeating, but which suggested my having found favour in her eyes.<break time="100ms" />As the reader may believe, I took particularly good care to report to my Lady on the following morning all that I had seen regarding the Duke and Duchess.
    </voice>
</speak>
