<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The other elderly-looking gentleman said: "Well, Squire Johnson you have known me for years as the parson of the parish and my name is the Rev. Mr. Scarlett and I expect you to take my oath against any other person's."<break time="100ms" />The young gentleman now spoke: "Oh, I am a medical student going home from college. My name is Charley Stuart and I am sure to fall in love with every pretty girl I see, especially such an angel as this!" giving me a most loving look.<break time="100ms" />"Now, then," said Squire Johnson, "if you, Miss, will give us your name we will proceed."<break time="100ms" />I replied: "My name is Susan Gardiner and I charge Parson Scarlett and Charley Stuart with touching my naked body."<break time="100ms" />Squire Johnson wrote this down in his pocket-book and then said: "Miss Susan, you say you charge these gentlemen with an indecent assault! Please state the particulars."<break time="100ms" />I did so, saying the Parson put his hand on my bottom, "when the coach by that sudden jerk threw me into your arms and you kissed me. The other gentleman, called Charley Stuart, put one of his hands between my thighs, very high up, at the same time."<break time="100ms" />Squire Johnson.- "Now Parson, what is your reply to those charges?"<break time="100ms" />Parson.- "Oh, I saw the young lady's petticoats disarranged and I tried to replace them."<break time="100ms" />Squire J.- "And you, Charley Stuart?"<break time="100ms" />CHARLEY.- "Oh, I plead guilty and promise not to do it again until the next time."<break time="100ms" />Squire J.- "Gentlemen, from your replies I am quite satisfied that you are both guilty of the offence charged against you; and my sentence is that you each pay Miss Susan immediately the sum of half-a-crown, that you each beg her pardon and that you each offer to show her your pricks. Come, Parson, you first, out of respect of your cloth, as you are in holy orders."<break time="100ms" />Parson.- "Never did I hear a more impartial and righteous sentence."<break time="100ms" />So he paid me the half-crown at once and pulled out his tool; it was short and thick with an enormous red head.<break time="100ms" />Charley said: "See Miss Susan, I offer you this half-crown for the sweet kisses you gave me. Here, balanced on the head of my prick and it is cheap enough."<break time="100ms" />And Squire J.- "Now, Miss Susan, I offer you this half-crown, and as it is now four o'clock, before the coach will stop, I propose that you should give us some entertainment - and answer all our questions truthfully."<break time="100ms" />Parson.- "Also obey us in all our wishes."<break time="100ms" />Charley.- "And Miss Susan, if you do, you shall be paid a guinea from me."<break time="100ms" />Squire.- "And another from me."<break time="100ms" />Parson.- "And I will give another, that will make three golden guineas! Think, what a lot of money!"<break time="100ms" />Dear May, do not blame me for acceding to their wishes. I knew I was completely in their power, and then the presents of the guineas! It seemed riches indeed to me, who had never possessed more than a few shillings at one time in my life.<break time="100ms" />So I dried my tears and taking up the three half-crowns, said: "Do not harm me, good gentlemen! I will agree to your proposals and trust to your honour, as I am only a girl entirely at your mercy, but I should vastly like three guineas."<break time="100ms" />"A very sensible good girl," said the Parson.<break time="100ms" />"You are an angel," said Charley.<break time="100ms" />Parson.- "I will ask Miss Susan if she has any hair on her little slit?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes," I replied.<break time="100ms" />Squire.- "What colour?"<break time="100ms" />"Light red."<break time="100ms" />"Did you ever allow a man to look at your cunt?" said Charley.<break time="100ms" />"Yes."<break time="100ms" />Parson.- "And suck it, I'll be bound?"<break time="100ms" />Charley. - " And kiss it?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes."<break time="100ms" />Squire.- "Then Miss Susan shall be laid across the laps of two of us, and the other shall kiss and suck her pretty cunny."<break time="100ms" />"Agreed!" they all cried.<break time="100ms" />And this was done in succession, until all three had had their turn. To do this my petticoats and smock were raised so as to expose to view my thighs and belly. Then each gentleman knelt on the floor of the coach and kissed and sucked my cunny.<break time="100ms" />The Parson asked: "How much time, Squire, do we have before the coach stops?"<break time="100ms" />"Three hours."<break time="100ms" />The Parson then said: "That will be ample time for Miss Susan to strip herself naked, and to let us enjoy looking at her charms in the nude state."<break time="100ms" />"Yes," said the Squire, "plenty of time."<break time="100ms" />I replied that I should take cold.<break time="100ms" />"No, I'll take care of that," said Charley. "I will keep you warm. I will give you brandy from this bottle."<break time="100ms" />"But I shall be seen by passers-by," again I objected.<break time="100ms" />But the Parson and Squire agreed to keep the curtain of the coach-windows drawn down, sufficient to prevent all chance of anyone seeing me.<break time="100ms" />"Now," said Charley, "I will be your lady's-maid and disrobe you."<break time="100ms" />He then took off my bonnet and shawl, then my frock stays and petticoats. I begged hard to be allowed to retain my smock, but all in vain as the Parson said it would interfere with the full view of my naked body; besides, he said: "Eve was naked in the Garden of Eden, so there's Scripture for you, Miss Susan."<break time="100ms" />I was praised for the whiteness and firmness of my skin, and my shape was much admired.<break time="100ms" />Two of them sat on one seat of the coach and one on the other, with their knees as close to one another as possible, and on this broad lap I was laid and rolled over and over, their hands roving over my back, shoulders and bosom, belly and bottom, in succession, one pointing out to the other some attraction that he specially admired.<break time="100ms" />My mouth and both hands were next occupied with three pricks at once, and I was obliged to change from one to the other, until each had his prick sucked.<break time="100ms" />Next I was seated between two of them on the edge of the seat. Then they raised my legs higher than my head, and told me to jut my belly well forward. This had the effect of exposing my bottom-hole as well as my cunny. Then one gentleman would fuck me in this position and then the others would change places, until all three had fucked me. But I will say, they all withdrew their pricks before spending and spouted their sperm over my belly, as it was solemnly promised by them all that there should be no risk of getting me with a child.<break time="100ms" />By the time they managed to get a couple of fucks each, the time came for me to resume my clothing, which I was thankful to do. And I was only decently dressed when the guard's horn warned us the coach was about to stop.
    </voice>
</speak>
