<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Oh, they were made to suck the slits of the schoolgirls and to submit to have their pricks sucked in turn."<break time="100ms" />"And how did the school-madame fare?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, the villains grossly insulted her by examining her cunt, and telling her she was too old to allow them to give her any pleasure of that kind, so they cut a bunch of twigs from the bushes and forced her on all fours, bared her backside and gave her a good flogging."<break time="100ms" />"Do you mean to state that all these outrages took place on the high-turnpike road?"<break time="100ms" />"Well, yes, that is to say, close to it, for there was a piece of turf or grass-land rather wide at the side of the road at this place. In fact, there were a few trees and bushes growing there."<break time="100ms" />"Did no person pass in travelling along the road, while this took place, for it must have taken some time?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, it took an hour or more, but a farmer with his wife riding behind on a pillion, and one wagon loaded with hay; accompanied by the wagoner, were all that passed by during the time. Part of the hay was unloaded to serve for beds on which to extend the unfortunate lady-passengers and the farmer was compelled to fuck his wife in public."<break time="100ms" />"Did Dick Turpin take part in these outrages?"<break time="100ms" />"No, he told his men to fuck any way they took a fancy to, but he kept watch most of the time and gave the necessary directions to his men so that several of them kept watch in turn, while the others committed these outrages on their victims."<break time="100ms" />"Do you mean to say that the ten schoolgirls were all raped and their maidenheads taken?"<break time="100ms" />"Certainly; if they had any to lose! They were all fucked before my eyes."<break time="100ms" />"How did it all end?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, after a while Captain Dick said: 'That's enough for this time, boys. Mount and away!' And so they rode off leaving all the victims tied and bound until some passer-by should come and relieve them. Of course we called for help directly after our tormentors had left us and in half-an-hour some foot passengers and also the returning mail-coach came by and released our bonds and we all made the best of our ways to our destinations."<break time="100ms" />The young man now spoke. "It is all quite true, Miss, I assure you; I was one of the passengers by the down-mail on that occasion and I saw the condition of the ten schoolgirls as described by our friend here. They were all tied to trees with their arms behind them, and their clothing raised and tied close to their shoulders so as to expose their bellies and all below.<break time="100ms" />"I could not help being delighted with the sight, although of course I pitied the poor things, and I delayed helping to release them in order to have a good view of their naked charms. I was much amused at the remarks of a worthy tradesman and his wife who were also looking at those schoolgirls. The wife spoke sharply: 'Well, Mr. Jones, I am ashamed of you to stand staring like a stuck pig at those naked shameless young hussies. Why don't they put their dresses down?'<break time="100ms" />"'Well, my dear,' said her husband, 'they have their hands tied behind their backs and can't help themselves, and as to my looking at them, my excuse is I never saw such a sight before! Why, there are ten naked bellies for me to look at and four have hardly any hair on their slits and the others all have black hair on them, but one, and she...'<break time="100ms" />"Here his wife angrily interposed: 'You have made good use of your eyes for these few minutes, Mr. Jones; I must say I am astonished at you, a married man and the father of six girls and four boys, so to demean yourself! Why don't you shut your eyes until this disgraceful exhibition is over?'<break time="100ms" />"'No, Mrs. Jones, I am not going to close my eyes! I may be called as a witness against the villains if ever they are caught, and if I shut my eyes how am I to describe to the jury the cruel state in which the girls are left?'<break time="100ms" />"'Well,' said his wife, 'had you not better try and catch those villains?'<break time="100ms" />"'No, my dear, my duty does not lie in that direction.'<break time="100ms" />"'Nor your inclination either,' retorted his wife, 'for evidently you prefer the safer course of feasting your eyes on these poor girls' nakedness.'<break time="100ms" />"'Well, my dear, you know I am always delighted to look at yours but you so seldom allow me to do so.'<break time="100ms" />'"I should think not, indeed,' said Mrs. Jones, 'and that reminds me that last Sunday I saw you take two of our daughters on your knee and I think you had your hands under their clothes!'<break time="100ms" />"'Nonsense! Mrs. Jones, only a little play and romping, for my girls are very fond of their old father; besides it is a father's duty to see if his girls' underclothes are clean and in the fashion.'<break time="100ms" />"'Now, Mr. Jones, do be quiet. What right has a man to be troubling himself about his girls' clothing?'<break time="100ms" />"'Why what I buy and pay for with my own money I have the right to examine, and you know I should never have married you if I had not examined you first!'<break time="100ms" />"'For shame, Mr. Jones, to speak about that here in the open air where anyone might overhear you!'<break time="100ms" />"'Now Mary Ann, dear, will you untie these poor girls' clothes from their necks and help me undo their hands?'<break time="100ms" />"So I then offered my assistance to several of the girls and helped to put their clothing down over their bellies, taking care to touch much of their naked bodies in doing so, and getting my hand on each of their bellies in the performance of this duty.<break time="100ms" />"I ought to mention that the place where these outrages took place was a kind of valley between two hills, and where a house was not in sight for many miles. It was up a lane through this valley that the highway-men came on horseback to do their unlawful work, and when they had completed it they went away down the valley again."<break time="100ms" />At this moment as the young man finished his account the coach gave a lurch forward, probably from the coachman suddenly whipping up the horses; however, I found myself flung against the elderly man sitting opposite me and he caught me firmly in his arms and kissed me, saying: "God bless me, Miss, don't be frightened, come to my arms, I'll take care of you."<break time="100ms" />I replied I could not help it and then felt a hand passing up my thighs from behind, and another hand patting my bottom.<break time="100ms" />I cried out: "Oh, this conduct is most shameful gentlemen, do leave a poor girl alone!"<break time="100ms" />"Why, what's the matter, my dear?" said the young man.<break time="100ms" />"Nobody is touching you," growled the old gentleman.<break time="100ms" />"Well, my dear, I am kissing you," said the one on whom I had been thrown.<break time="100ms" />"I know that," I replied, "but more than that has been done to me."<break time="100ms" />"Well," said he, "I am a magistrate and my name is Squire Johnson, and if you will sit by my side and make your complaint you shall have justice done to you."
    </voice>
</speak>
