<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Gent - You must forgive me but, do you know, I thought at first it was you.<break time="100ms" />Lady - Oh, you naughty satirical man.<break time="100ms" />Gent - What a troublesome complaint is piles!<break time="100ms" />Lady - Yes, poor mama and my sisters have them shockingly.<break time="100ms" />Gent - And you, come now, confess.<break time="100ms" />Lady - No, indeed, and indeed.<break time="100ms" />Gent - Not a little bit?<break time="100ms" />Lady - No, not a bit.<break time="100ms" />Gent - Do you find that your bowels act with regularity?<break time="100ms" />Lady - Quite so, thank you for your kind enquiries, I go punctually every ten days or so.<break time="100ms" />Gent - Now that is very naughty of you, you ought to go every morning.<break time="100ms" />Lady - But the seat is so dreadfully cold to sit down on in this nasty weather.<break time="100ms" />Gent - Might I warm it for you?<break time="100ms" />Lady - What would mama say?<break time="100ms" />(Here you see, the conversation is gliding into a flirtation and should be diverted unless you have honourable intentions. If you have, it may continue as follows:)<break time="100ms" />Gent - Your mama would say we were two cozy dicky birds to bolt ourselves into the water-closet.<break time="100ms" />Lady - But you would go away after you had warmed the seat, would you not, because I might make a little noise?<break time="100ms" />Gent - If it played a pretty tune I would love it.<break time="100ms" />Lady - And would you rumple the paper for me?<break time="100ms" />Gent - All day long.<break time="100ms" />Lady - For little me only and for no one else?<break time="100ms" />Gent - For no one but you would I rumple a particle of paper. Is it not extraordinary that there are no public urinals for ladies?<break time="100ms" />Lady - You men would be always standing about the doors,<break time="100ms" />Gent - But you ought to have them built like ours, you know, with the trough projecting a little further.<break time="100ms" />Lady - Butter-boat fashion, how very nice.<break time="100ms" />The Bankrupt Bawd.<break time="100ms" />Tune - "Vicar of Bray."<break time="100ms" />Near Jermyn Street a bawd did trade<break time="100ms" />In credit, style and splendour,<break time="100ms" />Well known to every high-bred blade,<break time="100ms" />And those of doubtful gender.<break time="100ms" />How nature once, in marring mood,<break time="100ms" />Her body formed, I'll tell ye,<break time="100ms" />Upon her back a swelling stood,<break time="100ms" />To mock her barren belly.<break time="100ms" />CHORUS:<break time="100ms" />For some succeed and others fail<break time="100ms" />That into commerce enter.<break time="100ms" />So few are chaste and many frail<break time="100ms" />In this great trading center.<break time="100ms" />In coney skins her commerce lay,<break time="100ms" />A charming stock she'd laid in;<break time="100ms" />She ne'er to smugglers fell a prey,<break time="100ms" />Her practice was fair trading.<break time="100ms" />These skins when dressed were red and white,<break time="100ms" />The fur of each fair creature,<break time="100ms" />Of different hues, as day and night,<break time="100ms" />Kept warm man's naked nature.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For some succeed, etc.<break time="100ms" />The trading stock of this old bawd<break time="100ms" />A vital stab sustain'd, sir,<break time="100ms" />The news like wild-fire flew abroad,<break time="100ms" />Each customer complairid, sir.<break time="100ms" />Some coney skins lay with a lot<break time="100ms" />By caution uninspected;<break time="100ms" />So quarantine, alas, forgot,<break time="100ms" />Foul plague the whole infected.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For some succeed, etc.<break time="100ms" />Now old and young her shop forsook,<break time="100ms" />Insolvent was her plight, sir,<break time="100ms" />When Habeas Corpus catch-pole took<break time="100ms" />Her body off by night, sir,<break time="100ms" />From Banco regis civil law,<break time="100ms" />To liquidate her debt, sir,<break time="100ms" />Between the sheets this old bawd saw<break time="100ms" />Of London's fam'd Gazette, sir.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For some succeed, etc.<break time="100ms" />To give each creditor his due,<break time="100ms" />Three men, the Lord's anointed,<break time="100ms" />Jack Wilkes, Lord Sandwich and Old Q<break time="100ms" />Were assignees appointed;<break time="100ms" />But luckless bawd! the after day<break time="100ms" />Her stock on fire they found, sir;<break time="100ms" />So 'twas agreed she could not pay<break time="100ms" />A condom in the pound, sir.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For some succeed, etc.<break time="100ms" />The skin (her own) this bawd had left,<break time="100ms" />Each assignee did handle;<break time="100ms" />'Twas found of all its fur bereft,<break time="100ms" />By singeing flame of candle;<break time="100ms" />Same butter'd buns concealed within,<break time="100ms" />Old Q's keen eye beset, sir;<break time="100ms" />So Wilkes defin'd this coney skin<break time="100ms" />A fund for floating debt, sir.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For some succeed, etc.<break time="100ms" />By headlong lust her claimants led,<break time="100ms" />They seized her mortal treasure;<break time="100ms" />The furious coney skin was spread,<break time="100ms" />A dividend past measure.<break time="100ms" />No wall came in, not one stood out;<break time="100ms" />The bawd was set at large, sir;<break time="100ms" />Her coney skin (of worth, no doubt),<break time="100ms" />Did every man discharge, sir.<break time="100ms" />Chorus: For some succeed, etc.<break time="100ms" />Facetiae.<break time="100ms" />Cease, foolish painters, Hercules to draw<break time="100ms" />With wooden club, inspiring man with awe;<break time="100ms" />A different club that here should adorn,<break time="100ms" />This god's most powerful weapon is the horn;<break time="100ms" />No mightier spear than that the champion hurls,<break time="100ms" />With which one night he fucked three score of girls!<break time="100ms" />A crowd of grave enquirers made resort,<break time="100ms" />To where the learned doctors held their court;<break time="100ms" />And asked them who had been that serpent brute,<break time="100ms" />Which tempted mother Eve to eat the fruit?<break time="100ms" />"Ye silly men," the sages did reply,<break time="100ms" />"Why do you waste your time and ours, oh, why?<break time="100ms" />Eve's tempting snake was but a long and thick,<break time="100ms" />Great, knotty, ruddy, massy, mighty prick!"<break time="100ms" />Always, except on Sabbath days,<break time="100ms" />Nell with her busy needle plays;<break time="100ms" />But not the milliner's needle, Miss!<break time="100ms" />No, 'tis the sailor's needle, dear!<break time="100ms" />That shows the mariner how to steer<break time="100ms" />Right through the ocean of her piss.<break time="100ms" />The Editor of the Standard is a good-natured fellow, ever ready to attend the wants of his customers, more especially when they happen to be good-looking members of the fair sex.<break time="100ms" />The following conversation which recently took place in the office of the Standard, fully carries out our assertion:<break time="100ms" />Enters Lady:<break time="100ms" />Lady - Is the Editor in?<break time="100ms" />Editor - Yes, Madame, what can I do for you?
    </voice>
</speak>
