<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Whilst on her back, sleeping as fast as a top,<break time="100ms" />He with keen cutting scissors her c-t made a crop.<break time="100ms" />Away went the thief, and the barber received,<break time="100ms" />The booty, for which a final caul he had weav'd;<break time="100ms" />But strange! whilst old razor the wig had in hand,<break time="100ms" />The pole in his breeches did constantly stand.<break time="100ms" />Well pleas'd with his plight, Razor laid by his work,<break time="100ms" />And lather'd the beard of his wife like a Turk.<break time="100ms" />"Keep the wig," said she, "love, don't expose it for sale.<break time="100ms" />'Tis bob for your head and a bob for my tail."<break time="100ms" />The wig frizz'd and curl'd, closely shav'd Codger's nob;<break time="100ms" />Away went the barber to try on the bob;<break time="100ms" />But the box waxing warm, Codger's passions did rise,<break time="100ms" />Which brought tears in his breeches instead of his eyes.<break time="100ms" />In rampant condition he flew to a fair,<break time="100ms" />And perchance met the Dolly he'd robb'd of her hair;<break time="100ms" />She whipp'd off the wig, cloth'd his parts with the caul,<break time="100ms" />So in went his dry bob, and wet bob, and all.<break time="100ms" />Now we know to be true what anatomists state,<break time="100ms" />That the fountain of love is supplied from the pate;<break time="100ms" />'Twas the jasey provoking, sirs, mark what I say,<break time="100ms" />Made his fountain of love's bason to play.<break time="100ms" />Then take my advice, ye old cocks of the game,<break time="100ms" />Whenever you find your wild passions grown tame,<break time="100ms" />Get a wig made of hair from the spot ye all prize,<break time="100ms" />And in spite of your prudence your pego will rise.<break time="100ms" />Come father dear! now lay your body down<break time="100ms" />Upon your daughter's naked belly white,<break time="100ms" />Now raptures soon shall our embraces crown;<break time="100ms" />This is the only road to true delight!<break time="100ms" />I know the lessons I have learnt from you,<break time="100ms" />Sweet lessons in the flowerY paths of love!<break time="100ms" />Sure I'll remember all I ought to do,<break time="100ms" />When I am under and you are above!<break time="100ms" />Enter at once, dear father, to my bower,<break time="100ms" />Each movement of your prick will give me bliss!<break time="100ms" />'Tis joy to me to know I have the power,<break time="100ms" />With you to share sweet rapture such as this!<break time="100ms" />How often you have praised my cunt's tight grip!<break time="100ms" />Each time you fuck 'tis better than the last!<break time="100ms" />Now from my cunt your prick will never slip!<break time="100ms" />Your legs and mine entwined shall keep it fast!<break time="100ms" />Only a father's love such joy can give,<break time="100ms" />United thus, forever I could live!<break time="100ms" />Nor envy those who boast a husband's love.<break time="100ms" />Give me always this prick, I ne'er will rove,<break time="100ms" />And never wish for any other man.<break time="100ms" />No prick with this, I'm certain, can compare!<break time="100ms" />Does it not take both of my hands to span?<break time="100ms" />Then what a wealth he has of curly hair!<break time="100ms" />Each morn upon my cunt his burning kisses fall,<break time="100ms" />Night after night his tongue enters my quim so small.<break time="100ms" />Do it again, papa, I can't forbear to call,<break time="100ms" />Even my mother laughs and says: "My husband dear,<break time="100ms" />Ram in your prick at once, and end this wild career."<break time="100ms" />When John and Sue had tied the nupital bands,<break time="100ms" />Like ardent lovers, join'd their hearts and hands,<break time="100ms" />Hymen prepared his torch to bless the two<break time="100ms" />And in them centered his peculiar care.<break time="100ms" />The blissful hour arriv'd, Sue to his bed<break time="100ms" />By buxom damsels joyfully was led;<break time="100ms" />One with officious hands her stays unlac'd,<break time="100ms" />While standers-by extoll'd her lessening waist;<break time="100ms" />Her garters some with eagerness untied,<break time="100ms" />And all by turns were variously employ'd.<break time="100ms" />Susan, with bashful modesty array'd,<break time="100ms" />Like to a prudent and virtuous maid,<break time="100ms" />Now plac'd in bed, these dubious thoughts arose:<break time="100ms" />"I fear this night I'll have no repose;<break time="100ms" />To bed with man; methinks is vastly odd,<break time="100ms" />Tho' matrimony was ordain'd by God.<break time="100ms" />Oh, how my virgin frame will shake with fear,<break time="100ms" />When am'rous John in glowing hopes draws near;<break time="100ms" />If my fair front to his I shall incline,<break time="100ms" />And all my blooming charms at once resign,<break time="100ms" />He'll say I'm bold and turn his head aside,<break time="100ms" />And think he's purchas'd a lascivious bride.<break time="100ms" />To him, my parts posterior if I turn,<break time="100ms" />He'll charge me with indecency and scorn-<break time="100ms" />But here he comes:- Oh, how shall I behave,<break time="100ms" />To show myself his true and faithful slave?<break time="100ms" />A medium I'll observe, fall which way it will;<break time="100ms" />Of his fair Susan John won't take it ill,<break time="100ms" />And that I no apology may lack.<break time="100ms" />I'm e'en resolved to lie upon my back."<break time="100ms" />God save our great Cunt! our Queen!<break time="100ms" />For ever may she reign,<break time="100ms" />Supreme o'er all!<break time="100ms" />Her praises we will sound,<break time="100ms" />True bliss in her is found,<break time="100ms" />She long ago was crowned,<break time="100ms" />Queen of the world!<break time="100ms" />Adam in Eden's bowers,<break time="100ms" />With choicest fruits and flowers,<break time="100ms" />Felt all alone!<break time="100ms" />Only his prick to frig,<break time="100ms" />When it was hard and big,<break time="100ms" />Till he felt with fatigue<break time="100ms" />Weary and worn!<break time="100ms" />Our Queen saw his distress,<break time="100ms" />And swift to his redress<break time="100ms" />From heaven she came.<break time="100ms" />Told him her name was Eve,<break time="100ms" />And asked him to believe<break time="100ms" />That she would relieve<break time="100ms" />Prick's burning flame!<break time="100ms" />Adam at once replied:<break time="100ms" />"For something I have sighed,<break time="100ms" />I knew not what!"<break time="100ms" />This cunt you show to me,<break time="100ms" />New strength puts into me.<break time="100ms" />And yet it seems to me,<break time="100ms" />My prick's more hot!"<break time="100ms" />Great Cunt, our Queen, then said:<break time="100ms" />"On this bank in the shade<break time="100ms" />I will lay down.<break time="100ms" />Put your prick in the slit,<break time="100ms" />Never fear the tight fit,<break time="100ms" />Push, and it will admit,<break time="100ms" />Your cock so brown!<break time="100ms" />Up and down move your bum,<break time="100ms" />In which I'll put my thumb,<break time="100ms" />To keep good time!<break time="100ms" />Shove your cock in and out,<break time="100ms" />Until from his blunt snout<break time="100ms" />The sperm shall madly spout,
    </voice>
</speak>
