<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />F lowers bloom their brightest there!<break time="100ms" />U nknown fragrance fills the air!<break time="100ms" />C ome, sweet Chloe, grant the prayer,<break time="100ms" />K neeling I make to thee!<break time="100ms" />F irm as a rock the noble martyr stood,<break time="100ms" />U nbending as a rod of tempered steel;<break time="100ms" />C almly he sees the touch ignite the wood,<break time="100ms" />K nowing the agony he soon must feel.<break time="100ms" />M ighty the influence which makes the body<break time="100ms" />Y ield prompt obedience to the power of will!<break time="100ms" />C onscious of being right, this is the motto,<break time="100ms" />U pon his banner writ in words of light.<break time="100ms" />N o other motive can supply the power,<break time="100ms" />T o cheer the martyr in his dying hour!<break time="100ms" />D ying because he would maintain the right,<break time="100ms" />E ver should rule in place of boastful might!<break time="100ms" />A nd so the martyr's name shall never die,<break time="100ms" />R ound the whole world the stirring tale shall fly.<break time="100ms" />P eoples unborn his noble name shall learn,<break time="100ms" />A nd his example make their bosoms burn;<break time="100ms" />P atriots shall hail him as a brother true,<break time="100ms" />A nd write his history for all to view!<break time="100ms" />A Yorkshire excursion train the other day contained a rather morose-looking individual, who being offered the newspaper, grumpily replied: "I don't read!"<break time="100ms" />"Will you take a cigar then?" asked another passenger.<break time="100ms" />"I don't smoke!"<break time="100ms" />Presently a third offered him his flask.<break time="100ms" />"I don't drink!"<break time="100ms" />This happened in a carriage with open compartments, so a clergyman who had overheard it all and thinking that perhaps a little intellectual conversation would be more to his taste, leaned over the back of the seat and said: "Would you like to step over here with us, there is only myself, wife and daughter?"<break time="100ms" />"I don't fuck!" was all he got for his kind intention.<break time="100ms" />And we need not say that he was both disgusted and chagrined as the laughter of the others pealed through the carriage.<break time="100ms" />A lady the other day, wishing to get an imbecile son into an asylum, consulted a doctor about a certificate and he naturally enquired as to the actions of the alleged lunatic.<break time="100ms" />Lady - I must tell you that lately at Christmas he would get up at night and eat all the mince-pie in the pantry.<break time="100ms" />Doctor - That is only gluttony.<break time="100ms" />Lady - There's something awfully shocking to tell: The other day he threw the servant down the stairs and fucked her!<break time="100ms" />Doctor - Mere depravity, that's, all. Now allow me to explain the difference to you, Madame! If you had told me that your son had eaten the servant and fucked the mince-pies there could have been no doubt about the necessity of confining him in an asylum.<break time="100ms" />This brings to my mind, says Lucidora, a tale I have heard of the late Sultan, who, being middle aged and worn out with the amorous exertions in the well-filled seraglio, determines to seek some fresh excitement; everything seems so insipid and blase to him.<break time="100ms" />At first he is at a loss how to amuse himself, but one day, discussing with his chief eunuch the arrangements and routine of the harem, a circumstance which never gave him a thought before suddenly gives him an idea that he may get both satisfaction and excitement from cunt, viz., that when he came to the throne (he was a nephew of the previous Commander of the Faithful), he left the Sultana Valide unmolested, who in the lifetime of his predecessor had intrigued in every possible manner to set aside his succession in favour of her own son contrary to the usual Osmanif custom. Since which time the baffled Sultana, a beautiful lady of about thirty, had peevishly shown her hatred of him by keeping the strictest seclusion, only walking by herself quite unattended in the most secluded part of the extensive gardens of the seraglio.<break time="100ms" />The Sultan had heard of the once famous beauty of this proud lady and was assured by the Chief of Eunuchs that she was still surpassingly lovely and was suspected of indulging in every variety of voluptuousness with the ladies of her suite in private.<break time="100ms" />sultan.- "At what hour does she generally take her walk in the garden?"<break time="100ms" />chief of eunuchs.- "About seven in the morning, your Majesty; she is an early riser and first goes to the Mosque then walks in the garden for an hour or more or sits under the trees reading some exciting French work, but retires as soon as the eunuch gardeners disturb her."<break time="100ms" />sultan.- "Well, good; keep the gardeners from that part of the garden tomorrow. I will have a private interview with her Majesty."<break time="100ms" />chief of eunuchs.- "Her Majesty would feel insulted to be addressed in the garden even by the Sultan. Consider, Sire, her late position, and what deference would she expect even from your Majesty yourself."<break time="100ms" />sultan.- "By the beard of the prophet! I'll bring her to her senses without even telling her who I am. She has never seen me. It will afford infinite satisfaction to<break time="100ms" />witness her naughty, proud indignation, at a stranger's intrusion on her privacy. But leave me to consider her dignity, all I want is that you keep out all intruders, and be sure to awaken me early enough in the morning."<break time="100ms" />Next day, at an early hour, the Sultan is ready for his anticipated excitement. It is a lovely morning in early spring; and he thoroughly enjoys the invigorating, soft sea-breeze which rustles the leaves of the trees over his head.
    </voice>
</speak>
