<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"No, no, dearest May," said Kate. "I shall never be jealous of you or any other girl your papa wished to fuck; in fact I should like to see him fuck all the girls in the parish, if he wanted to!"<break time="100ms" />Papa said: "Generous-hearted Kate, you shall never have cause to regret such unselfish conduct. It was the perfect nobleness and disinterestedness of your character which attracted me to you, and the more I see of your mental superiority the more I bless the hour we first became acquainted with each other! Now May, I am ready to fuck you!"<break time="100ms" />"And I, dear papa, am ready to be fucked," I replied smiling. Kate insisted on papa stripping himself perfectly naked and also on removing my smock. She then told papa to lie flat on his back with his prick standing erect; she then made me lie on top of him and she slapped my bottom in time to papa's heaves and thrusts until the crisis came and my womb was deluged with paternal sperm.<break time="100ms" />I was swimming in delight and could not help calling out: "Thank you a thousand times, dear papa, for this delicious treat!"<break time="100ms" />"And thank you, my darling child, for giving me such exquisite pleasure," replied papa.<break time="100ms" />In the next bout our positions were altered and Kate took part in the pastime, placing herself in such a position that papa could see her cunny while he fucked mine. We changed positions many times until papa said he must rest from his labours of love, and after partaking of refreshments we all three went to papa's bedroom and fell asleep on his bed, one on each side of him.<break time="100ms" />In the morning I asked papa to tell me how he became acquainted with Kate, and he replied as follows: "Last Christmas I went up to London for a holiday and at my club I met with several old friends, who had daughters at school with Madame Stewart at Hampton Court. Sir Thomas Moreton, my neighbour, was one of the party, and while drinking our wine, we talked about our experiences in fucking, and afterwards the conversation turned to the subject of schoolmistresses whipping their scholars' bottoms. I argued that it was not done nowadays but might have been done years ago.<break time="100ms" />"Sir Thomas laid me a £50 bet that I was wrong and offered to take me to Mme. Stewart's to prove it.<break time="100ms" />"I accepted his wager and on the following Saturday evening accompanied him to Mme. Stewart's to put his wager to the test.<break time="100ms" />"We were conducted to a room fitted up with all kinds of punishment apparatus and at one end was a raised dais or platform, under which we seated ourselves, and the door being closed we found the front of the platform was pierced with peepholes in all directions so we had a perfect view of the room, which was brilliantly lighted up with wax candles whilst our recess was dark.<break time="100ms" />"Presently six girls were brought in by the governess and Madame Stewart ascended the dais over our heads and gave orders for the number of stripes and read the list of offences.<break time="100ms" />"The fair culprits were placed with their bottoms towards the dais so we had a full view of their struggles and wrigglings as the rod fell on their thighs and bottoms and we had many a peep at the tender cunny which peeped from between their legs.<break time="100ms" />"My Kate was one that was punished on that occasion and I was especially attracted by the quivering of the lips of her cunny as the rod fell on her lovely bottom. At last I was sure I could see the dear girl give down the pearly drops in pleasurable emission. Such sensitiveness charmed me, and when the punishment was over I made an offer to Madame Stewart to take Kate home with me as a fucking-piece, offering her a bribe.<break time="100ms" />"Madame demurred at first then said the matter should be left to Kate's decision.<break time="100ms" />"She was called into the room and I told her how I was smitten with the sight of her naked charms and wanted her to come and live with me a few months every year.<break time="100ms" />"She first looked at my standing prick and then enquired if it would be any advantage to Madame Stewart and that if it would, she would come with me.<break time="100ms" />"I told her I offered Madame £50. 'Then,' said Kate, 'I will go with you and trust in your honour as to your treatment of me.'<break time="100ms" />"Such disinterested conduct is most uncommon in this money-loving age and I love and honour Kate for it."<break time="100ms" />I told my father I was sure he would be generous to both Kate and myself. He told me he was anxious I should be married to a gentleman of his acquaintance, an elderly rich widower. I enquired how he knew anything about me and what was his name? To which my father replied his name was Mr. Sinclair and it was his cock I had become acquainted with, that he was over eighty years old, so I should be a rich widow probably in a few years. That the old gent was able to do a fair amount of fucking, but if I wanted more I could easily get a young man for a pound a week to do it for me. I consented to my father's propositions and we invited Mr. T (the resident tutor at the school mentioned at the beginning of my tale), to come to the wedding. We also invited Susey and her uncle.<break time="100ms" />They all came and I was married one fine May morning out of compliment to my name. After the ceremony the clergyman asked permission to have the first kiss on my cunny, which I granted him in the vestry. We went for our wedding tour to the Isle of Wight for a month during which time my husband was satisfied he had got me with a child. He then gave me permission to have as much outside fucking as I wanted. I told him I should wait until we got home as I was longing for a taste of Mr. T's noble tool and also for my dear father's prick. My husband was pleased with my determination and engaged Mr. T as librarian, and in that capacity he remained until the lamented decease of Mr. Sinclair at the age of ninety, who left me with one daughter nine years old, and all his money.<break time="100ms" />As soon after his death as was decent I married Mr. S- whom I found to be one of the best husbands. Susey often pays us a visit and brings young girls with her to please Mr. T who has a penchant for the unfledged cunny, and often has a game of blindman's buff with the naked children, and a romp with my little Agnes when she is naked. The little darling is now twelve years old and very proud of being able to make "her new papa's cocky get big," as she says, by rubbing her little cunny against its head. Mr. T anticipates the pleasure of taking her maidenhead when she is fourteen. I tell him that it is too early and that he ought to wait until she is fifteen, but he is so impatient that I fear he will have his own way. So good reader, both lady and gentleman, farewell! And may you never want a fuck, Nor yet a prick or cunt to suck.<break time="100ms" />FINIS.<break time="100ms" />C ome love and dwell with me<break time="100ms" />U nder the greenwood tree,<break time="100ms" />N o one can happy be,<break time="100ms" />T han I shall be if bless'd with thee!<break time="100ms" />P laced near your mossy grot,<break time="100ms" />R ises a rustic cot.<break time="100ms" />I would bear thee to that spot,<break time="100ms" />C ool when the sun is hot;<break time="100ms" />K ind fair one, linger not!
    </voice>
</speak>
