<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Volume 18
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />Table of Contents<break time="100ms" />My Grandmother's Tale or May's Account of Her Introduction to the Art of Love<break time="100ms" />Acrostic - Madrigal<break time="100ms" />Acrostic - The Martyr<break time="100ms" />The Disagreeable Passenger<break time="100ms" />A Question of Lunacy<break time="100ms" />The Sultan's Reverie<break time="100ms" />How He Lost His Whiskers: An Episode in the Life of Steve Broad<break time="100ms" />The Novice<break time="100ms" />A Gentleman's Wig<break time="100ms" />Acrostic<break time="100ms" />The Wedding Night<break time="100ms" />God Save Queen Cunt<break time="100ms" />From an Unsophisticated Manuscript, Found Amongst the Old Lady's Papers After Her Death, Supposed To Have Been Written About A.D. 1797.<break time="100ms" />SUSEY'S LETTER CONCLUDED.<break time="100ms" />Uncle got up and came to meet me, saying: "Welcome, Susey, I am glad you have come! How blooming you look! You must want your supper after such a long ride."<break time="100ms" />I threw my arms around his neck and kissing him, said: "Thank you, dear Uncle, for all your great kindness and especially for this lovely silk dress and the pretty garters you gave me."<break time="100ms" />"Does the dress fit you, my dear?" he asked, placing his hands on my bosom and squeezing it gently.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, Uncle dear," I said. We then had supper, and Uncle insisted on my drinking four glasses of the champagne, which I found warmed up my blood as doubtless Uncle intended it should do.<break time="100ms" />After supper he said: "Susey, if you love me, show me your garters."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Uncle!" I replied blushingly, "would that be decent and proper?"<break time="100ms" />"You are an ungrateful girl to refuse the first trifling request I make," he said.<break time="100ms" />"Not ungrateful, Uncle," I replied; "see here, please examine my pretty garters," and I stretched out both my legs as I continued sitting in my chair. Uncle was on his knees between my legs in a moment, and put his hands first on one garter and then on the other, unclasping them and kissing my thighs just above the stockings.<break time="100ms" />Then he said: "Dear Susey, do you know that your mother was my favourite sister? And that as children we used to sleep together, and were fond of taking off each other's nightdress and of examining the difference in our naked bodies, and making water in the same pot. And now, dear Susey, I want to tell you that your dear mother on her death-bed confided you to my care, and I have paid for your education and maintenance all your life; and now I hope you will love me and be a comfort to me in my declining years."<break time="100ms" />"Yes, dear Uncle," I said, "you may depend on my doing everything in my power to give you pleasure."<break time="100ms" />"That's a good girl," said Uncle. "But now you can do something this minute to please me, and that is to show me your cunny!"<break time="100ms" />I told him he could look at it if he wished. So as I was seated in an easy-chair he lifted one of my legs over an arm of the chair and telling me to hold my clothing and chemise out of the way, he exposed my cunny and bottom-hole to his delighted view, and covered both with kisses, sucking and putting his tongue as far as possible into both places. The end of this, of course, was that I gave down my liquor of love over his tongue and he greedily sucked up every drop, declaring it was most delicious. After this he pulled out his prick and pretended to me that he had fucked my mother, therefore he had a right to do the same to me! I laughed at this reasoning and feigning ignorance of his meaning asked him to explain everything. He then laid me on the sofa before the fire and undressed me and also himself, all the time praising the whiteness of my skin, and then, dearest May, he fucked me, and fancied he was the first that had penetrated my virgin slit, as he fondly called it.<break time="100ms" />Now I must close this letter, hoping you have had as much pleasure as I have in the way of fucking. By the way, dear May, why don't you get your father to fuck you? Uncle says you would find it delicious, for he knows your father well and says he remembers that his cock is both long and very thick!<break time="100ms" />I remain, darling May, your loving friend, SUSEY.<break time="100ms" />P.S.-Be sure and keep this letter a secret and don't let your father see it for the world! Write soon and tell me everything.<break time="100ms" />I put this precious letter in my pocket and then remembered that Kate had never told me how she first became acquainted with my father. So I went into the dining-room in search of her and found her and papa sitting on the sofa, with their private parts exposed and each was fondling and touching the other's genitals.<break time="100ms" />Papa caught sight of me and called out: "Come in May, I want you most particularly." I went up to him. He continued: "I want to see if the hair on your cunny is as fine and silky as this on Kate's cunt. Now be a good obedient girl and I will give you a silk dress and you shall choose the colour yourself."<break time="100ms" />How this promise dazzled me! I had had only one silk dress many years before and now the promise of choosing one myself conjured up visions of beauty to my mind's eye.<break time="100ms" />I replied quickly: "Yes, dear papa, I will do all you require," and I raised up my clothing as I stood in front of him.<break time="100ms" />"That is not convenient," he said. "You had better slip off your clothes except the chemise. Kate will help you." So in a few moments my dress and petticoats were on the ground and I was en chemise as I did not wear drawers in those days. In taking my dress over my head my pocket was emptied on the carpet and the letter caught my father's eye. "Oh, a love letter," he cried, "fine goings on, Miss May! I must read this letter from your favoured lover!" and he picked it up and commenced to read it.<break time="100ms" />"It is not a love letter," I said, "but one from my school-friend Susey who is in Scotland with her uncle."<break time="100ms" />"All the same I shall read it aloud," said my father. And he did so.<break time="100ms" />And Kate whispered to me: "Don't be afraid of anything, May dearest, I will take your part."<break time="100ms" />My father was delighted with Susey's letter and as his breeches were unbuttoned as he sat on the sofa I could see his pego rise to a fine erection as he came to some of her descriptive passages. At last he came to the end where she advised me to get my father to fuck me, and then he cried out: "Sensible girl this Susey! I wish she were here now. I must invite her and her uncle, my old friend, on a visit this summer, and we will have glorious times! But at present I am concerned to examine closely my daughter's cunny! And if she consents, willingly will I fuck her for I cannot use force to my own daughter, I love her too well for that! Only if she cheerfully consents to let me have my will, she shall have five guineas in addition to the silk dress and I will take her to the theatre one night each week!"<break time="100ms" />I exclaimed: "You dear kind papa! How much I love you! Yes, do whatever you like with me and teach me how to give you pleasure. I hope, dear Kate will not be jealous of poor little me?"
    </voice>
</speak>
