<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"If your honour will allow me to explain it in my own way and give you a little bit of my history I think I can prove it is all a mistake."<break time="100ms" />"Well," said the magistrate, "go on."<break time="100ms" />"Well, your honour, a year or two ago I had a little money and wishing to see life I took a walk late at night in the neighbourhood of Haymarket, and got into the company of one of those girls."<break time="100ms" />"One of what girls?" said Norton.<break time="100ms" />"A whore."<break time="100ms" />"Well, sir, your expression is far from elegant, but I understand you."<break time="100ms" />"Well, your honour, this girl enticed me home and there I found a lot of her companions and a nice little spree we had. At last we proposed a game of blindman's buff, and as I was the only male present it was proposed that we should all strip and then the ladies should be blindfolded and a prize given to the lady that caught me. Oh, it was jolly fun to see the girls running about naked and catching hold of each other and their slipping their hands down to the proper place to feel if it was the man they held; but they kept giving me such jolly slaps on my bottom that I tried to run out of the door when one of the girls picked up my umbrella which stood in the corner and made a lunge at me (the devil must have looked). Oh, the tip of the umbrella entered my fundament as it was turned to her and as she withdrew it the ferule was left behind, and there it is now, and every time I sigh-"<break time="100ms" />"Every time you what?" asked Mr. Norton.<break time="100ms" />"Well, every time I fart, if you like, the ferule whistles and the dogs follow me and I can't help it."<break time="100ms" />Mr. Norton laughed heartily at this explanation, told him not to diet windily, and let him go.<break time="100ms" />But, however, to return to Steve. He soon got to be really in love with Letty, proposed marriage to her and had the full consent of her brother Alf, and the promised consent of her father; and it was arranged that on the return of Alf and his sister to their country home, Steve should come on a visit and get the old boy's consent.<break time="100ms" />The old gentleman invited him to get a look at him.<break time="100ms" />The time came. Alf and Letty went home and Steve was soon to follow.<break time="100ms" />At last the day arrived and he went.<break time="100ms" />After picking up his traps, bidding his landlady good-bye, and giving the slavey a farewell grind on the kitchen-dresser, he took himself down to the station, booked for Fairbanks, and was soon seated alone in a first-class carriage.<break time="100ms" />Alone! Yes, all but a delightful companion - the last number of The Pearl with which and his favourite meerschaum Steve whiled away the time as the stations flew past.<break time="100ms" />It was a beautiful day but he heeded not the aspect of the country, so thoroughly was he absorbed in the doings of Lady Pokingham and Miss Coote, etc.<break time="100ms" />All this excited his imagination until he got in a most furious state, not knowing how to ease his torment, and only wishing that he had a companion on the journey, whether male or female, he would have heeded not. He was in such a pitch of excitement that he would have got into a kangaroo, when-<break time="100ms" />The train stopped at Bellevue, and-<break time="100ms" />A young lady got on board carrying a rather large bundle which she placed under the seat and then sat down.<break time="100ms" />Steve's heart bounded as he noticed her light flowing hair, her airy step, and her little figure. But she was closely veiled and as yet he could not see her face, but the<break time="100ms" />lovely swell of her bosom, the creamy whiteness of the little bit of her throat that was visible convinced him that she was young and lovely.<break time="100ms" />The train sped on. Modestly the young lady kept her veil down and Steve thrust The Pearl in his pocket and was soon deep in the Times.<break time="100ms" />Oh, how that veiled face piqued him! Again, again and again he cast his eyes to it over the Times but the veil was still down.<break time="100ms" />"Does the draught annoy you?" said Steve, pointing to the partly opened window.<break time="100ms" />"Not at all, thank you," replied a sweet voice behind the veil.<break time="100ms" />Something in the voice thrilled Steve through. He had heard it before he felt sure, and he was more anxious than ever to see the face it belonged to.<break time="100ms" />At last as they passed a certain station with a sigh of relief she threw up her veil and turned her face to her hero.<break time="100ms" />"Good heavens, Kate, is it you?"<break time="100ms" />"Why, Mr. Broad, who would have thought of seeing you. Oh, I am so glad. You know that odious old lawyer, that wanted to marry me? Well I am positively flying from him and until I passed this station I felt they would pursue me. That is why I kept myself veiled but now I am quite out of my trouble, I think; for I have got a disguise which I shall put on. I tried all I could to get into an empty carriage but the guard assured me there was not one, but now you can help and not hinder me."<break time="100ms" />Let me tell you now, that Steve and the lady were old friends. They had met the first time at some private theatricals. Steve made love to her in the character of a French Count on the stage, and in his character of an English lover off the stage, he managed to make a first appearance in Kate's delicious cunny. In fact he took her maidenhead and many a delightful love-fuck they had, until Kate went abroad. And now they had met again under such strange circumstances.<break time="100ms" />"Let me tell you quickly," said Kate, "I am engaged to Paul Jellocombe, you remember him. Well, love, you won't be jealous when I tell you we are going to be married as soon as ever I am of age. I have escaped from home and mean to stay with Paul's folks until a few weeks elapse when I shall be my own mistress. And now for my plan: I have eluded them so far, but for fear they should dispatch a message to the telegraph station and stop me I have brought a disguise, and now, help me on with it, quick. You shall be my lady's-maid."<break time="100ms" />Before Steve had time to get his breath the charming, volatile girl took off bonnet and cloak, undid her dress, whipped it off around her feet, exposing a lovely pair of white shoulders and two glowing breasts, small for her size, but round, polished as marble.<break time="100ms" />If Steve's priapus had before been excited it was now delirious.<break time="100ms" />Jumping from his seat he helped her take off her petticoats, etc., until she came to her drawers.<break time="100ms" />"Stop sir, that will do," said Kate, "I don't want any further undressing. No! No! Don't be foolish. I can allow no liberties. Quick, I know this line well, you have only just time to turn me into a middy before we get to the next station."<break time="100ms" />Stooping as she spoke she undid the bundle at her feet and quick as her nimble fingers could move and with Steve's assistance, she was soon dressed as a middy. Her light hair was tucked cleverly up, a short crisp wig assumed. Her cap stuck jauntily on her head. She looked as smart and trim a middy as ever saluted the quarter-deck.
    </voice>
</speak>
