<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />With a brutal laugh he shoves his toe into her crack, saying: "Now the cold will keep out of there, too!" Then unloosening her clothes and allowing her to uncover her face he enjoys the spectacle of her tearful, pitiable looks as she sobs and moans in her exhausted state. "Ha, ha! a little water will revive you, you wanton Sultana. You'd better pick yourself up and go back to your apartment," said he, making water all over her and even into her gaping mouth.<break time="100ms" />She chokes, gasps and falls back in a lifeless swoon. This last indignity had finished her.<break time="100ms" />So having her to recover as best she could he retires from the scene.<break time="100ms" />A few days afterwards the Sultan requests an audience of the Sultana Valide, as he hears she has been indisposed, and when; ushered into her apartment she receives him unveiled in consequence of his exalted rank as her sovereign.<break time="100ms" />the sultan, refusing to be seated.- "Madame, hearing you were ill I have brought you a present which I hope may restore your animation a little; especially if you use it vigorously as I have seen you do." And he places in her hands a casket of Morocco leather, ornamented with gold, which contains her godemiche. "If your<break time="100ms" />Imperial Highness will look, you will see how I have improved it." (He had put a quantity of her own hair on the india-rubber to make the instrument look more natural.) "I have still enough left to make myself a keepsake," said he, inclining his head as he withdrew from her apartment. "Au revoir, I have repaid you for all your former kindnesses to me."<break time="100ms" />You may imagine the angry, furious looks of indignant hate which she cast at him as he looked steadily at her, enjoying her shame and confusion whilst giving his present.<break time="100ms" />You didn't know Steve Broad? More's the pity! A jollier, better-heard and manlier fellow never pissed against a wall.<break time="100ms" />He was my constant chum from the time we occupied some diggings in Camden Town. Till he went to Australia we were together.<break time="100ms" />The Siamese Twins, Castor and Pollux, were not more inseparable.<break time="100ms" />Old Jack Falstaff and Prince Henry and Poins loved each other because "their legs were both of a bigness."<break time="100ms" />Shall I whisper the secret or one of the secrets of our attachment? Our pricks were both of a length and our arse-holes the same gauge. Don't infer too much from that admission. It was not often that we fucked. There, I will tell you a story that will show you the sort of fellow he was.<break time="100ms" />Steve had a pal, Alf Nugent, and he and Alf had lived together as chums. Alf occasionally receiving a visit in his lodging from a pretty sister, Lettice, as they called her from Letty Nugent, a charming little blonde with oh! such shoulders; a mouth humid and peachlike and a pair of eyes that would entice the bark off a tree.<break time="100ms" />It was not long before Steve and Letty struck up an acquaintance. Steve could make love like a Romeo.<break time="100ms" />Letty was "willing" as Barkis, and the brother Alf was not one to spoil sport, so the three got on charmingly together, Alf often gave a pleasant little party. I was invited. Steve had made my acquaintance in the city, and took me there. I introduced a young girl Kitty Marshall, and Alf brought his inamorata, Nellie Grover. So that the six of us formed a pleasant little gathering and rare fun we had.<break time="100ms" />Let me sketch for you one of our social meetings after a recherche supper, prepared by the nimble hands of Letty Nugent, who turned out every article as palatable as Ruth Pinch's Steakpie.<break time="100ms" />The table was cleared of all but wines and fruits, the couches were drawn up to the fire and the six of us would go in for a little fun.<break time="100ms" />Steve would warble in his rich manly voice a polly song, such as:<break time="100ms" />There's a thing that bears a well-known name,<break time="100ms" />Though it is but a little spot;<break time="100ms" />Its smell sets my heart and my brain in a flame,<break time="100ms" />And its touch makes my prick grow hot,<break time="100ms" />'Tis the sweetest thing this world can show,<break time="100ms" />To praise it can't be wrong;<break time="100ms" />'Twill set your blood in a fervid glow,<break time="100ms" />Make your prick grow stiff and long.<break time="100ms" />'Tis a woman's cunt. Her glorious fan,<break time="100ms" />Oh, a cunt is the pride of an Englishman.<break time="100ms" />That cunt will not be treated with shame,<break time="100ms" />But calls for proper respect;<break time="100ms" />And though mostly fit for a fucking game,<break time="100ms" />Yet it sometimes in mourning is decked.<break time="100ms" />Then beware how you go with the darling then,<break time="100ms" />Or perhaps sorely punished you'll be;<break time="100ms" />For cunt won't be the sport of men,<break time="100ms" />When it wants its privacy.<break time="100ms" />For caprice is part of cunt's own plan<break time="100ms" />To enhance its joys to an Englishman.<break time="100ms" />But when cunt is ready, I give you the tip,<break time="100ms" />No half-hearted play can it stand;<break time="100ms" />It likes to be fondled with tongue and with lip,<break time="100ms" />And shuns not the touch of your hand.<break time="100ms" />But the glorious Prick sets Miss Cunt in a thrill,<break time="100ms" />She loves a prick, long, thick, and firm.<break time="100ms" />And she'll wriggle and pant till you madly fill<break time="100ms" />Her bang full of glowing sperm.<break time="100ms" />You may frig and gamahuche and try every plan,<break time="100ms" />But fair fucking's the pride of an Englishman.<break time="100ms" />Of course a song like this was well received and quickly followed by a practical illustration.<break time="100ms" />My little lady, Kitty Marshall, warmly defended gamahuching and so did I; for laying Kitty down on the couch and parting her beautiful legs I displayed to the others a cleft that an angel would think it a new joy to suck. Soon the whole six of us were engaged in an amorous orgy, and Steve, who certainly could boast the most magnificent priapus that ever adorned a man, took pretty little Letty in his arms and gave her what you may call an "Exhibition Fuck." His balls knocked against the entrance of her lovely quim and at last when she wriggled and panted and hugged<break time="100ms" />him into a spend he poured such a libation into her that we could see it overflow and they mutually lay entranced until we revived them with some glorious wine.<break time="100ms" />Then we would go in for a game of blindman's buff, all being stripped naked and armed with birch; we would scamper about the room, cutting right and left, and endeavouring to land some smart blows on each other's glowing posteriors, until thoroughly exhausted; we would sit down on our smarting arses for a good story or song.<break time="100ms" />Apropos of our game of blindman's buff, Alf told us a good story.<break time="100ms" />A respectable-looking old buck was brought before Mr. Norton, the magistrate, charged with dog stealing or rather enticing ladies' dogs to follow him with the intention of stealing them.<break time="100ms" />"Well, sir," said Mr. Norton, "what have you to say to this charge?"
    </voice>
</speak>
