<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The transformation was no sooner completed than the train stopped at a station, and they both jumped out for refreshments.<break time="100ms" />The rollicking girl, her walk, her gait, showed her well fitted to play her part. She was indeed no mean actress.<break time="100ms" />As soon as they were back in the carriage, which Steve adroitly secured for themselves by puffing a tremendous cloud of smoke in the eyes of an old lady who would have entered, Steve took the middy on his knee.<break time="100ms" />"Well, Kate, love, this is quite an adventure and I tell you, it is a long way to the next station, and as it has been one of the great ambitions of my life to fuck a midshipman this is too good an opportunity to let it pass."<break time="100ms" />Kate offered no resistance. Thrusting his hand into the bosom of her jacket he first felt her round and polished breasts, pinched her nipples and fired her with his wanton touches and the hot burning kisses he printed on her lips. Then unbuttoning his trousers he allowed his splendid staff d'amour to display itself before her.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Steve, how it has grown since I saw it last," said Kate mischievously as she took it in her hand.<break time="100ms" />"Yes," said Steve, who could not resist a pun, "I have heard him groan for a taste of your darling cunny. Come, let me feel how it is getting on?"<break time="100ms" />As he spoke he slid his hand into her trousers and felt her cunt, moist and mossy, tickled her clitoris, and roused all her warming passions.<break time="100ms" />As the train sped on they abandoned themselves to all that their impassioned natures could suggest.<break time="100ms" />Steve knelt down on the floor of the carriage and opening wide Kate's legs he pressed his hot lips to her creamy cunt, and gamahuched her, until she spent in delirious pleasure.<break time="100ms" />And then when all his feelings were working up to such a pitch of excitement that he could no longer contain himself, he laid her supple form over the seat and getting into her from behind he thrust his prick to the very hilt in her reeking cunt. One, two, three thrusts and as he clasped her to him with a convulsive thrill he poured out his manly balm in an ecstasy of enjoyment.<break time="100ms" />"Hi, hi! Stop that you infernal scoundrels! Oh, you dirty rascals!"<break time="100ms" />In a sudden bewildered start of alarm they looked round to see a red, round, indignant face, ornamented with a bristly white moustache arid surmounted by a tuft of white hair that made the upper part of the head look like an infuriated cockatoo.<break time="100ms" />His face was peeping on them through a window in their compartment, which being concealed by a curtain the same colour as the carriage they had not noticed.<break time="100ms" />The passenger in the next compartment, reaching something from the back over his head, was prompted to draw the curtain and his restless, listless curiosity was rewarded by seeing Steve ram his hungry prick into Kate's writhing cunt, but as the old boy thought, into the arse.<break time="100ms" />In a minute Steve and Kate arranged their costume, and were sitting down whilst the passenger continued to glare at them muttering subdued imprecations and swearing he would charge them at the next station.<break time="100ms" />Without turning his head Steve whispered to Kate to get out at the next station, to bolt through for the highroad and leave him to detain the old boy until he could join her.<break time="100ms" />Quick as thought, as they neared the station, Steve bolted out, using a railway key he always carried. He locked the compartment in which the old man was alone and he and Kate dashed through the station before the fat old duffer could cause them to be stopped.<break time="100ms" />Quickly as they could they made for the country and had a parting rural fuck which they thoroughly enjoyed.<break time="100ms" />There is really something delightful in rural out of doors, al fresco fuck, the music of the birds, the babbling of the nearby stream, the fresh air fanning your face, and invigorating your frame, seem to me to always give great zest and vigour to the performance. I know for myself the thrusts I give are more vigorous, the sperm I spend is more copious and the thrill always more delightful when I have a glorious country-fuck in the open air.<break time="100ms" />"Good-bye, I am sure it will not be long before I see you again," said Kate. "And married or not, remember, there is always a loving, dear, affectionate little cunny to welcome you whenever you see me."<break time="100ms" />"Farewell," said Steve, "and be sure my prick will always stand your true friend."<break time="100ms" />So they parted.<break time="100ms" />A hearty welcome awaited Steve at the hands of Alf Nugent and his charming sister Letty.<break time="100ms" />They were alone in the house, their father being expected shortly, so they made him quite free.<break time="100ms" />After a jolly meal for which his long walk had given him an appetite, Alf said: "Now let me show you our private boudoir."<break time="100ms" />Following him, Steve soon found himself in a most tastefully furnished little room. A pianoforte stood in one corner, other musical instruments were about the room, splendid pictures of voluptuous scenes adorned the walls and a glorious couch that seemed fit for a seraph to recline on stood the chief object of attention.<break time="100ms" />"And now," said Alf, "before my father comes home, and he will not be long, he has only some slight business in the town, let us see if you are in good form. Letty is dying for a fuck and I shall have great pleasure in seeing you operate."<break time="100ms" />Steve was quite reinvigorated. It took but a little time for them to undress the lovely girl and lay her at full length on the soft spring-couch.<break time="100ms" />In a few moments Steve was on her, and his prick buried to the hilt in her luscious cunt.<break time="100ms" />"Go to it, Steve," said Alf. "Give it to her. The young hussey has some good stuff to spend, I know, for she sucked my prick three times yesterday. There now, you are getting slow but I'll warm you up, I warrant," and suiting the action to the word, Alf seized a birch from a corner and laid it smartly across Steve's arse.<break time="100ms" />This quickened his strokes and soon a shiver shook their bodies and Letty and he melted in a glorious spend.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, poor Alf, look at his prick," said Letty.<break time="100ms" />And turning around as he slid off her, Steve certainly noticed the stiffness of Alf's prick and it was in a most painful state of excitement.<break time="100ms" />Whilst Steve readjusted his clothes, Letty dropped quietly to her knees, and taking Alf's prick between her ruby lips, soon sucked it into a state of quiescence whilst Steve looked on highly amused at the look of gratified pleasure which soon spread over Alf's countenance.<break time="100ms" />"Hark!" said Alf, "what is that! A carriage, as sure as I live, it must be father. Look, Steve, from the window, who is it?"<break time="100ms" />Steve looked out.<break time="100ms" />"It is an old gentleman coming up the garden walk, Alf. Is that your father?" Alf peered out.<break time="100ms" />"Yes."
    </voice>
</speak>
