<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Then for heaven's sake don't let him see me, I must disguise myself. I cannot stop now to tell you how, but something must be done to destroy my identity or I am done for. Quick, Letty, you go down and meet your father; Alf and I will join you presently!"<break time="100ms" />Letty soon disappeared, though burning with curiosity. She was docile and did as she was bidden.<break time="100ms" />"Now, Alf," said Steve, "your guv'nor saw me in the railway carriage fucking a lovely girl, but as I was having her backwards and she was disguised as a sailor - a tale hangs to it but I can't tell you now - I expect he thought I was doing a bit of backdoor work and as he may be a particular old boy he must not know me again."<break time="100ms" />Steve was a young man of decision. Although it cost him a sigh, his beautiful whiskers were, soon sacrificed. His tact and skill soon changed his whole appearance and when he descended to join Letty and Mr. Nugent, but for a sign from<break time="100ms" />Alf, Letty would not have known him. Much less did Mr. Nugent recognize the bold flicker of the railway.<break time="100ms" />That's how Steve lost his whiskers.<break time="100ms" />A curious sequel hangs to the story. After dinner, when the gentlemen were alone, the old gentleman began:<break time="100ms" />"A very curious circumstance happened to me this morning when in a railway- train. I happened accidentally to look through the window of the compartment and saw a young man actually in the act of indecency with a midshipman; the rascals escaped by locking me in the carriage. However, in the carriage he had left, the young villain dropped a book. I took charge of it; as I had no spectacles I did not look close at it but as it doubtless contains some clue to the rascal, look at it for me."<break time="100ms" />Steve saw in a moment it was The Pearl; but knowing no clue to his identity was in it, he just glanced at it, handed it back, advising old Nugent to look at it more closely in the privacy of his chamber.<break time="100ms" />The old chap retired presently for his afternoon nap, taking the book with him, and soon after they heard peals of laughter from his room. Then he was heard walking up and down and soon his voice was heard calling Patty, his favourite servant.<break time="100ms" />Alf and Steve peeped through the keyhole after she had entered the room and saw him reading passages from the book. Then taking her in his arms he laid her on the bed, and raising his shirt-tail, he displayed his prick, stalwart and strong. In a few moments it was lodged in her creamy cunt. And both Steve and Alf were convinced that the old boy knew the way there.<break time="100ms" />In the evening old Nugent called Letty and Steve, joined their hands and said: "Bless you my children! A delightful little work I have been reading today has put fucking in such a beautiful light that I at once give you my consent to commence it as soon as possible. I have quite altered my opinion about that young fellow I saw and am convinced that to give his prick a treat is the first duty of every man at all times. I propose now that your nuptials shall be celebrated by a glorious fucking tournament."<break time="100ms" />This was done. Happiness was the lot of them all that evening.<break time="100ms" />Old Nugent never found out Steve's escapade. He died soon after and left them a heap of money, and so amorous was the old boy to the last that they had to send for the servant to toss him off, before they could get the lid on the coffin.<break time="100ms" />Kate married and is quite happy and I long to see Steve and have another laugh with him over: "How he lost his whiskers."<break time="100ms" />---<break time="100ms" />The ladies in America have taken to dabbling on the Stock Exchange.<break time="100ms" />The following telegrams passed between two lady friends and rather puzzled the telegraph officials.<break time="100ms" />"Dear Louise, a bull here has a large concern for which he is anxious to find an opening. Can you accommodate him?"<break time="100ms" />The reply was:<break time="100ms" />"I cannot at present as my monthly settlements are on, but if the bull can keep it standing for a week, I have no doubt I can find a vacancy for it."<break time="100ms" />Q.- When is a newly married lady like the Victory at Trafalgar? A.- When her cock-pit is full of bloody semen.<break time="100ms" />A pretty little novice in her convent woke at dawn,<break time="100ms" />And looking from her lattice she spied upon the lawn,<break time="100ms" />A handsome shepherd quite intent<break time="100ms" />On playing with his instrument, his instrument so long!<break time="100ms" />She raised the window softly and watched him for a while,<break time="100ms" />Delighted with his movements, then asked him with a smile:<break time="100ms" />"Oh shepherd, pray, my wish consent,<break time="100ms" />And say what is that instrument, that instrument so long?<break time="100ms" />You play with it so nicely, it gives me joy to see,<break time="100ms" />So dear, I implore you, to teach the same to me;<break time="100ms" />Oh, kind young shepherd, pray consent,<break time="100ms" />I'll finger well your instrument, your instrument so long!"<break time="100ms" />He looked up to her lattice with pleasure in his eye,<break time="100ms" />And cried: "Come down, fair maiden, for there you are too high,<break time="100ms" />Far, far too high for the extent,<break time="100ms" />That I can stretch my instrument, my instrument so long."<break time="100ms" />She tarried not a moment, but swiftly rushed below,<break time="100ms" />And with the handsome shepherd she learned her lesson so<break time="100ms" />That soon she played most excellent<break time="100ms" />Fantasies on his instrument, his instrument so long!<break time="100ms" />The first sweet lesson over for her too fast, she then<break time="100ms" />In winning tones addressed him: "I'd like to play again.<break time="100ms" />Once more her fingers to work went,<break time="100ms" />Which made him use his instrument, his instrument so long!<break time="100ms" />But strangers seemed approaching, the fair girl bid him fly,<break time="100ms" />And cried: "Oh, don't forget me, whene'er you travel by,<break time="100ms" />Oft, oft, come back, and we'll invent<break time="100ms" />Fresh tunes for that dear instrument, that instrument so long!"<break time="100ms" />Tune-"Derry-Down."<break time="100ms" />I sing not of despots, or slaves who submit,<break time="100ms" />Not of farmer George, Jenky, Dundas, Fox or Pitt!<break time="100ms" />My ballad's the bantling of laughter and gig,<break time="100ms" />'Tis of an old cock in a c-tified wig.<break time="100ms" />'Gainst the poll tax of Pitt this old codger did rave,<break time="100ms" />Like a felon transported, it forc'd him to shave.<break time="100ms" />"Tho' tried for my life," said th' old buck,<break time="100ms" />"I'll rob The tail of some Dolly to build a brown bob."<break time="100ms" />Near Somerset House he fell in with a tit,<break time="100ms" />And he thought for his purpose the c-tling was fit;<break time="100ms" />But when he examin'd her parts; d'ye see,<break time="100ms" />All the hair of her c-t wouldn't make a toupee.<break time="100ms" />The same night he picked up a merry-ars'd wench,<break time="100ms" />The hair-quantum stuff of the wise-wig'd bench;
    </voice>
</speak>
