<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />His hands pressed my face down more and more at the moment, but presently relaxed, and then with a long drawn sigh he leant back exhausted in the chair.<break time="100ms" />"Look now, you rude girl, what have you done to Mr. Royston? Take that — and that —- and that — will you ever peep or be so rude again?" The housekeeper almost screamed as she finished me off with three tremendous cuts, which I afterward found had fairly brought the blood, still at the moment I did not feel them so much as I had at 6rst, a warm glow pervaded my veins, and I felt on fire for something inexpressible. The pain and pleasure so intermixed as to excite all the lechery of my youthful nature.<break time="100ms" />Mr. Royston presently took me on his knee and kissed me for the pleasure he told me I had given him, then asked me a lot of questions about what I had seen on the previous night.<break time="100ms" />"Why I saw you shove this great thing of yours right into Miss Wilberforce," I replied, "and it didn't seem to hurt her a bit, and then you both heaved and pushed at one another till you suddenly got tired and almost rolled off her, was it that you spurted something into her, like you did in my face just now, sir?"<break time="100ms" />I was fondling it with my hands, whilst he repaid me with lots of kisses, as his Angers were playing with and tickling my little slit, so that I could hardly sit on his knee.<break time="100ms" />Miss Wilberforce had thrown off all her clothes, and was now tossing about naked on the bed.<break time="100ms" />"Phoebe dear, don't play with that stupid man any longer," she at length burst out. "He must know that great thing of his can't have a little girl, bring him here at once to me, darling, or he will again shoot his love juice, and waste what I ought to have."<break time="100ms" />He had just thrust his tongue in my mouth, but I wrenched my face away, and springing from his lips drew him to the bed by his Cupid's battering ram, then as he got over his longing lady love I slapped his bottom as hard as I could with one hand, whilst the other directed Mr. John Thomas into the haven of bliss, and continued to tickle his hirsute appendages as they dangled against her beautiful buttocks at every plunge.<break time="100ms" />He seemed rather lazy over the business, but she, to judge by the way she clasped her arms round his neck, threw her legs over his loins, and heaved up to meet every shove of his great engine, (which I could see was glistening with the nectar of love, she could not retain directly he was into her), was in a perfect rage of lustful desire.<break time="100ms" />"Get the rod, Phoebe," she exclaimed, "and pay him out for whipping you, he is not half brisk enough for me, and will be all night coming if you don't make his bum smart, my dear!"<break time="100ms" />Too pleased not to do it, I snatched up the rod, and did my duty so well that his posteriors were soon wealed and scored, till they began to look quite raw, and he fairly bounded under my strokes.<break time="100ms" />At last they came together with cries of delight, such as "you love, you dear, oh shove it into me — give me all — every inch. Ah —- oh, oh, oh! I shall die! etc," from Miss Mabel, whilst Mr. Royston audibly groaned out, "Oh, heavens! My God! What a delightful spend!" and then both of them seemed perfectly exhausted for a few minutes as they lay listlessly in each others arms, with their eyes shut, and their limbs loosely but lightly intertwined.<break time="100ms" />After this I stayed with them rather over a year, and during that time assisted at many of their little parties of pleasure.<break time="100ms" />At length Mr. Royston, who was really very fond of me, thought I ought to learn a business, so they brought me to town, and apprenticed me to Madame Coulisse, a fashionable milliner, who occupied the whole of the upper part of a large house in New Bond Street.<break time="100ms" />She had six young ladies as assistants, besides myself and three others as apprentices or improvers, as well as Miss Wallis, the cutter out and sub-manageress under herself.<break time="100ms" />Our hours were tolerably easy, in fact much more so than I had expected, after all the tales I had heard about overwork, etc. We were only kept to business from nine a.m. to six p.m. daily, in fact there never seemed a great abun- dance of work about, a few ladies certainly came every day upon business, but Madame evidently did not give great satisfaction, as I heard them complain of the work, and customers very seldom seemed to favour her with a second order.<break time="100ms" />The apprentices were sent to bed about eight o'clock, and we often heard loud laughing as if gentlemen were in the house, and a great deal of running up and down stairs.<break time="100ms" />Madame seemed very fond of me, and I was treated with great kindness, in fact she soon had me to act as a lady's maid to herself, and being often alone with her she got from me the complete tale of my previous life.<break time="100ms" />"Ma foi," she exclaimed, when I had told her all, for she regularly wormed it all from me, "but you are von leetle cocotte, I will soon make you grand lady. Phoebe is too common a name for my house, I will call you Vanessa, from Milord Byron — good name make fortune."<break time="100ms" />Then she explained to me that her millinery business was all a sham to keep the house respectable, and that every evening gentlemen came to see the young ladies. "You have gentlemans, and I give you clothes, and no nothing to do."<break time="100ms" />So the bargain was concluded as it were without my even saying a word.<break time="100ms" />Chapter II<break time="100ms" />Sale of my Virginity to a Gentleman, who takes me away from the the House in New Bond Street.<break time="100ms" />It took a day or two for Madame Coulisse to rig me out with all new clothes. She actually sent me to another milliner to have my things made in the best possible fashion, then one Sunday afternoon she took me and two of her young ladies for a drive in Hyde Park, during which I noticed several gentlemen stop and speak to her in a lew tone, as they looked at me rather significantly. This was her market. I was sold to advantage before we drove back to the house.<break time="100ms" />The same evening, about ten o'clock. Madame sent for me to her boudoir, she had previously told me to make myself look my very best, as she expected to be able to introduce me to a very nice gentleman during the evening (of course keeping to herself the fact of having sold my maidenhead for a couple of hundred pounds).<break time="100ms" />On entering I saw a fine aristocratic-looking man seated by her side on a sofa.<break time="100ms" />"Allow me, Milord, to introduce Mdlle. Vanessa. Have you ever seen a prettier little thing, she is barely thirteen, and I warrant her genuine." Then turning to me, "This gentleman, Vanessa, wishes to honour you with his love, be as good a girl as you promised, my dear, and you will have nothing but happiness to look forward to in my house," saying which she vanished from the room, and left me vis-a-vis with his lordship, who rose, kissed my lips, and drew me to his side on the sofa.
    </voice>
</speak>
