<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Too frightened to refuse she continued to relate how Charlie seemed to spurt something warm into her, and that when he drew his affair out, it was followed by a small quantity of excrement, as she could not help herself, which so enraged him that he wiped his soiled cock on her face, and tried to shove it into her mouth. "Now," she concluded, "I have really told you everything, and he would have been locked up, only I was too ashamed to go against him; I only wish I could serve him out, as he always laughs when he meets me, and smacks his lips as if tasting something nice."<break time="100ms" />This tale had so worked them all up that Jack now called Nelly's attention to what the others were doing, as she had been hiding her blushing tearful face on his bosom as his fingers frigged her tight bum-hole and cunny both at once, whilst she had stammered out the account of Charlie's outrageous conduct.<break time="100ms" />Cousin Emma was riding on Spencer's pego, which could be seen going in and out of her lecherous gap, as she sat astride of his lap, and rode up and down on his shaft, her lips glued to his, and her tongue in Ms mouth. Each time she went up the vermillion lips of her cunt could be seen protruding as they seemed to cling tightly round . the rather brown looking cock they were sucking so deliciously, and which glistened with their mutual spendings.<break time="100ms" />The Hon. Priapus was seated on the sofa with Fuckatilla on his lap, his fine large instrument buried to the roots of its hair in her beautiful cunt, she had her back to him but his arms were keeping up her clothes, and his hands tickling her slit in front through the opening of her drawers. Frank Jones stood close in front of the amorous girl, who had her hands on his pego, ticking his balls and caressing the shaft, exposing the bursting head of his jewel at every backward motion of her hand, as she softly passed it up and down. The scene was exquisite, Jack hugged his trembling little partner to his bosom, and afraid to attempt her ravishment at the moment, placed his throbbing prick in her hand, and whispered in her ear to place it between her thighs, and close them tightly upon it, whilst he reclined backwards, and held her between his legs, making her ride on his affair with her toes just touching the floor; thus he had all the sensations of a delicious fuck without hurting little Nelly; each one seemed to try to prolong the pleasure, but although their movements were . very slow and gentle, the sight of each other's enjoyment had such a stimulating effect that they all seemed to come at the same moment, Jack's spending's flying out a good distance on the floor, from between the cheeks of Nelly's buttocks, just as the others all died away in ecstasy.<break time="100ms" />"Now for full dress, 'beauty unadorned,'" said the host, "or we shall be too warm to appreciate Frank's new dream, I only hope it is as good as the last, about the circus performance."<break time="100ms" />They were soon divested of every covering, and after a glass of champagne all round, Frank was ready to relate how he dreamt the old year out, and the new year in, so taking Cousin Emma on his lap, he made her keep a. hand on his now limp concern, whilst he had two of his fingers groping about her clitoris.<break time="100ms" />"When I went to bed last night," he began, "I really meant to lay awake and hear all the church bells join in their annual welcome to the new year, but it generally happens that we sleep when we want to keep our eyes open, and vice versa; just so with me, I couldn't keep awake for the life of me, and was presently dreaming all sorts of rubbish; during the day I had casually looked into that old pamphlet about the defeat of the English by the Germans at the battle of Dorking, so I suppose my dream turned that way, for I seemed to be in my studio, when old Lord Dufferstones rushed in almost frantic with fear, exclaiming, 'Jones, what awful news, the army is beaten and the guards annihilated, the Germans will sack London and ravish our wives and daughters as soon as they can get here!"<break time="100ms" />"Every man must fight for his home, I'll do my best to kill at least one enemy before they do for me, and let everyone else do the same, and the bloodthirsty rascals will find it costs them dear," I replied, feeling quite a hero in the presence of the old coward.<break time="100ms" />" 'Oh, dear! oh, dear! it's no use, Jones, we shall all be slaughtered like sheep!' he raved, tearing his hair.<break time="100ms" />"Without waiting to hear any more from him I seized a sword and a revolver, and rushed out into the Strand, where I soon heard that the Uhlans had already reached Steatham, and were also close to New Cross in another direction.<break time="100ms" />"Night was coming on, there were dense crowds in the streets some armed, others clamouring for arms, each one encouraging the other to fight to the last. A perfect panic prevailed at the Northern and Eastern Railway Stations, especially as all the trains went away loaded with fugitive women and children, and none but old men were allowed to accompany them, but it soon came to an end for the want of rolling stock, as the companies having once got it away, would not let any empties return for more, lest the enemy might capture them.<break time="100ms" />"All night we worked away, making barricades on Westminster Bridge, supported by others in Parliament Street, a few old officers directing the workers, but no general plan of defense seemed to be carried out, as there was no general anywhere, they had all gone out with the army, and had been killed, captured, or prevented from retreating on the capital.<break time="100ms" />"At last morning came, and we could soon hear the sound of distant firing, which gradually came nearer and nearer, till the attack was commenced on all the bridges at once, from London bridge to Putney.<break time="100ms" />"Without artillery it was impossible to stem the advancing tide of Germans, they carried the bridges very quickly, shooting and bayonetting the defenders in thousands; now they surged into the bottom of Parliament Street, and as I sat on one of the bronze lions at the foot of the Nelson column encouraging everyone to die rather than yield, I could see the battle slowly coming up to the Horse Guards, and also that the Houses of Parliament were on fire.<break time="100ms" />"Waterloo Bridge was gone, and the enemy now began to take us in Hank from the Strand, whilst others having passed Vauxhall were already swarming the parks and Belgravia, and in possession of Buckingham Palace.
    </voice>
</speak>
