<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Ha! that's how you would serve me, is it, you cheat; begone this instant, or I will inform the hotel people of your character. Go quietly and I shall only retain the genuine five hundred francs to pay my hotel bill. But for decency's sake put away that shame-faced affair of yours; see his drooping head, you might walk out with it proudly, but like that no woman would see it without disgust."<break time="100ms" />That was the end of them, they sneaked away from the hotel without settling their bill, but my Indian Nabob paid it for them, and kept so close to me during my stay in Paris that I didn't have a chance of another adventure. He wanted me, as a travelling companion, but being enriched to the extent of over £60,000 and my jewellery, I thought of returning to London and persuaded him to take Mlle. Zara, having first made a bargain with that mercenary young lady to share all profits as long as he kept her, which has brought me in quite £5,000 a year ever since.<break time="100ms" />In spite of all my good fortune my aversion to the tyranny of a husband, and my naturally wanton nature impelled me to continue a gay life.<break time="100ms" />On the journey to London I picked up a handsome officer of the Guards, who, when we started from Dover, secured a first class compartment to ourselves in the mail express to Victoria, and compensated himself by a good old-fashioned English f—k on the seat of our carriage, declaring the French whores were damnable in comparison to a modest English girl, which I passed myself off for. I pleased him so, and allowed him to kiss everything, and so cast my glamoured spell around him, that ere we reached town I had the promise of an establishment at Kenningston to be furnished at his expense, while we stayed at the Grand Hotel. In a week it was ready, and I took up my abode here, but my guardsman was too hot even for my wanton constitution, there was hardly a bed, table, couch, or chair but he would have me upon it; go where he would the f——g mania was upon him, especially if he saw a fresh piece of furniture to have me upon. Pianos were his especial delight, to mount my posteriors up on the keys, and either suck or f—k me in that position, was the greatest pleasure he could have; in fact, it was a standing joke amongst the officers of his corps about "pianos getting out of time so soon, where Capt. Somerville had his strum upon them."<break time="100ms" />Besides this he was so awfully jealous my life began to be miserable, so that at last when one day, furiously complaining of my flirtation, he asked me if I was tired of him. "Yes, certain-ly," I replied, "and the sooner you give me up the better!"<break time="100ms" />His feelings were so hurt that he instantly wrote me a cheque for £1,000, and told me I might keep the house and shift for myself. This exactly suited the plans I had been marking out for myself as soon as I could get quit of him, without apparently acting with palpable ingratitude.<break time="100ms" />You are too well acquainted with the doings in my house for me to give an account of my present life, but should you wish for a Christmas party next year, and you are a good boy in the meantime, I may look up and jot down for your amusement some of the voluptuous adventures which I have heard of, or been a party to, since I became such a well known member of the Demi-Monde.<break time="100ms" />For the present this is the end of Vanessa.<break time="100ms" />Everyone complimented Spencer on his tale, and then their host turning to Fuckatilla, said, "You know, my little dear, the treat I promised you; I think Vanessa's story has warmed me up for the business of five to one, there are only four males in the party, but I have a nice dildoe for your cousin, and when Emma straps it on she will be as good as a man, and last a deal longer. We will all have a sip of my magic Mouche D'Espagne chocolate, which I have kept in reserve on the hob, to invigorate us for the last orgie of the night, then to work."<break time="100ms" />The tiny cups were handed round, and even little Nelly had hers to sip; the effect was indeed magical, each prick in a few moments stood in a state of bursting grandeur, the girls' eyes rushed with lustful desires. Nelly was down on her knees, almost devouring Jack Turdey's affair, so ravenously did she gamahauche him, as she begged that as he had a moderate sized cock he would try and make a real woman of her.<break time="100ms" />"No, no, my little darling!" said Bigcock, as he excitedly fastened the dildoe on Cousin Emma, an enormous thing, about nine inches long, and thick in proportion. "You shall work off your excitement by birching us all round, as there is nothing else for you to do. Get that great bunch of birch from the sideboard, and pay us out with it as hard as you can."<break time="100ms" />A couch without a back was placed in the centre of the room, Cousin Emma reclined on her back, then Fucktilla spitted herself on the dildoe, till her cunt was deliciously gorged by the soft flesh-like india rubber tool which made her spend in a moment, as she bounded on the joy-giving instrument, her cousin sucking her bubbies for her with all the abandon of lust.<break time="100ms" />Frank Jones and Spencer on either side placed their pricks in her hands to frig, whilst Bigcock presented his for her mouth to suck, and Jack Turdey last of all took the position he so dearly loved au derriere, where he revelled in the delightful pleasures of her fundamental rosebud.<break time="100ms" />Nelly Racquet now applied her rod with vigour, her right hand switching them one by one as she ran round the group, frigging herself with her left hand at the same time, exclaiming every now and then, "Hold tight; go it. Fuck away. You won't let me know what it's like, so I'll pay you all out in spite. Don't your bums look pretty! I've made Jack's bleed." Till at last she was so carried away by the wantonness of her feelings, she dropped the rod, and mounted on Fuckatilla's back, with her bottom to Jack, who had to postillion her with his finger in her tight little arsehole as she screamed with delight.<break time="100ms" />This scene lasted a long time, each one swimming in lubricity till the effects of the Mouche D'Espagne were exhausted.<break time="100ms" />They had a glass of champagne to revive themselves, then finished the night by all joining in the following:<break time="100ms" />Christmas Anthem.<break time="100ms" />Christmas has come! let affection and folly,<break time="100ms" />Run through the land from the North to the South,<break time="100ms" />Hang up the mistletoe, nail up the holly,<break time="100ms" />Frolic and fun be the talk of each mouth,<break time="100ms" />For each one to flirt, and to drink, and to eat;<break time="100ms" />Aged and Young, come! now, this is the Season,<break time="100ms" />All have enjoyment — my prick "sees no reason,"<break time="100ms" />Why Christmas should pass, and he not have a treat.<break time="100ms" />Ruddy his tip, as the bright Holly merry!<break time="100ms" />Round are his balls, as the Pudding so gay;<break time="100ms" />White pearly drops, like the Mistletoe berry,<break time="100ms" />They shall distil from his touch-hole to-day.<break time="100ms" />I will sip toddy, forget worldly scheming.<break time="100ms" />Prick! I feel for you a friendship sincere;<break time="100ms" />Pledge me in a draught, and your top ruddy beaming,
    </voice>
</speak>
