<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />He kissed or sucked on eagerly for a moment or two, then jumping up, knelt on the bench between her legs, his great thing sticking out in front of his belly from a profusion of dark hair, which adorned that part of his person. He opened Mrs. Jones' thighs till I could quite see her love gap with pouting vermillion lips glistening with moisture, then to my astonishment he directed the head of his big engine, and opening those lips with one hand actually shoved the whole length of the tremendous thing up into her belly, till it was buried out of sight.<break time="100ms" />This seemed to wake up the matron, for suddenly throwing her arms round Mr. Watson, she heaved up her bottom to meet his thrusts, which he for his part was quite ready to respond to, kissing her face and lips ardently all the while, till after a few minutes both of them seemed as it were, to melt away, and lay listless in each other's arms.<break time="100ms" />Now was my time to slip away, which I did, but what an impression that scene had upon me, it thrilled my whole soul, and circulated a fire through every vein of my body, which increased so violently as almost to prevent respiration.<break time="100ms" />I was now only too well disposed, young as I still was to enter into any rude game that might offer with my own or the opposite sex.<break time="100ms" />I had a little bed-fellow, Sarah Marsh, about my own age, her I admitted to my confidence, and we resolved the very first chance to have a game ourselves with one of the boys.<break time="100ms" />It so happened that in a day of two was the annual treat, and we all went to the park attached to the hall to spend the day.<break time="100ms" />The village squire was a liberal man, the grown-up paupers, both old and young, were regaled to their hearts content, whilst the children ran about at pleasure in the grounds or a large wooded dell in the dark. Sarah and myself selected a pretty boy of about twelve for our sweetheart, and told Johnny Stones (that was his name), that we had something so nice to let him into.<break time="100ms" />Soon finding ourselves in a place quite free from observation, we told him the story about Mr. Watson and Mrs. Jones, and asked him to try and do the same for us; he was seated on the grass eating a cake so we soon had his little pintle out, it stood almost directly, and he tried to get into first one and then the other of us, but it hurt so much we had to give it up, and contented ourselves by sucking and kissing each other's affairs, which we thought very nice. Suddenly, "Haw, haw — ha, ha — here's a go," startled us from our game.<break time="100ms" />"Don't be frightened dears," said a kind voice. 'I'll give you a shilling each to let me play with you."<break time="100ms" />It was Squire Benson himself, and the sight of the bright silver soon made us at our ease, and we promised never to tell a word.<break time="100ms" />He made us unbutton and get out his affair, but what a contrast to the workhouse master's grand instrument, Mr. Benson's was a little thing only a trifle five inches in length, but he was delighted to have us handle and kiss it, then laughing when we told him all about Mr. Watson and the matron, and how we had failed in our endeavours to get Johnny's thing into us, he told us he could tell a much better way which would do no harm, as the front way made babies; then he made me kneel all fours on the grass, and took Johnny's pintle into his mouth, wetting it first with his saliva before he made him shove at my bottom-hole, it soon slipped in, and my boy kneeling behind me with his arms round my belly, worked away in the vent-hole, and gave me exquisite pleasure; meanwhile the Squire telling my partner not to mind a slight pinch, soon planted his own affair in Johnny's bum, whilst he made Sarah tickle and play with him, and put her finger up his own bottom.<break time="100ms" />We kept at this game for a long time, till it was beginning to get almost dusk, I did not feel anything myself, except an exquisite titillation of the anus, but Johnny told me he felt the Squire quite plainly as he twice emitted into him, and that it was lovely and warm.<break time="100ms" />Our sweetheart was sent to a situation soon after this, and Sarah and myself remaining constant friends we kept our secret to ourselves, and varied our amusement as much as possible, using Angers or tongues as the fancy took us, still we were very careful, for fear of being found out, and did not run into any very great excesses.<break time="100ms" />Soon after I was twelve years old they put me out to be nursemaid in the family of Farmer Royston. He was the grandest man of the village after the squire and the rector, having a large farm and a fine water mill as well.<break time="100ms" />Mr. Royston was a widower, who had recently lost his wife, who left him with a rather large family of all ages, from sixteen to two years old, the household being now presided over by a Miss Mabel Wilberforce, in the double capacity of housekeeper and governess.<break time="100ms" />Master Charlie, the eldest, went to school, and only came home for the holidays, as also did the Misses Gertrude and Lily, who were fourteen and thirteen respectively, besides these there were five younger ones with whom I had more specially to do under the supervision of Miss Wilberforce; the farmer was a jolly fine man, not yet forty I should say, and had such a way of talking to or looking at the girls, that anyone could not be slow to see, that he had a considerable amount of human nature about him.<break time="100ms" />I slept in the nursery with the children, Mr. Royston and the housekeeper occupying two rooms on the same floor, whilst three maid-servants slept in an attic above, where there was also a couple of small rooms, only used during the holidays for the accommodation of Master Charlie and his two elder sisters.<break time="100ms" />Amongst my other duties I had to wait at table, and it did not take me long to find out that a very tender tie of some sort existed between the farmer and his housekeeper, for he always called her "my dear," and treated her with every possible mark of deference, and in fact she ruled him, as well as everything else in the house.<break time="100ms" />Before I had been a week in the house I came upon them accidentally one day in the garden, they were quite unaware of being observed, he was kissing her tenderly, and I heard him say, "Then, dear Mabel, you promise to make me happy to-night?" her face was averted and looking down, but I could hear a soft "yes" in reply.<break time="100ms" />Not doubting but a real love scene would be enacted between them that night, I slipt away, resolving in my mind how it might be possible to be a spectatress of their transports, as I had of the amours of Mr. Watson and the matron of the workhouse.
    </voice>
</speak>
