<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall;<break time="100ms" />The sight gave me a peculiar shock,<break time="100ms" />I found myself rubbing my sensitive jock,<break time="100ms" />They had real turtle, and I had the mock,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall.<break time="100ms" />CHORUS: — Under, andc.<break time="100ms" />"That's something like a song, can't you, Mr. Bigcock, sing us another?" said the vivacious Nelly, who had joined heartily in the chorus.<break time="100ms" />"No, you little darling!" laughed their host, "but I will just give you a new Aesthetic Nursery Rhyme, and then have Mr. Spencer's tale."<break time="100ms" />An Aesthetic young miss of Calcutta,<break time="100ms" />Set all the men's hearts in a flutter,<break time="100ms" />Her bubs were intense,<break time="100ms" />Her arse was immense,<break time="100ms" />And her cunt quite too utterly utter!<break time="100ms" />Taking up his manuscript, "My tale," said the reader, "is called 'Vanessa, the Story of a Milliner's Apprentice, or Memoirs of a Lady of Pleasure in London'."<break time="100ms" />Introduction<break time="100ms" />To the Reader,—<break time="100ms" />The subject of these pages is a very fashionable beauty in Kensington at the present time; long since, when I first made her acquaintance she promised to write out all the most interesting incidents in her life, and at last I have prevailed upon her to keep her word, and am thus enabled to make public a most interesting story of a real lady of pleasure, from the days of her youth and poverty up to the present time, when she is now one of the shining lights of the highest circle of the Demi-Monde.<break time="100ms" />THE AUTHOR<break time="100ms" />VANESSA, andC.<break time="100ms" />Chapter I<break time="100ms" />Apprenticeship, andc.<break time="100ms" />I WAS BORN IN A WORKHOUSE, IN THE WEST of English, my poor mother giving up her last breath as she gave me life. An orphan from my birth, who never even knew who her father was.<break time="100ms" />Like the celebrated Cora Pearl, who lately married a rich nobleman in Paris, after having been the bright particular star amongst les files du monde of that great city; I also had a very common name, hers, I believe, was Emma Crutch, mine nothing more than Phoebe Smith, the same as my poor mother's.<break time="100ms" />Well, to go on with my story. I believe that as I got out of babyhood I grew so intelligent and pretty that I became a general pet amongst all the officials of the workhouse master, matron, doctor, etc., everyone seemed to take an interest in little Phoebe, and thanks to natural quickness, my education was far better than usually the result of such surroundings, but you may guess I had many very curious adventures even in my earliest days of girlhood.<break time="100ms" />The matron often sent me messages to the rector and others in our village, as she knew it gave me pleasure to run out now and then.<break time="100ms" />Our rector was a nice old gentleman, nearly eighty years of age, and he would often ask me into his study, under pretense of examining me, to see how my education was going on. The old man really seemed to feel his feet a little during these visits, and generally gave me sixpence for a nice kiss before he would let me go. Of course I was always glad to go to the rectory, especially as Mrs. Wilson, the housekeeper, often gave me sweets and cakes in addition to the parson's sixpences.<break time="100ms" />At last I was upon quite familiar terms with him, and used frequently to sit on his knee and kiss him, as he called me a dear little pet, and very frequently his hands would go up under my clothes, till they felt my thighs and even something else, as he explained to me what a pity and shame it was that the guardians did not allow drawers, "You would look so pretty little Phoebe, properly dressed," he would say and go on all the while taking liberties which at the time my innocence did not see any harm in.<break time="100ms" />I was nearly ten years old, when one day, our matron told me that Mrs. Wilson at the rectory wanted me to help her for the afternoon, if I could be spared, "so you had better make yourself nice, and go at once, my dear," and I did not want telling twice.<break time="100ms" />The old parson was delighted to see me.<break time="100ms" />"Mrs. Wilson sent for my pet to spend the afternoon with me, as she is going out, and I have such a surprise for you, Phoebe," he said.<break time="100ms" />The housekeeper was soon gone, and I now believe it was a regular planned thing between them, as when he died he left her a house and two pounds a week for life.<break time="100ms" />Leaving my straw hat and cloak in Mrs. Wilson's room, he led me to the study, where he took me on his knee and almost stifled me with kisses.<break time="100ms" />"What do you think I have got for my pet?" he asked.<break time="100ms" />"Is that all you think of, Phoebe? Wouldn't you like to see yourself in fine clothes, eh?"<break time="100ms" />I jumped off his knee in delight, as I clapped my hands, exclaiming, "You old dear, let me see them, I don't believe you have got them!"<break time="100ms" />"Open that parcel there, and I must help you put them on," he said, pointing to a large brown paper package on a chair in one corner. The end of it was there was a complete outfit, little low necked silk dresses, stays, petticoats, drawers, chemise, etc., trimmed with lace, and even silk stockings, and such beautiful little slippers with high heels and buckles of silver.<break time="100ms" />How his hands trembled as he helped me first to strip, and then to put on all this finery which quite fired my young imagination, and made me think of the possibility of yet being a real lady, as I knew I was beautiful. Even when quite naked it banished all ideas of anything wrong, I only thought the old parson was fond of his pet, and wanted to please me.<break time="100ms" />His hands wandered over every part of me, before the dressing was commenced, then when I stood before him, only dressed as far as my stays, petticoats, and drawers, he took no end of time turning me round and examining if everything fitted properly.<break time="100ms" />Then he began to tell me what a naughty boy he was, that I ought to play at being schoolmistress, and whip him well.<break time="100ms" />The fun of the thing took possession of me at once, and as he had often shown me a birch rod, and said he would use it some day if ever he found me a naughty girl, I knew the drawer where I could lay my hand upon it.<break time="100ms" />"So I will, you bad boy, I know where Tickle Toby is kept," I said, getting the rod out.<break time="100ms" />He took it from my hand, and said, "Now, Miss Phoebe, don't spare my bottom. I have been so naughty, and if you do it nicely you shall soon come to live with us, and be my schoolmistress very often."<break time="100ms" />Nothing would do but I must take his breeches down and birch him well, which at last I did, and he was so impudent, and tried all he could to irritate me by calling me "a cruel little wretch, an ugly thing, etc.," that I paid him out finely. The scene always amuses and tickles my fancy even after all these years, and I do not know to what lengths we might have gone after a while, had not the poor old rector died very soon after, and so dispelled all my dreams of finery, etc., for a time.
    </voice>
</speak>
