<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />I hardly got over my sea-sickness before we came in sight of Gibraltar, but the short stay for the necessary operation of coaling only admitted of a very short stay on shore. However, I now began to feel much stronger, and under the influence of sunny skies and delightful sea breezes, I began to feel the necessity of a voluptuous adventure such as would accord with the natural warmth of my constitution, and satisfy the craving of my sensual appetites.<break time="100ms" />We had a lot of handsome young fellows on board, on their way to India, many of whom in the course of their harmless flirtations caused the flame of desire to thrill through my veins, but however pleasant these utterings of emotion might be, there was no chance of being able to enjoy anything more, as they were all two or four in a little cabin, and we also had two young ladies in the same compartment with myself and chaperone.<break time="100ms" />Captain Beard, the commander of the vessel, was a regular lady's man, and had been so very kind in his enquiries about me, during the first few distressing days of the voyage, and I now noticed he eyed my every movement, and as I knew he had a spacious cabin all to himself, as well as being a handsome middle aged man, exactly the sort of fellow who can please a thoroughly lecherous girl, as I only too well knew myself to be (a man of the world not too much used up, is far better than any youthful lover, the latter is too impetuous to satisfy, whilst the former draws out his pleasure to such lengths, and knows so many delightful devices for raising desire and increasing excitement, that they make the women love them in spite of themselves).<break time="100ms" />I gave him every possible encouragement, and if eyes can speak, plainly told him what I wanted.<break time="100ms" />When not on duty he continually attached himself to me, played draughts with me, or brought out books for me to read, amongst others, "Moths by Ouida."<break time="100ms" />The evening after leaving Gibraltar I was reading on deck, till just as it was getting dusk I found him by my side.<break time="100ms" />"Well, Miss De Vere, (that was the name I had assumed), what is your opinion of Ouida as an authoress?"<break time="100ms" />"Ah, Captain Beard, you must be a naughty man to give me such a book to read, there is very little left to tell, and that can be imagined!" I replied.<break time="100ms" />"I'm sure it's a highly proper book."<break time="100ms" />"Then, sir, I'm sure you have worse in your cabin library, how I should like to have a rummage there when it is your watch on deck," I said laughingly.<break time="100ms" />"Hem! so that's your opinion, is it, Miss De Vere; well, I will tell you in confidence that I have a really naughty book, called "Fanny Hill," which an old maiden lady, I once had for a passenger, left behind in her cabin, and the stewardess brought it to me; of course, I told Mrs. Robins that I should burn it, but it was too good to be destroyed."<break time="100ms" />"For shame, sir! Mind no one hears you telling me, but you really have excited my curiosity captain, and you know nothing is scandalous unless found out," I said, archly. "Now, couldn't you lend me that book to read? Sub Rosa, of course!"<break time="100ms" />"Why!" he ejaculated, with a laugh, "I can lend you 'Sub Rosa' itself, it is a magazine, but only the first three numbers have come out yet, there is a hitch of some sort about the publication, you know that sort of thing often gets seized by he police in England, it is rather free and funny, but nothing compared to 'The Pearl'."<break time="100ms" />"'The Pearl,' what's that, a book?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, the most extraordinary magazine ever brought out in parts, I have it complete for the eighteen months it came out, plates and all, but it's too bad for a young lady to look at."<break time="100ms" />"What a naughty man you are to mention things, and say I mustn't see them, but I must sir! I'm not afraid, and can take care of myself, still, captain, dear, I might perhaps go as far as a kiss, if you promise to behave yourself; now will you let me see them?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, dear Miss De Vere, if you can guess that riddle, you can read it by the binnacle lamp, but I know you won't be able to answer it."<break time="100ms" />He gave me a slip of paper, which I took to the light, and read as follows:<break time="100ms" />A RIDDLE.<break time="100ms" />Letitia has a large one, and so has cousin Luce,<break time="100ms" />Eliza has a small one, though large enough for use;<break time="100ms" />A child may have a little one enclosed within a clout;<break time="100ms" />In fact, all females have one, no girl is born without;<break time="100ms" />But men, nor boys, nor bucks, nor bear, nor ram, was ever known;<break time="100ms" />To have one either large or small, to rightly call his own;<break time="100ms" />All fowls have one — not cocks, of course; and though prolific breeders,<break time="100ms" />The fact that fish have none is known to piscatorial readers.<break time="100ms" />Hermaphrodites have none, mermaids are minus too,<break time="100ms" />Nell Gwynne possessed a double share, we read, if books are true.<break time="100ms" />Lasciviousness there has its source, harlots their use apply,<break time="100ms" />Without it lust had never been, and even love would die.<break time="100ms" />'Tis used by all in nuptial bliss, in carnal pleasure found,<break time="100ms" />Destroy it life becomes extinct, the world has but a sound.<break time="100ms" />Beneath a soft and glossy curl, each lass has one in front,<break time="100ms" />To find it on an animal, you at the stem must hunt.<break time="100ms" />Now tell me what the object is? but pause before you guess it,<break time="100ms" />If you are mother, maid, or man, I swear you don't possess it!<break time="100ms" />"You impudent man, to give me such a thing as that to guess at, of course it's too bad to mention!" I said, running back to where he sat.<break time="100ms" />"Ha! ha! he laughed." It is quite harmless, and as innocent as possible, of course everybody thinks its something dirty, but can't you see it's only the letter L—?"<break time="100ms" />"But you won't deprive me of the sight of your curiosities of literature, because I couldn't guess that seemingly rude riddle?"<break time="100ms" />"You are such a dear young lady, I haven't the heart to refuse, but you know it's awfully imprudent, even with an old fellow like me, who has to set a good example to all the passengers and crew, why if they once thought me even the slightest bit immoral I should have to give up the ship, it would not be thought safe for single ladies or young wives, without their husbands to go in my vessel. Luckily, we have no gamblers on board, (they often sit up all night, and spoil every chance of even an innocent lark), after eleven o'clock there won't be a soul stirring, you can then slip into my cabin, and look at the books and pictures I will leave on the table, my watch isn't up till twelve, then I can join you and explain anything you might like to know. Dear Miss De Vere, you have made my heart all of a flutter, only to think of the kiss you promise, I must leave you till then, or they may say I'm having a flirtation with you, au revoir!"
    </voice>
</speak>
