<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"So my little dear you are willing to make love with me, look, if I am pleased I shall give you these sovereigns," showing me a handful of gold. "When I make love I don't like crying and sulks, it takes it all out of me."<break time="100ms" />I blushed awfully, but when he kissed me again I gave him a little one in return, as I clung round his neck, and promised to try and please him if he would not hurt me much.<break time="100ms" />"Ah, then you know a little, my dear?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, madame has told me it hurts first, and gives great delight afterwards — I — I want to be a woman, sir!"<break time="100ms" />"And so you shall, let us undress, and try what yonder spring bed will do for us, by Jove! I'll take you and keep you if you please me, Vanessa, I want a girl no one has ever had."<break time="100ms" />We were both soon reduced to a state of complete nudity, except stockings and garters, then lifting me on the bed he jumped up beside me, and began to examine all my charms, first my firm round little bubbies, then my mount just sprouting as it was with a light silky growth of hair, but the spot below was too attractive for him to linger long before he put his finger there.<break time="100ms" />It made me wince, the passage was too narrow and tender.<break time="100ms" />"You love!" he exclaimed, Ms eyes almost darting fire as he spoke, whilst I actually saw his manly affair quite suddenly lift its head, which had up to this been only partially erected. "You love! you're a real virgin, are you not? How I shall love you, Vanessa! Now? be good, and bear a little pain for the sake of the pleasure to come, then I will pay the old bitch her money, and take you away. I won't leave such a jewel in her care for a moment, she would sell you again before to-morrow night. No, darling, you must belong to me alone!"<break time="100ms" />Then raising my buttocks, he put a pillow under my bottom, and getting between my legs, his fingers gently opened the lips of my pussey, and pointing the head of his moderate-sized dart of love to the entrance, he pushed as far as it would go, then feeling the obstruction of my hymen, he paused for a moment, then thrust so suddenly and fiercely that I fainted from the excessive pain, but he effected his purpose at once, so that my defloweration was complete, and he was buried to the roots of his hair when I came to myself in a minute or two.<break time="100ms" />Presently he began to move, thrusting slowly in and out, with a poking kind of motion, then I felt his warm juice spurt right up into my vitals as it were, and so oil the wounded passage that I soon began to feel some pleasureable sensations, which increased as he went on again till I began to meet him with all the ardour of my warm temperament, now fairly aroused for the first time to the true joys of womanhood.<break time="100ms" />How we struggled, lovingly and yet almost furiously, to get more love from each other. My champion was a good man, and his size just suited me, we swam in delight three times before he was compelled to cry a go.<break time="100ms" />Then embracing me most tenderly, he sponged my lacerated parts till he had cooled them, and removed all trace of the havoc he had committed. I really loved him for his tender kindness, and when he made me dress and took me in his carriage, in spite of all Madame's protestations that she would not have me taken away, I threw my arms round his neck and sobbed with tears of gratitude.<break time="100ms" />We went to a fine hotel, and the next day saw me installed as his mistress in a pretty suite of chambers at the West End, near Belgrave Square.<break time="100ms" />I do not want to mention his name, but shall simply call him My Lord, he was so kind to me, and I believe from the first almost loved me to distraction, he got French, English, and musical governesses for me, and took the greatest possible pleasure in seeing me do the honours of his table when a friend or friends visited at our chambers, but it was not to last long, only two brief happy, happy years, and then all was blown to the winds, at least of that real and pure happiness which I enjoyed with him.<break time="100ms" />He had a bosom friend, a Mr. Gower, in fact a regular chum, who spent hours with him every day, they were partners in every sport, on turf and in everything. He was a much younger and handsomer man than his lordship, and being so often in his company, sometimes he would call and catch me alone, and wait for my protector.<break time="100ms" />My God! what an oily tongue that serpent had! How he flattered me and led me on till I really loved him as much as his friend, it was rank adultery. I felt I must have him, and that he would soon ask me to be unfaithful to my protector, to whom I owed my happiness, my all; still I knew I should yield, I had a fancy and couldn't help myself.<break time="100ms" />At last the fatal promise was given, but we had to wait for an opportunity for the feast of love we were to taste on the sly.<break time="100ms" />Our's were the only inhabited chambers in the house at night, and his lordship seldom left me to sleep alone.<break time="100ms" />At last the chance came, my protector had a great match on at Newmarket, but Mr. Gower was too ill to go with him. As soon as he had started I gave my servant a holiday for the night, and about eight o'clock in the evening my paramour came. I was careful to put up the chain to the street door, his lordship had a latch key, and my guilty conscience told me there was just a chance of his return, although extremely improbable.<break time="100ms" />How lovingly we walked up the stairs together, after a long luscious kiss behind the street door. I had prepared a nice little cold collation with plenty of champagne, for I must admit having always had a great partiality for the sparkling fizz.<break time="100ms" />How he bore me to the sofa in a perfect transport of impatience, raised my clothes, and kneeling down, printed hot burning kisses on the sensitive spot itself, till I fairly begged he would give me a better proof of his manhood.<break time="100ms" />Our first conjunction was far too impassioned to last long, we came together at once in a Hood of bliss, but he kept his place, and soon almost drove me out of my mind by the thrilling effect of his thrusts, he was a little bigger made than his lordship, and Riled me up so tightly that it seemed most exquisite. However, this second turn came to the usual delicious ending, then we sat down to supper, and I must confess he was allowed to pledge me so frequently in bumpers of champagne, that I got quite lecherous, threw off my clothes, made him undress, and then persisted in sitting on his lap with his fine John Thomas buried to the hilt in my crack, and throbbing inside in response to the delicious love grips my tight sheath kept indulging him with.<break time="100ms" />At last we went to bed, and then commenced a regular battle of love, my champion was quite my equal in lust; how we joined and grappled in our love struggles, each one unable to subdue the raging fires of the other, or even a little quench the constantly increasing flame of desire.<break time="100ms" />"Hark! I hear a key in the street door," I whispered in alarm, "it must be My Lord returned, what shall we do?"
    </voice>
</speak>
