<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />On plea of a headache I kept on deck, and did not retire at the same time as Mlle. Zara and the other two young ladies who occupied our cabin, and as soon as I found all clear, slipped into the captain's room, which was a most comfortably furnished place, roomy, with a good sized table under a brilliant swinging lamp at one side, whilst at the other was his berth with the curtains closely drawn. Several small books, with very unpretending covers, lay upon the table, and at once attracted my attention, so I sat down for a good look over them. The first I took up had a curious frontispiece of a gentleman holding his cocked hat partly in front of a laughing face, whilst his open breeches exposed the delight of life in all its rampant glory; an extraordinary thrill passed through my whole frame as I caught sight of it, and caused me to exclaim to myself almost sotto voce, "How I should like to see the real thing at this moment!"<break time="100ms" />"You have your wish, darling!" some one said in reply, which gave me quite a start, as I thought it must be one of the young officers or a passenger, but to my great astonishment there was the captain getting out of his berth, and nothing but his shirt to cover his nakedness. "What a fairy you must be, Miss De Vere, you wished, and, Presto! here it is, all alive and real!" as he raised his shirt to expose a fine looking ladies' toy to my astonished gaze.<break time="100ms" />"Pray, sir, for heaven's sake! cover up that awfully dreadful looking thing!" I said in a loud whisper.<break time="100ms" />"It's only that to an old maid, not to a delightfully voluptuous minded pretty girl as I guess you to be. Darling, you can't look me in the face and say truthfully that you are a stranger to the delights of sexual intercourse?"<break time="100ms" />"No, captain, I don't wish to pretend to such squeamish morality, according to my code of morals; love is very nice, and a proper thing to indulge in between discreet people, and is only immoral and scandalous when found out. I would never have encouraged you, as I know I have, had I not believed you to be a very prudent man with a reputation to preserve."<break time="100ms" />"Your remarks show more wisdom than I should have expected in one so young; besides, do you not find that we middle aged men of the world know better how to please the ladies, and prolong the pleasure than young men or youths who are so impetuous that everything is over almost before you begin to realise its pleasures. This is 'Fanny Hill,' the celebrated book that everybody has heard of, but so few seen, because it is so difficult to purchase, as shopkeepers who risk selling such books are liable to two years imprisonment," he said, taking a book from the table and drawing me on his lap on the couch, at the end of the cabin, where I sat on his knee as he turned over the leaves, and pointed out all the variety of enjoyment depicted in the numerous and luscious plates.<break time="100ms" />My whole frame quivered with emotion, and I could feel his frightfully stiff affair throbbing under my bottom as I sat on his lap, and hardly resisted his busy hands, as they were rapidly unfastening every part of my dress.<break time="100ms" />My head dropped on his shoulder as I whispered faintly, "Oh, do let me go, it is too bad to have let me see such things!" Yet I never made any effort to get away from him; he glued his lips to mine, and tipped the velvet so delight- fully that my tongue involuntarily responded to the loving challenge, and at the same moment a blissful shudder, which ran through my body, must have let him know that the critical moment had arrived in spite of myself.<break time="100ms" />"My God, darling, I have made you come!" he said, laying me gently back on the sofa, "I must kiss you till you come again, and suck up every drop of the pearly nectar of love as it distils from the petals of your rosebud."<break time="100ms" />Almost quicker than I can write it he had turned up my skirts and found the critical spot, my legs opened mechanically at the first touch of his lascivious tongue, as I felt it at the entrance of my crack.<break time="100ms" />Good heavens! how he tickled my clitoris, as I came again and again, my very soul seemed to melt into his mouth, under the combined titillation of his tongue, fingers and long beard, which last, by its friction on the lips of my slit, added considerably to my exquisite pleasure.<break time="100ms" />At last I begged he would get up and let me have him in the orthodox fashion, but he first divested himself of his shirt, then pulled off everything from me till I was as naked as he was, then throwing himself upon me, his mouth sought not my lips, but the little strawberry nipples of my small firm orbs of love. The ravenous manner in which he sucked and almost devoured them was so exciting that I threw my legs over his buttocks, and with my right hand took hold of his modest affair which had been resting and palpitating on my belly, as if afraid to go near my Venus's wrinkle.<break time="100ms" />How I burned to feel it inside me, his ardent attentions to my titties shot such a flame of desire to the very tips of my toes that it was impossible to delay any longer. My hand placed the head to my slit, and a slight upward heave of my bottom sheathed it to the hilt at once, as he was not big, and my plentiful emissions had so lubricated the passage.<break time="100ms" />Both of us seemed driven into a lustful fury by the previous long and loving dalliance, the Rood gates were opened, and my copious emission so delighted him that I was quite afraid his cries of ecstasy would be heard by someone.<break time="100ms" />"You darling, you love! How delicious, you make me come in a moment! My God! there it is! For heaven's sake do something to me — pinch me — put your hand on me. Ah ah! Ah! ! I'm done for, love" as he almost fainted.<break time="100ms" />After this we had some champagne, then producing a light switch of birch, nothing would please him but I must whip his bottom with it, even though I made the skin look quite raw and scratched all over. It both amused and excited me, and I was amply repaid for my trouble, by the increased ardour this essence of birch seemed to instil into him.<break time="100ms" />It was nearly daylight before he allowed me to leave, and we repeated our revels the two following nights, and when I went ashore at Malta he insisted upon my taking all I wished for of his erotic collection of books and pictures.<break time="100ms" />The captain is one of my best friends, and regularly stays at my house every time he is home from a voyage.<break time="100ms" />I only had one chance of fun at Malta, and that was with a noble young middy, about my own age, who I thought would afford me great pleasure, and accordingly allowed him to take me for a drive, and enjoyed a very considerable amount of al fresco love during the excursion.<break time="100ms" />My next move was to Naples, then to Rome and Florence, and on to France via Genoa and Turin.
    </voice>
</speak>
