<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Lord Dufferstones was ordered to stand up, and told that it was useless for him to persist in his lies, about inability to pay, to which our chief added his opinion, 'that probably the daughters of such an old liar were only mock modest after all.'<break time="100ms" />"The old man trembled like an aspen in abject fear of what might be going to happen, whilst the girls hid their crimson faces from sight, and sobbed with indignant shame.<break time="100ms" />"The old sergeant now re-appeared with a couple of good birch rods, canes, whips, and scourges, all of which he informed us had been found in the housekeeper's room, below, in a cupboard, and added to the colonel, I find, sir, he is a lord, and has been in the habit of inflicting personal chastisement on the bare bottoms of the young servant girls, or boy pages, with the assistance of his housekeeper, who always had complaints to make and faults to find which needed correction. They always carried it out on afternoons when the young ladies were gone out for a drive, so this is their stock in trade, laying his bundle on a table close at hand.<break time="100ms" />"'Very fine, indeed,' laughed the old German, as he turned again towards the prisoners, 'you sergeant, give the housekeeper a good taste of the whip, amuse yourselves by making the youngest servants insult and Hog her; up here we will let these English aristocrats know what it is to suffer such degrading punishments, and so you are a Milord, a proud noble, but I can see you're a coward; out with your dirty old cock, sir, and show it to your pretty mincing mock modest daughters, let them see their real papa. Ha! ah!! what a joke!'<break time="100ms" />"His lordship moaned, his horror and surprise were really too great for words.<break time="100ms" />"'Come here, young lady, take your hands from your face, and tell me your name, no nonsense or I will have your skin cut off your bottom by your own father's whips and rods,' said the chief sternly to the eldest girl.<break time="100ms" />"'Nora, my name is Nora Dufferstones, your Excellency, oh, have mercy on us and our poor old father!" exclaimed that young lady, starting forward, and throwing herself at his feet, with all the abandon of despair.<break time="100ms" />"'Nora, eh! a very pretty Irish name; ahem, get up my dear, you see the helpless state of your papa, with his hands tied behind his back; it's a very delicate thing to mention, but I'm an old soldier, you won't mind me, my dear, the fact is these gentlemen, — hem, yes, these German officers want you and your sisters to see your papa's cock, the real author of your being, you observe he is unable to get it out himself, so please unfasten his front, and pull it out. Ha! you hesitate to obey, I did not want to be severe, get up and do as I tell you, this — this very instant, you English bitch,' as he spurned her from him, and spat in her face.<break time="100ms" />"The poor girl was awfully abashed at this violence and insult, sobbing, crying, blushing, and indignant all at the same time, whilst her two younger sisters, Ringing their arms around her neck, added their cries and sobs to hers.<break time="100ms" />"You would have thought such a scene as this would melt the sternest hearts to pity, but on the contrary it excited every one present, and I do not believe but that every one wished to prolong their sense of smarting humiliation; at least I can say my prick was bursting in my trousers, in fact all the young officers seemed wrought up to an equal state of voluptuous emotion; even their own father, bound and a prisoner as he was, seemed to derive pleasure at the sight of their agonized distress.<break time="100ms" />"'No more of this, girls!' shouted the old German in a furious voice, 'will one of you do as I tell you immediately. By Jove! you shall suck your father's prick till he spends, for not minding my orders!' he had taken up a small sharp cutting whip, and was slashing the three sisters without mercy, over their heads, necks, or faces, several of the cuts drawing blood; the poor victims shrieking in helpless terror, clinging yet closer together, as the blood streamed from the broken weals on their tender and delicate flesh.<break time="100ms" />"'Now look up at these, gentlemen,' he resumed, dropping the whip from his hand, 'I believe they are about to shower their love juice upon you.'<break time="100ms" />"Every prick in the room (except his lord- ship's) was out, and there were fourteen or fifteen red-headed bursting penises presented to the gaze of the horrified girls as we closely surrounded our prisoners, frigging ourselves, and shoving them close to their mouths, noses, or eyes, so that our spendings deluged the blood- stained faces, or went down their gasping throats.<break time="100ms" />"'Horrible! Nasty! Disgusting!' they shrieked in chorus.<break time="100ms" />"'Then do as I order you at once!" thundered the colonel. 'Lady Nora, unbutton your father's breeches; Lady Kathleen, you put in your hand and pull out his cock, and you my little innocent Lady Ellen shall pull back his wicked old fore- skin and frig him. Now be quick, what is the use of pretending to be so shocked and mock modest? Ha! ha! ! As if I don't know how the young ladies play with each other's cunnies, or examine the cocks of the pages in these aristocratic mansions, why I am given to understand they are very hot beds of sensuality!'<break time="100ms" />"'He had again taken up the terrible whip, and was pointing them to the task with it, but seeing their determined reluctance to obey, he threw it aside, and ordering us to tie the old man down in a chair, then asked us to stretch the three young ladies on the floor face downwards, and to slap their obstinate arses till they were obedient.<break time="100ms" />"The colonel sat down, and there were at least three of us to each of the victims, so we arranged them with their bottoms towards him, Lady Nora in the centre, and a sister on each side of her. How they kicked and screamed as we deliberately and slowly turned up their skirts, first discovering their beautiful legs encased in white silk stockings, through which the tint of their flesh could almost be seen, whilst their small feet and elegant chaussures quite enchanted us. We pulled their drawers open behind to show the marble whiteness of their buttocks, and rucked them up so as also to expose nearly half of their beautifully developed thighs.<break time="100ms" />"They were all three very lovely brunettes, with very dark brown hair, and hazel eyes shaded by long dark lashes, which added to their Gushed faces, and tearful, frightened looks, made a sight to stir the blood of the most icy temperament you could imagine.<break time="100ms" />"'Now,' said the colonel, 'I want to make sure of not missing the sight if the slapping makes them spend, so please tie an ankle of each of the younger sisters to the ankle of Lady Nora, and then two of you at the outside can keep all their legs well open. It's delicious to watch the quivering of their pretty little cunts at every slap, as the excitement and heat of their parts increases.'
    </voice>
</speak>
