<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"How pretty the three bottoms looked, with just a glimpse of tight little wrinkled brown bum-holes, and the slits underneath; the two eldest fairly ornamented with dark silky hair, whilst the youngest, Lady Ellen, had only a suspicion of down upon her sweetly interesting paraphernalia of love. I was holding the untied leg of the latter, so was close enough to study all the minutiae of what her position exposed to view.<break time="100ms" />"'Are you all ready?' asked the old German, 'then three of you kneel across their backs, with your faces to their rumps, and be ready to slap as I count, and be sure to keep good time, or I will select others the next time we have a treat of this kind to enjoy. Now—one—two—three!'<break time="100ms" />"So beautifully was it done that the smacks fell like a cracking volley, the victims screaming and kicking in pain and humiliation at every slap.<break time="100ms" />"'Delightful! — de - li — ci — ous! — de — li — ci — ous!' exclaimed the colonel, his face glowing with pleasurable emotions. 'Look at their crimson faces, streaming eyes, and heaving bums; watch the kicking and twisting of their lovely limbs. See now, look closer as I go on. Four — five — six — seven — eight. Ha, that's prime, splendid indeed! Lady Nora's already spending; did you notice how the lips of their cunts opened and twitched at every impact of the hand. Now let them get up, and see if they will obey my orders, but mind tie up all their skirts well above their waists, and put the tails of their chemises well away, so as that we may enjoy the sight of their bums and cunts where the drawers are open.'<break time="100ms" />"It was a delightfully ludicrous sight when the three girls stood blushing in front of our old colonel, with their skirts tied in a knot behind, just above their waists, cunnies and bums peeping out from the opening of their drawers in front or behind, as we happened to view them.<break time="100ms" />"'Well, girls,' the colonel went on, 'now you have had a taste of what we can do with obstinate husseys like yourselves, are you inclined to carry out my orders, or must we proceed to more cruel extremities?'<break time="100ms" />"They all sank on their knees again, and with streaming eyes, begged in the most piteous manner that his excellency would have mercy on them and their poor old father, praying especially to be spared the degrading shocking test of obedience suggested in the order.<break time="100ms" />"'Then why is he such an obstinate old fool? Don't talk to me about inability to pay the half-million ransom, I know every one in this square has hundreds of thousands a year; the long and the short of it is you shall frig him to death if he does not promise the money, do you think the Germans have come here not to enrich themselves?'<break time="100ms" />"Seeing their utter state of confusion and bewilderment, he rose from his seat and took up the little whip again. 'Now girls, you English bitches shall find that old Cuntswigger, Colonel Cuntswigger I should say, of the Pomeranian Guards, is a man of his word? I do mean you to do it, so now begin — begin — begin!' slashing each of them in turn, till the blood dripped down the inside of their drawers, plainly showing by the stained marks, the terrible force of his cuts. 'It's no use shrieking for mercy!' as he laughed at their frantic cries, 'the only way to get off is to begin the task, your minds are altogether wrong, or it would delight and give you pleasure to play with a prick, especially your father's!'<break time="100ms" />"Old Dufferstones was so excited that he fairly groaned at the sight of his daughters' distress and humiliated agony, whilst his big prick, old and debilitated as he almost always seemed, was swollen and throbbing in his breeches.<break time="100ms" />"Catching sight of him, the colonel called on us all to help, so without mercy the three sisters were pushed and dragged up to the old man's chair, where he sat with his hands tied behind him, quite helpless, but as red as a turkey cock and glaring with excitement.<break time="100ms" />"We first pointed out to them the fine erection which was so plainly visible, the colonel giving the old man's prick a very painful cut as he drew their attention to it; then one of the officers took Lady Nora's hand and made her stroke and feel how her father's affair throbbed under her touch. She closed her eyes but re-opened them with a start of horror, as some one behind suddenly rammed his finger into her bottom-hole, and turning round tried to box the ears of her fundamental ravisher, exclaiming with great indignation, 'Monster, how shameful, would you outrage me so?'<break time="100ms" />"'Bravo, you're a spirited girl, but a fool!' laughed the old German, 'that young gentleman only wants to give you pleasure, my dear; go on boys, give them a good bottom frigging!'<break time="100ms" />"It is impossible to describe the delightful scene which followed, an officer on each side held the girls' hands, which they would place on the old man's prick, or make them feel their own, whilst a third one behind was busy with his finger in their bums; our cocks were let out and placed in their hands, and we made them see how we spent, then insisted they should suck their slimy fingers clean, and taste the fingers of the gentlemen who had had them up their bottoms; they were awfully shocked and distressed, yet we could plainly see that all three of them were sensually excited by what they had seen and felt behind.<break time="100ms" />"'Now, this is all play, and papa is waiting for his turn; after all, my dears, you are not nearly so loving as the daughters of old Lot, who made their father tight and then seduced him to fuck them. Mein Gott, it must have been delicious for the old fellow!'<break time="100ms" />"Nora was brought as close as possible to her father, and ordered to unbutton his trousers, the colonel cutting her hands with the whip, and not at all mindful if he hit her papa's affair as he did so; at last she seemed to comply in a act of desperation, and actually swooned away as his big cock burst into view slimy with spend, and stained with blood from some of the colonel's reckless cuts, which had slightly abraded the tender skin of the prepuce.<break time="100ms" />"'We'll soon bring your sister round, Lady Kathleen, but you must first kiss and stroke your real papa,' continued old Cuntswigger, as we made her take old Dufferstone's cock in her hand, and pressed her head down till she kissed it. Then she was allowed to stand aside whilst we forced the young Lady Ellen to take papa's Priapus in her mouth, as the colonel with a fine birch switched her backside to make her do it properly.
    </voice>
</speak>
