<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />His first thrust made her scream with pain, and beg him to be more gentle, but after going at quarter speed for a few strokes, he gradually put on the steam, till both seemed perfectly furious, as he thrust and she heaved up to meet every plunge of that awful weapon, just as if it was nothing out of the common. I could hear the concussion at every stroke as his piston rod was sheathed to the hilt, and the bag of treasures below banged against her beautiful rump. Their kisses and sighs, or exclamations of delight mingled with the other sounds, and the creaking of the bed, all put together so moved the blood in my veins that lifting my night-dress, my hands were soon busy rubbing the electrical spot till we all seemed to melt away in an ecstasy of bliss at the same moment.<break time="100ms" />It was too much for me, I fairly fainted, and falling down in the closet, aroused them from their delicious after lethargy. Mr. Royston must have run away, but Miss Wilberforce dragged me from the closet, and when I came to a little I found myself lying on her bed, she had assumed her chemise de nuit, and was holding a smelling bottle to my nose.<break time="100ms" />You may be sure I was awfully frightened, but she soon reassured me by promise of forgiveness, so that I told her all.<break time="100ms" />I shall never forget that woman, her blood was on fire; she told me I had spoilt her amusement for the rest of the night, and must make up for it by playing with her.<break time="100ms" />This was perfectly in accordance with my own excited feelings, and I threw myself into her arms at once, how she kissed me all over, then stretching her body over me, with her head towards my feet, buried her face between my thighs, and sucked me so deliciously, that I could not help doing the same to her, making her fairly emit her love juice into my mouth over and over again, whilst she for her part sucked every atom of honey that was to be extracted from my little virgin flower.<break time="100ms" />What a night that was, but at last tired out by the excess of our lubricity, we sank into a refreshing sleep, and only awoke long after daylight, by the children in the nursery calling out for Phoebe.<break time="100ms" />"Run back and make some excuse, my dear," exclaimed Miss Wilberforce, almost pushing me off the bed, "but mind not a word to any one, and Mr. Royston shall come here this evening to hear your explanation, but don't be frightened, I won't let him hurt you."<break time="100ms" />In the course of the day Miss Mabel whispered to me that Mr. Royston had determined to give me a whipping for my spying, but it should not be too severe? and that she was going to give the other servants and children something to make them sleep well, in case of any noise.<break time="100ms" />What a trepidation the announcement put me into, the very idea of being punished by a great strong man like the farmer seemed awful. He must have a heavy hand I thought.<break time="100ms" />I dreaded the night, which seemed to come only too soon, I couldn't look at Mr. Royston, or meet his eye in any way, and was conscious of being continually on the blush as I waited at table.<break time="100ms" />Miss Wilberforce ordered me to come to her room in my nightdress, as soon as the children were fast asleep.<break time="100ms" />I was put into her bed, whilst she, having un- dressed, sat down in a dressing gown to read the little book I had seen the night before.<break time="100ms" />Presently coming to the bed, she sat down on the side, and said, "Look here, Phoebe dear, that is what you will have to bear."<break time="100ms" />I turned my eyes to the book, and saw a picture of a naked man whipping a little girl with a birch rod, the culprit seemed to be crying out with tears in her eyes, whilst a lady also naked was kneeling down and caressing, the stiffened engine of bliss which stuck out in front of the gentleman.<break time="100ms" />"Do you know, Phoebe," she went on, "that birching is a great inducement to the pleasures of love, and excites both ladies and gentlemen so much that it is often indulged in, not for the purposes of punishment, but to increase their enjoyment, so you need not fear it is so very dreadful; see, here are several more plates showing how the act of love is done, you are too young for that yet, but shall see us do it, and mind, you make yourself useful, Mr. Royston wants you to handle that great thing of his, and after playing with it a little you must insist upon helping him to put it into me, and tickle him behind whilst he is having his fun."<break time="100ms" />"Have you got little Phoebe here?" asked Mr. R— entering the room in his shirt at the moment.<break time="100ms" />"Here she is, dear, in my bed," replied Miss Mabel, "but don't be too severe with her."<break time="100ms" />"You little minx!" he said, approaching the bed, "I've got a bumtickler for you, at least I told Miss Wilberforce to make one; I'll teach you to peep at me again!"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, pray sir, oh — I don't know what made me do it," I said, frightened, and beginning to sob.<break time="100ms" />"Out you come, Phoebe! It's no use snivelling before you're touched. Miss Mabel shall whip you well, till you promise never to peep again," he said sharply.<break time="100ms" />Afraid of the consequences, I tremblingly obeyed, and stood with tearful eyes before Miss Wilberforce. "Oh, do sir, forgive me this once," I sobbed.<break time="100ms" />"No, no, no, you've seen too much, we must make sure of her silence. Mabel, dear, make her kneel down in front of me, as I sit in the easy chair, then I can hold her head and shoulders, whilst you can tackle her bum properly for her," he said, then seating himself I had to kneel in front of him as if saying my prayers, whilst he pulled up my night-dress over my head, and pressed me down right over his organ of love, which I could feel sticking up under his shirt, and throbbing against my face.<break time="100ms" />They didn't give me much time to think about my position. Swish went the rod, and I felt a sharp stinging cut right round my naked posteriors. Another and another followed in rapid succession. Swish — swish — swish, etc., and if I had not stuffed my night-dress into my mouth, I should have howled with pain, the cuts were so sharp.<break time="100ms" />"That's right, Mabel, make her feel it till her bottom is well scored with red marks and weals, it's beautiful to see it flush under every cut!" exclaimed Mr., Royston, "touch her upon the tenderest parts, make the ends of the rod tickle the inside of her thighs, don't even let her little crack escape free."<break time="100ms" />He held my head down so tightly, but whether it was my writhing about under the sharp pain, or his own doing I don't know, somehow that great thing of his got uncovered, and was rubbing its nose right in my face.<break time="100ms" />Remembering Miss Mabel's injunctions, I thought the best plan to avert further punishment would be to fondle it at once, so one hand clasped its immense thickness, whilst my lips caressed the great ruby head; almost in aninstant I felt a strong convulsive throb, and if I had not closed my lips at the moment he would have choked me with a tremendous emission, which as it was spurted all over my cheeks and neck.
    </voice>
</speak>
