<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />At the Holy City I had an adventure with a cardinal at a masked ball, but when we came to the point I found my old lover was actually a eunuch and incapable of sexual intercourse, much as he desired it, in fact it seems that these emasculated beings are madly desirous of coming at women, although they know they must fail at the critical moment. However, my loving toil and submission to his kisses and caresses were well repaid by the presentation of a magnificent parure of diamonds, as I had indulged the old lecher for several days.<break time="100ms" />Leaving Lyons by railway for Paris, I dropped in for a laughable adventure. I had three travelling companions, a young dark Indian gentleman, and two Frenchmen, the former who could speak English quite engrossed me to himself, and I was much amused by the remarks of the two natives of France, as they thought I did not understand, and evidently did not care if my blackamoor did.<break time="100ms" />"Don't you see she's game for it, only he's in the way? What a lascivious eye. Mon dieu! how she makes me stand, when she twists about as she laughs; what a lovely and graceful Tournure. Fancy having such an English darling, etc."<break time="100ms" />All alone with these three (I had sent Mlle. Zara on to Paris to secure apartments), of course I resolved in my mind whom I liked best.<break time="100ms" />With returning health my thoughts were getting more practical and business like. The black though handsome was repulsive to me, on the other hand the two Frenchmen were handsome, vigorous looking fellows, just such as would take a wanton woman's fancy.<break time="100ms" />My supposed ignorance of French was an advantage I resolved to make the most of.<break time="100ms" />At every stopping place I had three obsequious cavaliers, the Frenchmen could speak a little English, and pressed me to go with them to the Grand Hotel at Paris, and they would pay all expenses, assuring me they were independent gentlemen, which on arrival at the South Eastern terminus I agreed to do, declining a similar invitation from the Indian, and wishing him "Au revoir" just to air my little French.<break time="100ms" />At the table d'hote, and in the evening to the theatre, my new friends were all compliments, and little double entendres in broken English, and when I finally parted with them for the night it was with great hopes of seducing me on their side, which I had carefully fanned all the while they were with me.<break time="100ms" />Bolting the door carefully, as I fancied they might be bold enough to take the liberty of intruding on my privacy, I proceeded to undress and have a bath, which I had ordered to be prepared in the room. Once or twice I fancied I heard a suppressed sigh or some one breathing in the room, and thought that whoever they were, the sight would do them good, and it tickled my fancy to think what a rampagious state the sight of my naked figure might drive them into.<break time="100ms" />A deeper sigh than usual drew my attention to the bed, certainly there was a person in it, and moving too. Quick as thought and naked as I was, I rushed across the room, and pulling off the bedclothes, there lay my Indian in the very act of emission, I had caught him with his hands upon himself, enjoying the sight of my bathing and his masturbation at the same time.<break time="100ms" />"Dear lady, forgive me, your charms made me desperate and when you preferred those two canaille of Frenchmen to me, an Indian prince, I resolved to have you in spite of all. I can do anything here, as I pay for my rooms in the hotel all the year round. Jump into bed as you are, don't put on your envious night chemise!"<break time="100ms" />"Not with a black man, no money shall tempt me; be off, or I'll ring for help!" I exclaimed.<break time="100ms" />"Every woman has her price, and yours shall be diamonds," he laughed. "See, I will place this necklet around my standing Priapus, and your own hand must remove it; and then anything else you may wish for shall be yours."<break time="100ms" />Too good to be refused and resolved to make the most of such a Croesus, I got into bed by his side, and taking my handkerchief wiped and kissed his affair as I took possession of the guerdon of love, then kneeling over his face I presented my longing gap to his lips for him to kiss, and shall never forget how he sucked and thrust in his tongue, it was the longest I ever knew a man to have, the warm bath had so warmed and prepared me for pleasurable excitement, that I fell back in ecstasy almost in a moment after feeling the lascivious touches of that electric tongue, this made him furious with lust, he sprang up and threw himself upon me with all the impetuosity of his nature. His love dart entered, it filled and continued to swell up inside my vagina in such an extraordinary manner, that I had never felt anything like it before. If his arms had not encircled me like a vice, I could not have got away from him, he could neither push further or withdraw. He kissed me, and thrust his tongue into my mouth, till I could scarcely get my breath, while both our bodies trembled with emotion, and I could feel a constantly recurring emission from him every few minutes.<break time="100ms" />How long this lasted it is impossible to say, for I fainted, and when I came to myself should have been sure it was only some frightful nightmare, but for the casket and diamond necklet, besides a rouleau of notes which I found on the dressing-table.<break time="100ms" />At dejeuner I was joined by my two Frenchmen, and heard one tell the other that the only way to get me was to make me drunk, so they invited me to take wine in their apartments, but they little reckoned they would meet their match, as I slyly emptied every glass under the table, and joining them in every toast, at last had the satisfaction of seeing both of them under the table, where I left my lovers who had got through one hundred and fifty francs worth of wine to no purpose.<break time="100ms" />The night I spent with my Indian prince, and experienced the same delightfully awful sensations, and again met my Frenchmen at dejeuner in the morning. One now plainly told the other that money was my object, observing, "give her one thousand francs of our notes," with a sly laugh, which made me at once suspect they were escrocs or card sharpers. After the repast one of them escorted me to the drawing room, and finding ourselves alone, threw himself on a sofa by my side, and coolly taking out his John Thomas in a standing state, told me it was the yesterday's champagne had so heated him he must have me.<break time="100ms" />"What a joke, Monsieur, but perhaps I might for the one thousand francs your friend told you to offer me; that is, if they are genuine!" I replied laughingly in French.<break time="100ms" />"Ma foi, and you understood all we have talked about, but look, my notes are genuine!" as he handed me a five hundred franc note; "Look, I have more like it as soon as I've enjoyed you," he said, holding the case open for me to put it back with its companions; but instead of doing so I abstracted another, which I saw in a moment was a flash one.
    </voice>
</speak>
