<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />The craven-hearted coward was frightened in a moment, and would have been caught where he was but I had the presence of mind to shove him into a closet on the landing, and throw his clothes after him. The bell was ringing furiously, and the knocker made a fearful din. So kicking all the debris of the supper under the table, and only leaving my own plate and glass, I at last put on a wrapper and let him in.<break time="100ms" />"What a time you were, Vanessa, there's been an accident on the line, so I returned to town, and shall go in the morning again."<break time="100ms" />"Yes, love, I couldn't help it, I was fast asleep, the fact is I've drunk a whole bottle of fizz to myself, dearie," I replied with a feigned yawn.<break time="100ms" />"Zounds, girl! what a state the bed is in!" he exclaimed, noticing it for the first time. "Who have you had here?"<break time="100ms" />"No one, love, pray don't look so cross, I have been tossing about for hours thinking of you, and only a little while ago fell off to sleep and had a frightful night-mare, dreaming we had been captured by brigands, they tied you to a tree and were just drawing lots who was to have your little girl, when your knocking and ringing put an end to it; wouldn't it have been awful to have been really true?"<break time="100ms" />"Then I suppose, Vanessa, that I'm the brigand to have you, now I've got in?" he said, his face relaxing into a smile, and beginning to throw off his clothes. "I wanted you awfully a little while ago, when our train was blocked on the line and that is the cause of my coming back for a bit of love."<break time="100ms" />"Then love, come to bed quickly, I do want you so, you will divert my thoughts, and cool my hot blood," I said, hoping to distract his attention, and prevent notice being taken of the debris under the table, and more especially as I fancied I heard my gallant sneaking downstairs at the moment.<break time="100ms" />Throwing off his clothes, he carried me to the bed with an impetuosity quite unusual to him, as he laid me upon my back and got between my readily opening legs, my hand guided his impatient courser to the love mark, which, notwithstanding all its previous battering and the night I had had, was again in a tremor of longing expectation, my blood had been so fired by the champagne that my lubricity was perfectly unquenchable, I felt as if I could have engaged a dozen lusty men, one after the other, at that moment.<break time="100ms" />The insertion of a second priapus in my excited affair seemed such a bon bouche and unexpected pleasure, as it glided slowly up the well-lubricated sheath, and if he had not been especially amorous he must have noticed that I was not nearly so tight as usual on a first penetration. My arms clasped him closely to my body, our lips met in hot burning kisses, I sucked his tongue into my mouth in the most lascivious manner, my legs crossing over his buttocks with all the abandon of a perfect bacchante.<break time="100ms" />Almost in an instant, before he had given more than three vigorous thrusts, I felt the warm rush of his seed up into my very vitals, which had such a thrilling effect on me that my own emission instantly Rowed in response to his, the floodgates of love mingled their flow in the most ecstatic manner.<break time="100ms" />Without for a moment relaxing in stiffness, his weapon kept its place in my hot throbbing sheath, and soon commenced another course (it must have been the heat of my vagina, which infused, or rather, kept such strength in him, for it was quite unusual), his swollen and eager courser plunged forward in the most vigorous manner, and so worked up all the lubricity of my nature, that quite forgetting everything else, I fancied it was my paramour still in my arms, and just at the moment of coming, I murmured "Oh, Henry! Oh, Gower, I shall die, you kill me with love you darling."<break time="100ms" />He sprang from my embrace as if a serpent had stung him, exclaiming, "Vile wretch, that's it, is it, he must have been here when I came? Ha! what's this, his watch, by God!" as he caught a glimpse of the chain peeping from under the pillow, and thrusting his hand under brought out the damning evidence of our guilt.<break time="100ms" />"Revenge is sweet, however," he went on, grinding his teeth and white with rage, "I'll kill you first and him afterwards."<break time="100ms" />Paralyzed with fear, and seeing him take up a small stiletto belonging to myself, from the toilet table, I threw myself on my knees, all naked as I was, and clasped my hands round his waist, imploring and shrieking for mercy! mercy! ! mercy! ! ! mercy! ! ! afraid to look up and meet his relentless look. My face was buried in the dark hair at the bottom of his belly, with his stiff pego brushing against my cheek in undiminished size, as if also as indignant as its owner.<break time="100ms" />"Too late, Vanessa, you should have thought of that before, nothing but blood can wipe out such injuries!" he hissed rather than spoke, at the same time I felt one arm grasped by his powerful hand, wrenching me away from his body, and a perfect rain of stabs pierced neck, bosom, and arms. Shrieking I bit his arm in my struggle for life, and as he let go slipped under the bed for protection from him, where, covered with blood, I sobbed and begged to be spared, promising never even to mention it or prosecute him, if he would but fetch a doctor to save me from bleeding to death.<break time="100ms" />Strange to say, he now relented, and ran for a surgeon. "Save her life, save me from being her murderer, and keep our secret, here's £500 and a 1000 more if you cure her!" he said nervously, as he brought Dr. Smithson to the side of my bed, where I was weltering in my blood.<break time="100ms" />As for myself I had crawled upon the bed, and wrapped the sheets as tightly as possible round my wounds, instinctively feeling they were not mortal, unless the How of blood should be too great.<break time="100ms" />"My lord, you may rely upon my honour as a gentleman, unless the case proves fatal," was the reply. "I will do my best You had better not have a nurse, I will attend to the case myself, and get some one to mind my patients meanwhile; I do not think it will be more than a fortnight before she is convalescent, and if I act as nurse the secret will be safe," said the doctor when he had dressed my wounds.<break time="100ms" />There is no occasion to go into the details of my recovery, his lordship never saw me again, and in about a month's time the doctor handed me a cheque for £2000, saying he thought I should now be able to shift for myself.<break time="100ms" />Chapter III<break time="100ms" />Travels and Adventures. In Search of Renewed Health. Return to London, and Take a House.<break time="100ms" />BY DR. SMITHSON'S ADVICE I DETERMINED TO go to Naples for a few months, so in a few days I found a ladylike person, about thirty-five, who undertook to be my chaperone for a salary of £10 per month, and all expenses paid.<break time="100ms" />Mademoiselle Zara de Foutre seemed to me a highly accomplished and desirable companion, speaking French, German, and Italian fluently, so having invested the sum of £1500 in Consols, and provided myself with necessary letters of credit, we sailed from London in the steamer Garonne, for the capital of what used to be called the Two Sicilies.
    </voice>
</speak>
