<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"I longed so to see the girls again, my cock has been standing all day at the thoughts of it, that at last, in a fit of desperation, I started too soon, hoping to enjoy a smoke with you, but as luck would have it, I dropped upon these three dear girls having a frig and gamahuche on the sofa, as I entered without knocking, the door not being properly closed," said Jones.<break time="100ms" />"Well, go on, tell me ail about it."<break time="100ms" />"You see, Nelly here, was kissing Fuckatilla's fanny," he continued, "whilst Cousin Emma had got a dildoe, or something, to fuck herself with; I suppose they found it in one of your drawers, it was only a few minutes before you burst in upon us. My first impulse was to withdraw."<break time="100ms" />"Tell that to the marines, Frank," interrupted his friend. "If your cock didn't stand in a moment I'll forfeit a pony, and call up the girls to decide!"<break time="100ms" />Never mind about betting, I might lose," continued Frank with a laugh, as he could see that Bigcock had his hand under the little girl's clothes, as she sat on his knee with her face hidden in his bosom. "Emma sprang towards me at once, exclaiming, 'A man, a man, just the thing we want, and had my breeches unbuttoned in a moment, searched for and drew out my stiff prick before the astonished Nelly, asking her if she would not like to stroke such a fine plaything. Nelly was bashful but not timid, although she blushed up to her eyes; they made hep handle and stroke my prick up and down, but the little dear would not look in my face, her eyes were all for Mr. Jones's big thing, which presently astonished her by being what she called sick over her hands, and would not touch it again. The girls were too excited, but I heard you come up to the door, and once or twice heard a sigh or a grunt as the scene affected you, so no doubt you know all the rest."<break time="100ms" />"Just so," replied the Hon. Priapus. "Now, Nelly Racquet, that's your name, I believe, you must give me a kiss."<break time="100ms" />The girl looked up, her fine large eyes suffused with tears, whilst her lovely face was almost of a damask hue, overspread as it was with blushes of shame at hearing Frank tell everything she had done.<break time="100ms" />"Don't be shamefaced, or frightened Nelly, we like you too much, and will show you such fun; now didn't you like Fuckatilla's finger tickling your cunny after the slapping. I could see how you hugged and kissed her?" taking the girl's lovely blushing face between both his hands and holding it up for a kiss almost sucking her breath away.<break time="100ms" />"It's all so new, I'm afraid," sighed the little girl.<break time="100ms" />"Afraid of what my dear? Is it this?" as he let out his great fiery-headed battering ram, and placed it in her hand; "It's the most tenderhearted thing in the world, and was made for little girls to play with."<break time="100ms" />"La, sir! that's what makes the babies, a big girl told me so one day. I was looking at some dogs, as cruel boys were beating them with sticks to separate them; she said a man's thing was exactly like a dog's in shape, but I'm not afraid, sir. It can't hurt me, I'm so young. Do men and women stick together like dogs?" asked the sophisticated girl.<break time="100ms" />"That's right, stroke it up and down," said the barrister, "but why do you ask such a question?" as he was now tickling and gently frigging her tight little cunt again, and kissing her all the while.<break time="100ms" />"Because a big boy once wanted me to let him do it to me, but I wouldn't, though I let him feel and tickle me as you do, and I played with his cockey. I was afraid we might stick together and get caught," she replied.<break time="100ms" />Here Frank Jones was so excited that he declared Bigcock was not to have all the fun to himself, and with his breeches still down, presented his stiff prick for her to caress.<break time="100ms" />Nelly took one in each hand, blushing deeply again, yet with a loving smile as she looked in their excited faces, "What impudent things!" she exclaimed, as she seemed to tremble all over, "shall I rub their noses together? You know girls play at flatcock, haven't you boys ever done anything of the sort together?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, yes! that's delightful, you little dear; pull the skins back and rub the heads together!" gasped both of them almost simultaneously as they both spent at once, and the sperm dripped from between her fingers as she held the two throbbing heads of their penises tightly together.<break time="100ms" />Each kissed her rapturously, almost knocking their heads together, in their hurry to do so, then when a little calmer, Bigcock and Jones put their affairs out of sight, after making Nelly first wipe them with a soft towel and kiss each cockey, and tickle the tip of the eurethra with her tongue for a moment, just to prove her love. The former now opened a drawer, and pulling out a very pretty young lady's watch and chain, presented them to the astonished and grateful girl.<break time="100ms" />The presentation was hardly over before Spencer and Jack Turdey arrived. The latter at once perceived that he had been too late for some of the fun, as he observed whilst shaking hands with his friends, "You might have asked me to come a little earlier, but I'll have a kiss of this delicious little child before I enquire more!" kissing Nelly very amorously on her cherry lips.<break time="100ms" />"It's no slight, I can assure you my old chum; you can see something has happened, but it was solely owing to circumstances over which we had no control," said Bigcock, "I had even got this precious little darling as an extra treat for our after supper seance of love."<break time="100ms" />"Ah! Ha! ha! ! that's good, is it not Spencer? So I suppose the circumstances over which you had no control were your randy pricks, the sight of her was too much for you, eh," laughed Jack.<break time="100ms" />"Only a feel, and a spend or two; she's a real little virgin," said Frank deprecatingly.<break time="100ms" />"Well," replied Jack, "you fellows deserve birching or bottom fucking for it, that's all I have to say. I'm not jealous, only devilishly inclined for a fuctious evening."<break time="100ms" />No more was said about it, but their host observing that supper would be ready in a few minutes, asked if they had heard the new anecdote about the Prince of Wales' visit to the East London Hospital?<break time="100ms" />"No, old fellow, let's have it"<break time="100ms" />"It's not much," continued the host, "His Royal Highness went to inspect the East London Hospital, so going into the male-ward, he asked the man in No. 1 bed, "What's the matter with you my man, are you comfortable, or have you any complaints?"<break time="100ms" />PATIENT. —Got the pox, your Royal Highness, the doctors do all they can for me, and the nurses are very kind, everything's so nice, I shall be sorry to go out again when I am well, because I'm a very poor man.<break time="100ms" />H.R.H. —Noble institution, glad to hear you are so well cared for. Goes on to No. 2 bed, "Well, my man, how are you, what's the matter with you?"<break time="100ms" />PATIENT. —Pretty well, your Royal Highness, got a bad fistula, but everything's nice and everybody is kind to me.
    </voice>
</speak>
