<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Very well, sir, I'm sure you are virtue itself in disguise," replied the lively girl, "but let me advise you to take a walk on the Embankment or somewhere for a couple of hours, and leave all the arrangements to me, and cousin Emma. She will be here presently, as I guessed your little game and asked her to come by five o'clock."<break time="100ms" />Returning from his stroll about half-past seven, the Hon. Priapus as he ascended the staircase to his chambers, was astonished at hearing the voice of his friend Frank Jones threatening somebody if they would not do something; so he proceeded cautiously on tip-toe to learn what fun was up, and listening at the key-hole heard him say, "The impudent little thing, doesn't mind handling or stroking my prick, but won't suck it, well see about that, won't we Fuckatilla? Now, just take her across your lap; that's it, turn up her skirts, let us have a good look at her pretty bum. Ha, I must kiss it, wait a moment before you begin to slap."<break time="100ms" />Just at this instant his Hon. friend thought of a famous peep-hole he had once made in the wall for some purpose, so shifting his position, he was soon in full view of the parties inside his room. It was indeed a sight to give any one a rampant cockstand. There was Fuckatilla holding the struggling little Nelly Raquet across her knees as she sat on the sofa, whilst Frank Jones was helping her lift the girl's petticoats, Cousin Emma was by the side of Frank, who had his breeches down, and his prick at full cock, which she was frigging beautifully, pulling back the foreskin from its ruby head at every motion of her hand, whilst her eyes seemed beaming with sensual desires as she regarded the object of her caresses.<break time="100ms" />"Hold the little devil, or she will kick my face!" exclaimed Frank, kneeling down and shoving his nose between the cheeks of the little girl's bottom, where no doubt his tongue was busy tickling the virgin slit." "Ha!" he exclaimed, "you see I will kiss your cunney for you, Miss Nelly, now won't you promise to kiss my little cockey?"<break time="100ms" />"Ah! No, never!" was the sharp response of the little girl, "the nasty thing would be sick in my mouth. It was, you know, all over my hands as I was stroking it."<break time="100ms" />"You won't!" said Frank, getting up and turning to Emma, who he pulled on his lap, "Then Fuckatilla shall slap your bum, till you promise to give it a good suck, not only a kiss, mind!"<break time="100ms" />"No, I'll never do such a nasty trick. Ah! oh! oh! you hurt so! What a shame!" she screamed, as the smart painful slaps began to tingle her bottom.<break time="100ms" />"Go on! go on! Don't spare the obstinate little hussey!" exclaimed Frank, "it's delicious to see her kicking, and watch the constant shifting of the rosy Rush on her delicate white flesh at each impact of your hand on her tight skinned rump."<break time="100ms" />He had now got Emma fairly astraddle across his lap as he sat on a chair where she was riding him impetuously a la St. George, with her petticoats well up, so that the action of her bottom could be seen beautifully, in fact Frank's hands being round her waist under her clothes, kept them so, and he has pulled her drawers well open, so that he could see everything in the glass over the mantle-piece, which divided his attention with the interesting slapping match going on upon the sofa.<break time="100ms" />But it was the latter scene which most interested the gentleman at the peep-hole. Nelly Raquet was such a piquant little beauty, though not quite thirteen, she was small for her age, but beautifully formed, her feet, legs and bottom, were as exquisitely shaped as any Epicurean could wish to feast his eyes upon, whilst her face, which he could see perfectly, although it was turned away from Frank, had its beauty heightened by the crimson blushes of shame by which it was suffused, at being so humiliated before a gentleman; large dark flashing eyes, in which the tears sparkled like diamonds, and a set of pearly teeth, rosy lips, and black glossy hair as fine as silk made a tout ensemble, sufficiently ravishing to whet the appetite of a rone, however satiated he might have felt before she met his view.<break time="100ms" />"By jingo!" exclaimed Mr. Priapus Bigcock sotto voce, "she's a dainty bit that would stir up my blood had I been as old and effete as Beaconsfield himself, by-the-bye, I wonder if champagne jelly is good to induce sensual desires in old people, I'll ask my uncle to try it; he told me last night he hadn't had a rise since he was made a judge six years ago, it's a pity such a jolly old cockolorum can't enjoy a bit of young cunt now and then."<break time="100ms" />Meanwhile the game inside was progressing rapidly.<break time="100ms" />Frank and Emma seemed to come together in a luscious spend, whilst Fuckatilla, to judge by her excited loks, was also spending from the effects of sympathy, and the sight of the pretty wriggling bottom, she was so artistically slapping, for presently her hand dropped upon the rosy bum of her little victim, and slipping down to her cunney, tickled the darling with her fingers, till Bigcock could see the glistening of spendings on them as they worked in and out of the tight little sheath. Nelly turned up her face to Fucktilla, her eyes beaming with love and excitement as she clasped her friend round the neck with both arms, and kissed her rapturously, as she said with an agitated voice, "How my bum burns, and enjoys the tickling of your fingers, dear, it's so delicious I would do anything to feel like that again!"<break time="100ms" />She was now told to kiss Mr. Jone's cock quickly or Mr. Bigcock would catch them there, and whip them all unmercifully with a big birch rod, "And that, my dear, you would and no laughing matter, when it cuts your flesh till the blood comes!"<break time="100ms" />Here Bigcock, who had spent in his breeches, thought it time to put a stop to further proceedings, or it would spoil Jones and the girls for fun after supper, so suddenly opening the door, he frightened poor little Nelly almost out of her wits, by exclaiming, "So I will, I'm really astonished at Mr. Jones behaving so with you girls. It's most disgusting, you shall all be well whipped before twelve o'clock, or my name's not what it is; be off, you two, (turning to the other girls), leave Nelly with me, or she may run home, and make haste to have the supper ready!"<break time="100ms" />Fuckatilla and Emma vanished at once with a sly glance of fun at Mr. Priapus, as he took the alarmed Nelly on his lap. The door being closed, he went on to question his friend Frank, as to his early arrival.<break time="100ms" />"The fact is, old fellow," replied Jones, "that I have been quite demoralized by your Christmas Eve's entertainment, the delights of that night are ever running through my brain, and last night again I had another wonderful dream, such scenes, and such reality about it all."<break time="100ms" />"So much the better, my boy, said Bigcock, "it will be something to relate after supper, but how about being here so early, nine o'clock was the time you know?"
    </voice>
</speak>
