<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />Running up to the nursery I examined every part to see if there was any prospect of getting a sight into Miss Mabel's room, which was next to it, in one corner there was a clothes closet, which gave me a presentiment of some sort of access to the next apartment, and imagine my pleasure when I found that the back of it was evidently a door of communication with the key to the other side, so I ran round into her room and discovered a similar closet, not locked, so that I could enter and unlock the door, which I found opened easily and noiselessly for my purpose. As there was no handle on my side I took the key, so as to be able to open it when I pleased.<break time="100ms" />Her bed was in a small alcove, opposite to this closet, and the outer door of the closet I found had a small round hole, where a knot had fallen out of the wood, forming a splendid peep-hole for observation on everything that might be done by her or her lover.<break time="100ms" />Night came, and I was on the tip-toe of expectation. Retiring to rest with the children, I kept awake till I heard Miss Wilberforce enter her room, then getting out of bed put on my stockings and crept to the place of observation.<break time="100ms" />She had loosened her hair, which fell in long wavy golden masses all over her shoulders, as she sat in a low chair looking at a small book. She had a lovely pale Grecian type of face, which Hushed with evident blushes every now and then, as she turned over the pages.<break time="100ms" />Presently I saw it drop from her hands, as she nervously raised her clothes, and seemed to me to be titillating her most private charms, as I heard her say with a sigh, "What a time he is coming. Why did he give me such a book?"<break time="100ms" />Just then I observed Mr. Royston quietly enter the room behind her, so that he was almost touching her back before she was aware of it. He had nothing but his shirt on.<break time="100ms" />"Mabel, love, I'm in such a state, and you, darling, are not even undressed yet!" he said in a low voice.<break time="100ms" />She turned with a start.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Mr. Royston, how you startle me. Oh, for shame, sir, to expose yourself so!" as he raised his shirt, and let her see his Cupid's battering ram in a glorious state of erection. It was a tremendous affair, quite ten inches long, as thick as my wrist, and tipped with a fiery-looking purple head, which I can only describe as being mushroom shaped, in fact I have never seen such an engine of love ever since, it was perfectly unique in its style as far as my varied experience goes.<break time="100ms" />"What a monster, and can such an awful looking thing as that give me pleasure, and can I make you happy by submitting to its ravages in my tenderest parts? Mr. Royston, you know I told you that I had been seduced by my cousin two years ago, who failed in his promise to marry me, after I was so foolish as to surrender my virtue. His was only an ordinary sized shaft of love, and gave me intense pleasure, the recollections of which only made me too easily listen to your tender proposals, and, besides, I admit that your book has had a most demoralising effect on me, in fact I was quite ardently longing for you to come and ease the warmth of a certain little spot, but it's all gone now, the sight of such a tremendous thing quite frightens away all thoughts of love!"<break time="100ms" />"Nonsense, Mabel darling," he replied, falling on his knees in front of her, and taking her hand in his, printing hot impassioned kisses for a moment or two, then went on, "Why so afraid, you know the joys of love, my size will only en- able me to give you greater pleasure, the fuller your little purse is gorged by my big shaft the greater ecstasy for my love, no girl was ever mortally or even seriously wounded in that dear spot, which even now I know must be palpitating and fluttering with unsatisfied expectations of bliss. Besides, my love, you shall find me so gentle and careful not to hurt you in any way, we will use a little cold cream to facilitate affairs, and after one insertion all will be joy and love unspeakable. Come, darling, let me assist to undress my pet!"<break time="100ms" />She was helpless in his hands, I could see she feared her fate, and yet was drawn towards it by some irresistible fascination.<break time="100ms" />Presently he had her as naked as the day she was born. Then throwing off his own shirt, he took her in his brawny arms and carried her to the bed.<break time="100ms" />What a contrast between them; his almost Herculean frame, the muscles of his legs and arms, and back standing out in fine relief, a veritable study for a sculptor. He was a dark handsome man, close shaved, with fine black bushy whiskers, his bosom ornamented in the centre and round the paps with quite a profusion of hair so strongly indicative of manly vigour, whilst his mushroom-headed stag projected from a perfect profusion of black curls at the bottom of his belly. His inamorata, a pretty blonde with golden hair, blue eyes, with a rather light graceful figure, just plump enough to make a pretty tournure, small round firm bosoms, with delicious little strawberry nipples, which looked so impudently inviting as almost to distract the attention from the charms of her Mons Veneris, covered as it was with soft downy light hair, which hardly shaded an almost imperceptible crack, just visible at the bottom of her belly.<break time="100ms" />She still had on her slippers, silk stockings, and pretty garters, which added greatly to her generally ravishing appearance. I hate naked feet, they are so much prettier when properly dressed, and I fancy the majority of my readers are of the same opinion.<break time="100ms" />Instead of placing her on the middle of the bed, he let her down on the edge, so that if she had sat up her feet would just have touched the floor, then inclining her body backwards he gently opened that pretty pair of legs till I could plainly see the cherry lips of a lovely tight looking love grot, which he speedily began to kiss, as if he would eat it.<break time="100ms" />How she squirmed and twisted under that lascivious tongueing, till I could hear her sigh out? "You darling, what heavenly pleasure you give me. Oh — oh — oh!! I can't help it, you make me come, you dear man. Now try your affair, love, and be gentle, I do want you so, you've made me feel so, so naughty, you dear fellow!"<break time="100ms" />He was up from his knees in a moment, and taking some pomade from a pot on the toilet table, lubricated that mushroom-headed affair, till it glistened in the candle-light, then quickly presenting it to the dear spot he had been so amorously kissing a moment or two before, and opening those luscious looking lips as well as he could with his fingers, I was tremendously astonished to see him soon get it all into her, although certainly to judge by the expression of her face it was not quite a painless operation.<break time="100ms" />She threw her legs over his buttocks and clasped him amorously with her arms, as he laid over her body and joined his lips to hers in long sucking kisses, making (as I now imagine) that tremendous affair of his throb inside of her tight-fitting sheath, till she was almost beside herself with lust, and heaved up her bottom as a challenge to him to start on his ride.
    </voice>
</speak>
