<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    <voice name="en-GB-LibbyNeural">
        Christmas Annual 1881
    </voice>
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" /><break time="100ms" />New Year's Day; The To Swila<break time="100ms" />Chapter I<break time="100ms" />Le Jour de l'An.<break time="100ms" />PAST FOUR O'CLOCK IN THE AFTERNOON, AND I'm only just out of bed; how I have slept since that little devil of a Fuckatilla left me at 7 a.m.! Well, I must dress and make up as if just arrived so as to deceive the old mother, it won't do for her to find out I've slept with the pretty Susan all night. Ha, what a clever little schemer she is to suggest that she would sleep in my bed to air it against the morrow, when I was to return to town, and then let me know so I could let myself in after the old woman was gone to bed. By Jove! I think it is well aired now, we've been fucking in it like steam, spending the old year out and the new year in; I believe our first fuck ended in a delightful spend on both sides just as Big Ben struck twelve. Now I'll make haste, then ring for Mrs. Childings, and order the supper; what a happy thought that of mine, promising to send her down to my aunt's at Richmond, as soon as I got back, she will stay there all night, and Fuckatilla will fetch her cousin to help, the same as on Christmas Eve, that ever-to-be-re-membered Christmas Eve, it beats all the fun I ever had, but my name's not Priapus Bigcock if we don't top it tonight.<break time="100ms" />At last he left the bedroom in great coat and hat, with a small valise, as if just arrived from a journey, closed the door behind him, and rang the bell for the housekeeper.<break time="100ms" />"Mrs. Childings, a Happy New Year to you, didn't expect me quite so soon, I must have a fire at once if you will be so good as to send Susan up to light it," he said, Ringing aside his overcoat and taking off his wrapping. "I've had a fine bracing journey up to town, its a lovely day to begin the year with; by-the-bye can you run down at once to my aunt's at Richmond, her cook is ill, and they have a party coming on this evening. I would have stopped myself, but for my previous engagement with my old chums this evening. I promised you should start at once, so Susan shall fetch her cousin to do for us as soon as she has lighted the fire. Make haste, aunt is in a terrible muddle, it will be two guineas in your pocket, and I knew you could help her better than any one; those confectioners and other fellows she is obliged to employ, worry her to death, and you can take all that off her hands. Never mind about us, we can be jolly and how, start off quick."<break time="100ms" />Too pleased with her job, Mrs. Childings quickly thanked him for recommending her, and left the room to send up Susan, and start off herself.<break time="100ms" />"My little darling!" exclaimed the Hon. Priapus, coming behind the pretty girl as soon as she had entered and was kneeling in front of the empty grate, "haven't I arranged it all finely, make haste and fetch Emma," as he caught up her clothes behind and exposed her splendid bottom, just peeping out between the open slit of her pretty drawers; the sight makes him randy in a moment, his big prick is out, and ready for a fuck dog fashion, in spite of Fuckatilla's protestations for him to be quiet, and keep his nonsense till the evening, "I'll burn it with the poker if you don't leave me alone, you impudent fellow!"<break time="100ms" />"Ha, I like that idea, especially as you have to light the fire and warm it first, I'll poker you; my prick doesn't want a fire to warm it, it's boiling over already!" he laughed, not able to retain himself from spending all over her bottom, the playful resistance of the girl had so excited him.<break time="100ms" />"What a shame!" she said, "to go on so, no one would think how you had indulged with me all last night, and now to begin again so soon, sir," as she put her hand behind and guided the shaft of love to her longing slit. "See, you can't get in unless I let you, you naughty, bad boy!"<break time="100ms" />"But now I'm in I guess I'll stop there as the dog said," he laughed, clasping her firmly round the buttocks and fucking away furiously. "How deliciously tight it feels this way, I can quite fancy its your little gas pipe behind that is nipping my prick so beautifully."<break time="100ms" />"Push, push, fuck, fuck," she almost screamed in reply, "this is the finest way we have found out yet, you seem to get so far in, and to excite me more than ever. Oh, oh, oh! I'm coming, I can't stop it!" as she really fainted away in delight, and nearly unshipped his cock at the moment of spending, by going Rat on the hearthrug, where she lay whilst he revelled in the tightness and voluptuous contractions of her vagina.<break time="100ms" />At length he withdrew his dripping tool, and turned his attention to the girl, who speedily came round when he sprinkled her face with cold water, opening her eyes with a loving smile on her lips as she slowly realized who it was attending to her.<break time="100ms" />"How heavenly! how delightful!" she sighed.<break time="100ms" />"I seem to have enjoyed an age of bliss, how long did I faint?"<break time="100ms" />"Not five minutes, my little dear," he replied. "Now we will be serious, and behave ourselves till Frank Jones arrives; he's sure to be first again. Light the fire, and then fetch your cousin Emma at once, and do you know another nice little girl you could get to stop all night with you, and join in our games?"<break time="100ms" />Fuckatilla rather pouted at this suggestion, but her pretty face speedily relaxed again into a smile, as she said, "So you want a change, do you? I'll serve you out for it when you least expect it, sir! Wasn't I enough for you last night, and equal to all your lecherous ideas?"<break time="100ms" />"Just listen to the jealous hussey, she wants my cock all to herself!" laughed the young barrister. "You shall have a prick in your cunt, arse, mouth, and hand all at once before tomorrow morning, if you only get us another nice little girl as pretty as yourself, my dear, try your best and you'll get a fine New Year's gift."<break time="100ms" />"Little Nell is just the girl for you," replied Fuckatilla. "Nothing delights her so much as to see cats, dogs, or rabbits fucking, although she's not quite thirteen, and I'm sure doesn't know what it is herself; besides, she's such a delicious little titbit, I've often tickled her myself for fun; we call her Nelly Raquet because she was found on a doorstep in Racquet Court, by an old printer, who having no children of his own, took the pretty baby home, and kept her as a daughter ever since, but she's a perfect little devil for fun, and sure not to split, whatever we may let her see or join in."<break time="100ms" />"All right, dear Fuckatilla, only mind, jealousy's a thing we don't admit here. You girls must be all love and no selfishness, then everything will be charming," replied the voluptuous minded young roue as he hummed —<break time="100ms" />The ladies, the ladies, I love them all,<break time="100ms" />So let them be stout, or let them be thin,<break time="100ms" />Or let them be short, or let them be tall,<break time="100ms" />My prick's so randy I'm sure to get in;<break time="100ms" />I've a fuck, a fuck, a fuck for them all!<break time="100ms" />Them's my sentiments, my love!"
    </voice>
</speak>
