<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />H.R.H. —Beautiful charity, quite a paradise for the sick poor to come to; and what may be the matter with you? addressing the man in No. 3 bed.<break time="100ms" />PATIENT. —Got an ulcer in my mouth, obliged to have my jaws tied up, your Royal Highness, in a very sepulchral voice.<break time="100ms" />H.R.H. —Well, how are you getting on?<break time="100ms" />PATIENT. -Only pretty well, your Royal Highness.<break time="100ms" />H.R.H. -Only pretty well, have you got any complaint to make?<break time="100ms" />PATIENT. -Yes, your Royal Highness, I want to go into No. 1 bed. I want to see the doctor first!<break time="100ms" />H.R.H. —What's that for, don't you have proper attention?<break time="100ms" />PATIENT. —Well your Royal Highness, the doctor goes to that fellow in No. 1 bed and pulls his cock about, then he goes to No. 2, and shoves his finger up his arse, and then he comes and puts his finger in my mouth; I want to see the doctor first.<break time="100ms" />H.R.H. —Very reasonable, shouldn't like that myself; I'll make a note of it, and then sotto voce, filthy places these hospitals after all, I pity the poor beggars who get into them, they may have to eat shit or pox juice, or what not; I don't think I'll go much further round, I've a most pressing engagement.<break time="100ms" />Chapter II<break time="100ms" />Frank Jones' dream of the Sack of London by the Germans after the Battle of Dorking.<break time="100ms" />Supper was now announced, but it is needless to say much about that, except that the four young gentlemen again treated all the girls as if they were perfect ladies. Nelly Racquet was a great favourite, but her two friends were not in the least jealous of the constant attention of the Hon. Priapus and his chums, to their younger companion, who delighted her new found acquaintances by the display of ready and pert replies to all their sallies and badinage.<break time="100ms" />"Jack," said the barrister to his friend, "what do you think? Our little Nelly here was telling us that a big boy once proposed to her to let him do as the dogs do, only she was afraid they might stick together, but you played with his little cock, didn't you, my dear?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, yes! I wasn't afraid to do that, you should have seen how he pushed it in and out of my hand, and his red face and startling eyes, as he almost screamed, 'Oh!! oh!! oh!!! it's coming, it's coming, Nelly,' and then the thick cream drops spurted out. It was the first time I had ever seen anything of the sort, and was afraid I had hurt him."<break time="100ms" />SPENCER. —She's a sly little thing. I'll warrant you a good whipping if you don't tell us all he did to you!<break time="100ms" />NELLY. —That was all at that time, except his tickling my little pussy, as he called it, with his finger.<break time="100ms" />JACK.—What do you mean by "at that time," did he do anything else another day?<break time="100ms" />NELLY. —I really can't tell you any more, I should be so ashamed, blushing furiously as she thought of what she had allowed the boy to do.<break time="100ms" />They all saw that there was something behind the blush and supper being over they determined to hear what it was.<break time="100ms" />"Now," said Jack, "we must know what it was that you did that time; it must have been something fine, or you would never blush so."<break time="100ms" />NELLY. —I'll never tell, indeed I won't.<break time="100ms" />SPENCER. —Then we must try a light stinging switch; Jack, will you lay her over your lap, and turn up her clothes as artistically as possible.<break time="100ms" />Nelly, who had up to this, been rather impudently defiant, was seized and drawn across the lap of Jack Rurdey, in spite of her screams and protestations, her quivering lips and tearful eyes only adding to the enjoyment of the company, who began to get quite excited as the pretty fat buttocks were gradually exposed to view.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! no!! no!!!" she screamed. "I can't stand that again. Mr. Jones slapped me so before, my poor bum is quite sore!"<break time="100ms" />"Just what I expected, you and Bigcock had been up to," said Jack, and then sternly to Nellie. "I want to know all about that boy, not about my friends here; there, will that make you speak out?" giving a sharp slap with his heavy hand, which sounded clearly through the room, leaving an intermixture of white and rosy marks on the poor girl's smarting bum, where his hand fell. "Do you want another, my little dear, to make you tell us?" smacking her again still harder, regardless of her cries and kicks, which quite delighted them all.<break time="100ms" />"Wait stop!! Ah, no more, pray sir!" sobbed the beautiful little victim, the tears running down her crimson cheeks, "I will, I will tell you all!"<break time="100ms" />"Then sit up on my knee and speak out, you dear little silly, so that we can all hear," said Jack, lifting her up, but keeping her clothes up by one arm round her waist, as he kissed the tearful face, and kept his other hand in possession of her unfledged cunny, "I didn't want to hurt you, but we must know all about it."<break time="100ms" />"Well, you must know," she began, "it is not long ago, but one day he found out I was all alone in the house, so that bad, rude Charlie knocked at the door, and rushed in soon as it was opened, dragged me into the little parlour, threw me down, and began what he called a rare lark, but I assure you it was no fun to me, he turned up my clothes, slapped my rump so that I screamed with pain, and then turning me over on my back, he spit on my pussy, and said it was a silly looking thing without hair on it, so he painted it all round with a bit of coal; you can't tell how ashamed and angry I was with him for being so rough and nasty. I struggled and tried to bite him, but he was so strong I lost all my strength, and lay sobbing and crying on the hearth-rug; then the beast declared he would serve me still worse, but — but — but I can't tell any more; oh pray don't ask me!"<break time="100ms" />"Go on," said Jack, sternly, "or we shall serve you still worse. Did he shove his cock into you here?" tickling her cunny with his forefinger.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, no, worse and worse," sobbed the ashamed girl, "but I can't tell!"<break time="100ms" />"Well, then," said Jack, "I guess it was there, was it not?" as he was trying to push his forefinger up Nelly's little tight fundament.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! Oh, no! Never again!" screamed the prisoner. "It hurts so, and is so nasty."<break time="100ms" />"I thought we should find out," said Jack, delighted at his success. "So he got in there, did he?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, it was cruel," sobbed Nelly. "He thumped me about so because I kept the cheeks of my bottom tightly together; he had turned me on my face, you must know, and at last when I was nearly dead, he got a lump of butter off the table and greased the hole, then forced his stiff cock right up my behind. Now pray let me go, sir!"<break time="100ms" />"But that wasn't all, besides Emma here knows all about it, so we will birch you dreadfully, if you don't say how he finished with you!" exclaimed Spencer, who was being gently frigged by the cousin.
    </voice>
</speak>
