<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Whilst this was going on, I got so excited that seeing Lady Nora lying on the carpet quite unconscious, I threw myself upon her, and forcing her legs apart, drove my Aery steed at the outworks of her virginity; the sudden shock at once brought her round, so as to realise the situation in a moment. With a scream of horror she struggled so violently as almost to throw me out, but I had the head fairly lodged, and enfolded her in my arms as tight as a boa constrictor. Another furious lunge and I felt she was conquered, and at the same time spurted a tremendous gush of spend into her womb, just as she swooned again. It was delightful to me, the painful and hard won victory seemed to make my enjoyment tenfold more delicious, as my cock soaked and throbbed within the soft, yet tightly contracted folds of her vagina.<break time="100ms" />"'Pull him off!' shouted old Cuntswigger, 'how dare you sir, without orders, thank your stars you do not belong to the 2nd Pomeranians!'<break time="100ms" />"Instantly they dragged me from the darling Nora, who I had so long secretly loved, to be revelling in her cunt seemed the very scene of bliss. My prick was still distended in the most lustful manner, and stained with a mixture of my spendings and her virgin blood, but what was my surprise when in an instant old Cuntswigger was down on his knees gamahuching me in the most delightful manner, sucking, smacking his lips, and enjoying the taste of my prick with the greatest gusto, till I almost choked him with another delicious emission. He swallowed every drop, and then letting me go, said, as he licked his foaming lips, "Ha, my boy, I wouldn't have missed that treat for my share of the prize money; it's really the only thing I can now enjoy, the blood and spendings from a reeking prick which has just taken a maidenhead. Now get into her again, and let us enjoy the sight of seeing you work her up to the highest pitch of sensual excitement.'<break time="100ms" />"She was just opening her eyes and coming to herself, when I rammed my prick into her again with tremendous force, which at once made her painfully realise how she was placed; her pale features were instantly suffused with the deepest crimson, as she ground her teeth in an agony of rage, shame, and as I guessed, impotent desires for revenge, even biting her lovely lips till the blood came.<break time="100ms" />"Ah, Nora, dear Lady Nora!" I almost screamed with delight, as my arms pressed her body to mine with all the strength I could so well exert in my erotic fury, "I know it is cruel, but the very pain you suffer confers on me the greatest pleasure, your crimson cheeks and blood-stained lips only add to my voluptuous ardour, whilst my happy prick revels in the blood of your ravished virginity, I will also suck some of it from your inviting lips!" as I glued my lips to hers, almost sucking her breath away. "Don't you begin to feel a little forgiveness now, dear Nora? Are your feelings dead to the stirring emotions of love? See, I am not afraid to trust the tip of my tongue between your teeth." My motions now began to have a slight effect, and this tipping the velvet seemed to add marvellously to the incipient excitement, the hitherto slight motions of her buttocks in response to the thrusts of King Priapus, suddenly quickened into almost frantic bounds, threatening to unseat her active rider, who fortunately was able to hold on, and go the pace the impetuous steed plunged into.<break time="100ms" />"Old Cuntswigger was in ecstasies, he knelt down behind us, forced one finger up my arse-hole, part of the same hand tickling my balls; his other hand was equally busy with Nora, postillioning her bottom in the most exciting way, with one digit, whilst the next one was inside her deliciously tight cunt, feeling how my prick was going on, and adding greatly to our enjoyment.<break time="100ms" />"This was too good to last long, we came together in tremendous gushes of sperm, which churned into whitish troth as our motions continued, oozing out on his fingers, which he took pleasure in licking one after the other, urging us not to stop but to go on again without resting to recover ourselves, but seeing I was rather ragging after such an extraordinary bout, he ordered some one to freshen me up with a birch rod. That ended my dream, for the first cut was such a stinging whacker that I awoke with a start."<break time="100ms" />Chapter III<break time="100ms" />Conclusion of the Evening, Spencer reads his Tale of of Vanessa.<break time="100ms" />"And quite as well," exclaimed Fuckatilla, "it was beginning to get painfully cruel. I like tender love best."<break time="100ms" />"So do I, that is exactly what I think, although a few skilful strokes of the twigs are delicious provocatives to sensual enjoyment, I don't like going to extremes," said Spencer. "Now I vote for a bit of fun, then I will read you a tale called Vanessa, which I have got ready especially for this evening, and trust you may approve of its not too florid style, as I have tried to write it something in the style of 'Fanny Hill'."<break time="100ms" />"I shall call on Jack Turdey for a song first. Mind, my boy, it is one of the newest out," said their host.<break time="100ms" />"You shall have, 'Under the Garden Wall,' I got it at a convivial a night or two ago," said Jack, clearing his throat, "here goes!"<break time="100ms" />UNDER THE GARDEN WALL<break time="100ms" />I went to piss 'gainst a walnut tree,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall,<break time="100ms" />When I saw such a sight that startled me,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall,<break time="100ms" />At first it was dark, but I soon made out,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall,<break time="100ms" />A male and a female were there without doubt;<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall,<break time="100ms" />I wasn't long guessing what they were about,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall.<break time="100ms" />CHORUS: —<break time="100ms" />Under the garden wall, the fellow was young and tall;<break time="100ms" />The lady was fair beyond compare, she little suspected that I was there;<break time="100ms" />Her clothes were up, and her arse was bare!<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall.<break time="100ms" />I saw she'd a pair of delightful thighs,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall;<break time="100ms" />And he had a prick of enormous size,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall;<break time="100ms" />I heard her exclaim, "What a beauty, dear Jim!<break time="100ms" />Be quick you old ducky, and do put him in;<break time="100ms" />Go gently at first, or you'll split my young quim,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall.<break time="100ms" />CHORUS: — Under, andc.<break time="100ms" />I then heard a groan, and I then heard a grunt,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall;<break time="100ms" />Said she, "How I love you to tickle my cunt,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall;<break time="100ms" />The sight gave me palpitation of the heart,<break time="100ms" />When I saw how she squirmed on his blooming dart,<break time="100ms" />With excitement, when one of them let a loud fart,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall.<break time="100ms" />CHORUS: — Under, andc.<break time="100ms" />My prick got stiff 'gainst the walnut tree,<break time="100ms" />Under the Garden Wall;<break time="100ms" />And I found no inclination to pee,
    </voice>
</speak>
