<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Oh! don't Charles, dear, you tickle me so," then flinching, and squeezing her buttocks together, I had nothing for it but to put my prick in her hand. She immediately guided it to and engulphed it in her burning cunt up to the very hair. I found I apparently got in fully an inch further this way—the position also gave my beautiful instructress more power of pressure on my prick—then her glorious buttocks, heaving under my movements, and exposed in all their immensity, was most exciting and beautiful. I seized her below the waist with a hand upon each hip, pressing her magnificent backside against me each time that I thrust forward. Oh! it was indeed glorious to see. I was beside myself, and furious with the excitement the view of all these charms produced upon me. My charming mistress seemed equally to enjoy it, as was evinced by the splendid movements of her body; till at last overcome by the grand finale, she sank forward on her belly, and I followed on her back, without losing the position of my throbbing prick within her. We both lay for some time incapable of movement, but the internal squeezing and convulsive pressure of her cunt on my softened, but still enlarged prick, were exquisite beyond imagining. At last she begged me to relieve her. Getting out of bed, she sighed deeply, kissed me tenderly, and said, "My dear Charles, we must not be so extravagant in future, it will destroy us both—come, let me see you to your bed." The sight of my lovely mistress standing naked in all the glory of her beauty and perfection of form began to have its usual effect upon my prick, which showed symptoms of raising his head again; she gave it a pat, stooped down, and for a moment plunged its head into her beautiful mouth, then seizing my night-shirt, she threw it over my head and conducted me to my own bed, put me in, tucked me up, and tenderly kissing me, left the room, first unlocking my door and then locking the door of communication between the two rooms. Thus passed the first glorious night of my initiation into all the rites of Venus, and at the hands of a lovely, fresh and beautiful woman, who had only been married long enough to make her a perfect adept in the art. Never, oh never! have I passed such a night. Many and many a fine woman, perfect too in the art of fucking, have I enjoyed, but the novelty and the charm, the variety and the superiority of the teacher, all combined to make this night the ne plus ultra of erotic pleasure.<break time="100ms" />It need not be said that, exhausted by the numerous encounters I had in love's battlefield, I fell into a deep and sound sleep, until aroused by being rudely shaked up. I opened my eyes in astonishment. It was my sister Mary. She threw her arms round my neck, and kissing me, said—<break time="100ms" />"You lazy boy, do you know they are all down at breakfast, and you still asleep. What has come over you?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh!" I said, "I got frightened with a horrible dream, and lay awake so long afterwards that when I did sleep, I overslept myself."<break time="100ms" />"Well, get up at once," and pulling the clothes quite off me, she laid bare my whole private parts, with my cock, as usual in youth on waking, at full stand.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! Charlie," said Mary, fixing her eyes upon it in astonishment at its thickness and length. "How your doodle has grown," and she laid hold of it. "Why it is as hard as wood, and see how red its head is." Without her knowing why, it evidently had its natural effect on her sense, and she flushed as she squeezed it.<break time="100ms" />"Ah! my dear Mary, I have learnt a great secret about that thing, which I will tell you the first time we can be quite alone and secure from interruption. Just now there is no time, but before you go downstairs, let me see how your poor little Fanny is."<break time="100ms" />We had been used to these infantile expressions when in our ignorance and innocence we had mutual examinations of the difference of our sexes, and my sister was still as ignorant and innocent as ever. So when I said that I had not seen it since it was so ill-treated in the terrible whipping she had received from Miss Evelyn, she at once pulled up all her petticoats for me to look at it.<break time="100ms" />"Lie back for a moment on the bed."<break time="100ms" />She complied. I was delighted. The prominence her mons Veneris had assumed, the increased growth of moss-like little curls, and the pouting lips of her tiny slit—all was most promising and charming. I stooped and kissed it, licking her little prominent clitoris with my tongue; it instantly hardened, and she gave a convulsive twitch of her loins.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! Charlie, how nice it is! What is it you are doing? Oh, how nice! Oh, pray go on."<break time="100ms" />But I stopped, and said—<break time="100ms" />"Not at present, my darling sister, but when we can get away together I will do that and something much better, all connected with the great secret I have got to tell you. So run downstairs, and tell them why I had overslept myself, but not a word to anyone about what I have told you. I will be down in a trice."<break time="100ms" />She went away, saying—<break time="100ms" />"Oh, Charlie, dear, what you did just now was so nice, and has made me feel so queer; do find an early opportunity of telling me all about it."<break time="100ms" />Very few minutes sufficed to finish my toilet and bring me to the breakfast table.<break time="100ms" />"Why, Charlie," broke out my mother, "what is this horrid dream?"<break time="100ms" />"I can hardly tell you, my dear mother, it was so confused; but I was threatened to be murdered by horrid-looking men, and at last taken to high rocks and thrown down. The agony and fright awoke me, screaming, and all over perspiration. I could not sleep for hours after, even though I hid my head under the clothes."<break time="100ms" />"Poor child," said Mrs. Benson, who was quietly eating her breakfast. "What a fright you must have had."<break time="100ms" />"Yes, ma'am, and at the same time, as I awoke with a scream, I was afraid I might have disturbed you, for all at once I remembered I was no longer in mamma's room, but next door to you. I hope I did not wake you?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, no, my dear boy; I never heard you, or I should have got up to see what was the matter."
    </voice>
</speak>
