<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />It was thus I paid down my first tribute to Venus. I thought long over this evident approach to familiarity on the part of Miss Evelyn, and went to sleep with a lively hope of a more private interview with her, when I trusted that her evident passion would initiate me in the pleasures to be derived from her beauteous body.<break time="100ms" />But again fate intervened, and another, not less beautiful, more experienced, and more inclined for the sport, was to be my charming mistress in love's revels.<break time="100ms" />Two days after this, Mr. Benson was unexpectedly called away on pressing affairs, which he feared might detain him three weeks. He left Mrs. B. with us. As he had to be driven about nine miles to the town where the coach passed, mamma took the opportunity of going to the town with him. Mrs. B. complained of not being equal to the fatigue, and mamma told Miss Evelyn she would like her company, and as the two girls wanted new shoes, they could go also; I was to remain at home, and mamma desired me to be quiet and attentive to Mrs. Benson, who, observing no one, said to me, with a peculiar look:<break time="100ms" />"I shall want you to hold my skeins, Charlie, so don't go out of the way, but be ready for me as soon as they are gone."<break time="100ms" />She then went up to her bedroom, where Mr. B. immediately joined her, no doubt to re-enact the scene I had already witnessed from the closet on a previous day. They were fully half an hour occupied together. At length, all was ready, and off they went, leaving me to a fate I had little dreamt of.<break time="100ms" />Mrs. B. proposed we should go up to the drawing-room, which looked out to the garden, and was nowhere overlooked. I followed her, and could not help admiring her fine figure as she preceded me in going upstairs. Although pale in complexion, she was well made, and very elegant in her carriage, and sat down on a low easy chair, throwing herself completely back, and crossing one leg over the other, apparently without being aware that she carried her petticoats up with the action, and exhibited the beautiful underleg up to the garter.<break time="100ms" />I had never forgotten the day, when secreted in the closet, I had seen them completely exposed, and how charming they were. Her present negligent attitude, although far from the same exposure I speak of, was still, with the former recollection running in my head, enough to set my whole blood on fire. I have before remarked what a power beautiful and well-stockinged legs, and ankles and small feet, had upon my nervous system, and so it was now. As I gazed upon her handsome legs, ankles, and feet, I felt my prick swell and throb in a manner that could not fail to be perceptible to Mrs. B, especially as her head lay on a level with that part of my person as I stood before her.<break time="100ms" />Although she continued knitting, I could see that her eyes were directed to that part of my person, and fixed upon the increasing distention of my trousers. In a few minutes she gave me a skein of worsted to hold, and desired me to kneel in front of her, so as to bring my hands down to the level of the low chair on which she was seated.<break time="100ms" />I knelt close to the footstool on which her foot rested; it was raised up, and a very slight movement brought it against my person, at first rather below where my throbbing prick was distending my trousers. As she commenced to wind her ball, she gradually pushed her foot further forward, until the toe actually touched the knob of my cock, and occasionally moved it right and left, exciting me beyond measure.<break time="100ms" />I flushed up to the very ears, and trembled so violently that I thought I should have dropped the skein.<break time="100ms" />"My dear boy, what is the matter with you, that you blush and tremble so, are you unwell?"<break time="100ms" />I could not answer, blushed more than ever. The skein at length was finished.<break time="100ms" />"Charles," she said, "get up, and come here."<break time="100ms" />I rose and stood by her side.<break time="100ms" />"What have you got in your trousers that is moving?"<break time="100ms" />And here her busy fingers commenced unbuttoning them. Released from confinement, out started my prick—stiff as iron, and as large as that of a youth of eighteen. Indeed, I was better hung than one boy selected out of five hundred of that age. Mrs. B., who had pretended to be perfectly astonished, exclaimed—<break time="100ms" />"Good gracious, what a pego! Why Charles, my darling, you are a man not a boy. What a size to be sure!" and she gently handled it. "Is it often in this state?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, ma'am."<break time="100ms" />"For how long?"<break time="100ms" />"Ever since Miss Evelyn came."<break time="100ms" />"And pray, sir, what has Miss Evelyn's coming had to do with it?"<break time="100ms" />"I—I—I—I—"<break time="100ms" />"Come now, Charles, be candid with me; what is it you mean where you say Miss Evelyn has caused you to be in such a state, have you shown her this, and has she handled it?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh! dear no; never, never!"<break time="100ms" />"Is it her face, her bosom, or her legs that have captivated you?"<break time="100ms" />"It was her feet and ankles, ma'am, with her beautiful legs, which she sometimes exhibited without knowing."<break time="100ms" />"And do all ladies' legs and ankles produce this effect upon you?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, yes, ma'am, if they are neat and pretty!"<break time="100ms" />"And what make you so excited now?"<break time="100ms" />"It was the sight of your beautiful legs just now, and the recollection of what I saw the other day, ma'am," I stammered out, blushing more than ever.<break time="100ms" />While this conversation was going on, her soft hand grasped my distended prick, and had commenced slowly slipping the loose skin over the swollen head, and allowing it to slip back again.<break time="100ms" />"I suppose, Charles, after what you saw in the closet, you know what this is meant to do."<break time="100ms" />I muttered out an indistinct reply that I did, and I hung down my blushing face.<break time="100ms" />"You have never out it into a lady, have you?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh! dear no, ma'am."<break time="100ms" />"Would you like to do so?"<break time="100ms" />I did not answer, but sheepishly held down my head.<break time="100ms" />"Did you see what I had in the same place, when you were in the closet?"<break time="100ms" />I muttered, "Yes, ma'am."<break time="100ms" />"Would it afford you any pleasure to see it again?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, yes; so much!"<break time="100ms" />Mrs. B. rose, went to the window, drew down the blind, then gently turned the key in the door. Returning to the chair, and drawing well up her dress, petticoats and chemise, she exposed all her person up to the middle of her belly; and sat down stretching herself backwards, and opening her thighs well.<break time="100ms" />"Well, my dear boy, look at it if you wish."
    </voice>
</speak>
