<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />While I was undoing my trousers, I observed that Miss Frankland had quite lifted up her outer frock, and had sat down, evidently intending to flog me across her knee. Both being ready, she told me to put the footstool by her side and kneel upon it, then desiring me to bend forward over her knees she put one hand over my body to hold me down; then uncovering my bottom, and taking the rod, which was by her side, she raised her arm and gave me a fearful cut, which made me not only flinch, but cry out most lustily. Blow followed blow, causing at first great agony, that made me cry again in good earnest; then the very continuance of the blows seemed to deaden the parts until I hardly felt them. This was succeeded by a titillation and lascivious excitement which speedily brought my prick out in the fullest vigour. I then began to push it against Miss Frankland's thigh, and to wriggle myself nearly off her knees. Seemingly to prevent this, she passed her left arm quite round my body, bringing her hand under my belly, and, apparently by accident, against my prick, which she grasped, and I could feel her hand pass both up and down it as if she was measuring its length and thickness, continuing all the time to shower down blow after blow on my devoted backside. As she held a firm grasp on my prick, I pretended to be evading the blows, while in reality I was thrusting it in and out of her hand with the utmost energy and excitement, which speedily brought on the delightful crisis, and with a cry of rapture I gave down a copious discharge into her hand, and sank almost senseless on her lap. I pretended complete loss of consciousness, which she believing, she gently felt, and even frigged a little, my prick, pressing me the while close to her body, and then I felt a shudder run through her whole frame. I have no doubt she was in a paroxysm of lust, and had spent, I gave her time to recover a little, and then pretending to come to my senses, but in a confused state of ideas, said—<break time="100ms" />"Oh, what has happened? I have been in heaven!"<break time="100ms" />Then raising myself, and apparently only just recognising Miss Frankland, I threw my arms round her neck, and exclaimed—<break time="100ms" />"Dear Miss Frankland, do flog me again if it will produce again such ecstasies as I never before experienced."<break time="100ms" />Her face was flushed, her eye shone with all the fire of libidinous passion. My prick had hardly lost its stiffness when I spent, and was now projecting out firmer than ever.<break time="100ms" />"Why, Charles, I thought you a mere boy, while you are quite a man with such a thing as this."<break time="100ms" />"Oh!" I cried, "do continue to hold it, you give me such pleasure!"<break time="100ms" />"Has anyone else ever held it in this way?"<break time="100ms" />"No, I never felt anything like it before."<break time="100ms" />"But don't you know what this is meant to do?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, yes, it is what I piddle from."<break time="100ms" />She laughed, and asked if it was often in its present state of stiffness.<break time="100ms" />"Every morning when I awake it is so, and it hurts me very much until I piddle."<break time="100ms" />"And has no one ever taught you any other use of it?"<break time="100ms" />"No, what use can it be of?"<break time="100ms" />"You dear innocent boy, if I could trust you, I would teach you a secret that this dear thing would greatly enjoy. But can I trust you?"<break time="100ms" />"Oh, certainly, dear Miss Frankland, I know what you mean now, to repeat the delicious sensations you gave me a few minutes ago. Oh, do, do! do it again, it was far too nice for me ever to tell anybody, as long as you will do it for me."<break time="100ms" />"Well, Charles, I will trust you. Do you know that women are differently formed from you?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, I used to sleep in mamma's room, and I have often been surprised to see that she piddled from a long hole, and had not got a doodle like I have to piddle from."<break time="100ms" />"My dear innocent Charlie, that long hole was made to take in this dear fellow here that is throbbing almost to bursting in my hand, and if you promise me faithfully never to tell any one, I will teach you how it is done."<break time="100ms" />You may be sure my protestations of secrecy were most earnest.<break time="100ms" />"Look here then, my dear boy, and see what I have got between my legs."<break time="100ms" />She laid herself back on the long chair, drew up her petticoats, and exhibited to my charmed gaze the wondrous wealth of hair she possessed. Opening her legs, I saw the wide-spread rosy lips showing themselves in beautiful contrast to the coal-black hair that grew in the greatest profusion all round the lower lips, and extended also some five or six inches down the side of each thigh. But what at the moment most astonished me, and drew all my attention, was to see a deep red clitoris standing out from the upper part of her cunt quite stiff, and as long and as thick as the middle finger of a man. I very nearly betrayed myself at the sight, but, fortunately, was able to keep up the character of apparent ignorance I had hitherto shown, and said—"You, also, have got a little doodle to piddle with?"<break time="100ms" />She laughed, and said—<break time="100ms" />"It is very different from yours. Give me yours here, that I may kiss it."<break time="100ms" />She fondled it for a second or two, and then could not resist the impulse to take it into her mouth and suck it.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, what pleasure! I shall die!"<break time="100ms" />"Not yet, dear boy; kneel down there, and I shall instruct you in the real secret of pleasure."<break time="100ms" />But, before she could do anything, I threw my head down, crying out—<break time="100ms" />"I must give this pretty little fellow a taste of the pleasure you have just given mine."
    </voice>
</speak>
