<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Now, Master Dale, we shall see if this birch will cool your itching for feeling your pretty cousin's private parts."<break time="100ms" />Poor Dale had never yet been punished more severely than by the hand of his mamma, and certainly trembled at the sight of the formidable birch rod threatening his now bare bottom; yet, notwithstanding his fears, the allusion to the pretty private parts of his cousin so fired his imagination that his cock instantly stiffened and stood out, to the infinite delight of the doctor, who augured therefrom a future further felicity. Keeping him standing close beside him, and enjoying the sight of his youthful charms so deliciously exposed immediately before his eyes, he proceeded—<break time="100ms" />"So, Master Dale, you have, it seems, been gratifying yourself with looking and feeling between the legs and thighs of a pretty young girl of fifteen, your cousin, is she not?"<break time="100ms" />"Yes, sir," sobbed out the youth.<break time="100ms" />The doctor's gaze was fixed upon the stiff and rampant member of the youth, watching the throbbings produced by every allusion to the luscious scene of the day before.<break time="100ms" />"Now, come, tell me all about it," said he, putting his arm round the sobbing boy's waist, and making him stand still closer beside him. "Was she such a very pretty girl?"<break time="100ms" />Another throb of the rampant member.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, sir."<break time="100ms" />"And you saw all her legs, thighs, plump little bottom, rosy pouting little slit"—(throb—throb—throb)—"moist with the dew of excitement and amorous play eh?"<break time="100ms" />The little machine seemed ready to burst at the thought of it.<break time="100ms" />"And did it have the same effect as I see it now has on this? Dear me, how naughty it is."<break time="100ms" />And here the lecherous doctor took the rampant little cock in his hand and pressed it.<break time="100ms" />"And what did she do to this, did she touch it so?" squeezing it gently.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, sir," stammered out the youth, who was getting greatly excited.<break time="100ms" />"And so?" said the doctor, passing his hand gently and caressingly up and down the stiffened and throbbing little cock.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, sir."<break time="100ms" />"And so, too, I'll be bound," pushing back the foreskin off the head, and as quickly replacing it, several times.<break time="100ms" />"Ye—es. Oh! sir; oh! oh!"<break time="100ms" />The boy's feelings, as the doctor swiftly frigged his cock, began to be exquisite. The doctor could not resist the temptation of bringing things to a crisis. Clasping the youth tightly with one arm, he continued his toying with the plaything in a quick exciting manner, apparently without reflecting upon what he was about, uttering, at intervals—<break time="100ms" />"Dear me," and "how naughty it was of you; but how pretty she must have been to tempt you to do so, was it not?"<break time="100ms" />The lovely youth was now in paradise. In the exquisite sensations of pleasure he felt he was losing all consciousness when the doctor suddenly stopped short and said—<break time="100ms" />"This is indeed, a pretty piece of business, seducing your young cousin; you must be cured of such doings in future by means of a good flogging with an excellent birch rod, and on this your saucy bottom."<break time="100ms" />Here he let fall the arm that had clasped the boy's waist, and let his hand wander over the plump, hard, and lovely orbs. The doctor now took up the rod which he had previously dropped to occupy his hand with the charming young prick he had just been so deliciously frigging. Shaking the rod angrily at the now trembling youth, he exclaimed, in a fierce voice—<break time="100ms" />"Now, you young rascal, down, down on your knees, and beg to be flogged."<break time="100ms" />The poor boy was forced, trembling, to obey. This over, the doctor commanded the delinquent to lie down across the sofa. Reluctantly he complied, but at last he straddled across it with his snow-white plump backside fully bared to view, and a fair mark to the threatening rod. He looked like a young Adonis displaying his beauties to a satyr. The doctor was greatly excited at the lovely prospect, and gloated his eyes on the beautiful display, and, then and there, there sprang up a determination to fully enjoy the ravishing of these virgin charms before many weeks were over. Lifting the rod on high, he cried out—<break time="100ms" />"Now, you young villain, I'll teach you to look up young ladies' petticoats again, I warrant."<break time="100ms" />Clasping him tight round the waist, the rod descended smartly on the lovely hillocks of the boy's charming backside.<break time="100ms" />"There! there!" cried the doctor at each blow.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! sir, oh! Do pray forgive me!" screamed the beautiful youth, as he felt the stinging strokes descend on his hitherto virgin posteriors.<break time="100ms" />"Oh sir. Oh! sir. I'll never do so any more. Oh! sir. I won't indeed. Oh! pray, sir, have mercy."<break time="100ms" />The doctor, whose erotic passions were fully aroused, was deaf to all his entreaties, and kept on flogging harder and harder, and faster and faster while the poor boy's bottom bounded and tossed upon the sofa; but he was kept in a firm position by the strong arm of the doctor, who, to hold him the faster, had laid hold of the stiff cock still at full stand.<break time="100ms" />"No, no," said he, "you shall not escape my cuts, I assure you," cutting at the lovely delicate buttocks with all his might.<break time="100ms" />"Oh! oh! sir; mercy, mercy; I can't bear it."<break time="100ms" />"You must bear it, you young rascal you shall have no mercy until I have made your bottom bleed for your crime."<break time="100ms" />The poor youth, from the pain he was suffering, bounded up and down on the sofa as he felt the stinging blows descend upon his bottom. This action caused his standing cock to rub up and down in the doctor's warm hand, who seemed to have accidently laid hold of it. The effect was such that the poor youth hardly knew whether he felt most pleasure or pain, for while his posteriors were of a burning heat, the warmth flew to the opposite part, which was so deliciously clasped in the doctor's caressing hand. He ground his teeth with pleasure and pain, he ceased to cry out, but sobbed and moaned with the excess of indefinable feelings. The doctor never ceased lecturing him, dwelling continually on the beauties of his lovely young cousin and the scene in the arbour. He thought but of her, of her lovely pink little slit so sweetly shaded with soft downy short curls; how she had so charmingly caressed his cock, until he felt a heave and a shudder, another, a sensation as if he was going to expire, a short cry, a catching of his breath. Wildly and vigorously he thrust his member down on the doctor's warm hand, he shut his eyes, he felt not the rod, although the doctor redoubled the strokes with all the force of his arm, and drew blood at every cut. A bound, a convulsive start, and he felt as if his lifeblood were coming from him—out it spurted in large drops on the sofa and on the doctor's hand. The youth had with difficulty shed another tribute to Venus. For a moment or two he felt as if in paradise, but a sharp cut from the rod quickly aroused him. He was soon fully alive again to its tortures.
    </voice>
</speak>
