<speak version="1.0" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2001/10/synthesis" xml:lang="zh-HK">
    
    <voice name="en-GB-RyanNeural">
        <break time="100ms" />"Why, you young rascal, what is this you have been doing on my best sofa, eh, sir?" said the doctor.<break time="100ms" />Another sharp stroke demanded a reply.<break time="100ms" />"I, sir. Oh! sir; indeed I—that is—indeed, I don't know."<break time="100ms" />"No lies or evasions here, sir, for they will not avail you. Your bottom shall pay for this nastiness. Why, what is it? What can it be? I never saw the like of this in my life, I declare," and he examined it with his eyeglass, saying more to the same effect.<break time="100ms" />Poor Master Dale was, we know, quite in the dark as to what it could be, or how it came there.<break time="100ms" />"Has this ever occurred to you before," asked the doctor.<break time="100ms" />"Yes, sir, yesterday, when my cousin was caressing it in her mouth," replied the frightened youth, "but I really don't know how it happened, and did not mean any harm."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, indeed!" said the doctor, "your mother did not mention that, did she see you?"<break time="100ms" />"No, sir, it happened just as she was coming through the shrubbery, and was all over before she reached the arbour."<break time="100ms" />"And so your cousin took it into her mouth, why did she do that?"<break time="100ms" />"She was curious to see what was under the skin of its head, and finding it would not go back without hurting me, she put it into her mouth to wet it and make it go back easier, which it did for the first time; she pulled it forward again, and again put it into her mouth to push the skin back with her lips, when I felt funny all over, and something came out of me into her mouth."<break time="100ms" />"Indeed! Well, you must tell me all about that another time. This flogging will be enough for the present, but I shall punish you for your nastiness some other time. Put up your trousers, in a day or two I shall want you in this room to pay for your dirty conduct."<break time="100ms" />The poor boy retired, sobbing hysterically.<break time="100ms" />The second day after this the doctor sent for Master Dale, who, in the meantime, had occupied the bedroom next to mine. The doctor was in his private room in his dressing-gown, long and flowing, so that for the moment it concealed the fact that he had nothing but his shirt on below it. He received Master Dale somewhat sternly, saying—<break time="100ms" />"Now, sir, for your punishment for your last nasty misconduct."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, sir," said the frightened and trembling youth, "I really could not help it," and he began to cry. "Oh! pray, sir, don't flog me so hard again."<break time="100ms" />"The more trouble that you give me, the harder will be the flogging. Now take off your jacket and waistcoat."<break time="100ms" />The youth did so.<break time="100ms" />"Now come close to me."<break time="100ms" />The doctor then lowered down Dale's trousers, and raising his shirt, contemplated with great pleasure the pretty belly of the lovely boy, and then turning him round, under pretence of seeing if the weals of the last flogging were still visible, he gazed on his white firm backside and swelling thighs, examining the marks still left from the previous punishment. He then turned him round, and inspected the pretty little cock, which, under the mortal fear he was in, hung down its head in a limp and pitiable state.<break time="100ms" />"And so this is the little offender," said he, applying his hand to it, and squeezing and pressing it gently. "What a naughty little thing it is!"<break time="100ms" />The youth could not avoid showing the pleasure these lascivious caresses gave him, and smiled.<break time="100ms" />"Oh, don't smile, sir, this is no laughing matter. Look at the marks of the mess you made on my sofa," pointing to it. "I can't have my furniture spoiled in this manner, so if your little cock is to be naughty again, I must flog you upon my knees, but first come here; take off these trousers, which hanging about the legs are only in the way—there. Now sit down on my knee, and tell me all about this naughty little thing."<break time="100ms" />He drew aside his robe, so that the boy's bare bottom came in naked contact with his brawny naked thighs, and the youth could feel the doctor's prick swelling up, although that part was still covered with his shirt. The doctor, taking hold of the youth's now standing prick, asked if it had ever behaved so badly before the scene with his pretty young cousin.<break time="100ms" />"No sir, never. I never thought of it until I got sight of her bare bottom and other parts by accident."<break time="100ms" />The doctor continued his toyings, caressing the young balls, and feeling all over the plump and firm backside.<break time="100ms" />"Why, he is going to be naughty again!" said the doctor, as the youth's prick throbbed under his exciting touches. "I must flog your bottom for all this, for it is very naughty and improper. Why, you seem to take a pleasure in it."<break time="100ms" />"Oh, sir, I never felt anything so delightful," said Master Dale.<break time="100ms" />"The more reason I should punish you, but remember, you bad boy, if you are to do that dirty thing again, you must do it on my knee, and not on the sofa."<break time="100ms" />The doctor then took the birch in hand, and with his arm round the boy's waist, drew him to him, but before laying him across his knee, he slipped the boy's shirt over his head, leaving him stark naked in all the glorious fairness of skin and beauty of form. The doctor's eyes gloated over the charming sight, but becoming too excited to pause longer, he drew up his own shirt, displaying his fine pego at full stretch. He bent the boy's warm body over his brawny thighs, and with his arm pressed his glowing form against his own rampant pego—Dale's young stiffened cock rubbing against the naked thigh he lay on. The doctor now raised the rod, and said—<break time="100ms" />"Now, sir, for your punishment, I must flog this round, hard, little bottom, till it reddens again."<break time="100ms" />Whack, whack, went the birch rod, but with much less force than on the previous occasion, but still sufficiently stinging to cause the youth to move up and down, rubbing his cock against the doctor's thighs, and causing him such ecstasies as hardly to allow him to feel the blows. His warm soft flesh, too, rubbing against the doctor's large, stiff tool, soon put them both in a delirium of delight. The doctor then changed his position, and drew the boy more over his belly, so that his great prick could get between the boy's thighs, rubbing under his balls in the trough between the buttocks, while the boy's cock rubbed against the doctor's belly.<break time="100ms" />"Now," said the doctor, "I have got you fast, and must teach you not to play such naughty tricks in future."<break time="100ms" />Whack—whack, again went the rod, causing the most delicious movements of the boy's backside upon the doctor's excited prick, and not less upon his own, which was rubbing against the doctor's belly, giving fresh pleasure at each repetition of the blow. But neither of them had spent yet. The boy's bottom was now red with a glowing heat, and his cock was in a state of intense excitement, and the doctor's tool was as stiff and randy as possible. The doctor now ceased his flogging, and squeezing the boy tight against his person, said—
    </voice>
</speak>
